[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,1,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.65,0:00:10.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(197.4,200.557)}{\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs25\b1\bord0\shad0\c&H78BDE7&\fad(0,808)}24小时\N\N{\fs15}第二季  第二十四集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.11,0:00:13.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(189.6,121.6,193.8,105.6,0,356)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad3\3c&H2F2F2F&\4c&H336D99&}{\fs10}{\t(0,356,\fs20)\fn方正正中黑简体}前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.86,0:00:15.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这之后你可能联系不到我了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You may not be able to contact me after this.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.57,0:00:15.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(307.2,44.553)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.61,0:00:15.65,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(288.6,52.553)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.65,0:00:15.70,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(270,59.753)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.70,0:00:15.74,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(252.6,67.753)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.74,0:00:15.78,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(234,76.553)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.78,0:00:15.82,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(217.2,82.953)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.82,0:00:15.87,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(196.2,90.953)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.87,0:00:15.91,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(181.2,100.553)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.91,0:00:15.95,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(162,107.753)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.95,0:00:15.99,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(145.2,114.153)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.99,0:00:17.74,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(129,122.153)\fad(0,305)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.71,0:00:17.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-为什么  -查普尔找我麻烦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Why? - Chappelle became a problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.75,0:00:20.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我把他麻晕了  他们盯上我了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So I had to take him out of play and they're onto me now.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.20,0:00:22.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们马上就会带我走的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So it's only matter of time before they'll take me out.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.10,0:00:23.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我该找谁帮忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who do I contact if I need help?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.59,0:00:26.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我派米歇尔去外面建立一个区外站点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm setting Michelle onto the field to set up an off-site station.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.06,0:00:28.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你被逮捕了  米歇尔·德斯勒在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're under arrest. Where's Michelle Dessler?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.25,0:00:29.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我能找到她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can find her.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.92,0:00:32.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,确认  中央调度  我们已经将她扣押\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Affirmative, Central. She's in custody.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.40,0:00:36.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金  有人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kim? Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.59,0:00:35.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(65.4,229.353)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.63,0:00:35.68,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(85.2,219.753)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.68,0:00:35.72,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(106.2,207.753)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.72,0:00:35.76,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(127.2,194.953)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.76,0:00:35.80,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(150.6,183.753)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.80,0:00:35.84,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(169.8,172.553)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.84,0:00:35.89,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(189.6,160.553)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.89,0:00:35.93,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(211.8,148.553)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.93,0:00:35.97,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(232.8,137.353)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.97,0:00:37.81,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(253.2,124.553)\fad(0,313)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.25,0:00:38.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你是什么人  -我叫凯特·华纳\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Who are you? - I'm Kate Warner.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.39,0:00:39.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你父亲叫我来接你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your father sent me to come get you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.02,0:00:43.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我爸为什么会叫一个他刚认识的人来接我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why would my dad send someone he'd just met to come get me?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.96,0:00:45.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他信任我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He trusts me.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.23,0:00:47.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们越早离开  你和你爸就越早能团聚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The sooner we leave, the sooner you and your dad can be together.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.23,0:00:49.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,司法部长给我打了电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The Attorney General called me.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.24,0:00:50.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他说你想让我做你的律师\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He assumed you'd want me for your counsel.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.90,0:00:49.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(293.4,50.953)}大卫·帕尔默
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.95,0:00:49.99,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(270,61.353)}大卫·帕尔默
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.99,0:00:50.03,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(245.4,71.753)}大卫·帕尔默
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.03,0:00:50.07,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(222.6,82.4)}大卫·帕尔默
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.07,0:00:50.11,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(199.2,94.153)}大卫·帕尔默
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.11,0:00:50.15,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(174.6,103.753)}大卫·帕尔默
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.15,0:00:50.19,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(150.6,112.553)}大卫·帕尔默
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.19,0:00:52.15,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(126.6,125.353)\fad(0,306)}大卫·帕尔默
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.83,0:00:51.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们告诉你什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What have they told you?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.95,0:00:53.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你被内阁弹劾了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You've been removed from office by the cabinet.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.69,0:00:55.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,基于我认为是被彼得·金斯利伪造过的证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This country is about to go to war based on evidence
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.65,0:00:58.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个国家即将开战\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}manipulated by a man named Peter Kingsley.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.12,0:01:00.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你竭尽所能调查他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need you to find out everything you can about him.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.39,0:01:04.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-现在怎么办  -我们还有最后一种办法\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What happens now? - We got one last play. Deliver Kingsley.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.04,0:01:03.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(308.4,45.353)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.09,0:01:03.13,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(288.6,54.153)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.13,0:01:03.17,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(268.2,62.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.17,0:01:03.21,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(249,70.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.21,0:01:03.25,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(226.2,79.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.25,0:01:03.29,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(207,90.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.29,0:01:03.33,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(185.4,100.553)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.33,0:01:03.38,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(166.2,106.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.38,0:01:03.41,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(145.8,115.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.41,0:01:05.25,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(124.2,124.553)\fad(0,309)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.15,0:01:07.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他太危险了  你没法接近他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's far too dangerous, and you'll never get close to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.17,0:01:11.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你说得对  我做不到  但你可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're right. I won't, but you will.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.05,0:01:12.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金斯利不知道休伊特已经死了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kingsley doesn't know Hewitt's been killed.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.07,0:01:14.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你如果说你可以交出休伊特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you tell him you can deliver him,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.81,0:01:15.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,应该会引起他的注意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that should get his attention.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.93,0:01:18.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要你录下我们对话的带子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want the tapes that you made of our conversation.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.41,0:01:20.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,作为交换  我会交出亚历克斯·休伊特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll give you Alex Hewitt in return.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.40,0:01:21.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  洛杉矶体育场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. LA Coliseum,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.98,0:01:23.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,18号门  30分钟后见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}gate 18, 30 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.70,0:01:25.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反恐组会如何开始支援你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What kind of support will you be getting from CTU?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.99,0:01:27.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在完全没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As of now, none.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.61,0:01:29.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,字幕\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack? Jack!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.19,0:01:38.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs15\t(696,6577,\fs16)\c&H4BAAAD&\fad(1697,1183)\pos(187.2,191.79)}以下故事情节发生在早晨7点到早晨8点之间
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.75,0:01:48.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你没事吧  -没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You OK? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.04,0:01:57.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,启动啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.29,0:02:01.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,该死  车启动不了了  我们得下车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Damn it. The car won't start. We gotta get out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.21,0:02:06.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的安全带卡住了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My seat belt's jammed.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.64,0:02:11.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,帕尔默女士  我需要你的帮助\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mrs. Palmer, I'm gonna need your help.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.53,0:02:17.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,帕尔默女士  别这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mrs. Palmer, please don't do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.59,0:02:20.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  杰克  但我必须先顾自己\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry, Jack, but I have to take care of myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.49,0:02:22.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等我自由了就帮你叫救护车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When I'm free I'll call an ambulance for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.63,0:02:26.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你不能这样  -我别无选择\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You can't do this! - I don't have a choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.55,0:02:28.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是个非常让人敬佩的人  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're a very impressive man, Jack,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.15,0:02:31.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但你眼中不是对就是错  就跟大卫一样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but you see everything as either good or bad, just like David.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.57,0:02:34.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但这个世界远比这复杂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And the world is so much more complicated than that.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.16,0:02:35.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  其实很简单\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, it's simple.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.27,0:02:36.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,战争即将爆发\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's a war about to start
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.39,0:02:38.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而你是唯一能帮我阻止它的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and you're the only person who can help me stop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.39,0:02:43.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那总统呢  -是他抛弃了我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What about the president? - He turned away from me.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.73,0:02:46.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们一起度过了25年  开创事业\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}After 25 years of building a life together,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.24,0:02:48.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,建立家庭  他却抛弃了我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}a family, he turned me away.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.66,0:02:51.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们终究会发现你参与了这起阴谋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Eventually they will connect you to this conspiracy.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.49,0:02:54.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那颗核弹根本就不该爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That bomb was never supposed to go off.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.10,0:02:56.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天发生的一切本都不该如此\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}None of this was supposed to happen this way.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.10,0:02:59.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道  我相信你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know. I believe you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.14,0:03:01.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你现在就可以终结这一切\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You can put an end to it now.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.94,0:03:03.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你帮我给金斯利定罪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you help me get Kingsley,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.90,0:03:06.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你丈夫就能重新成为总统了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}your husband will get his presidency back.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.04,0:03:07.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那将是你的功劳\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That will be because of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.66,0:03:10.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,帕尔默女士  求你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mrs. Palmer, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.27,0:03:12.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,该死的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}God damn it!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.78,0:03:30.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想让我做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you want me to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.89,0:03:35.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抽屉里有把刀  帮我把安全带割开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's a knife in the glove box. Help cut me out.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.39,0:03:41.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,进来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on in.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.91,0:03:44.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样好多了  更简洁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is much better. It's simpler.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.09,0:03:47.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们必须得合理解释\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We gotta be able to explain this thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.06,0:03:48.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要跟你谈谈  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need to talk to you, Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.77,0:03:49.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我五分钟后下来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll be down in five minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.93,0:03:51.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.00,0:03:53.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很重要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's important.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.58,0:03:57.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.55,0:04:11.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.31,0:04:13.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是彼得·金斯利的档案\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a flash file on Peter Kingsley.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.86,0:04:15.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们几分钟前刚做好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They pulled it up just a few minutes ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.87,0:04:19.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,彼得·金斯利  杰克·鲍尔认为的幕后凶手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Peter Kingsley, the man Jack Bauer thinks is behind the bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.95,0:04:21.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里面有金斯利的通话记录\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's a record of phone calls that Kingsley made,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.58,0:04:23.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最近的是在六个小时前\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}some as recently as six hours ago,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.47,0:04:25.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,打给一个叫乔纳森·华莱士的士兵的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to a soldier named Jonathan Wallace.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.87,0:04:27.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,华莱士是珊瑚蛇部队的成员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wallace was a member of the Coral Snake brigade.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.10,0:04:30.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他先前杀了自己的战友\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He apparently killed his own men.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.65,0:04:34.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道华莱士是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know who Wallace is.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.29,0:04:38.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,轰炸机已经飞过了最后一个检查点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The planes have passed over their final checkpoint
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.97,0:04:41.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在一个小时之内就能达到目标\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and will be reaching their targets within the hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.60,0:04:43.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们的主要目标都是军事设施\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Our primary targets are all military,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.81,0:04:44.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但其中有一个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but one includes
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.56,0:04:47.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,包含了在居民区内的指挥中心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}a command-and-control centre inside a residential area.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.65,0:04:50.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尽管我们的武器已经很智能了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As smart as our weapons have become,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.64,0:04:53.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可能还是会有附带损伤\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}there may be some collateral damage.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.95,0:04:56.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是说平民伤亡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You mean civilian casualties.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.55,0:04:58.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.96,0:05:03.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没有办法避免吗  -恐怕没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- There's no way to avoid these? - I'm afraid not.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.44,0:05:08.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我们就必须要承受了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then it's something we're just gonna have to live with.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.96,0:05:14.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,莱恩·查普尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ryan Chappelle.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.11,0:05:16.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,莱恩  我是麦克·诺维克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ryan, this is Mike Novick.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.90,0:05:19.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有什么事吗  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How can I help you, sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.08,0:05:21.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道今天出现过一些疑虑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know there's been some confusion today
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.96,0:05:24.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是针对塞浦路斯录音的真实性的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}about the veracity of the Cyprus audio.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.24,0:05:27.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有  我们的团队和中情局的结论是一样的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not really. Our teams came to the same conclusion as Langley.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.83,0:05:31.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知不知道杰克·鲍尔是否还在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you happen to know if Jack Bauer's still trying
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.17,0:05:33.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,寻找证据证明录音是伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to find evidence that the recording was fabricated?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.10,0:05:37.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  但他的行动没有得到我们的授权\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, I believe he is, but he's operating outside our authority.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.24,0:05:39.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想让你协助他的调查\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you to assist his investigation.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.03,0:05:42.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-先生  我都不知道他在哪  -那就去找\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Sir, I don't even know where he is. - Then find him.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.39,0:05:47.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,诺维克先生  我不太确定您为何要我这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Novick, I'm not sure why you're asking me to do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.22,0:05:50.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,据我所知我们已经开战了  我也按此操作了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I was told we're already at war and to proceed accordingly.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.23,0:05:53.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们还没有开战  三十分钟后向我报告\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're not at war yet. You have 30 minutes to report back to me
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.91,0:05:56.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鲍尔的进展和你的行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the findings of Bauer and your efforts.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.26,0:05:58.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-但先生...  -这是命令  莱恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- But sir... - That's a direct order, Ryan.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.67,0:05:59.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有我的电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You have my channel.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.71,0:06:02.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,到时候打这个号码  就这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you to call me back on this line. That's all.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.27,0:06:10.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我一个小时内就上飞机  -怎么迟了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'll be on the plane within the hour. - Why the delay?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.33,0:06:12.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,核弹在错误的地点爆炸了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The bomb detonating in the wrong location
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.56,0:06:14.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给我造成了一点麻烦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}created a little extra work for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.50,0:06:16.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,希望我不需要担心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nothing to worry about, I hope.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:16.77,0:06:19.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,完全不需要  先生  细节我就不赘述了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, not at all, sir. I won't bore you with the details.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.43,0:06:20.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,赘述一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bore me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.53,0:06:24.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还需要处理亚历克斯·休伊特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I still have to take care of Alex Hewitt.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.47,0:06:28.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,休伊特是唯一能破坏这件事的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hewitt is the only one who can bring this whole thing down.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.73,0:06:31.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你之前说你能抓到他  -我没找到他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You told me you'd have him by now. - I wasn't able to find him.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.86,0:06:34.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我已经在处理了  不必担心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I'm taking care of it. Don't worry.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.29,0:06:44.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,坐下  你们俩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sit down, both of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.65,0:06:47.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不需要把米歇尔关在这\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look you don't need Michelle here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.27,0:06:48.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她只是按我的命令做事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She was acting under my orders.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.52,0:06:51.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我能自辩  托尼  -我说坐下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I can defend myself, Tony. - I said sit down.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.15,0:07:01.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你们帮我联系杰克·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need you to get me in contact with Jack Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.20,0:07:08.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我懂了  杰克得到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, I see. Jack got some support
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.06,0:07:09.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,高层的支持  上面给你压力了  是不是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}above you and now you're being squeezed, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.10,0:07:11.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能不能联系到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can you do it or not?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.69,0:07:13.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,发生了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's goin' on?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.24,0:07:18.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鲍尔的证据可能确实不是空穴来风\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bauer's evidence might actually have some relevance.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.83,0:07:20.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也就是说我们是对的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Which means we were right.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.96,0:07:23.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  你们差点让我昏迷了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. You damn near put me in a coma.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.40,0:07:24.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是袭击\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's assault.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.50,0:07:33.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样  你撤销对我们的指控\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll tell you what. You drop the charges against us...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.99,0:07:37.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们就帮你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and we'll help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.72,0:07:43.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想想吧  莱恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, Ryan.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.59,0:07:46.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你心里很清楚这是你最好的选择  不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You of all people know that's your best move, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.38,0:07:54.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好吧  -要书面的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Fine. - In writing.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.07,0:07:59.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行  行  书面的  快给我联系鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, all right, in writing. Just get me in touch with Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.83,0:08:04.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们不应该请求支援吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shouldn't we just call for help?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.42,0:08:07.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没人能求救  我不是在以反恐组的名义行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's no one to call. I'm not working under CTU's authority.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.62,0:08:09.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在他们眼中  我根本不存在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As far as they are concerned I don't exist.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.52,0:08:11.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-所以我们只能靠自己  -完全靠自己\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- So we're out on our own. - Completely.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.11,0:08:15.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你们没事吧  需要帮助吗  -他受伤了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You folks all right? You need some help? - He got hurt.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.97,0:08:19.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你能送我们去医院吗  -好  当然\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Can you get us to a hospital? - Uh, yeah, yeah, sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.06,0:08:22.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-帕尔默女士  你得开车  -什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Mrs. Palmer, you need to drive. - What do you mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.43,0:08:23.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  我们需要用你的车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry, but we need your car.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.61,0:08:26.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别乱来  来  拿着吧  给你们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, easy, all right? Go ahead, take it, it's yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.16,0:08:30.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.58,0:08:52.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们准备好了  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're ready, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.52,0:09:07.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,华纳小姐  你好  我是凯莉·特纳\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Miss Warner. Hi. Carrie Turner.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.85,0:09:08.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你好  凯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hi. Kate.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.40,0:09:12.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你一定就是杰克的女儿金了  -我爸爸呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You must be Jack's daughter Kim. - Where's my dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.57,0:09:15.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他还在出外勤  你要不在这等会儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's still in the field. Why don't you wait here for a moment.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.50,0:09:17.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我去告诉莱恩·查普尔你来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll go tell Ryan Chappelle that you're here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.55,0:09:20.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我来吧  凯莉  -你不是被拘捕了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'll handle this, Carrie. - I thought you were in custody.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.02,0:09:22.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我被释放了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was released.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.04,0:09:26.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金  我听说了你的遭遇  你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kim, I heard what happened to you. Are you all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.53,0:09:29.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I guess so.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.10,0:09:33.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只想见见我爸  确认他没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I just wanna see my dad and make sure he's OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.95,0:09:35.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他现在不在这儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, he's not here right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.04,0:09:36.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他几个小时之内都不会回来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He won't be back for a couple of hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.17,0:09:38.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他知道我在这儿吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Does he know I'm here?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.07,0:09:40.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还不知道  但他只要打电话来我们就告诉他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, not yet, but we'll tell him as soon as he phones in.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.97,0:09:43.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克坚持让我们一到这儿就打给他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen, Jack insisted we call as soon as we get here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.16,0:09:45.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道  但他现在联系不到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I understand. He's just not reachable right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.13,0:09:46.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会让凯莉送你们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I'm gonna have Carrie take you back
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.43,0:09:48.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把你们安置好  我马上就过去  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and get you situated. I'll be there in a minute alright?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.57,0:09:53.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不会有事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's gonna be OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.01,0:09:57.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ok.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.89,0:10:01.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,华纳小姐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Miss Warner?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.36,0:10:06.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道你知道了没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know if you're aware of this but...
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.81,0:10:09.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们释放你父亲之后他又回来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}your father came back here after we released him.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.46,0:10:11.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.56,0:10:13.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他想在你妹妹被带走之前再跟她见一面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He wanted to talk to your sister before she was taken away.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.10,0:10:18.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他们把玛丽带回这儿了吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- They brought Marie back here? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.91,0:10:27.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你欺骗了我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You lied to me?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.78,0:10:30.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你杀了雷扎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You killed Reza?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.48,0:10:34.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你还想杀你的亲姐姐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You tried to kill your own sister?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.82,0:10:37.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你居然情愿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You were willing to set off
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.19,0:10:41.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在一座千万人口的城市引爆核弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}a nuclear bomb in a city with ten million people?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.09,0:10:50.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你告诉我为什么  因为我需要知道为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You tell me why. Because I need to understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.72,0:10:54.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我是他们强迫你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell me that they forced you to do it,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.94,0:10:57.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们给你洗脑了  威胁你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that they brainwashed you, that they threatened you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.96,0:11:01.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你可以告诉我你不知道自己在做些什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You can tell me that you didn't know what you were doin'.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.03,0:11:05.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,肯定是有原因的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There must be a reason.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.71,0:11:09.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有原因  爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There is no reason, Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.35,0:11:16.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没法接受\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't accept that.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.53,0:11:25.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也不能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I couldn't either.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.78,0:11:29.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,直到我看着她的眼睛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Until I looked into her eyes
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.32,0:11:32.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她却拿枪指着我  想要扣下扳机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and she pointed a gun at me and started to pull the trigger.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.32,0:11:40.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,相信我  爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Trust me, Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.20,0:11:44.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她不会给你任何答案的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's not gonna give you any answers.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.48,0:11:51.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她给不了  至少不是我们能理解的答案\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She can't. At least, nothing that we could ever understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.46,0:12:07.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Dad...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.85,0:12:15.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.32,0:12:36.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.93,0:13:14.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你以为你在外面是安全的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You think you'll be safe out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.96,0:13:20.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You won't be.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.13,0:13:39.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-杰克  我是托尼  -托尼  你回来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Jack, it's Tony. - Tony, you back in play?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.75,0:13:42.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  杰克  金来反恐组了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Jack, Kim's here at CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.54,0:13:46.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-她很安全  -谢天谢地  别告诉她情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- She's safe. - Thank God. Don't tell her what's going on.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.60,0:13:49.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-就告诉她我会尽快回去  -我会的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Just tell her I'll be back as soon as I can okay? - I will.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.57,0:13:51.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  我是莱恩  我们需要谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen. Jack, this is Ryan. We need to talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.98,0:13:53.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,莱恩  你这个混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ryan, you son of a bitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.55,0:13:55.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你让那架直升机不要接我和休伊特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You stopped that chopper from picking up me and Hewitt.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.83,0:13:58.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,休伊特死了  你个人需要对此负责\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hewitt's dead. I'm holding you personally responsible.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.06,0:14:00.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听我说  杰克  情况有变\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen, Jack, things have changed.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.50,0:14:03.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们现在全力支持你  说说你的行动情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You got full support. Give me your mission profile.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.18,0:14:06.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我和金斯利约好了要见面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've set up a meeting with Kingsley.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.24,0:14:09.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们会在洛杉矶体育场见面  18号门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna meet him at the Los Angeles Coliseum, gate 18.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.21,0:14:12.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,帕尔默女士已经同意佩戴窃听器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mrs. Palmer's agreed to wear a wire and she's gonna get him to
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.82,0:14:15.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她会让他确认核弹和那三个国家没有关系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}confirm that the three countries had nothing to do with the nuke.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.46,0:14:18.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我希望你先不要行动  等待支援\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you to stand down until you get some support.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.05,0:14:19.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们的人马上就到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Our people will be there soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.39,0:14:20.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不行  没有时间了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, we don't have time.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.95,0:14:22.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金斯利要求会面现在就开始\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kingsley's expecting the meet to go down now.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.98,0:14:24.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你需要支援\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You need backup.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.23,0:14:27.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,莱恩  你要是想帮我  就去找\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ryan, if you wanna help me, get me voice prints of
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.55,0:14:30.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,彼得·金斯利和雪莉·帕尔默的声纹用以确认\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Peter Kingsley and Sherry Palmer now to use for authentication.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.47,0:14:32.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Done.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.76,0:14:35.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还需要一个和白宫的实时音频传输频道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I also need a live audio feed to the White House.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.00,0:14:36.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你希望总统能旁听\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You want an audience with the president.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.11,0:14:37.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.54,0:14:41.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行  我给你  确保这个电话能打通\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. You will have it. Make sure you keep the line clear.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.97,0:14:43.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,收到  我们准备进入体育场了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Copy. We're pulling into the Coliseum now.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.96,0:14:46.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们需要派一队特警去现场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We need to get a SWAT team to his location.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.41,0:14:54.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在那儿停车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Pull over there.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.47,0:14:59.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在车里等我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wait here for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.66,0:15:15.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,下来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.16,0:15:23.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给你装窃听设备\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's get you wired.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.61,0:15:31.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把外套脱到肩膀\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Take your jacket off your shoulder.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.58,0:15:36.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是无线传输器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is a wireless transmitter.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.13,0:15:40.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们找不到的  也不能追踪信号\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They won't know to look for it. They won't be able to trace it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.51,0:15:45.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这太疯狂了  我们不该自己做这些\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is crazy. We shouldn't be doing this alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.40,0:15:46.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们没有别的选择了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We don't have another choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.31,0:15:49.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,记住  金斯利没找到休伊特就不会想走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just remember, Kingsley doesn't want to leave here without Hewitt.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.09,0:15:52.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是我们的优势\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's gotta be to our advantage.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.27,0:16:01.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了  说句话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, say something.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.06,0:16:04.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我害怕\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm scared.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.28,0:16:08.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  工作正常\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, it's working.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.14,0:16:22.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-喂  麦克  -总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yes, Mike. - Mr. President,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.98,0:16:25.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不赞成对军事行动有任何拖延\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I am against any delay in our military actions.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.70,0:16:26.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我从一开始就这么说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have been from the start.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.90,0:16:30.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我们现在很有希望在半个小时内\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But there is a good chance we will receive conclusive evidence
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.27,0:16:33.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,获取确凿的证据证明塞浦路斯录音是伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}in the next half hour that the Cyprus recording is false.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.48,0:16:35.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,麦克  我们知道是"第二波"\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mike, we know Second Wave
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.48,0:16:36.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,将核弹带进了国境\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}brought the nuke into the country
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.63,0:16:38.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们也知道"第二波"的背后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and we know Second Wave is sponsored
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.46,0:16:41.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是这三个国家在资助  是我漏掉了什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}by these three countries. What am I missing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.02,0:16:43.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还不知道全部细节  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't have all the details, Mr. President,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.01,0:16:45.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我刚刚得知"第二波"组织\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I just learned about a possible link
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.13,0:16:48.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可能和一个叫彼得·金斯利有关\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}between Second Wave and a man named Peter Kingsley.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.92,0:16:49.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他又是什么人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who the hell is he?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.71,0:16:52.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很显然他是里海\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's apparently part of a consortium
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.81,0:16:56.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,石油利益团体的一份子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}of oil interests with contracts in the Caspian Sea.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.39,0:16:58.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你意思是  核弹背后牵涉到一个石油财团吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So what are you saying? An oil consortium's behind the nuke?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.51,0:17:01.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克·鲍尔觉得他能从金斯利那里套到话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack Bauer believes he can get a confession from Kingsley.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.37,0:17:03.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他安排了语音实时监听\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's set up a live audio feed.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.69,0:17:05.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,麦克  再有不到20分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mike. Our bombers are due to
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.30,0:17:07.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们就要开始使用炸弹轰炸了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}drop their payloads in less than 20 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.33,0:17:10.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鲍尔随时都可能和金斯利见面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bauer's meeting Kingsley any minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.65,0:17:14.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,此语音设备是实时输出的  测试一二三\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is the live voice print.Testing one two three.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.44,0:17:18.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是我们已经有的音频记录\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And this is the voice file we have on record
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.74,0:17:22.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,此音频也能说明  说话人正是雪莉·帕尔默\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}which will prove that it is, in fact, Sherry Palmer.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.35,0:17:23.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\frz356.9\move(231,126.4,216.6,127.2)}{\fn方正兰亭特黑长简体\fs8\b0\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H583822&}输出语音分析中
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.52,0:17:23.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(215.4,128)\frz357.6}{\fn方正兰亭特黑长简体\fs8\b0\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H583822&}语音匹配成功
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.06,0:17:24.89,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an8\frz357.6\move(215.4,126.4,197.4,96,151,818)}{\fn方正兰亭特黑长简体\fs8\b0\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H583822&}语音匹配成功
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.89,0:17:25.60,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an8\frz357.6\move(248.4,155.2,236.4,151.2)}{\fn方正兰亭特黑长简体\fs8\b0\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H583822&}语音匹配成功
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.52,0:17:26.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-已确认  -下面那个是金斯利吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It's confirmed. - The one below is Kingsley?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.96,0:17:29.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没错  匹配效果不错  -你们能听到吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yeah. Matches were good. - Are you guys getting this?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.92,0:17:32.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-能听到  -好  支援何时能到  莱恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- We're good here. - OK. How far out is our backup, Ryan?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.87,0:17:35.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-11分钟后  -太久了  我们得行动了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- They're 11 minutes out. - That's too long. We've gotta go now.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.94,0:17:38.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-稍等  杰克  -我们没时间了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Just wait. Jack. - We can't wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.03,0:17:38.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们距约定时间已经\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're already ten minutes
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.82,0:17:41.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,晚了10分钟  普莱斯考特准备好了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}past the meeting time. Is Prescott ready?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.08,0:17:43.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,准备好了  托尼在和白宫那边联系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, Tony's on with the White House.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.54,0:17:45.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们在安排实时语音监听\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're setting up a live audio feed now.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.64,0:17:47.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那好  我们准备出发了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, good. We are set to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.82,0:17:52.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你感觉如何  帕尔默夫人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How are you doing, Mrs Palmer?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.33,0:17:56.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我一露面金斯利如果要杀我该怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's to prevent Kingsley from shooting me the moment I appear?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.67,0:17:58.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金斯利在得到休伊特之前不会轻举妄动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kingsley won't do anything until he gets Hewitt.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.21,0:18:01.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但当他意识到我们手上没有休伊特...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But the moment he realises we don't have Hewitt...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.70,0:18:04.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会保护你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll be covering your back.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.27,0:18:09.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,考虑到你现在的处境这并不能使我安心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's not very comforting considering the condition you're in.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.81,0:18:13.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我可能有生命危险\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I may not make it out of this.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.14,0:18:18.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,实话和你说  帕尔默夫人  有这个可能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not gonna lie to you, Mrs. Palmer. That's a possibility.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.03,0:18:30.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我这么做是为了大卫  你是知道的  对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm doing this for David. You know that, don't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.23,0:18:34.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.89,0:18:38.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能告诉他吗  万一我有什么不测\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Will you tell him that? In case something happens.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.53,0:18:45.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会的  帕尔默夫人  快去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll take care of it, Mrs. Palmer. You've gotta go now.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.35,0:19:17.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-麦克  -是我  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Mike. - Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.94,0:19:19.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们刚刚弄好语音监听\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We just finished setting up the feed.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.96,0:19:21.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我希望这么做不是徒劳一场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I hope this isn't gonna be a waste of our time.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.19,0:19:25.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,相信我  总统先生  我也希望如此\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Believe me, Mr. President, so do I.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.54,0:19:29.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么回事  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's going on, Mike?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.98,0:19:34.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生和我都觉得你应该参与其中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The president and I thought you should be part of this.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.38,0:19:37.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,和普莱斯考特及司法部长一起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Along with Prescott and the Attorney General,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.16,0:19:39.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对这次实时录音进行监听\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we will be listening to a live feed.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.57,0:19:43.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-关于什么  -对彼得·金斯利的诱捕行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Of what? - A sting operation against Peter Kingsley.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.59,0:19:46.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,据悉他是今天炸弹案的策划者\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It appears he was the architect of today's bombing
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.78,0:19:48.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,及塞浦路斯录音的提供者\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and the delivery of the Cyprus audio.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.26,0:19:53.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-鲍尔找到金斯利了  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Bauer found Kingsley. - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.22,0:19:58.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但...  和金斯利见面的不是鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But... it won't be Bauer who'll be talking to Kingsley.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.79,0:20:00.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只要他承认犯罪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What difference does it make
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.43,0:20:02.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是谁又有什么区别呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}as long as we get him to incriminate himself?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.05,0:20:06.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么回事  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What is it, Mike?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.09,0:20:16.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雪莉要和金斯利见面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's Sherry who'll be talking to Kingsley.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.60,0:20:19.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.52,0:20:24.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看样子金斯利几个月前找到雪莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It seems that Kingsley recruited her some months ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.63,0:20:26.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她也参与其中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She was part of this.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.77,0:20:34.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雪莉帮这个叫金斯利的干活\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sherry was working with this man, Kingsley?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.07,0:20:35.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看样子是的  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It appears that way, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.85,0:20:39.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为了引爆炸弹以及挑起战争吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}To detonate a nuclear bomb and start a war?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.69,0:20:40.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不会的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.04,0:20:45.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还不清楚她知道多少  参与了多少\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's unclear how much she knew, or how deep she was in it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.60,0:20:51.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们只能希望她能从金斯利嘴里套出罪供\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We just have to hope she can extract a confession from Kingsley.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.23,0:20:54.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以现在雪莉和杰克·鲍尔合作面对金斯利\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So now Sherry is working with Jack Bauer to bring down Kingsley?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.29,0:20:59.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错  而且需要冒着巨大风险\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes. And at considerable risk to herself.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.04,0:21:58.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,斯科特  没有我的命令别轻举妄动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Scott, don't do anything until I tell you to.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.08,0:22:00.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们需要休伊特  -明白\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- We need Hewitt. - Understood.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.57,0:23:01.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-休伊特在哪儿  -他很安全\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where's Hewitt? - He's safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.09,0:23:03.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他在哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where is he?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.02,0:23:09.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你骗了我  你一直都想引爆炸弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You lied to me. You wanted this bomb to go off all along.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.26,0:23:13.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你利用了我和罗杰·斯坦顿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You used Roger Stanton and you used me.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.73,0:23:15.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.54,0:23:17.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如今我和你还有引爆的核弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, now I'm tied to you,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.57,0:23:21.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,脱不了干系了  我想安全脱身\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and the nuclear detonation. I want safe haven.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.06,0:23:24.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这不关我的事  -你脱不了身了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- That's your problem. - Well, I just made it yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.46,0:23:28.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为在我安全之前你别想见到休伊特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because you won't see Hewitt until I'm safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.26,0:23:32.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-别跟我讨价还价  -别侮辱我的智商\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Don't horse trade with me. - Don't insult my intelligence.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.13,0:23:35.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-确认  他就是金斯利  -莱恩  是他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Confirmed, we got a match on Kingsley's voice. - Ryan, you got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.02,0:23:39.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得到休伊特之前你哪儿也别想去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're not going anywhere till I have Hewitt.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.19,0:23:42.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,少跟我来这套\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That doesn't work for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.31,0:23:48.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在我安全离开之后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll call you on this line to
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.99,0:23:53.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会打这个电话告诉你休伊特的位置\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}give you Hewitt's location after I'm safely away.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.64,0:23:55.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你无需知道我要去哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't need to know where I'm going.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:56.03,0:23:58.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  我们还没拿到所需信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, we're not getting what we need here.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.17,0:23:58.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她会拿到的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She'll get it for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.08,0:24:08.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-现在该说说录音的事了  -录音我带了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Now there's the matter of the recordings. - They're right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.56,0:24:11.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你和我交谈的电话录音都在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Every phone conversation between you and me.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.27,0:24:20.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  录音我都要  包括塞浦路斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. I want all of them, including Cyprus.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.48,0:24:26.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要塞浦路斯干什么  那跟你没半点关系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why Cyprus? You had nothing to do with that.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.77,0:24:28.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-安全起见  -安全起见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Insurance. - Insurance?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.68,0:24:31.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一旦国家发动战争\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Once the country goes to war,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.64,0:24:34.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,政府绝对不会将它曝光的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the government will never let that be exposed.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.31,0:24:37.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,休伊特是唯一可以伤害到我们的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hewitt is the only one who can hurt us.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.49,0:24:41.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-因为他伪造了塞浦路斯的录音  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Because he forged the Cyprus recording. - Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.48,0:24:43.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行了  托尼  证据有了   让我接手吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, Tony, you got your proof. Let me go ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:43.62,0:24:46.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-快下命令  -需要白宫确认才行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Give me the green light. - Get it confirmed from the White House.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.28,0:24:48.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她不能久留下去  快点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She can't stay much longer. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.23,0:24:49.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是阿尔梅达  你们满意了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is Almeida. Are you satisfied?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.93,0:24:51.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反恐组想知道证据是否能证明\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}CTU wants to know if that's enough to prove it
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.65,0:24:53.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,塞浦路斯录音是假的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Cyprus recording's false.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.40,0:24:55.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们能确认这是实时的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Have you confirmed this is live
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.57,0:24:57.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,以及说话人的身份吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and the voices have been authenticated?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.60,0:24:58.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可以  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.30,0:25:04.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-就这样  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- So that's it. - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.44,0:25:08.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我一落地...  电话联系你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When I land... I'll call you.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.42,0:25:16.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在虚张声势  休伊特不在你手里  对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're bluff in'. You don't have Hewitt, do you?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.60,0:25:19.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不  他在我手里  -不  他不在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Oh, yes, I do. - No, you don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.03,0:25:28.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,斯科特  解决掉她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Scott, take her out.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.59,0:25:38.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杀了她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kill her.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.17,0:25:48.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快跑  雪莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Run, Sherry!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:51.88,0:26:53.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快  快跑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.63,0:27:07.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,帕尔默夫人  快离开这里  快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mrs. Palmer, get out of here. Go!
Dialogue: 0,0:28:44.99,0:28:46.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:52.69,0:28:55.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你今天给我添了不少乱啊  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You've caused me a lot of trouble today, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:00.60,0:29:02.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不会把休伊特交给我  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're not gonna give me Hewitt, are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:45.42,0:29:48.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  轰炸机还有三分钟到达目标\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President. Our bombers are three minutes from the targets.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:48.24,0:29:50.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,启动序列61T1\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Initiating sequence six one tango one.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:53.39,0:29:55.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,目标进入视野  武器已锁定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Target in view. Weapons lock.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:56.47,0:29:57.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是否准备发动攻击\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are we go for a strike?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.52,0:30:01.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是否进行轰炸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are we go for a launch?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:03.75,0:30:05.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们正在待命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We are awaiting command.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.07,0:30:07.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,取消攻击\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Abort the attack.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.10,0:30:11.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,取消  取消\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Abort, abort.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:26.02,0:30:29.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你什么意思  金斯利死了  这怎么可能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you mean, Kingsley's dead? How could that happen?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:29.58,0:30:31.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我警告过你此人不能用\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I warned you not to use him.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:31.87,0:30:34.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们已经用了  他也失败了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So we did use him and he failed.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.26,0:30:35.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但这不重要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But it won't matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:35.12,0:30:36.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一旦战争发动  我们就没事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Once the war starts we'll be OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.26,0:30:41.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不会有战争了  -为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It isn't going to start. - Why's that?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:41.56,0:30:43.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统已经发现了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The president found out about
Dialogue: 0,0:30:43.04,0:30:45.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,塞浦路斯录音的事  攻击取消了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the Cyprus recording and called off the attack.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.49,0:30:47.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不会有什么战争了  马克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There isn't going to be any war, Max.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:50.05,0:30:54.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我们就换个方式做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well... we're going to have to do this another way.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:54.50,0:30:58.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-换个方式  什么意思  -很快你会知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Another way? What are you talking about? - You'll find out.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:58.68,0:30:59.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,计划从今天开始\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It'll start today.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:09.09,0:31:11.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是我  行动吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's me. Go ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.15,0:31:17.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,内阁取消了之前的行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The cabinet has annulled its earlier action.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.15,0:31:19.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我已指示特勤处\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have instructed the Secret
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.30,0:31:21.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,恢复你作为美国总统的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Service to resume its charge of serving you
Dialogue: 0,0:31:21.83,0:31:23.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一切职能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}as President of the United States.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.63,0:31:26.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I see.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:27.49,0:31:31.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也要引咎辞职  即刻生效\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've also tendered my resignation, effective immediately,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:31.31,0:31:32.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那些反对你的内阁成员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and those members of the cabinet
Dialogue: 0,0:31:32.49,0:31:34.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,同样也将提交辞呈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}who voted against you have also agreed to resign.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.13,0:31:40.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,吉姆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jim.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:44.22,0:31:46.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先生们  女士们...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Gentlemen, ladies...
Dialogue: 0,0:31:49.49,0:31:51.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们今天差点发动可怕的战争\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we came dangerously close to war today.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:53.27,0:31:55.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们所有人对核弹引爆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That all of us reacted emotionally
Dialogue: 0,0:31:55.25,0:31:57.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,产生的情绪是可以理解的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to the nuclear detonation is understandable.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:59.44,0:32:03.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但领导者需要有超乎常人的忍耐力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But leaders are required to have patience beyond human limits.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:06.54,0:32:10.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们差点进行的行动应该只在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The kind of action we nearly took should only be exercised
Dialogue: 0,0:32:11.25,0:32:14.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迫不得已的时候才能实施\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}after all other avenues have been exhausted.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:16.39,0:32:20.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在满足最严格的证据以后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}After the strictest standard of proof has been met.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:22.53,0:32:24.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如此快的把我排除在外\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}By casting me aside so quickly,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:25.81,0:32:27.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是你们对标准要求的降低\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you effectively lowered those standards.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:29.03,0:32:30.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是个深刻的教训\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And that was a profound mistake.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.69,0:32:47.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然而  这种问题你们不可能重蹈覆辙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was not, however, a mistake you're likely to make again.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:49.61,0:32:52.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因此  我不接受你们的辞呈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Therefore I do not accept your resignations.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:54.98,0:32:56.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当前我们的国家亟待抚平\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have a nation to heal today.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:59.43,0:33:03.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们在其中充当着至关重要的角色\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And all of you play a vital role in that healing process.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:07.37,0:33:08.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President...
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.25,0:33:12.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道该说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know what to say.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.87,0:33:16.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,无需多言\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's nothing to say.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:18.07,0:33:19.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们还有事要做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have work to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.33,0:33:22.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That'll be all.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:29.03,0:33:31.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-珍妮  安排场新闻发布会  -什么时候\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Jenny, set up a press conference. - When?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:31.57,0:33:34.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,越快越好  会议需要面向公众\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As soon as you can. And I want it public.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:34.70,0:33:36.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想和人民直接对话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want to speak to the people directly.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:37.24,0:33:38.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们需要我的保证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They deserve my assurance.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.57,0:33:40.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:45.48,0:33:51.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,麦克  我想再次感谢你关键时刻致电反恐组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mike, I wanna thank you again for calling CTU in the 11th hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.82,0:33:54.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,应该的  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:02.26,0:34:04.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但你本该始终站在我这边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But you should have been with me to the end.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:06.73,0:34:08.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我对你的期望如此\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's what I expected of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:10.02,0:34:11.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这也是我任命你的原因\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's why I appointed you.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:22.02,0:34:25.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要解除你的职务  立即生效\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm relieving you of your post, effective immediately.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:31.63,0:34:32.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:50.94,0:34:54.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢  长官  这不是我一个人的功劳\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you, sir. I can't take all the credit myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:54.27,0:34:56.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这归功于乔治·梅森出色的团队\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a great team George Mason put together here.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:58.77,0:35:01.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  我会的  谢谢  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, I will. Thank you, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:03.14,0:35:06.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼  刚刚是地区主管沃恩来电\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony. That was District Director Vaughn.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:06.57,0:35:07.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他不知该如何感谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's so happy with what we
Dialogue: 0,0:35:07.54,0:35:09.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们今天的所作所为\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}did here today he doesn't know where to start.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:10.60,0:35:11.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's great.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:14.42,0:35:17.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说吧...  有什么事  伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So... what's up, my friend?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:20.52,0:35:21.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个嘛...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, um...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:24.43,0:35:25.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是这样的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it's like this.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:27.35,0:35:28.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要不解雇我...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Either fire me...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:29.33,0:35:30.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要不从我椅子上滚开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}or get out of my chair.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:53.28,0:35:54.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,椅子是你的了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The chair's all yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:03.08,0:36:04.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-嘿  -嘿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Hey. - Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:06.33,0:36:09.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,换班人员到了  他们已经跟上进度了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The new shift is here. They've been brought up to speed.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:11.46,0:36:13.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在想我要接上我弟弟回家了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was thinking I'd get my brother and go home.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:20.84,0:36:22.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle, um...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:23.42,0:36:25.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天有很多人都出了很多力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}there's a handful of people who made a big difference today.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:27.19,0:36:28.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你就是其中一员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're one of'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.25,0:36:31.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你做了些艰难的选择\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You made some tough choices
Dialogue: 0,0:36:31.30,0:36:33.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,和我对着干  我想让你知道  你是对的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and went up against me. I want you know, you were right.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:36.93,0:36:37.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:39.94,0:36:43.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以  不如你先回家休息一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, um... why don't you go home and get some rest?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.56,0:36:54.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.76,0:37:02.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,明天见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}See you tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.42,0:37:24.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  女士  我需要检查下你的包\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry ma'am. I'll need to see the contents of your bag.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:24.78,0:37:26.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是凯特·华纳  她是金·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm Kate Warner and this is Kim Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:43.84,0:37:44.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.19,0:37:53.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-亲爱的  -爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Hey, honey. - Daddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:56.75,0:37:58.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一切会好起来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's gonna be all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:05.63,0:38:06.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:11.28,0:38:12.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.10,0:38:20.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I love you too.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:34.31,0:38:37.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸  我会照顾好你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Dad? I'm gonna take care of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.30,0:38:51.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我强烈敦促大家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I urge you in the strongest terms
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.93,0:38:53.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不要轻信那些你听到的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}not to indulge any rumours or
Dialogue: 0,0:38:53.65,0:38:57.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,或者将会听到的谣言或理论\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}theories that you may have heard, or may soon hear.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:58.51,0:39:02.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一旦真相大白  我会告知大家的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Once the facts are known, I will present them to you myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:02.89,0:39:05.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在此之前  我们都是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Until then, know that we are
Dialogue: 0,0:39:05.09,0:39:08.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,安全的并且这份安全将保持下去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}all safe and that we will continue to be safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:10.89,0:39:12.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天我们能做的最爱国的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The most patriotic thing that
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.13,0:39:16.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就是尽情享受我们的生活\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we can all do today is to keep living our lives.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.35,0:39:22.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以我敦促大家  回到工作中  回到学校\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So I urge you all, go back to work, go back to school.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:24.01,0:39:27.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为我们每天享有的自由  争取到的自由\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because the freedom we enjoy, the freedom that we earn every day,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:27.73,0:39:28.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是我们从敌人那里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is the very thing that
Dialogue: 0,0:39:28.63,0:39:31.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真真实实得到的  也使我们屹立不倒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}will defeat our enemies and keep us strong.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:33.77,0:39:35.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天佑美国\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}God bless America.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:38.96,0:39:42.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天佑所有人  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}God bless us all. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:42.90,0:39:46.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,非常感谢  上帝保佑你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you very much. God bless you.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.37,0:39:50.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:51.29,0:39:53.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢  很高兴见到你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you. Good to see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:54.42,0:39:56.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:05.29,0:40:07.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:09.97,0:40:10.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:12.04,0:40:13.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President!
Dialogue: 0,0:40:17.58,0:40:18.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:21.56,0:40:23.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,打扰了  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Excuse me, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:23.54,0:40:24.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:25.15,0:40:26.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:28.19,0:40:29.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你好  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Hi. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:31.99,0:40:33.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-上帝保佑你  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- God bless you. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:39.84,0:41:41.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-说吧  -得手了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yes. - It's done.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:42.80,0:41:43.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,辛苦了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:54.70,0:41:55.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:05.07,0:42:08.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统倒下了  快叫医护人员  快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The president's down! We need medical assistance. Help!
Dialogue: 0,0:42:13.51,0:42:14.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:16.82,0:42:19.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  会没事的  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr President? It'll be all right, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:20.07,0:42:22.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快叫救护车  快点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We need an ambulance! Help!

