[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,1,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.69,0:00:10.90,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(197.4,200.557)}{\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs25\b1\bord0\shad0\c&H78BDE7&\fad(0,808)}24小时\N\N{\fs15}第二季  第十二集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.53,0:00:13.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(189.6,121.6,193.8,105.6,0,356)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad3\3c&H2F2F2F&\4c&H336D99&}{\fs10}{\t(0,356,\fs20)\fn方正正中黑简体}前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.84,0:00:16.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们已经在斯坦顿和击落鲍尔飞机的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We've established a direct link between Stanton
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.81,0:00:19.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,变节雇佣军之间找到了直接联系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and the rogue mercenaries that shot down Bauer's plane.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.26,0:00:21.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,斯坦顿不会轻易开口的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stanton won't be easy to break.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.87,0:00:18.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(93,234.953)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.92,0:00:18.96,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(111,219.753)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.96,0:00:19.00,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(129.6,205.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.00,0:00:19.04,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(148.8,188.8)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.04,0:00:19.08,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(168,173.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.08,0:00:19.12,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(187.2,156.553)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.12,0:00:19.16,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(207.6,141.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.16,0:00:19.21,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(221.4,126.153)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.21,0:00:21.21,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\fad(0,308)\pos(241.2,109.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.01,0:00:22.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们可能需要放宽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We may need to expand the limits
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.52,0:00:24.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你过去的底线\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}of how far you've been willing to go in the past.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.86,0:00:27.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,斯坦顿先生  根据总统的命令\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Stanton, by order of the president,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.35,0:00:28.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要将您关押起来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm placing you under arrest.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.86,0:00:29.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我现在要你做的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What I'm about to ask you to do
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.69,0:00:32.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不在你特工处的工作范围内\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}falls outside the parameters of your charge of Secret Service.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.55,0:00:33.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你需要我怎么做  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What would you like me to do, sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.58,0:00:37.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道你在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know what you're talking about.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.41,0:00:44.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-她现在在哪里  -她在车祸之后就逃走了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where is she now? - She ran off after the accident.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.64,0:00:43.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(258,213.353)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.68,0:00:43.73,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(236.4,197.353)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.73,0:00:43.77,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(215.4,182.153)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.77,0:00:43.81,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(195.6,165.353)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.81,0:00:43.85,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(175.2,149.353)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.85,0:00:43.89,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(155.4,132.553)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.89,0:00:45.90,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\fad(0,307)\pos(133.8,115.753)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.65,0:00:46.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道她是想躲开当地警方\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know whether she was trying to avoid the local police
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.57,0:00:49.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还是不想被带回洛杉矶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}or whether she was just trying not to get brought back to LA.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.43,0:00:50.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,找到她  乔治\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just find her, George.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.46,0:00:58.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-玛丽  我们有麻烦了  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Marie, we have a problem. - What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.70,0:00:57.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(108,37.353)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.74,0:00:57.79,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(129.6,50.953)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.79,0:00:57.83,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(149.4,63.753)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.83,0:00:57.87,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(169.2,76.553)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.87,0:00:57.91,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(189.6,89.353)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.91,0:00:57.95,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(211.8,102.953)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.95,0:00:57.99,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(231.6,115.753)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.99,0:00:59.95,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\fad(0,308)\pos(245.4,124.553)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.68,0:01:00.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,贝希尔和马尔科死了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Basheer and Marko are dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.27,0:01:01.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你需要我做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you need me to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.36,0:01:03.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们本来应该去拿触发器的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They were supposed to pick up the trigger.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.01,0:01:04.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去哪里拿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.08,0:01:06.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,马尔科工作的地方  在他的储物柜里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}At the place where Marko worked. In his locker.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.84,0:01:08.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你必须想办法打开这个储物柜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You must do whatever you can to gain access to this locker
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.97,0:01:11.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,并尽快把触发器拿给奥马尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and bring the trigger to Omar as soon as possible.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.04,0:01:12.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会搞定的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll take care of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.24,0:01:14.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得我也应该有权知道具体情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think I've earned the right to know what's going on.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.92,0:01:13.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(275.4,225.353)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.97,0:01:14.01,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(256.2,209.353)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.01,0:01:14.05,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(237,195.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.05,0:01:14.09,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(219.6,180.553)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.09,0:01:14.13,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(201.6,166.153)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.13,0:01:14.17,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(181.2,151.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.17,0:01:14.21,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(162.6,135.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.21,0:01:16.26,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\fad(0,311)\c&H449BA1&\pos(143.4,119.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.88,0:01:17.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们相信赛伊德·阿里是一起恐怖袭击的主脑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We believe that Syed Ali is at the centre of a terrorist attack
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.96,0:01:20.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们需要你帮我们指认他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We need you to identify him for us.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.48,0:01:23.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他在里面  赛伊德·阿里  他在里面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's in there. Syed Ali. He's in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.50,0:01:26.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Damm it!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.59,0:01:27.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他死了  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's dead, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.43,0:01:30.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些衣服不是这个人的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}These clothes don't belong to this man.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.37,0:01:32.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,守住出口  守住出口\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Maintain secure exits. Maintain secure exits.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.99,0:01:34.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿里还在大楼之中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ali is still in the building.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.99,0:01:40.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs15\t(696,6577,\fs16)\c&H4BAAAD&\fad(1697,1183)\pos(187.2,191.79)}以下故事情节发生在晚上7点到8点之间
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.08,0:02:00.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们解决问题前\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're gonna have to step outside
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.86,0:02:02.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你得在外面待着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}until we get the situation resolved.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.98,0:02:04.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鲍尔探员让我留下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Agent Bauer told me to stay.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.56,0:02:07.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-去和他说吧  -我会的  你先出去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Talk to him. - I will. As soon as you step outside.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.14,0:02:08.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她要留下来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She stays with us.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.29,0:02:10.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们找到阿里时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's gotta make the final identification on Ali
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.41,0:02:12.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她要对阿里做最终的确认\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}as soon as we find him.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.86,0:02:15.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  我从阿里烧毁的那人口袋里找到这个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK. I got this in the pocket of the man Ali set on fire.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.20,0:02:17.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这可能是阿里带着的文件的一部分\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It might be a part of a document Ali was carrying.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.47,0:02:19.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拍下来传给反恐组  看他们能否找到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Photo it, send it to CTU. See if they can find it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.76,0:02:22.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是想保护这个人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you trying to protect this man?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.90,0:02:25.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  鲍尔探员  我不会错付忠诚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, Agent Bauer, I have no misplaced loyalties.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.76,0:02:28.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你们找的人杀害了无辜的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If the man you're looking for has murdered an innocent,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:28.08,0:02:31.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,伊斯兰教和你们一样视其有罪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}he is as guilty in the eyes of Islam as he is in yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.02,0:02:33.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我找的那个人今天在洛杉矶启动了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The man that I'm looking for set in motion a plan today
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.80,0:02:36.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一项引爆核武器的计划\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to detonate a nuclear weapon in Los Angeles.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.79,0:02:41.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-确定吗  -是的  确定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Are you certain? - Yes, we're certain.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.58,0:02:43.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们估计  如果炸弹引爆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We estimate between one and two
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.26,0:02:46.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,将会有一百万至二百万人丧命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}million people will die if this bomb goes off.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.16,0:02:48.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先生  这就是我们必须立刻找到他的原因\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That, sir, is why we need to find him now.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.36,0:02:51.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你告诉我详情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you for informing me,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.30,0:02:54.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是我对你们是完全坦诚的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I can be no more honest with you than I have been.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.34,0:02:57.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是如果你找到这个人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But if you find this man,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.28,0:03:00.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也许我能用你们所不能的方式和他聊聊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}perhaps I can talk to him in a way you cannot.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.58,0:03:02.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说服他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Persuade him.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.64,0:03:04.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鲍尔探员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Agent Bauer?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.09,0:03:09.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.84,0:03:15.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们找到了些东西  你该看看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We found something I think you should see.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.12,0:03:23.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们发现了这个活板门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We found this trap door.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.28,0:03:25.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你给我们的平面图里都没有显示\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's not on any of the schematics you gave us.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.40,0:03:32.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,打开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Open it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.21,0:03:41.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我下去  我要自己下去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I go down... I'm going down alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.66,0:03:42.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道这是你的行动...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know this is your operation...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.87,0:03:43.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听我说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.84,0:03:45.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们刚失去了一个阿里的同伙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We just lost one of Ali's men
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.80,0:03:47.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他的牙齿里藏着氰化物胶囊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to a cyanide capsule hidden in his tooth.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.38,0:03:50.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们必须假设阿里也会如此结束他的生命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have to assume Ali's willing to take his life the same way.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.47,0:03:52.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不能让他看到我们追来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He can't see us coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.29,0:03:56.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让你的人在梯子下方集合\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Have your men assemble at the base of the ladder.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.29,0:03:57.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等我指示\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Await my instructions.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.14,0:04:02.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你带警棍了吗  给我拿着  好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Have you got your baton with you? Let me have it. OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.88,0:04:35.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你好  -玛丽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Hello? - Marie.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.60,0:04:38.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-计划有变  -为什么  怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- There has been a change of plans. - Why? What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.01,0:04:41.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去会合点吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just go to the rendezvous point.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.57,0:04:45.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我在约定时间一个半小时后还没到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If I'm not there within one half-hour of the time we have planned,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.69,0:04:47.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道要做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}then you know what to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.62,0:04:51.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-记得我说的话吧  -记得\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You remember what I said, yes? - I remember.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.58,0:05:15.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我控制了嫌疑人  快进来  快进来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've got the suspect! Engage the room! Engage the room!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.06,0:05:19.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抓住他的腿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get his legs!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.84,0:05:24.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就是他  是赛伊德·阿里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's him! That is Syed Ali!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.19,0:05:26.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,带她出去  带她出去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get her outta here! Get her outta here!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.78,0:05:27.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,带她出去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get her outta here!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.71,0:05:42.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我拿到氰化物了  带他出去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got the cyanide. Get him ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.45,0:05:46.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,贝克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Baker!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.37,0:05:50.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,查查他在和谁打电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Find out who he was talking to.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.36,0:06:00.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,坐在这里难免会觉得一定有什么误会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's hard not to sit here and think that there must be some mistake,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.56,0:06:02.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,即使你们掌握了那些证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}even with the evidence you have.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.67,0:06:06.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这显而易见  鲍勃\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's black-and-white, Bob.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.86,0:06:09.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你女儿杀了雷扎和我们两个探员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your daughter killed Reza and two of our agents.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.86,0:06:11.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你帮助我们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I need you to help us
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.95,0:06:15.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,弄清楚她和赛伊德·阿里的关联\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}understand what her connection to Syed Ali is.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.51,0:06:18.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我知道她参与其中  我不会袖手旁观的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If I'd known she was involved, I would have done something.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.12,0:06:20.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在你知道了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And now that you do know,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.90,0:06:24.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这能解释她的某些奇怪行为吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}does it help explain any strange behaviour?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.64,0:06:28.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能告诉我们的任何事都有帮助\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Anything you can tell us will help.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.82,0:06:30.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.97,0:06:36.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在伦敦工作时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Marie went to college in London
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.74,0:06:38.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽在那里上大学\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}while I was working there.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.46,0:06:41.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那时她妈妈去世了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's when her mother died,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.44,0:06:44.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这对她打击很大  我们都很难过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and it hit her hard, hit us all hard.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.90,0:06:47.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.04,0:06:50.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她离开了一阵子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She ran away for a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.06,0:06:52.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,多久\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How long?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.71,0:06:59.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大概三四周\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Three, maybe four weeks.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.58,0:07:02.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们报警了  但是...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We got the police involved, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.17,0:07:06.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她写了封信说她没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}she sent us a letter saying that she was fine,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.69,0:07:10.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她在旅行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that she was travelling
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.02,0:07:13.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是需要一些空间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and she just needed some space.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.16,0:07:17.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她回来后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And when she came back...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.93,0:07:21.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我见到她实在太高兴了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was so grateful to see her
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.40,0:07:24.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也就没有再多问\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that I stopped asking questions.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.43,0:07:31.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有感觉到有什么改变吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No sense that anything had changed?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.00,0:07:34.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,某些本质上的变化\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Any fundamental difference?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.06,0:07:40.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她的政治倾向不明显了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She had become less politically inclined.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.11,0:07:45.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽总是盲目地响应号召  令人尊敬的号召\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Marie had always flirted with causes, respectable causes.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.21,0:07:50.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,比如"拯救荒野"或者"废除死刑"\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Like save the wilderness or abolish the death penalty.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.97,0:07:53.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她不再说起那些事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She stopped talking about all that.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.07,0:07:58.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当你变得激进时就会如此\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's precisely what happens when you're radicalised.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.53,0:08:00.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,操纵者训练你不再\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Handlers train you to stop
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.05,0:08:03.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谈论任何事  沉默不语\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}talking about anything, keep it to yourself,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.72,0:08:05.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样你就能更好地融入背景\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so you're better able to blend in with the background.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.47,0:08:09.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽有操纵者\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Marie had handlers?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.66,0:08:15.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,着急吗  稍等我一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, can it wait? I'll be right back with this.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.47,0:08:24.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是来自清真寺的扫描图\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This scan came in from the mosque.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.43,0:08:26.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在阿里的衣服里发现的烧毁的纸片\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A burnt paper fragment found in Ali's clothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.35,0:08:30.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,唯一可见的是左下角\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The only thing visible is in the lower left quadrant.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.71,0:08:33.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,像是一串数字  六位或八位\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It looks like a piece of a number. A six or an eight.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.86,0:08:36.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们所有的鉴识人员都在现场吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are all our forensics people out in the field?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.39,0:08:38.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们从圣地亚哥请了外援默多克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We got Murdoch on loan from San Diego.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.70,0:08:40.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他是计算机图像方面的专家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's an expert with computer imaging.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.72,0:08:42.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果有人能看清  就是他了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If anyone can see this, he can.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.65,0:08:46.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你好啊  我是乔治·梅森\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How are you doing? George Mason.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.52,0:08:48.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你好  我是兰迪·默多克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, man. Randy Murdoch.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.15,0:08:49.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-很高兴见到你  -很高兴见到你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Pleased to meet you. - Good to meet you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.68,0:08:54.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有办法加速这个过程吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Any way to accelerate the process?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.66,0:08:57.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的处理器比你们现有的快得多\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My CPU's a lot faster than anything you guy got.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.11,0:08:59.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,建立并行处理可能需要过多时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Parallel processing could take too long to set up.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.31,0:09:01.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-但是看这个  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- But, check it out. - What's happening?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.23,0:09:02.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果上面有内容  我就能得到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If there's anything there, I'll get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.70,0:09:05.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好  托尼还有杰克想要的卫星信号呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Great. Where's Tony and the satellite feed Jack wants?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.81,0:09:06.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,正在进行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In progress.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.16,0:09:08.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-谢谢你  继续跟进  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Thank you. Keep it up. - All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.56,0:09:31.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有谁知道炸弹的事  史坦顿先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who else knew about the bomb, Mr. Stanton?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.00,0:09:33.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道你在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know what you're talking about.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.69,0:09:36.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克·鲍尔现在正在审讯赛伊德·阿里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack Bauer is interrogating Syed Ali as we speak.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.60,0:09:38.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们会及时跟进\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll be informed of his progress
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.05,0:09:41.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,审讯过程  但是目前为止没什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}on a minute-by-minute basis, but nothing yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.19,0:09:44.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们确信这个人知道炸弹的位置\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're certain this man knows the location of the bomb?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.10,0:09:45.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克·鲍尔确信\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack Bauer is.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.10,0:09:47.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,确保他能够得到所需的任何资源\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Make sure he has all the resources he needs.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.22,0:09:48.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.40,0:09:50.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这种痛苦只会更强烈  更难受\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The pain's only going to get much, much worse.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.22,0:09:57.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你可以让它停止\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You can stop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.45,0:09:59.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,西蒙斯探员告诉我罗杰\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Agent Simmons tells me that Roger
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.83,0:10:03.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,曾经受到过同样的抵抗审讯训练\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}was received the same training of resisting interrogation he did.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.08,0:10:05.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要加大电压了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm increasing the voltage.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.60,0:10:07.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是每个人最终都崩溃了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But everyone breaks eventually.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.68,0:10:24.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听你说你有进入时的位置吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I understand you have an entry point?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.17,0:10:25.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,据我们了解  她在路线简图上的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As far as we know, she entered the forest
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.72,0:10:28.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,8-3和8-4位置间进入了森林\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}somewhere between 8-3 and 8-4 on the topo map.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.54,0:10:29.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,具体方向呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And heading?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.62,0:10:31.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有  不知道她去了哪个方向\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. No idea which way she was headed.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.06,0:10:34.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-保持联系  -你在做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Keep me posted. - What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.10,0:10:36.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,发动更多的人在外面寻找杰克的女儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Getting more men out there looking for Jack's daughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.22,0:10:38.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我明确告诉你要把力量集中在炸弹上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I told you specifically to divert resources to the bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.99,0:10:40.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,卫星信号正在生成\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The satellite feed is happening.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.31,0:10:41.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吗  我没用我们的资源\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right? I'm not using our resources.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.78,0:10:43.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是让警长去找找她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was telling the sheriff to look for her.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.25,0:10:46.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼  你就是资源  别被这事分散注意力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony, You're a resource. And don't let it split your attention.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.15,0:10:47.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我向杰克保证我会竭尽所能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I promised Jack I'd do everything in my power
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.45,0:10:50.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,寻找金  你也说过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to look for Kim. Just like you did.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.19,0:10:53.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金在爆炸半径之外  整个洛杉矶还很危险\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kim is outside the blast radius. The rest of Los Angeles isn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.65,0:10:57.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,集中注意力找炸弹  托尼  所有人都是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stay focused on the bomb, Tony! That goes for everybody!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.47,0:11:05.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,洛杉矶郡护林站\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}LA County Ranger Station.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.85,0:11:07.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是反恐组的托尼·阿尔梅达\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is Tony Almeida at CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.57,0:11:08.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有什么事  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, Sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.33,0:11:11.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想追踪一个小时前进入森林的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm trying to track somebody went into the forest about an hour ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.91,0:11:13.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,稍等为您转接\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hold while I transfer you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.53,0:12:13.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有人在那吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, somebody there?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.73,0:12:16.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.94,0:12:21.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是谁  你在这做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who are you? What are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.65,0:12:23.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我  你在这做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Me? What are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.32,0:12:29.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我遇到一场车祸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got into a car accident.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.55,0:12:34.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就开始跑  等我意识到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I started running, and before I knew it,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.03,0:12:36.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就在这里了  我不知道我在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was out here. I had no idea where I was.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.42,0:12:38.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我被这东西卡住了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got stuck in this stupid thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.05,0:12:41.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  我只想\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, all I wanna do is
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.46,0:12:43.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,回到高速路上  离开这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}get back to the highway and get outta here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.86,0:12:48.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你开始为什么要跑离高速公路呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why were you running from the highway in the first place?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.24,0:12:50.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我说了  我吓到了  惊慌失措\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I told you, I was scared and panicked.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.43,0:12:54.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Damm it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.42,0:13:18.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天哪  谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, God. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.30,0:13:36.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,过一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Coming through here.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.83,0:13:43.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们正在就位  贝克结束\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're moving into position now. Baker out.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.73,0:13:56.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道你是谁  我知道你做的一切\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know who you are. I know everything that you've done.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.69,0:13:58.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,炸弹在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where is the bomb?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.84,0:14:05.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,炸弹在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where's the bomb?!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.76,0:14:11.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在浪费我的时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You are wasting my time.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.44,0:14:17.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,炸弹什么时候爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When is the bomb gonna detonate?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.64,0:14:20.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是你在浪费时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're the one wasting time.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.21,0:14:24.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我今天醒来的时候就知道自己将死去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I woke up today knowing I will die.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.22,0:14:29.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我可以让你在从未想象过的巨大痛苦中死去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can make you die with more pain than you ever imagined.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.54,0:14:39.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我在天堂也就有更多的欢愉了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then I will have that much more pleasure in paradise.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.45,0:14:41.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想得美\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.21,0:14:48.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们得想办法送你到最近的护林站\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We gotta figure out how to get you to the nearest ranger station.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.99,0:14:52.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没关系  我不要去那里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, that's OK. I don't wanna go back there.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.05,0:14:56.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,和你逃离高速路的原因一样吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The same reason you ran from the highway?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.29,0:15:07.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我来吧  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here, I got it. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.15,0:15:16.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,高速路要往那个方向走几公里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The highway is a couple of miles that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.03,0:15:22.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但路不安全  地形复杂  夜里很难走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But the way there is not safe. The terrain's too rough to follow at night,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.59,0:15:24.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那边还有美洲狮\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and there's cougars up in that area.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.09,0:15:29.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我家在那个方向八百米\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My place is a half-mile that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.92,0:15:32.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可以让你过一夜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I could put a roof over your head for the night.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.73,0:16:00.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是这个清真寺的阿訇\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I am the imam of this mosque.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.61,0:16:06.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你否认这些人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you deny these men's accusations
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.74,0:16:07.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所说的你密谋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that you are planning to
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.71,0:16:11.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,引爆一枚会杀死百万人口的炸弹的罪名吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}explode a bomb that will kill millions of people?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.15,0:16:17.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,《古兰经》明确禁止\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The Koran clearly forbids
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.03,0:16:19.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,屠杀无辜的平民\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the killing of innocents and non-combatants.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.37,0:16:21.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你和我一样很清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know this as well as I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.42,0:16:25.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们对《古兰经》理解不同\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have different interpretations of the Koran.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.91,0:16:27.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的理解错了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You are misguided.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.57,0:16:32.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有人扭曲了先知的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Someone has twisted the words of the prophet.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.21,0:16:35.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真主不爱护行凶者\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Allah does not love aggressors.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.06,0:16:39.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听我说  谋杀一个无辜的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen to me. The murder of one innocent,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.68,0:16:43.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,更不要说百万人  不会让你上天堂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}let alone millions, will not get you into paradise.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.25,0:16:48.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天堂见面后咱们再辩  阿訇阿尔弗拉尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We will continue this debate when I see you there, Imam Al Fulani.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.94,0:17:00.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要把这个电脑上的图片转移到这些显示器上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want the images you get from this computer transferred to these monitors.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.22,0:17:03.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我和利用我们的宗教\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have talked to men
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.28,0:17:06.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,传达他们的恨意的人谈过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}who misuse our religion to channel their hate,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.46,0:17:09.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我还没见过把冲动付于实践的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I have not known anyone who would act on their impulses.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.74,0:17:12.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你觉得有什么办法改变他的想法吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can you make an appeal you think that'll make any difference?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.79,0:17:15.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我可以再试试  但我觉得不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I will try again, but I don't think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.82,0:17:17.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们也没这个时间了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We don't have that kind of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.11,0:17:19.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,求你了  我想再试试\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please, I want to try again.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.11,0:17:22.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,接下来的事不能把你牵扯进来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You can't be involved with what's gonna happen next.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.29,0:17:25.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请护送他上楼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please escort the gentleman upstairs.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.04,0:17:28.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-鲍尔探员  -来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Agent Bauer? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.69,0:17:32.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们找回了阿里手机拨通的上一个号码\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We recovered the last number Ali dialled on his cell.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.78,0:17:36.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,区号是310  555-2130\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a 310 area code. 555-2130.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.01,0:17:38.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们正在追查  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- We're doing a work-up on it now. - OK, good.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.07,0:17:42.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等  号码是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wait. What was that number?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.99,0:17:49.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,555-2130\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}555-2130.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.66,0:17:56.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这不可能  那是我妹妹的号码\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, that's not possible. That's my sister's cellphone number.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.83,0:18:07.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,到底怎么了  你瞒了我什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's going on? What are you not telling me?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.29,0:18:09.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给我们一点时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why don't you give us a minute?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.68,0:18:19.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你妹妹的未婚夫雷扎和我们的两名探员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your sister's fiancee Reza and two of our agents were found shot to death
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.32,0:18:21.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一个半小时前在你父亲的大楼被击毙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}in your father's building about an hour and a half ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.43,0:18:26.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么  -你妹妹玛丽当时和他们在一起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What? - Your sister Marie was with them.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.10,0:18:31.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-玛丽  她没事吧  -他们不知道她在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Marie? Is she OK? - They don't know where she is right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.26,0:18:35.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你原本打算什么时候告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When were you going to tell me?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.14,0:18:36.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当我们确认\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When we had confirmation
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.36,0:18:38.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是她开的枪之后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that she was the person that pulled the trigger.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.10,0:18:43.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么  太荒唐了  你怎么能这么想\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What? That is ridiculous. How could you even think that?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.74,0:18:45.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为我们拍到了她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because we have video tape on her.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.45,0:18:47.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,过去的一个半小时内\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She was the only person seen leaving
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.74,0:18:50.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只有她离开了你父亲的大楼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}your father's building in the last hour and a half.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.95,0:18:57.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她肯定是想逃跑  她可能受伤了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She was probably trying to escape. She could have been hurt.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.63,0:19:00.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你只知道他打了她的电话  不知道她接没接\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know that he called her number. You don't know if she picked up.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.92,0:19:02.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可能她的手机被偷了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The phone could have been stolen!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.41,0:19:03.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你真这么想吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You really believe that?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.48,0:19:05.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你真的相信你妹妹和此事完全无关吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You really believe your sister has nothing to do with this?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.18,0:19:08.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我真的相信\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, I really believe it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.57,0:19:12.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有个方法可以证明给我看  打给她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's one way you could prove that to me. Phone her cellphone.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.98,0:19:13.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但如果她接了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But if she picks up,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.73,0:19:15.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你得尽可能让通话时间拉长\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you have to talk to her and keep her on the phone
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.15,0:19:16.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我们能找到她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}as long as possible so we can find her.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.64,0:19:19.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样才行  你能做到吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's the deal. Can you do that?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.39,0:19:21.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ok.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.57,0:19:26.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ok.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.76,0:19:29.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ok.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.91,0:19:32.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我马上回来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna be right back.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.27,0:19:36.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,贝克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Baker?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.89,0:19:42.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们需要追踪一通电话  但改一下我方号码\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We need to trace a cellphone call. But manipulate the caller ID.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.77,0:19:43.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们得让它看起来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We need to make it look like
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.37,0:19:46.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,像是从凯特·华纳的手机上打的  现在就办\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it's coming from Kate Warner's phone. Get on it now.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.45,0:20:10.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都配置好了  我们的设备\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The whole set up is just in here. Our equipment will make it
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.79,0:20:12.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会让它看起来像是从你的手机上拨出的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}look like you're calling from your cellphone.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.50,0:20:14.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉她你过去几个小时没听到她的消息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell her you're worried because you haven't heard from her
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.10,0:20:15.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很担心她  但是不要慌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}for the last few hours but don't be panic.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.93,0:20:17.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们连接了运营商的网络\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're linked into the cell-provider network.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:17.46,0:20:19.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们可以在十五到三十秒内三角定位\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We can triangulate within 15 to 30 seconds.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.46,0:20:22.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一旦锁定  就算挂断也能追踪那部手机了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Once we lock, we can track the phone even after the call ends.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.10,0:20:24.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好  打电话吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, good. Let's make the call.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.75,0:20:28.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果不是她接呢  她不接呢  别人接呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What if it's not her? She doesn't answer? What if it's someone else?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.73,0:20:30.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,正是我们要弄清楚的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's what we need to find out.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.10,0:20:33.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  现在找到你妹妹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate, finding your sister right now
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.91,0:20:35.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能拯救数百万人的生命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}could save the lives of millions of people.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.35,0:20:37.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托你打电话吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please make the call.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.66,0:21:00.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,喂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.72,0:21:03.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,喂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.48,0:21:06.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's me.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.39,0:21:11.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我联系不上爸爸  他还没回来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I haven't been able to reach Dad. He's not back yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.83,0:21:13.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.24,0:21:19.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是在开车兜风  让头脑清醒些\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just taking a drive... to clear my head.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.51,0:21:23.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我能懂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.42,0:21:29.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,关于这一切  玛丽  我很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm so sorry, Marie, about everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.89,0:21:30.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.15,0:21:40.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要在家里见吗  找点吃的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you want to meet back at the house? Grab a bite?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.27,0:21:43.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can you?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.53,0:21:49.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们找到雷扎了吧  他们知道出什么事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They've found Reza, haven't they? They know what's happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.22,0:21:55.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道  我不知道出了什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know. I don't know what happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.40,0:21:57.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, Marie.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.65,0:22:00.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我吧  求你了  怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell me, please, what happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.33,0:22:04.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不会理解的  凯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You wouldn't understand, Kate.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.78,0:22:11.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是你杀了雷扎吗  还有那些探员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You killed Reza? And those agents?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.27,0:22:14.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为了事情改变必须要有人牺牲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}People have to die for things to change.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.87,0:22:16.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,已锁定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're locked.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.63,0:22:23.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不会这样做的  你不是这种人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You couldn't have done this. You're not this person.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.16,0:22:25.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们逼你的  你不知道自己在做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They forced you. You didn't know what you were doing.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.23,0:22:33.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,追踪到西尔马市的十个街区范围内\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We tracked it to a ten-block section of Sylmar.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.66,0:22:35.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,之后失去信号\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We lost the phone after that.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.11,0:22:37.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,联络加州高速巡警  让他们封锁那十个街区\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Contact CHP, tell them to shut down that ten-block radius.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.66,0:22:39.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把玛丽·华纳的特征发过去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Send vitals on Marie Warner.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.57,0:22:40.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-让他们找到她  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Tell them to find her. - Got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.19,0:22:44.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不知道她和谁在一起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't know who she was with!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.55,0:22:48.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们可能逼迫她  你不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They could have been forcing her. You don't know!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.65,0:22:57.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很遗憾  很遗憾\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.62,0:23:11.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,护林站有消息了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Any word back from the ranger station?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.25,0:23:12.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还没有  他们展开了搜索\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nothing yet. They mounted a search.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.64,0:23:14.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但晚上搜索速度很慢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But they can't cover as much ground at night.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.07,0:23:18.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼  我刚发给在清真寺的杰克  看看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony. I just sent this to Jack over at the mosque. Check it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.52,0:23:21.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这张纸的纸浆规律很不寻常\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This paper has a very irregular pulp pattern.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.08,0:23:24.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,整个流程的最后一步\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The final step in the process
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.14,0:23:26.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是从多个点取样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is to take samples from various points,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.60,0:23:29.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,通过电脑算法算出\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to create a CGI algorithm of what the paper looked like
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.31,0:23:32.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这张纸没有任何书写痕迹时的样子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}without any of the writings or other impressions on it, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.18,0:23:34.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后减去我们实际拍摄的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We then subtract that from
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.24,0:23:36.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,纸张样貌  就显示出\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}what we've actually got, and what we get...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.31,0:23:43.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,任何打破这个规律的痕迹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is a representation of anything that interrupts that pattern.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.52,0:23:52.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就是这个  好  这只是一部分\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There it is. OK. This is only a partial.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.97,0:23:54.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有几个痕迹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There are a few more markings.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.07,0:23:57.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这几个的右边还有子母和数字\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There are letters or numbers just to the right of these.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.82,0:24:00.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我需要更多时间  这些更细微\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I need a little bit more time. They're more obscure.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.84,0:24:02.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对这些数字和字母的意义\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do we have any context whatsoever
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.34,0:24:04.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们有什么理解吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}as to what these numbers and letters refer to?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.73,0:24:07.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有  他们拍了纸的两面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. They photographed the paper on both sides.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.36,0:24:10.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只有这个区域有信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's the only area right here with any information on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.74,0:24:12.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  做得不错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. Good job.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.26,0:24:14.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔  派能派出的所有人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle, get anyone we can
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.36,0:24:16.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去查这一串字母和数字\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}spare on that sequence of letters and numbers.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.84,0:24:19.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,查车辆识别码  车牌  装货单\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Check VIN numbers, license plates. Shipping manifest.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.28,0:24:22.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有让密码组看看这是不是密码  好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Also get crypto to see if that's a code, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.01,0:24:23.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我来办\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.88,0:24:29.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-鲍尔探员  -是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Agent Bauer? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.93,0:24:33.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反恐组刚发来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This just came in from CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.06,0:24:41.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,打开门  打开门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Open the door. Open the door!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.79,0:24:43.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,N34  是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}N34, what does that mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.89,0:24:46.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What does that mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.47,0:24:51.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你搞砸了  阿里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You screwed up, Ali.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.39,0:24:54.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们会把这组数字和数据库里的一切交叉对比\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna cross-reference that number with everything in our database.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.89,0:24:57.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽·华纳正在被带回来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Marie Warner is being picked up as we speak.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.65,0:25:01.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错  所有线索快拼到一起了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's right, all the pieces are starting to come together.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.15,0:25:03.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,无论如何  我们都会找到这个炸弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No matter what, we'll find this bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.25,0:25:06.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以你要不现在告诉我  要不我让你好受\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So you can either tell me now or I can make you suffer.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.64,0:25:09.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想受苦吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You wanna suffer?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.48,0:25:15.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我告诉过你了  我不怕死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I already told you. I'm not afraid to die.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:15.44,0:25:17.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你今天死的唯一方式就是被我杀掉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The only way you're gonna die today is if I kill you.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.10,0:25:20.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的炸弹不会炸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your bomb's not going off.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.05,0:25:23.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他们说有直播信号过来了  -接通\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- They said we have a live feed. - Patch it through.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.80,0:25:24.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,开始吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:34.31,0:25:35.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你现在不说炸弹在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Those men will kill your family
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.72,0:25:37.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些人就会杀了你家人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}if you don't tell me where the bomb is now.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.59,0:25:54.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我鄙视你  因为是你逼我这么做的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I despise you for making me do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.25,0:25:57.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们在等我下令\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're waiting for my order.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.14,0:26:03.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是你最后的机会  炸弹在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is your last chance. Where's the bomb?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:18.44,0:26:19.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:22.12,0:26:23.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道杰克·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you aware Jack Bauer's
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.10,0:26:25.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在以赛伊德·阿里家人的性命相要挟吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}threatening the lives of Syed Ali's family?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.38,0:26:27.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.97,0:26:30.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他家人在哪  -在他们国家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where is the family? - In their own country.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.72,0:26:34.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反恐组一直在联络当地的安保部队\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}CTU's been in contact with the security forces there
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.25,0:26:36.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们抓了阿里的家人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}who have Ali's family in custody.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:37.31,0:26:37.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们刚收到消息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We just got word that
Dialogue: 0,0:26:37.96,0:26:40.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克要求他们一个接一个杀掉阿里的家人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack has requested they kill the family one by one
Dialogue: 0,0:26:41.80,0:26:44.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,直到阿里说出炸弹的位置\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}till Ali tells us the location of the bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.46,0:26:54.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你估计安保部队会这么做吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Would the security forces do this in your estimation?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.18,0:26:57.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们确实会对平民下手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They do act against civilians.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.30,0:26:59.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们的政府也害怕一旦炸弹爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And their government is afraid of retaliation
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.68,0:27:00.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们会施加的报复行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}if a bomb does go off.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:00.72,0:27:02.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  我认为他们会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, I think they would.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.13,0:27:13.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们可以就这样不管吗  杀害无辜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can we let this happen? Condone the murder of innocent people?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:13.86,0:27:16.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你可以说炸弹是战争的标志\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your arguement will be that the bomb is an act of a war
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.47,0:27:18.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,战争无法避免地会带来平民死亡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and war's inevitable result in civilian casualties.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.94,0:27:20.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不想听什么理论  迈克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't want a rationale here, Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.23,0:27:22.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道有哪场战争\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know of a war where
Dialogue: 0,0:27:22.48,0:27:25.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是总统知情的情况下要杀害儿童的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}a president knowingly targeted children for assassination.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:25.10,0:27:29.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想想那次我们在医院附近发现的兵器工厂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Compare this to a weapons factory we discovered near a hospital
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.30,0:27:31.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们曾经遇到过的情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}a situation we have faced.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:31.56,0:27:33.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,知道通过炸毁工厂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A bombing would still be ordered
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.16,0:27:36.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会使更多人获救\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}on the logic that many more people will be saved
Dialogue: 0,0:27:36.17,0:27:39.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爆炸依然要实施\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}by the destruction of the factory.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.40,0:27:41.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里的数字甚至更有说服力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The numbers are even more compelling here.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:42.85,0:27:46.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可能会死几个人  但可以拯救数百万人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A few people may have to die to save millions.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:50.44,0:27:52.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么会走到这种地步呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How could it have come to this?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:05.75,0:28:07.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你妻子每天都在给你写信\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your wife's been writing you letters every day.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.87,0:28:10.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她不知道寄到哪里去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She doesn't know where to send them.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.24,0:28:16.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你也是你儿子阿萨德的榜样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your son Asad wants to grow up and be just like you.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:21.40,0:28:22.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他下周就十二岁了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Turns 12 next week.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:24.75,0:28:26.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想他撑不到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't think he's gonna make it.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.10,0:28:37.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道失去亲人的感觉是什么样的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know what it's like to lose someone,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.48,0:28:41.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就在你的眼前被夺去生命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to watch them get killed right in front of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:42.66,0:28:44.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不想伤害你的家人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't wanna hurt your family.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.30,0:28:48.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但如果你不老实交代\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I will order those men to pull that trigger
Dialogue: 0,0:28:48.44,0:28:50.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我就会命令那些人扣动扳机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}if you don't give me the information I need.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:55.04,0:28:56.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I am...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.35,0:29:00.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我听从真主的命令\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I am doing Allah's work.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:01.64,0:29:04.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  你要杀害数百万人的性命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. You're going to kill millions of people,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:04.71,0:29:06.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这才是你所做的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that's what you're doing.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:07.26,0:29:08.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鲍尔探员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Agent Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:09.23,0:29:10.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很重要  总统找你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's important. It's the president.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.71,0:29:21.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  我是杰克·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, this is Jack Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:21.34,0:29:22.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不能这么做  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can't let you do this, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:24.24,0:29:27.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,长官  阿里为了完成任务\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, Ali was willing to
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.43,0:29:29.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,愿意付出自己的生命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}take his own life to complete his mission.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.60,0:29:33.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他唯一的弱点在他的家人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}His only vulnerability is his family.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.03,0:29:36.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杀害无辜儿童不属于我们国家的审问流程\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It is not the official policy of this country to kill innocent children.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:36.79,0:29:39.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,长官  这次行动会在他的国家完成\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, the action would take place in his country.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.39,0:29:42.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不必参与  这可以是个现场临时决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You would not be involved. This would be a field decision.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.02,0:29:46.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我已经做出最终决定了  我很抱歉  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My decision is final. I'm sorry, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.80,0:29:48.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:52.76,0:29:54.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我明白  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I understand, Mr President.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:55.62,0:29:58.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  我不认为还有别的选择\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, I do not think that there is another alternative.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.91,0:30:01.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道做这个决定很困难  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know it's a difficult decision, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:04.98,0:30:05.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:07.68,0:30:09.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你的支持  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you for your support, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.98,0:30:13.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他允许了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He authorised the action.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:27.65,0:30:30.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  罗杰·斯坦顿不在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, Roger Stanton isn't available.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.12,0:30:32.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我什么时候才能和他通话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When can I talk to him?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:32.54,0:30:34.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道  我只能说这么多了  理查\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know, that's all I can say right now, Rich.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.63,0:30:35.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你有战术问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you have a tactical question,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:35.96,0:30:39.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,找斯科特·格兰特  今天他值班\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}talk to Scott Grant. He's got the NSA playbook today.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:39.43,0:30:41.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我可以用你的名字吗  -当然\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I can use your name? - Sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:41.68,0:30:45.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈克  我能和你说几句话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mike. Can I just have a quick word with you, please?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.20,0:30:46.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当然了  林\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, sure, Lynne.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:50.61,0:30:52.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不相信雪莉·帕尔默\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't trust Sherry Palmer.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:52.34,0:30:53.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得她不该出现在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I don't think she should be here.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:53.93,0:30:56.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我已经在忙着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm up to my eyeballs trying to
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.04,0:30:59.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把对罗杰·斯坦顿的审问向华盛顿瞒着了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}hide this interrogation with Roger Stanton from Washington.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.45,0:31:02.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你看不过去  能不能请你自己处理\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you have a problem, would you deal with it yourself, please?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:02.29,0:31:04.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你觉得你应该了解我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think you know me well enough to know
Dialogue: 0,0:31:04.37,0:31:06.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这绝对不是什么地盘争夺战\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}this is not some battle over turf.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:06.50,0:31:10.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这事关罗杰·斯坦顿  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- This is about Roger Stanton. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:11.06,0:31:13.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我一直在找时机告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was waiting for the appropriate time to tell you.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:13.06,0:31:14.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想确定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wanted to be sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.19,0:31:18.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有人告诉我有证据表明\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Someone has approached me with evidence of communications
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.73,0:31:21.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,罗杰·斯坦顿和雪莉·帕尔默之间有联系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}between Roger Stanton and Sherry Palmer,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:21.77,0:31:24.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,已经持续六个月了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and it has been over the last six months.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.83,0:31:29.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,罗杰说他们今天是第一次见面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roger said he met her today for the first time.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.26,0:31:32.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes. I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:38.16,0:31:40.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My God.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:44.10,0:31:46.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你认识雪莉已经很久了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You've known Sherry for a very long time.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:47.69,0:31:50.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你觉得她今天行事方式正常吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is today indicative of how she operates?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:53.45,0:31:55.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那对这件事你应该就没有多惊讶了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then this shouldn't be too much of a shock to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:57.82,0:31:59.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雪莉·帕尔默确实不简单\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sherry Palmer's a lot of things,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:59.80,0:32:03.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但说她是这个国家的叛徒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but a traitor to this country?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:04.92,0:32:09.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不相信  哪样的联系  电话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't believe that. What kind of communication? Phone calls?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.72,0:32:12.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  电话  邮件  迈克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes. Phone calls, emails. Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:13.70,0:32:15.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,面对面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Face to face.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:17.64,0:32:19.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的消息从哪儿来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who's your source on this?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.98,0:32:22.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我一直都在通过中介获取消息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've been getting everything through an intermediary,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:22.52,0:32:26.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我在十分钟后和源头那个人要见个面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I actually have a meeting with the source in about ten minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:27.39,0:32:29.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-哪里  -外面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where? - Off site.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.14,0:32:33.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要告诉总统吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you telling the president?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.55,0:32:37.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  他要操心的已经够多了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. He's got enough on his plate already.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:37.11,0:32:41.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而且  他会要证据的  你去和他见面吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And he'd want proof, anyway. You go ahead with your meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.08,0:32:44.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有消息记得告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me know what happens.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.97,0:32:51.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-小心点  -我会的  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Be careful. - I will. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.42,0:32:57.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们按计划行事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shall we proceed as planned?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:57.74,0:33:01.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  从他的长子开始  阿萨德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Affirmative. Start with the older son, Asad.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.19,0:33:04.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果不成功  换另一个孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If that's not successful, move on to his younger son.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:04.07,0:33:08.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-收到  等你下令  -可以行事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Copy that. Waiting for your orders. - We are a go.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:12.21,0:33:13.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不能再等了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't wait any longer.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:13.67,0:33:15.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我炸弹在哪里  否则我就要杀阿萨德了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell me where the bomb is or I will kill Asad.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:20.37,0:33:24.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿里  我知道你觉得你是对的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ali, I know you think what you're doing is right,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:24.15,0:33:25.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我的任务是阻止它的发生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but it's my job to not let it happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:25.74,0:33:27.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托不要让我这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please don't make me do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:27.61,0:33:30.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿萨德只是个孩子  告诉我炸弹在哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Asad is just a boy. Tell me where the bomb is!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:31.90,0:33:34.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我炸弹在哪儿  好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell me where the bomb is! Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:35.56,0:33:36.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杀了他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kill him!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.19,0:33:46.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No! No!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.95,0:33:54.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我炸弹在哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell me where the bomb is!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:56.53,0:33:59.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我  我就放过你剩下的家人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell me, and I'll spare the rest of your family!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:59.10,0:34:00.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你休想\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I will not tell you!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:01.39,0:35:05.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,计划有变  改成和我见面了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your meeting's changed. Now it's with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:08.46,0:35:10.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别  别想走  林  我们得谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, don't go anywhere, Lynne. We need to talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:11.71,0:35:13.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我不这么想  -我就是这么想的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I don't think so. - Yes, we do.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:13.68,0:35:15.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你把我和罗杰想到一起了  不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You think you've connected me to Roger, don't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:15.95,0:35:18.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这正是他们想要的结果\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's exactly what they want you to think.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:19.33,0:35:22.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他们是谁  -和罗杰同谋的那些人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Who is "They"? - The people Roger's conspiring with.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:23.97,0:35:26.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以你确定了罗杰·斯坦顿和此事有关\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So you're confirming that Roger Stanton is involved?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:26.87,0:35:28.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他早就知道炸弹的事情了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He knew about this bomb ahead of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:29.26,0:35:32.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,罗杰的参与程度比大卫知道的还要深\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roger's more involved than David could possibly know.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:33.66,0:35:35.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What the hell does that mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:36.69,0:35:38.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个阴谋  目的到底是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This conspiracy, what is its goal,then?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:40.69,0:35:42.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,夺取总统的职位\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}To take over the presidency.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:42.86,0:35:46.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些人在向你提供有关我的不实信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}These people are feeding you misinformation about me
Dialogue: 0,0:35:46.97,0:35:48.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为他们担心我挡了他们的路\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}because they're afraid I'll get in the way.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:49.64,0:35:49.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你和他们不是一伙的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you are not involved with them
Dialogue: 0,0:35:49.84,0:35:52.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你是怎么知道今天的会面的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How did you know about this meeting?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:52.28,0:35:55.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不必和他们同谋也知道怎样做是有效的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't have to be involved to know the moves that make it win.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:55.32,0:35:56.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你知道罗杰在干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you knew what Roger was doing,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:56.43,0:35:58.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那为什么你什么都不跟总统说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}why haven't you said anything to the president?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.13,0:36:00.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也许和你自己寻找线索\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Probably for the same reasons
Dialogue: 0,0:36:00.53,0:36:02.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是一样的原因\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you're keeping this line of inquiry to yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:03.35,0:36:06.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想掌握尽可能多的证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want to have as much concrete evidence as possible.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:07.09,0:36:10.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雪莉  你本可以在寓所的时候跟我说的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sherry, you could have said any of this to me back at the retreat.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:11.20,0:36:12.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么来这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why come here?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:12.88,0:36:16.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想跟你说明一下  就是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}To make a point. That's all.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:18.58,0:36:20.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说明一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}To make a point?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:22.16,0:36:24.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得这是对我的警告\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think this is a warning.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.13,0:36:29.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得你策划了这一切  展示你有多强大\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think you orchestrated all of this to show me how powerful you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.42,0:36:34.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我相信你一定有自己而不是为总统打的算盘\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I believe that you have your own and not the president's best interest at heart.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:34.34,0:36:36.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会尽全力确保\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I will do everything in my power to make sure
Dialogue: 0,0:36:36.22,0:36:39.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你伤害不了他  或者这个政府\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you don't hurt him or undermine this administration.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:58.38,0:37:01.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿萨德死了  我对此无能为力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Asad is dead. There's nothing I can do to change that.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.34,0:37:03.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但你还可以救法里德的命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You still have a chance to save Fareed's life.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:04.44,0:37:06.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我给你十秒钟  炸弹在哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll give you ten seconds. Where's the bomb?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:07.71,0:37:08.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你没时间了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're running out of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:08.96,0:37:11.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会叫这些人杀掉你最后一个儿子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I will tell these men to kill your last son!
Dialogue: 0,0:37:12.96,0:37:14.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,炸弹在哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where is the bomb?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:15.75,0:37:17.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行  把他杀了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's it. Take him out!
Dialogue: 0,0:37:20.30,0:37:21.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我告诉你  -等等\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I will tell you! - Hold it.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.43,0:37:23.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我告诉你  -现在就告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I will tell you. - Tell me now!
Dialogue: 0,0:37:24.30,0:37:27.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-在诺顿机场  -为什么  计划是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It is at Norton Airfield. - Why? What's the plan?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:30.30,0:37:35.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们计划飞到市中心  然后引爆炸弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We were going to fly over downtown and detonate it.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:37.93,0:37:42.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是真的  是真的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It is true. It is... it is true.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:50.89,0:37:52.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-德斯勒  -我是杰克  给我接梅森\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Dessler. - It's Jack. Get me Mason.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:53.18,0:37:53.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:56.05,0:37:56.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有什么消息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you have?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:57.14,0:37:58.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,炸弹在诺顿机场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The bomb's at Norton Airfield.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:58.57,0:38:00.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们计划飞到市中心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're planning to fly it over the city.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:00.94,0:38:03.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,诺顿是个中型机场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Norton's a medium-size airfield.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:03.04,0:38:05.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有货物运输  私人航运\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They do cargo, private aviation.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:06.36,0:38:08.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,每架飞机的尾翼号码都以N字打头\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Every plane's tail number begins with the letter "N".
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.20,0:38:09.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,应该就是这个了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's probably what this refers to.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.08,0:38:12.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,虽然还只是部分数字  但可以缩小范围了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's still only partial, but the nearest I can search.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.71,0:38:13.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  我们出发了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK. We're on our way.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:15.19,0:38:18.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,派B队  E队  L队去诺顿机场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're moving units Bravo, Echo and Lima to Norton Airfield,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:18.37,0:38:20.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们有理由相信炸弹就在那里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}where we have reason to believe that the bomb is located.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:20.82,0:38:24.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,联系联邦航空管理局  禁止飞机飞入或飞出\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Call FAA and have them ground flights in or out of Norton.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:24.12,0:38:25.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果发现飞机已经起飞\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If they do get the plane in the air,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:25.93,0:38:28.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们需要两架F-16做好拦截的准备\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we wanna have two F-16s at the ready to intercept.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.22,0:38:31.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还需要拆弹部队和特警部队到现场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll get bomb units and SWAT teams over there as well,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:31.80,0:38:33.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,动起来  各位\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so just move everybody.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:33.06,0:38:35.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有记住  不要与外界发生非必要的联系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And, remember, the "No unnecessary contact" Rule remains in place.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:44.97,0:38:46.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让华纳小姐靠边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Put Miss Warner against the wall.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:48.77,0:38:50.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你杀了我儿子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You killed my boy!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:50.18,0:38:51.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你杀了我儿子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You killed my boy!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.24,0:38:52.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你杀了我儿子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You killed my boy!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:53.13,0:38:56.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会找你算账的  你会付出死的代价\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I will get you for this! You will die for this!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:01.05,0:39:05.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你怎么能这么做  你比他们还要坏\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How could you? You're worse than they are.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:05.35,0:39:09.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把卫星恢复正常  我需要确认一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Reroute the satellite back to normal feed. I want confirmation.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:10.10,0:39:14.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,搞定了  你现在应该有画面了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Rerouted satellite. You should have live picture now.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.98,0:39:16.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.14,0:39:20.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,帮我拿一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hold this for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:23.44,0:39:24.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们准备从北边进入\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna come in from the north.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:25.65,0:39:28.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我们的人准备从南边的这两个门进去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Set up our men coming in from the south from these two gates.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:34.67,0:39:35.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他还活着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:41.47,0:39:42.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是在演戏\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was all an act.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.03,0:39:50.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  跟我来  我需要你帮我联系你妹妹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate, I need you to come with me, help me talk to your sister.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:50.76,0:39:51.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么  哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What? Where?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:51.44,0:39:54.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,诺顿机场  离这四十五公里  炸弹在那里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Norton Airfield. Thirty miles over from here where the bomb's located.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:54.49,0:39:56.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你真的觉得她在那里吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Do you really think she's there? - Yes, I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:59.51,0:40:03.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-拜托  凯特  我们时间紧迫  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Please, Kate, we don't have much time. - OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:05.98,0:40:06.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:11.27,0:40:12.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,交给你了  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here you go, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:24.79,0:40:27.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,醒醒  别昏过去了  斯坦顿先生  醒醒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wake up. Stay with me, Mr. Stanton. Wake up.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:28.68,0:40:32.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了  谁还知道炸弹的事情  斯坦顿先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There we go. Who else knew about the bomb, Mr. Stanton?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:42.58,0:40:44.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an2\fs16\bord0\shad2\b1\\pos(193.2,217.6)\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK}连接电池的电极
Dialogue: 0,0:40:53.55,0:40:54.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an2\fs16\bord0\shad2\b1\\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\pos(189,236.8)}测试
Dialogue: 0,0:40:55.80,0:40:56.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an2\fs16\bord0\shad2\b1\\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\pos(191.4,236)}行了
Dialogue: 0,0:41:28.63,0:41:30.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an2\fs16\bord0\shad2\b1\\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\pos(190.8,235.2)}接下来我们祈祷

