[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,1,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.69,0:00:10.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(197.4,200.557)}{\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs25\b1\bord0\shad0\c&H78BDE7&\fad(0,808)}24小时\N\N{\fs15}第二季  第十集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.53,0:00:13.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(189.6,121.6,193.8,105.6,0,356)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad3\3c&H2F2F2F&\4c&H336D99&}{\fs10}{\t(0,356,\fs20)\fn方正正中黑简体}前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.17,0:00:16.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,六个小时前  在一个仓库里发现了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Six hours ago, a cache of weapons-grade Plutonium
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.49,0:00:15.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(322.2,42.153)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.53,0:00:15.57,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(313.8,50.953)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.57,0:00:15.62,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(306,62.153)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.62,0:00:15.66,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(297,70.4)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.66,0:00:15.70,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(288.6,81.353)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.70,0:00:15.74,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(279,90.153)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.74,0:00:15.78,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(270.6,99.753)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.78,0:00:15.82,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(264,109.353)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.82,0:00:17.74,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(255,119.753)\fad(0,305)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.09,0:00:17.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一批武器级别的钚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}was found in a warehouse.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.61,0:00:20.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们还发现了这个  怎么解释  两位\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We also found this. What do you make of that, guys?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.00,0:00:23.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是我们公司的提货单\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is a bill of lading from our company.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.41,0:00:25.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,货是一个给赛伊德·阿里的集装箱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For a container sent to Syed Ali.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.69,0:00:29.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我能追踪装货单  数据库在办公室\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can track this shipping order. The database is at the office.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.35,0:00:32.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我父亲真的为政府工作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If my father really does work for the government,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.63,0:00:31.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(352.8,234.153)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.67,0:00:31.72,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(338.4,218.953)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.72,0:00:31.76,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(324.6,206.153)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.76,0:00:31.80,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(312,192.553)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.80,0:00:31.84,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(298.8,178.953)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.84,0:00:31.88,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(285,164.553)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.88,0:00:31.92,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(270,149.353)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.92,0:00:31.96,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(256.2,138.153)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.96,0:00:33.88,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\fad(0,304)\pos(244.2,124.553)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.92,0:00:34.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,难道他还不知道雷扎是否在做非法的事情吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}wouldn't he have known if Reza was doing something illegal?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.55,0:00:40.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你是谁  -我叫赛伊德·阿里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Who are you? - My name is Syed Ali.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.79,0:00:42.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你查了你不该查的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You were looking in places you do not belong.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.68,0:00:44.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,和我无关\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know anything!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.33,0:00:45.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杀了她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kill her.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.02,0:00:49.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们在下坠  飞行员不清楚情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're going down! The pilots don't know what happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.23,0:00:48.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(21.6,231.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.28,0:00:48.32,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(34.2,220.553)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.32,0:00:48.36,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(47.4,205.353)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.36,0:00:48.40,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(60.6,192.553)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.40,0:00:48.44,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(72,178.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.44,0:00:48.48,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(85.2,165.353)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.48,0:00:48.52,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(97.8,153.353)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.52,0:00:48.56,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(110.4,138.153)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.56,0:00:50.48,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\fad(0,269)\pos(122.4,126.153)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.72,0:00:51.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,感觉像是某种爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It felt like some kind of an explosion!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.59,0:00:54.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他们被击落了  -被某种地空导弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- They were shot down? - By some kind of ground-to-air missile.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.95,0:00:55.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,发现一名幸存者\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We got a survivor.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.45,0:00:57.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这看起来不像是搜救队\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That doesn't look like Search and Rescue.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.62,0:00:59.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们是来找你的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are they coming here for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.61,0:01:00.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.63,0:01:04.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,放下枪  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Drop it, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.98,0:01:08.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会告诉你核弹的位置  交换条件是对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll tell you where the bomb is in exchange for immunity...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.64,0:01:10.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谋杀杰克·鲍尔的豁免权\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}for the murder of Jack Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.53,0:01:12.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反恐组派人来接我们了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Someone from C.T.U. is supposed to come pick us up.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.43,0:01:14.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,警监说这不在他们的管辖权限内\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Captain says it's out of their jurisdiction.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.51,0:01:12.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(54.6,38.953)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.55,0:01:12.60,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(64.2,48.553)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.60,0:01:12.64,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(74.4,60.553)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.64,0:01:12.68,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(84,70.153)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.68,0:01:12.72,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(93,83.753)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.72,0:01:12.76,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(102.6,93.353)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.76,0:01:12.80,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(112.2,103.753)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.80,0:01:12.84,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(120.6,117.353)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.84,0:01:14.72,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(129.6,126.153)\fad(0,311)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.82,0:01:16.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们跟你说了为什么不能回洛杉矶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We told you why we can't go back to L.A.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.53,0:01:17.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  我知道  核弹嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I know-- the bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.34,0:01:21.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈尔斯女士  如果你提供的信息...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ms. Myers, if the information you provide...
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.06,0:01:20.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(310.2,234.953)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.11,0:01:20.15,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(289.2,219.753)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.15,0:01:20.19,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(263.4,204.553)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.19,0:01:20.23,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(238.2,192)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.23,0:01:20.27,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(216,175.753)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.27,0:01:20.31,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(194.4,159.753)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.31,0:01:20.35,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(172.2,147.753)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.35,0:01:20.39,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(150,131.753)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.39,0:01:22.31,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\fad(0,308)\pos(126,117.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.72,0:01:24.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能成功阻止核弹装置\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}culminates in the successful interception of the nuclear device,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.50,0:01:28.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你对杰克·鲍尔的谋杀罪将被赦免\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you'll be pardoned in advance for the murder of Jack Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.21,0:01:29.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.61,0:01:32.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,除此以外别无他法  就这样吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}there's only one right choice to make and you made it.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.57,0:01:39.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs15\t(696,6577,\fs16)\c&H4BAAAD&\fad(1697,1183)\pos(187.2,191.79)}以下故事情节发生在下午5点到6点之间
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.73,0:01:42.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,将由这位备受尊重的媒体人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You've been told by a well-respected member of the press,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.12,0:01:44.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,罗恩·维兰德先生向你们说明\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Ron Wieland,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.25,0:01:47.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个国家正面临一起迫在眉睫的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that there is an imminent terrorist threat
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.86,0:01:49.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,恐怖袭击\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}leveled against this country.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.27,0:01:52.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,截至目前为止  这是事实\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That is true, so far as it goes.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.59,0:01:54.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,稍安勿躁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.50,0:02:00.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,事实是  我们每天都会收到许多类似的威胁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The fact is, we get a dozen such threats every day.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.56,0:02:03.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,至于我了解的是否比我公开透露的多\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And do I know more about them than I publicly reveal?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.83,0:02:04.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当然\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.37,0:02:09.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,向公众公布的内容和时间是个判断的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What is released to the public and when is a matter of judgment.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.72,0:02:12.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们推选我做出这个判断\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You have elected me to exercise that judgment...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.42,0:02:14.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是为了国家的最大利益\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}in the best interests of this country.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.77,0:02:20.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这正是我上任以来在做的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's what I've done since I took office.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.51,0:02:22.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这也是我今天在做的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's what I'm doing today.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.34,0:02:24.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我可以向你们保证...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I can assure you...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.28,0:02:28.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们完全掌控住了局势\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that we have the situation well under control...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.44,0:02:32.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不需要担心  -总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- and there is no cause for alarm. - Mr. President--
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.96,0:02:33.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:36.81,0:02:38.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这可不是葛底斯堡演说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That wasn't the Gettysburg Address,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.35,0:02:40.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-但是能为我们争取些时间  -讲得不错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- but it should buy us some time. - It was fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.14,0:02:43.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克·鲍尔情况如何\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's the situation with Jack Bauer?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.42,0:02:45.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他还被尼娜·迈尔斯作为人质扣押着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's still being held hostage by Nina Myers.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.07,0:02:50.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不一定非要这样的  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It didn't have to be like this, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.94,0:02:53.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我从没想要针对你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I never meant for it to be personal.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.71,0:02:57.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你杀了我妻子就是针对我啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It felt pretty personal when you killed my wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.41,0:02:58.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我别无选择\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I had to.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.26,0:03:03.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,特里无意中听到了涉及我的逃跑路线的内容\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Teri overheard something that compromised my escape route.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.26,0:03:05.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那轰炸反恐组呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about bombing C.T.U.?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.23,0:03:07.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,轰炸那些你过去共事过的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All those people you used to work with?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.14,0:03:11.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没有轰炸反恐组  只是卖了图纸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I didn't bomb C.T.U. I just sold the plans.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.36,0:03:14.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有你不得不追随的信仰  尼娜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You believe what you have to, Nina,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.66,0:03:15.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可你杀了你的朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but you killed your friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.74,0:03:18.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,闭嘴  杰克  闭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shut up, Jack! Shut up!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.49,0:03:21.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们没什么可聊的了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, we are done talking.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.81,0:03:25.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们就等着帕尔默打电话来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're just going to wait for Palmer to call,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.35,0:03:28.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那时这一切就结束了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and then this will all be over.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.92,0:03:29.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,明白了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You got it?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.63,0:03:35.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,知道吗  尼娜  你是对的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what, Nina? You're right.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.42,0:03:39.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  我真的不想在这里坐以待毙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, I don't really want to just sit here and wait to die.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.29,0:03:43.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别动  杰克  我说真的  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't move, Jack. I mean it, Jack!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.76,0:03:49.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你在他们核实你提供的信息之前杀了我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You kill me before they verify the information you gave 'em.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.93,0:03:51.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你就违反了你们的协议\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You'll be in violation of your agreement.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.89,0:03:54.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他们会把你关进监狱  -你会死的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- They'll just slap your ass back in jail. - And you'll be dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.49,0:03:57.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我已经是行尸走肉了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm already dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.25,0:04:01.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是最后的警告  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is your last warning, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.54,0:04:05.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,够了  再走一步  我就开枪了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's it. One more step, and I'll shoot.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.96,0:04:10.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,前进  快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Move in! Go!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.36,0:04:11.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快  快  快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go, go, go!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.01,0:04:14.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,冲  冲  冲  抓住她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Move! Move! Move! Grab her.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.77,0:04:20.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-通知直升机  -让她起来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Notify the chopper. - Get her up.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.86,0:04:32.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-走吧  快走  -我们不回洛杉矶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Let's go. Let's go. - We're not going back to L.A.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.07,0:04:34.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们已经说过了  走吧  -绝不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- We've already been through this. Let's go. - No way.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.10,0:04:37.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我和你说了  -是的  炸弹  快走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I told you before-- - Yeah, I know-- a bomb. Move, walk.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.00,0:04:38.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,伙计  不说我们  你自己呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Man, forget about us. What about you?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.09,0:04:40.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想被炸成碎片吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You want to get blown to pieces?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.29,0:04:42.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  我和你说了我爸爸是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I told you who my dad was.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.22,0:04:43.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你觉得他们会从反恐组派人来吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You think they'd send someone from C.T.U.?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.92,0:04:45.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-上车  -我不回洛杉矶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Get in. - I'm not going back to L.A.!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.79,0:04:47.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-米格尔  -趴下  趴下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Miguel! - Get down! Get down!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.72,0:04:50.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-别动  别动  -抓住他了  抓住他了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Don't move! Don't move! - I got him. I got him.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.93,0:04:51.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米格尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Miguel!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.35,0:04:58.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-当心  -走吧  上车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Careful. - Let's go. Get in.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.43,0:05:04.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-是的  好  -你会告诉他吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yes, good. - You'll let him know?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.09,0:05:07.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  我会告诉他  结束了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, I'll tell him. It's over.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.50,0:05:10.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is Jack okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.22,0:05:12.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  他们在尼娜开枪前控制了她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes. They got to Nina before she could shoot him.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.27,0:05:14.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about her?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.52,0:05:16.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,按照您的要求  她受伤不严重\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just as you requested, she wasn't seriously hurt.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.10,0:05:19.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先生  他们在等待您的指令\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, they're awaiting your orders.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.47,0:05:22.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-要把她关进监狱吗  -不要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Do you want her taken back to prison? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.89,0:05:26.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要履行最初的协议  一旦确认她的信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll honor our original deal. I'll pardon her for the charges...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.38,0:05:28.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会撤销对她谋杀和叛国的指控\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}of murder and treason as soon as we confirm her information.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.81,0:05:31.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那您要把她拘留在哪里  -洛杉矶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- In the meantime, where do you want her? - Los Angeles.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.37,0:05:34.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让她也感受一下她制造的恐慌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let her share the fate of everyone she's endangered.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.11,0:05:37.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.27,0:05:42.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,确定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's affirmative.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.81,0:05:46.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在峡谷的南边与直升机碰头\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll meet the chopper just south of the gully in the field.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.34,0:05:48.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-收到  -收到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Roger that. - Copy.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.17,0:06:48.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\fad(359,265)\pos(198.6,214.153)}华纳企业
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.59,0:07:01.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们是来找你说的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're here to find transactions
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.89,0:07:04.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鲍勃·华纳和赛伊德·阿里的交易的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you claim Bob Warner had with Syed Ali.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.94,0:07:08.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尽快找到  我们就能尽快离开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The sooner we do that, the sooner we're out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.62,0:07:09.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,坐吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Have a seat.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.27,0:07:16.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这样我无法做事  -我来控制电脑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I can't work like this. - I'll be keying the computer.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:22.65,0:07:24.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么打开发票文件夹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How do I open the invoice files?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.52,0:07:33.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么  -我要看发票文件夹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What? - I need to access the invoice files.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.61,0:07:35.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,打开仓库文件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}File, open, warehouse.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.68,0:07:39.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他们如何排序的  -我觉得是时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How are they ordered? - Chronologically, I think.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.27,0:07:40.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你觉得\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You think?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.30,0:07:45.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  我的未婚妻因为我让她爸爸坐牢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, my fiancee just left me on my wedding day
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.60,0:07:47.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而在婚礼那天离开了我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}because I'm sending her father to jail.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.12,0:07:47.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而他是我老板\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Since he's my employer
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.91,0:07:50.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的整个人生都毁掉了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think that pretty much means my whole life's in the toilet.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.57,0:07:53.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以就别给我施压了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So why don't you cut me some slack?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.26,0:07:57.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这城市里某处有一个核武器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's a nuke somewhere in this city,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.45,0:08:01.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果接下来一小时你不给我点有用的信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and if you don't give me something useful in the next hour,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.91,0:08:06.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我就带你回反恐组  把你锁在顶楼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll take you back to C.T.U. and chain you to the roof,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.19,0:08:09.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那样你就能亲眼目睹这鬼东西爆炸了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so you'll have a front-row seat when the damn thing goes off.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.61,0:08:27.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(189,201.399)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord0\shad2\3c&H2F2F2F&}我以为你要杀了她的
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.53,0:08:32.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(192.6,202.199)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord0\shad2\3c&H2F2F2F&}如果她知道什么的话早就告诉我们了
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.45,0:08:37.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(190.2,199.799)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord0\shad2\3c&H2F2F2F&}可能吧  但是我想保险一点
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.49,0:08:42.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(192,200.599)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord0\shad2\3c&H2F2F2F&}我想最后祷告一次
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.50,0:08:45.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(192.6,202.199)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs18\b1\bord0\shad2\3c&H2F2F2F&}没问题  你去祷告  这里交给我
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.96,0:09:04.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想变成他这样吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you want to suffer as he did?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.72,0:09:07.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  当然不想\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, of course not.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.79,0:09:14.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那和我说说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then tell me...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.05,0:09:19.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你从你父亲的电脑里看到了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}what you've learned from your father's computer files.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.67,0:09:20.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你告诉了谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who you told.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.22,0:09:26.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我说过了  我什么都不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I already told you. I don't know anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.04,0:09:54.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.04,0:10:02.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-杰克  -总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Jack. - Mr. President,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.40,0:10:05.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在坠机地点袭击我们的士兵\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the soldiers that attacked us at the crash site,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.13,0:10:08.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们是美国人  至少是在美国接受训练的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}they were Americans-- or at least American-trained.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.04,0:10:09.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.74,0:10:12.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有一名被杀的士兵\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}One of the soldiers that was killed
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.47,0:10:15.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,手臂上有珊瑚蛇的纹身\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}had a tattoo of a coral snake on his arm.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.23,0:10:17.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是一个本宁堡团队的标志\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's a signature of a group out of Fort Benning.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.14,0:10:21.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么小组  -一个秘密的特别行动小组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What sort of group? - A deep cover special ops unit.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.88,0:10:24.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  我知道那个文身也只不过是因为\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The only reason I know about the tattoo, sir,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.52,0:10:27.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在我职业生涯的初期  他们想要招募我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is because early in my career they tried to recruit me.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.53,0:10:30.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们的指挥是一个叫塞缪尔斯上校的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Their commander is a Colonel Samuels.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.82,0:10:32.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我从没听说过这个小组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've never heard of this unit.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.21,0:10:34.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  不会让您知道的  这才是关键\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, sir, you wouldn't have. That's the point.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.20,0:10:39.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他们掩藏在国安局的预算里  -国安局\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- They'd be buried pretty heavily in N.S.A.'s budget. - N.S.A.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.76,0:10:45.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就算他最初是由国安局训练出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, even if N.S.A. originally trained him,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.16,0:10:49.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他现在也可能是自由杀手或者雇佣军\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}isn't it possible he's freelancing now-- a mercenary?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.58,0:10:52.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果只是文身那么简单  我同意您的观点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If it was just the tattoo, sir, I'd agree with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.47,0:10:55.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是袭击我们的那些人了解我们的飞行计划\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But the men that attacked us had access to our flight plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.91,0:10:57.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们只能从内部获取到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The only way they could have gotten that information
Dialogue: 0,0:10:57.78,0:10:59.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这类信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}was from on the inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.86,0:11:03.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  我知道我们被自己人袭击\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, I know it sounds very farfetched
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.46,0:11:05.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听上去非常牵强\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that we got attacked by Americans,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.24,0:11:09.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是那个文身非常独特非常非常明确\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but that tattoo is very distinctive and very specific.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:09.66,0:11:12.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,感谢你的信息  杰克  你现在在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I appreciate the information, Jack. Where are you now?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.44,0:11:13.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们在坐直升机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're in a chopper.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.49,0:11:16.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,正在飞往尼娜·迈尔斯提供给我们的地址\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're on our way to the address that Nina Myers provided for us.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.80,0:11:20.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很快就要降落了  预计15分钟后抵达\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We should be touching down soon, sir. Our E.T.A. is 15 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.96,0:11:23.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-随时汇报  杰克  -是的  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Keep me posted, Jack. - Yes, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.96,0:11:35.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,长官  杰克正赶往赛伊德·阿里家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, Jack's on his way to the Syed Ali house.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.44,0:11:36.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,需要我把信号接进来吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Want me to patch a feed up here?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.55,0:11:38.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不用了  我相信你们都准备好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. I assume you have that under control.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.65,0:11:41.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, we do.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.34,0:11:51.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有别的事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Was there something else?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.14,0:12:02.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很难过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.97,0:12:13.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,明天你打算做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, what are you going to do tomorrow?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.93,0:12:17.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么  -如果炸弹没爆炸的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What? - If the bomb doesn't go off.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.80,0:12:18.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想过吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thought about it?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.17,0:12:25.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没有  -还会过来上班吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- No. - Probably come back to work here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.03,0:12:28.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当然  为什么不来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course. Why wouldn't I?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.43,0:12:32.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也不知道  做这份工作你开心吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know. You happy in this job?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.06,0:12:38.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不管你信不信  我以前想当一名教师\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Believe it or not, I used to want to be a teacher.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.87,0:12:39.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很久以前了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Long time ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.25,0:12:42.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道我为什么没当成吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know why I didn't?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.64,0:12:45.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为国防部给的工资更高\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'Cause D.O.D. Offered me more money.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.80,0:12:47.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这就是我做出选择的原因\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's how I made my decision.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.84,0:12:52.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以是我让自己受苦的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, I made myself miserable,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.70,0:12:55.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也把痛苦带给了身边的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and I made everybody else around me miserable...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.49,0:12:58.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就因为每年多赚五千美元\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}for an extra $5,000 a year.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.64,0:13:00.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这就是我的代价\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That was my price.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.01,0:13:03.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很遗憾\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.57,0:13:11.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, Michelle, I'm--
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.25,0:13:16.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不是一个很会给建议的人  但眼下这情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}not a big advice-giver, but, under the circumstances,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.37,0:13:19.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,莫待无花空折枝\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}don't wait around for your life to happen to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.32,0:13:23.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,找到能让你快乐的事  及时行乐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Find something that makes you happy-- do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.87,0:13:26.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为除此之外的事情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'Cause everything else...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.27,0:13:30.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都是背景里无关紧要的噪音\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it's all just background noise.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.24,0:13:47.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-罗杰  -总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Roger. - Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.90,0:13:51.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把你知道的所有关于本宁堡军事基地\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell me everything you know
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.83,0:13:54.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,罗恩·塞缪尔斯上校的事情都告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}about Colonel Ron Samuels from Fort Benning.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.57,0:13:58.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我对塞缪尔斯上校一无所知\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know anything about Colonel Samuels.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.32,0:14:02.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那下面的一个叫珊瑚蛇的特别行动小组呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about a special ops unit from down there called Coral Snake?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.28,0:14:05.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  先生  毫不知情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, sir. Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.76,0:14:08.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,国安局出资的准军事组织\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How could N.S.A. be funding a paramilitary group
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.08,0:14:09.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你怎么会不知情呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and you not know about it?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.67,0:14:12.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不了解具体情况  我确实说不出来什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, without knowing specifics, I really can't say for sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.21,0:14:16.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我猜测应该是国防部\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My guess is that the Department of Defense...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.95,0:14:19.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,利用了某些可以自由支配的资源\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}has used some of their discretionary resources,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.38,0:14:23.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,以我们的名义拿到预算\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}attached our name for budgetary purposes.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.07,0:14:26.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-常有的事  -太荒谬了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Happens all the time. - That's absurd.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.44,0:14:28.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,国安局只是负责搜集情报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}N.S.A. is information gathering only.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.37,0:14:30.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有军事权限\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They have no military mandate.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.51,0:14:33.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我认为这个珊瑚蛇小组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'd assume that this Coral Snake group--
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.59,0:14:36.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,跟我们看到的其它的小组一样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}like many others that we see--
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.48,0:14:40.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,属于某些人的个人项目\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}falls under somebody's pet project.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.71,0:14:43.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-秘密出资的  -你是怎么知道的  罗杰\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It's funded on the sly. - How would you know that, Roger?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.45,0:14:46.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一分钟之前你还跟我说你一无所知\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A minute ago you told me you never heard of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.31,0:14:51.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是根据以往的经验推测  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm just conjecturing from past experience, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.11,0:14:54.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没有确凿的信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have no concrete information.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.15,0:14:57.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我去查查\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me look into it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.32,0:14:59.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.83,0:15:24.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克·鲍尔的飞机是被美国军事小组打下来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack Bauer's plane was shot down by an American military unit.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.13,0:15:30.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克亲口告诉我的  我就不说细节了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack told me himself. I won't go into details,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.47,0:15:32.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是我相信他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}except to say that I believe him.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.34,0:15:34.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,美国军队  为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}American military? Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.94,0:15:36.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我刚跟罗杰·斯坦顿谈过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just spoke to Roger Stanton.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.12,0:15:41.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我认为他对我有所隐瞒  我要逮捕他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think he's hiding something from me. I'm going to arrest him.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.28,0:15:45.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,逮捕国安局的领导\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Arrest the head of N.S.A.?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.75,0:15:49.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鲍尔说攻击飞机的小组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bauer said the unit that attacked his plane...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.21,0:15:51.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,跟本宁堡军事基地塞缪尔斯上校有关\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}was connected to a Colonel Samuels out of Fort Benning.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.68,0:15:54.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,塞缪尔斯是国安局出资的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Samuels is funded by N.S.A.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.58,0:16:00.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,恕我直言  大卫  这太牵强了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}With all due respect, David, that's pretty thin.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.35,0:16:04.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着确实是  但是大使的飞机坠毁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}By itself, yes. But the ambassador's chopper crash,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.69,0:16:07.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,军事人员撤离洛杉矶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the evacuation of military personnel out of L.A.,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.50,0:16:10.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,罗恩·维兰德逃脱拘捕\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ron Wieland's escape from custody--
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.44,0:16:13.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些事情都是斯坦顿到达之后发生的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}those things happened after Stanton arrived.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.00,0:16:16.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,开除斯坦顿会引发混乱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Firing Stanton will cause chaos.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.97,0:16:19.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所有机构都向他汇报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All the agencies report through him.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.07,0:16:22.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谁都知道他在负责炸弹的搜寻工作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's running the search for the bomb, for crying out loud.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.03,0:16:22.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果总统说得对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If the president's right,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.99,0:16:25.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他不是在搜寻  而是在阻碍\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}he's not running the search-- he's impeding it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.50,0:16:28.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他为什么要这么做  -我也不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Why would he do such a thing? - I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.11,0:16:32.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果他确实有罪  除掉他我们才更有可能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But if he is, we have a better chance of finding the bomb
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.69,0:16:33.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,找到炸弹的下落\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}if we get rid of him.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.89,0:16:38.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大卫  你不能凭直觉就做决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}David, you can't do this on a hunch.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.37,0:16:41.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果斯坦顿是无辜的  炸弹爆炸了的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If Stanton turns out to be innocent and that bomb goes off,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.87,0:16:44.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要对上百万人的死亡负责\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you'll be blamed for the deaths of a million people.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.60,0:16:47.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果他真的有罪  而你又袖手旁观的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you do nothing and he is guilty of something,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.82,0:16:48.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还是会遭到责难\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you'll be blamed anyway.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.85,0:16:50.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  最起码\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, no. At the very least,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.37,0:16:54.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们需要得到证明  拿到证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we need to get some kind of proof-- some evidence.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.91,0:16:57.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不能随便逮捕国安局的领导  大卫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You cannot just arrest the head of N.S.A., David.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.74,0:17:01.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雪莉说得对  麦克  我们需要证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sherry's right, Mike. We need proof.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.81,0:17:07.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给我找到斯坦顿和塞缪尔斯上校之间的关联\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Find me a connection between Stanton and this Colonel Samuels...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.84,0:17:09.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快点找\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and find it quickly.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.55,0:17:21.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,洛杉矶  470郡  请讲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}L.A. County 470, go ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.77,0:17:24.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是谷地的布朗警官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is Officer Brown with Valley.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.87,0:17:27.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请求跟比尔·古考夫警探通话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Trying to reach Detective Bill Gucoff.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.34,0:17:31.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,布朗  你正在把两个嫌疑人转移到总局吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Brown? Oh, you're transporting two suspects down to Central?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.53,0:17:34.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-是的  -稍等  我给你接过去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- That's right. - Hold on, I'll patch you through.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.81,0:17:37.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我是古考夫  -比尔  你好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Gucoff here. - Hey, Bill.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.07,0:17:41.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么事  -我正在把犯人带过去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yeah? - Listen, I'm bringing the prisoners down.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.23,0:17:44.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好的  -一切正常吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. You got everything under control?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.92,0:17:47.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那个男的不好对付  但是  -干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- The guy gave us trouble, but... - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.39,0:17:50.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把手帕从我口袋里拿出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get the bandana out of my pocket.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.09,0:17:53.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-为什么  -点火\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Why? - To start a fire.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.38,0:17:55.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么  你疯了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What? You're crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.75,0:17:57.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他得把车停到一边去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He'll have to pull over and stop the car.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.31,0:18:01.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后他就灭火了  然后呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And then he'll put it out. Then what?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.87,0:18:04.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不知道  也许破坏得程度\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know. Maybe-Maybe it'll do enough damage...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.86,0:18:06.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,足以让我们回到警局得\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and we'll have to go back to the station.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.55,0:18:08.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-能给我们争取时间  -疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It'll buy us time. - This is crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.64,0:18:10.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能比去有个核弹随时会爆炸的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Crazier than going to Los Angeles
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.92,0:18:12.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,洛杉矶还要疯狂吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}where a nuclear bomb might go off any minute?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.52,0:18:17.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有件事听着可能有点扯  但是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, listen, this may sound a little crazy, but,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.08,0:18:19.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你听说过关于\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}did you happen to hear anything
Dialogue: 0,0:18:19.23,0:18:21.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天有炸弹威胁之类的事情了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}about some kind of a bomb threat today?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.55,0:18:27.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我做不到  得你来  -不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I can't do this. You gotta do it. - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.23,0:18:30.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来吧  你能做到  你比较娇小\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on. You can do it-- you're smaller.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.13,0:18:33.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不  我没听说过  怎么了  -快点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- No. I haven't heard anything. Why? - Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.11,0:18:36.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你确定吗  没人提到过吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're sure? Nothing on your desk or anything?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.10,0:18:43.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么了  有人告诉你有炸弹之类的事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why? Did somebody tell you there was a bomb or something?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.12,0:18:47.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么情况  你知道我不知道的事情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's going on? You know something I don't?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.85,0:18:53.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也不知道  可能没什么  但是一个孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, I don't know. It may be nothing, but one of the kids here,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.74,0:18:56.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她爸在反恐组工作  然后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}apparently her father works for C.T.U. And--
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.38,0:19:01.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他告诉她有炸弹之类的消息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He gave her some kind of information about a bomb or something.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.32,0:19:03.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,帮我查证一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just check it out for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.21,0:19:05.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可能就像我说的  应该没什么事  不过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Maybe, like I said, it's probably nothing, but--
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.97,0:19:09.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没问题  -这就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- No problem. - Okay, good enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.15,0:19:10.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢  算我欠你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thanks. I owe you one.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.13,0:20:01.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,收到  517\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I copy that, 517.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.89,0:20:13.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-金  -坚持住\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Kim? - Hang on, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.94,0:20:25.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你好  有人能听到吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hello. Can anyone hear me?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.08,0:20:28.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,加州高速警察六号站  哪位\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is C.H.P. Station Six. Who's this?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.21,0:20:30.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金  金  别\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kim, Kim, don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.06,0:20:36.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们在圣费尔南多118号路  出了事故\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen, we're on San Fernando, the 118. There's been an accident.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.12,0:20:39.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-需要救护车立即到位  -当值警官怎样了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- We need an ambulance right away. - How's the officer in charge?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.54,0:20:41.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他伤得很重  还有个人也是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's hurt badly. So is someone else.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.64,0:20:43.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-两位伤员  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Two injured? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.99,0:20:46.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  待在原地  我们这就派人过去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, stay there. We're sending someone now.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.94,0:20:49.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-坚持住  -全体注意  全体注意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Hang on. - All units. All units.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.31,0:20:52.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请前往圣费尔南多118号路  医疗救助\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Proceed to San Fernando at the 118. M.P.A.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.18,0:20:54.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有警官受伤了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Officer down. Officer down.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.42,0:21:21.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我再问你一次\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm going to ask you just once more, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.51,0:21:27.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你告诉谁了  -我没和任何人说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Who did you tell?  - No one.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.81,0:21:33.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是那座房子的红外监测\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here's an infrared of the house.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.77,0:21:34.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,两个人  都在这间房里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Two people, both in this room.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.93,0:21:36.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,其中一个应该是赛伊德·阿里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We assume one is Syed Ali,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.28,0:21:38.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我们无法确定  所以两个人都要活捉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but since we can't be sure, we'll need to take them both alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.75,0:21:40.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的人准备好了没\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are your men in position?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.72,0:21:41.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-给他们九十秒  -很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Give 'em 90 seconds.  - Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.00,0:21:43.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-喂  -乔治  是我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yeah? - George, it's me.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.31,0:21:44.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  你在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, where are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.58,0:21:46.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在现场  赛伊德·阿里在房里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm on-site. Syed Ali's in the house.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:46.70,0:21:48.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们大约在一分钟后就要行动了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna be ready to move in about a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.30,0:21:49.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们还需要帮手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna need auxiliary teams...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.67,0:21:50.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,以便一查出炸弹的位置\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}ready to move in the city
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.75,0:21:53.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就进入城市行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}as soon as we find out the location of this bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.16,0:21:54.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好  这方面我们已经在准备了  -很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yeah, we're already working on it.  - Okay, good.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.63,0:21:56.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们一抓住他我就联系你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll get back to you as soon as we get him.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.52,0:22:01.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-是贝克探员吗  -我是贝克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Agent Baker?  - Baker here.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.65,0:22:04.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你的人准备好后立刻通知我  -收到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Let me know as soon as your teams are ready.  - Roger that.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.38,0:22:09.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是鲍勃·华纳的访问代码\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is Bob Warner's access code.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.69,0:22:13.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可以看到  他进入的次数大概是我的两倍多\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As you can see, he logged on roughly twice as often as I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.50,0:22:16.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里是限制区  华纳小姐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is a restricted area, Miss Warner.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.76,0:22:18.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要立刻见雷扎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need to speak with Reza right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.50,0:22:20.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,恐怕不可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm afraid I can't do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.00,0:22:23.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只要一分钟  是我们婚礼的事情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's going to take a minute. It's our wedding day.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.55,0:22:26.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我明白  但是我们正在进行调查\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I realize that. We're in the middle of an investigation.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.35,0:22:32.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我可以和雷扎说说话吗  -我已经尽力了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Can I talk to Reza for a minute? - I tried to explain.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.40,0:22:36.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-尽快  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Make it fast.  - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.67,0:22:42.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Marie?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.41,0:22:53.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我之前说的  不是故意的  我很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey. What I said before, I didn't mean it. I'm so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.18,0:22:55.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是这整件事太令人惊吓了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's just this whole thing has been such a shock.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.64,0:22:57.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事  没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's all right. It's all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.20,0:22:59.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是我要嫁的那个人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You are the man I'm going to marry.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.59,0:23:00.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我明白你在做的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know whatever you're doing
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.72,0:23:02.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都是有必要的  我爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is 'cause you have to do it, and I love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.36,0:23:05.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不管要发生什么  尽管来  -我的天使\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- And whatever happens, happens.  - My angel.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.27,0:23:08.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们得继续工作了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have to get back to work.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.38,0:23:13.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-如果你愿意可以在旁边的房间等  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You can wait in the next room if you'd like.  - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.78,0:23:39.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是一个小伤口罢了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's barely a nick.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.72,0:23:42.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看起来没有感受起来糟糕\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not nearly as bad as it feels.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.65,0:23:53.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你没有必要杀我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't have to kill me.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.99,0:23:57.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把我留在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}J-Just leave me here.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.59,0:24:01.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当他们发现我的时候  你早就跑得远远的了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}By the time someone finds me, you'll be a hundred miles away.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.59,0:24:10.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有事情要发生了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Something's going to happen very soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.90,0:24:14.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很可怕的事情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Something terrible,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.43,0:24:17.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会造成很大的痛苦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}which will cause much suffering.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.12,0:24:20.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样更简单\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This will be easier.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.48,0:24:32.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,后退  后退\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fall back! Fall back!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.14,0:24:37.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我有人质  如果你们靠近  我就杀了她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have here a woman! If you come any closer, I'll kill the woman!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.86,0:24:42.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把盾牌拿进来  快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bring the shield. Bring in the shield now!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.85,0:24:44.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,罗伯茨  我们需要盾牌  快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roberts, we need the body bunker right away.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.83,0:24:50.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们不谈判  也不行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They don't negotiate, yet they don't shoot.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.84,0:24:55.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们要活捉的不是你  是我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's not you they want alive. It's me.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.00,0:24:58.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我尝试把他击倒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll try to take him out with a beanbag hit.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.80,0:25:26.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嫌疑犯安全\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Suspect is secure.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:26.15,0:25:29.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来  你没事了  没事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on. You're all right. You're all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.04,0:25:31.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事了  没事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's all right. It's all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.47,0:25:36.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,放轻松  深呼吸  都过去了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just relax. Take a breath. It's over. It's over. Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.75,0:25:39.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-杰克  他癫痫发作了  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Jack, he's going into convulsions. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.26,0:25:44.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你看到他吃了什么吗  -我一直都盯着他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Did you see him take anything?  - I was watching him the whole time.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.06,0:25:49.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,氰化物  他一定已经早就放在自己嘴里了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's cyanide. He must have had it in his mouth already.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.58,0:25:52.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们需要一名医生  立刻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We need a medic in here now. We need a medic now!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.43,0:25:53.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,收到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Copy that.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.68,0:25:56.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-在路上了  -该死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- On the move.  - Damn it!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.69,0:26:03.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给他照相  录指纹  所有都要做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want him photographed. Fingerprints, everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.72,0:26:05.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,送给反恐局做分析鉴定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want it sent over to C.T.U. for analysis.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.56,0:26:07.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要证据证明他是赛伊德·阿里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want confirmation that that is Syed Ali.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.00,0:26:28.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你喊了他们  你得走了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You called them. You should go.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.42,0:26:31.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们到了我再走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll go when they get here.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:32.22,0:26:35.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那样太迟了  他们会发现你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It'll be too late. They'll see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:35.49,0:26:36.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.53,0:26:49.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你  谢谢你所做的一切\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you so much. For everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.31,0:26:55.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这一切都结束后  我会找你的  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As soon as this is all over, I'm going to find you, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.62,0:26:56.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我保证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I promise.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.64,0:27:04.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.29,0:27:39.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我看到他们了  -各位  这边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yeah, I see 'em. - Come on, guys. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.36,0:27:41.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看到编号了  是143\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Notify dispatch, it's 143.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.89,0:27:48.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们封锁了这片区域吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did you get the area locked down?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.33,0:27:49.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都封锁了  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir. It's all done.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:49.77,0:27:51.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我联系了洛杉矶警局\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I contacted L.A.P.D.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:52.41,0:27:54.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们一得到情报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As soon as we get the intel
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.47,0:27:55.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就让三小队护送她回反恐局\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we'll have Unit 3 escort her back to C.T.U.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.24,0:27:57.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你得喝点水\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You should drink some water.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.46,0:27:59.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  长官  我立刻处理\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir. I'll get on that right away.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.24,0:28:16.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  我叫杰克·鲍尔  是个联邦探员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate, my name is Jack Bauer. I'm a federal agent.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:17.24,0:28:19.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道你一定受到了很大的惊吓\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know you've been through a terrible ordeal in there,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.22,0:28:20.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但恐怕我还是得问你几个问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I'm afraid I'm going to have to ask you a few questions--
Dialogue: 0,0:28:20.62,0:28:21.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可以吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}would that be all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.62,0:28:24.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是怎么到这里的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How did you get here?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.11,0:28:29.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Um, I was...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:31.32,0:28:32.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想要帮我的妹妹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}trying to help my sister,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.68,0:28:35.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以我雇了一个私人探员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so I hired a private investigator.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:37.15,0:28:38.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那些人以为我们知道什么事情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Those men thought we knew something,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:38.50,0:28:40.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-但我们什么都不知道  -慢点  慢点说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- but we didn't know anything.  - Slow down, slow down.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:41.20,0:28:44.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,死在另一个房间的那个人  是个私人探员吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The dead man in the other room-- that was a private investigator?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.53,0:28:50.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,保罗·柯普林  他们对他做的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Paul Koplin. What they did to him--
Dialogue: 0,0:28:50.89,0:28:53.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们  这里还有别人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They? There was more than one man here?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:53.84,0:28:55.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-有多少人  -两个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How many men were there?  - Two.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.36,0:28:59.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,另一个在你们来之前就走了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The other one left before you came.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:59.94,0:29:04.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你知道他叫什么吗  -赛伊德·阿里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Did you get his name?  - Syed Ali.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:04.54,0:29:05.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,确定吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you sure?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.72,0:29:08.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能描述一样他的样子吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can you describe him for me?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:09.93,0:29:12.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,又高又瘦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Um, tall, thin.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.55,0:29:14.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你记得他穿的什么样子的衣服吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you remember what kind of clothes he was wearing?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.95,0:29:15.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,黑体恤\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Black shirt.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.57,0:29:20.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,前面有颗银纽扣\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}W-With s-silver buttons down the front.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.25,0:29:21.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,黑色裤子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Black pants.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:21.62,0:29:24.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你记得他出去后上了什么车吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you remember what kind of a car he got into when he left?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:24.53,0:29:25.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道他要去哪里吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you know where he was going?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.74,0:29:28.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Excuse me for one moment.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.56,0:29:33.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,贝克  我是鲍尔  赛伊德·阿里还活着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Baker, this is Agent Bauer. Syed Ali is still alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.90,0:29:37.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们需要寻找一个穿得一身黑的中东男子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We are looking for a Middle Eastern man wearing all black.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.53,0:29:38.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还不知道他上了什么车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I didn't get a make on the car.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:38.84,0:29:40.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把描述发出去  发起全境通缉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Send out the description and an A.P.B.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.53,0:29:42.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们得赶快找到他  -收到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- We need to find him now.  - Copy.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.09,0:29:46.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  你说你是来帮你妹妹的  她叫什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate, you said you came here to help your sister. Who is she?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.68,0:29:49.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽  玛丽·华纳\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Marie. Marie Warner.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.19,0:29:53.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她本该今天结婚的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She was supposed to get married today.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.94,0:29:59.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雪莉  把你和我说的告诉迈克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sherry, tell Mike what you told me.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.91,0:30:03.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有一个中情局过去曾经使用的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's a back-channel communications network...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:03.97,0:30:06.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,秘密通信网络  叫做奥普康通讯网\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that the C.I.A. Used to use called OPCOM.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.62,0:30:08.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,已经关闭二十多年了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's been shut down for over 20 years.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:09.22,0:30:13.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,上个月  国安局收到命令重启这个网络\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Last month, N.S.A. was given orders to resurrect it.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.28,0:30:16.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是只有罗杰·斯坦顿才能下的机密命令\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was an "Eyes only" order issued by Roger Stanton.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:22.93,0:30:24.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不确定这够不够\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not sure that's enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:24.63,0:30:26.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,单独一个命令是不够的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}By itself it's not,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:27.31,0:30:30.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,除非斯坦顿在过去的几小时内\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}unless Stanton used OPCOM to contact Colonel Samuels
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.36,0:30:31.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,通过这个网络联系了塞缪尔斯上校\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}in the last few hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:31.93,0:30:33.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我这边正在查\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My source is checking on that now.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.99,0:30:36.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈克  给司法部长打电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mike, call the attorney general.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.45,0:30:39.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,启动法律程序\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Start working on this from the legal side.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:40.84,0:30:42.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果发现他们有联系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If we find this connection,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.64,0:30:45.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就立刻行动  逮捕斯坦顿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we'll move on it, have Stanton arrested.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.96,0:30:59.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想我们已经找出个无名氏的身份了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think we've got a positive I.D. on John Doe one.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.06,0:31:00.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们把他的指纹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you to cross-reference
Dialogue: 0,0:31:00.18,0:31:01.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,和保罗·科普林对照一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}his prints with the name Paul Koplin.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:01.99,0:31:04.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-国家反恐局  -我是鲍尔  给我转托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- C.T.U. - It's Bauer. Put me through to Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:04.42,0:31:05.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别挂  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hold, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:06.84,0:31:08.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  我是托尼  怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, it's Tony. What's up?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:08.29,0:31:09.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼  我还在现场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony, I'm still at the house.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:09.20,0:31:10.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我刚刚询问完那个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just got finished questioning the woman
Dialogue: 0,0:31:10.85,0:31:13.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,被赛伊德·阿里折磨拷问的女人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that Syed Ali was torturing for information.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:13.39,0:31:16.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她叫凯特·华纳  我需要你查一下她的背景\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Her name is Kate Warner. I want you to run a background check.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.19,0:31:18.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你是说凯特·华纳吗  -是的  怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Did you say Kate Warner?  - Yeah, why?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.01,0:31:20.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我今早才抓了她的家人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I had her family picked up this morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:20.54,0:31:22.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我几小时前还和她在一起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was with Kate Warner a few hours ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:23.70,0:31:25.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在说什么  他们有什么联系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you talking about? What's the connection?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.23,0:31:26.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一个叫雷扎·纳耶尔的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A guy name Reza Naiyeer,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.52,0:31:29.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他妹妹的未婚夫和赛伊德·阿里有交易\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}her sister's fiance had dealings with Syed Ali.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:29.54,0:31:30.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当然了  他不承认\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course, he's denying it.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.69,0:31:32.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他说是他们的父亲  鲍勃·华纳\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He was saying it was the father, Bob Warner.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:32.82,0:31:35.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我让理查兹带纳耶尔去鲍勃·华纳的办公室了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I had Richards take Naiyeer over to Bob Warner's office...
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.29,0:31:36.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去黑他的电脑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to try to hack into his computer.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:36.97,0:31:38.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,华纳现在就在我这边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have Warner here with me right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.40,0:31:43.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  凯特愿意和你谈吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, will Kate talk to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:44.04,0:31:45.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她的家人可不配合我们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'Cause her family's not cooperating.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:45.95,0:31:48.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也这么觉得  但我还得给她一点时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I think so. But I got to give her a bit of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:48.02,0:31:50.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她受到惊吓了  你得看看这个地方\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's been through hell here. You should see this place.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.72,0:31:56.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-杰克  还有件事  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Jack, there's one more thing. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.59,0:32:00.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她父亲  鲍勃·华纳  是中情局的情报员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The father, Bob Warner, he freelances for the C.I.A.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:04.43,0:32:06.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  听着  这件事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. Look, we're gonna have to start
Dialogue: 0,0:32:06.38,0:32:07.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要从根挖起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}from the beginning on this thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.70,0:32:09.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你得重新审查所有信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're gonna have to run everything again,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.17,0:32:10.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把线索连起来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}start connecting the dots.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:10.71,0:32:13.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些人都和此事有某种联系  你要查清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}These people are involved somehow. You got to find out how.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:13.95,0:32:15.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有发现立刻告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get back to me as soon as you got anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.86,0:32:16.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, you got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:24.26,0:32:26.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,各位  你们得收拾离开了  我需要这间房\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Gentlemen, I need you to pack up. I need the room.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:29.46,0:32:31.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-贝克探员  -我是贝克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Agent Baker? - Baker here.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:31.96,0:32:34.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-华纳小姐怎么样了  -不太好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How's Miss Warner doing? - Not so good.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:35.19,0:32:36.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一旦你认为她准备好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As soon as you think she's ready,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:36.37,0:32:38.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要你带她回到浴室里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need you to bring her back down to the bathroom.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.77,0:32:40.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  贝克下线了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Will do. Baker out.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.76,0:32:47.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  那三个日期还有之后一周  稍等\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, those three dates and anything the following week. Hold on.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.91,0:32:48.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, good.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:48.88,0:32:50.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有发现立刻告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me know as soon as you find something out.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.63,0:32:53.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-总统先生  -有什么发现\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Sir. - What have we got?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.57,0:32:55.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我找到进入奥普康通讯网的方法了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I found a way into the OPCOM channels.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.85,0:32:57.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好  进入调查\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good, tunnel in.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:57.05,0:33:00.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,问题是里面的文件都有密码保护\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The problem is the files are pass code protected.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.44,0:33:02.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们需要内部协助才能打开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're going to need someone internal to open them.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:03.01,0:33:04.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这需要时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's going to take time.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:04.10,0:33:07.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等  不  我查到一个副主管的名字\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hold. No, it's not. I just got the name of a deputy director
Dialogue: 0,0:33:07.81,0:33:10.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他退休了  但是密码还有效\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}who's retired, but his code is still active.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:10.75,0:33:14.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们可以用这个  简  你可以等一下吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We could use that. Jean, could you hold on for a sec?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:15.75,0:33:16.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我看看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's see.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.51,0:33:21.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-试试这个  应该可以用  -我回来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Try this. They should work. - I'm back.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.97,0:33:23.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我去指挥中心  检查一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll head over to the O.C. And check it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.97,0:33:26.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好  太棒了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good. Oh, that's terrific.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:26.15,0:33:28.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我来交叉比对这些\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm going to cross-reference these,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.04,0:33:29.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我需要你留在办公室里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I need you to stay in the office...
Dialogue: 0,0:33:29.60,0:33:31.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为我需要你在那里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}'cause I'm going to need you there.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:31.74,0:33:33.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  谢谢  再见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right, okay. Thanks. Bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:35.31,0:33:36.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在整合塞缪尔斯上校的办公室\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm collecting the dates that
Dialogue: 0,0:33:36.77,0:33:39.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,登录奥普康网络的日期\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Colonel Samuels's office logged on to OPCOM.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.45,0:33:43.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果麦克查到斯坦顿的记录  我们可以比对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If Mike can trace Stanton's access, we can look for a match.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:43.53,0:33:45.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-很好  -如果有结果\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- That's great. - If we have that,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:45.27,0:33:47.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,证据就足够了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you'll have all the proof you need.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:47.31,0:33:50.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等  斯坦顿有十几个手下都有他的密码\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wait a minute. Stanton has a dozen staff who share his code.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:50.39,0:33:51.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我们怎么确定是他的嫌疑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How are we going to pin him?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:51.47,0:33:54.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有个四位密码是他专有的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's a four-digit subcode that only belongs to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.66,0:33:56.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们就用这个确认是他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's the one that'll nail him.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:59.47,0:34:00.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-雪莉  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Sherry? - Yes?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:01.59,0:34:03.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你今天帮了大忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're doing an incredible job here today.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:05.62,0:34:06.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:09.02,0:34:11.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我忘记了你多么擅长做这些事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've forgotten how talented you are at all this stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:13.54,0:34:17.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大卫  我和你一起工作超过25年了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}David, I've worked with you for over 25 years.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:17.94,0:34:19.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,熟能生巧嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It had to rub off on me somehow.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:22.76,0:34:23.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很高兴有你在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm glad you're here.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:28.80,0:34:30.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我一直都在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've always been here.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:33.25,0:34:34.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不要忘记\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You remember that.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:38.30,0:34:39.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:59.69,0:35:01.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好  有发现打给我  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- All right, call me if there's anything. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:04.15,0:35:06.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是芭芭拉从华纳的办公室打来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That was Barbara at the Warner office.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:06.62,0:35:07.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有什么发现\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What'd they find?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:07.49,0:35:09.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,目前还没有  他们还在清查记录\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nothing yet. They're still going through the records,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:09.60,0:35:11.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但雷扎似乎很配合\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but Reza seems to be cooperating.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:12.21,0:35:14.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要疯了  这完全解释不通啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is driving me crazy. It just doesn't make sense...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:14.95,0:35:16.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,赛伊德·阿里和帕萨迪纳的这家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that Syed Ali has a connection
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.31,0:35:18.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,中产家庭有联系这件事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to this white bread family from Pasadena.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:18.51,0:35:20.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以你相信鲍勃·华纳吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So you believe Bob Warner?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:21.11,0:35:23.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他的档案和表现\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's nothing in his profile or his behavior...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:23.49,0:35:26.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有任何和恐怖分子有联系的迹象\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that suggests that he's involved with terrorists.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:26.34,0:35:29.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错  但看看事实\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I agree, but look at the facts.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:29.32,0:35:32.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,华纳投资公司和阿里的联系有文件记录\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There is a paper trail between Warner Investments and Ali.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:32.41,0:35:35.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-凯特·华纳被绑架也事出有因  -我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- And Kate Warner was abducted for a reason. - I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:37.37,0:35:39.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  我要你整理一份\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, look, I want you to put together a list...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.89,0:35:42.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鲍勃·华纳公司里所有经理和主管的名单\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}of all the managers and directors of Bob Warner's company.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:43.11,0:35:44.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想扩大范围搜索\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want to widen the search a notch here.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.94,0:35:47.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好主意  -还有别的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- That's a good idea. - Anything else?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:48.20,0:35:49.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Um,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:50.10,0:35:53.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我刚跟梅森谈过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was talking to Mason before and--
Dialogue: 0,0:35:56.75,0:35:57.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:58.69,0:36:00.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道现在不是时候  但是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I know this is hardly the time, but,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:00.87,0:36:02.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道我们还剩多少时间了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know how much time we have,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:02.44,0:36:05.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以我想说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so I just wanted you to know...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:05.41,0:36:08.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你愿意什么时候和我约会的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that if you wanted to go out sometime--
Dialogue: 0,0:36:08.26,0:36:10.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-米歇尔  -听着  你什么也不用说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Michelle-- - Look, You don't have to say anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:10.74,0:36:13.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我只想告诉你我的感觉  -不  米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I just wanted you to know how I felt. - No, Michelle...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:16.28,0:36:17.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的感觉也一样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I feel the same way.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:20.95,0:36:23.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我一直保持着距离\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've just been keeping my distance because--
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.42,0:36:27.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为你和尼娜之间的事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because of what happened between you and Nina?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:31.73,0:36:32.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:34.77,0:36:37.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以你觉得我接近你是为了你的情报吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, you think I just want you for your information?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:40.85,0:36:42.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, uh--
Dialogue: 0,0:36:44.14,0:36:46.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are we saying here? That, uh,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:46.35,0:36:48.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我们能从核弹威胁中拯救洛杉矶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}if we save L.A. from a nuclear bomb...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:48.77,0:36:50.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我们就可以一起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}then you and I can get together
Dialogue: 0,0:36:50.92,0:36:52.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,享受晚餐和电影  对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}for dinner and a movie? Is that it?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:56.76,0:36:58.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我来准备名单  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'll get that list. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:07.59,0:37:10.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,赛伊德·阿里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Syed Ali left...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:11.37,0:37:13.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在杀掉科普林先生后离开了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}after he killed Mr. Koplin.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:16.52,0:37:18.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们谈了一两分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They talked for a minute or two.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:20.31,0:37:22.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看了我好几次\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They looked at me a couple of times.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:26.70,0:37:31.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好像是说  我没用了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was like... I wasn't important anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:34.80,0:37:36.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们拥抱之后  他离开了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They embraced and he left.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:41.08,0:37:43.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他走时他们有对话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did they say anything to each other when he was leaving?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:45.20,0:37:48.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有  但他们声音太低\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, but, they spoke so softly...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:49.46,0:37:51.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而且基本都是阿拉伯语\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and mostly in Arabic.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:53.16,0:37:55.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿拉伯语  你怎么确定的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Arabic? How can you be so sure?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:56.57,0:37:59.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,小时候我家住在沙特阿拉伯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My family lived in Saudi Arabia when I was younger.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:00.79,0:38:04.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我妹妹和雷扎订婚后  我又开始学了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When my sister got engaged to Reza, I picked it up again.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:04.71,0:38:07.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能听出他们说的某个字吗  什么都行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can you identify any words that they said? Anything at all?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.47,0:38:17.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"礼拜"  他们说了几次礼拜  是指祈祷\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Salat." They said salat several times. It means prayer.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.15,0:38:20.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我听不到太多  他们声音很轻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I couldn't really hear anything. They were so soft.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:21.48,0:38:24.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,贝克  我是杰克  我要你联络反恐组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Baker, this is Jack. I want you to get ahold of C.T.U.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:24.03,0:38:26.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要查25公里内所有的清真寺\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want a list of every mosque in a 15-mile radius.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:26.86,0:38:27.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,清真寺吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mosques?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.69,0:38:31.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿里走时他们在说祈祷的事  时间吻合\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They were talking about prayer before Ali left. The time fits.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:32.12,0:38:33.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,收到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roger that.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:36.23,0:38:37.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有帮助吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did that help?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.34,0:38:41.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  我想是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes. Yes, I think it did.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:42.95,0:38:43.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:44.12,0:38:46.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  现在按正常程序\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate, the normal protocol for me right now...
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.39,0:38:49.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我应该把你送回反恐组继续询问\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}would be to transfer you back to C.T.U. for further debriefing.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:52.35,0:38:55.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但事实是  我不知道赛伊德·阿里的长相\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But the truth is, I don't know what Syed Ali looks like.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:57.10,0:38:59.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有人知道  只有你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No one does, except for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:02.56,0:39:04.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你帮我指认他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need you to identify him for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.62,0:39:17.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-斯坦顿  -是我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Stanton. - It's me.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:32.86,0:39:34.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不该打给我这里的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know better than to call me here.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:34.05,0:39:36.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想提醒你  他们知道奥普康网络的事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wanted to warn you. They know about OPCOM.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:36.76,0:39:38.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么会  -我告诉他们的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How? - I told them.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:38.78,0:39:41.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你什么  -大卫已经查到线索了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You what? - David had the bit between his teeth.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:41.39,0:39:43.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,无论怎样他都会查出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He was going to find out one way or another.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:43.91,0:39:47.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样我能再一点点获得他的信任\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This way, I get him trusting me again, little by little.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.83,0:39:48.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们现在怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do we do now?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:49.11,0:39:51.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们会把你和被击落的飞机联系在一起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They'll connect you to the plane that was shot down.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:52.37,0:39:55.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在大卫正在起草逮捕令\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}David's having an arrest warrant drawn up as we speak.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:56.65,0:39:58.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,坚持住  罗杰\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stay the course, Roger.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:58.46,0:40:00.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这件事后  你会得到你想要的一切\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When this is over, you'll have everything you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:01.15,0:40:05.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,同时  你不能交代  这很重要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}While, in the meantime, it's important that you don't talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:05.15,0:40:07.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不交代你的事  是吧  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Don't talk about you, you mean? - That's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:07.65,0:40:10.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我保持在岗位上非常重要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's more important than ever that I stay in place.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:10.60,0:40:13.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我还有多少时间  -不多了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How much time do I have? - Not much.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:21.28,0:40:22.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hold on.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:23.52,0:40:26.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是运货单  去年一月录入\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here's a shipping order. It was entered last January.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:27.61,0:40:29.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鲍勃和我当时都在欧洲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bob and I were both in Europe at the time.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:29.58,0:40:31.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以他从海外登录了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So he logged on from overseas.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:31.15,0:40:33.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  不可能  这系统不支持国际登录\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, that's not possible. It's not international.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:33.86,0:40:36.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但也不是从这个终端登录的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But it didn't originate from this terminal either.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:40.19,0:40:41.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有人黑进了系统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Somebody hacked in.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:45.10,0:40:48.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等  这不可能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hold on. This can't be.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:48.71,0:40:50.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在我的电脑上设置了这个程序\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I set up this program on my own computer.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:51.77,0:40:53.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我以为你在国外\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I thought you said you were out of the country.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:53.85,0:40:56.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我把电脑留在了这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I left my laptop here.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:56.38,0:40:58.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有谁能用这个电脑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who else had access to it?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:59.84,0:41:00.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nobody.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:05.61,0:41:06.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,除了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Except...
Dialogue: 0,0:41:10.59,0:41:14.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-玛丽  -我没想到你能查到线索\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Marie? - I didn't expect you to find anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:17.38,0:41:19.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我低估你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I underestimated you.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:49.95,0:41:51.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,过去的两年\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The-The last two years
Dialogue: 0,0:41:51.97,0:41:55.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,全都只是逢场作戏  是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}have just been-- just been an act, is that it?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:55.71,0:41:56.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我对你来说没有任何意义是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean nothing to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:03.81,0:42:08.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不懂啊  说句话  玛丽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Huh? I don't understand. Say something, Marie!
Dialogue: 0,0:42:09.54,0:42:14.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雷扎  你真的是个好人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Reza, you really are very sweet.

