[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,1,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.69,0:00:10.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(197.4,200.557)}{\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs25\b1\bord0\shad0\c&H78BDE7&\fad(0,808)}24小时\N\N{\fs15}第二季  第十一集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.11,0:00:13.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(189.6,121.6,193.8,105.6,0,356)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad3\3c&H2F2F2F&\4c&H336D99&}{\fs10}{\t(0,356,\fs20)\fn方正正中黑简体}前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.96,0:00:17.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  在坠机地点袭击我们的士兵\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr President, the soldiers that attacked us at the crash site,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.91,0:00:14.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(153,239.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.96,0:00:15.00,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(162.6,221.353)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.00,0:00:15.04,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(174,202.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.04,0:00:15.08,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(185.4,183.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.08,0:00:15.12,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(195.6,165.353)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.12,0:00:15.16,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(205.8,146.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.16,0:00:15.20,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(216,128.553)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.20,0:00:17.12,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\fad(0,311)\c&H449BA1&\pos(225.6,115.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.93,0:00:19.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们是美国人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}they were Americans.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.37,0:00:22.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们的指挥是一个叫塞缪尔斯上校的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Their commander is a Colonel Samuels.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.08,0:00:25.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,袭击我们的那些人了解我们的飞行计划\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Whoever attacked us had access to our flight plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.32,0:00:27.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们只能从内部获取到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The only way they could have gotten that information
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.73,0:00:29.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这类信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}was from the inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.86,0:00:32.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,罗杰  把你知道的所有关于本宁堡军事基地\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roger, tell me everything you know
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.63,0:00:31.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(306,240.553)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.68,0:00:31.72,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(294.6,222.153)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.72,0:00:31.76,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(282,203.753)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.76,0:00:31.80,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(270.6,185.6)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.80,0:00:31.84,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(262.8,166.953)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.84,0:00:31.88,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(250.2,148.553)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.88,0:00:31.92,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(238.2,130.953)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.92,0:00:31.97,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(230.4,112.553)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.97,0:00:33.97,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\fad(0,308)\pos(226.8,106.153)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.80,0:00:35.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,罗恩·塞缪尔斯上校的事情都告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}about Colonel Ron Samuels from Fort Benning.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.66,0:00:37.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我对塞缪尔斯上校一无所知\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know anything about Colonel Samuels.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.87,0:00:39.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我刚跟罗杰·斯坦顿谈过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just spoke to Roger Stanton.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.59,0:00:42.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他对我有所隐瞒  我要逮捕他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's hiding something from me. I'm going to arrest him.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.60,0:00:45.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想提醒你  他们知道奥普康网络的事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wanted to warn you. They know about OPCOM.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.20,0:00:47.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么会  -我告诉他们的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How? - I told them.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.47,0:00:49.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样我能再获得他的信任\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This way I get him trusting me again.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.30,0:00:51.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她知道什么的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If she would have known anything,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.34,0:00:53.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,早说了  杀了她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}she would have told us. Kill her.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.15,0:00:53.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(124.2,235.753)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.19,0:00:53.24,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(141.6,216.553)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.24,0:00:53.28,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(157.8,196.553)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.28,0:00:53.32,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(175.8,174.953)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.32,0:00:53.36,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(192,153.353)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.36,0:00:53.40,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(211.2,134.953)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.40,0:00:55.41,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\fad(0,312)\pos(227.4,114.953)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.10,0:00:55.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你没有必要杀我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't have to kill me.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.73,0:01:02.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能听出他们说的某个字吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can you identify any words that they said?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.46,0:01:04.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"礼拜"  是指祈祷\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Salat. It means "prayer".
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.87,0:01:07.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要查25公里内所有的清真寺\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want a list of every mosque in a 15-mile radius.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.79,0:01:09.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道赛伊德·阿里的长相\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know what Syed Ali looks like.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.99,0:01:12.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你帮我指认他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need you to identify him for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.56,0:01:14.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-点火  -什么  你疯了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Start a fire. - What? You're crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.74,0:01:15.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能比去有个核弹随时会爆炸的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Crazier than going to Los Angeles
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.51,0:01:14.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(136.8,224.553)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.55,0:01:14.60,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(157.2,204.553)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.60,0:01:14.64,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(178.2,183.753)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.64,0:01:14.68,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(196.8,162.153)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.68,0:01:14.72,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(216.6,141.353)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.72,0:01:14.76,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(235.8,121.353)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.76,0:01:16.51,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\fad(0,307)\pos(242.4,114.953)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.93,0:01:17.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,洛杉矶还要疯狂吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}where a nuclear bomb might go off any minute?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.44,0:01:24.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,出了事故  需要救护车立即到位\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's been an accident. We need an ambulance right away.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:26.86,0:01:29.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-有人黑进了系统  -还有谁能用这个电脑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Somebody hacked in. - Who else had access to it?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.77,0:01:27.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(234.6,242.953)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.81,0:01:27.86,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(216.6,228.553)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.86,0:01:27.90,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(201,214.953)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.90,0:01:27.94,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(185.4,200.553)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.94,0:01:27.98,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(170.4,186.153)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.98,0:01:28.02,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(154.2,170.953)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.02,0:01:28.06,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(138.6,154.953)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.06,0:01:30.15,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\fad(0,308)\pos(123.6,142.953)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.36,0:01:34.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-玛丽  -我没想到你能查到线索\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Marie? - I didn't expect you to find anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.74,0:01:46.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs15\t(696,6577,\fs16)\c&H4BAAAD&\fad(1697,1183)\pos(187.2,191.79)}以下故事情节发生在下午6点到7点之间
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.02,0:03:25.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-喂  -玛丽  我们有麻烦了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Hello. - Marie, we have a problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.95,0:03:27.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.73,0:03:31.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,贝希尔和马尔科死了  车现在在奥马尔手里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Basheer and Marko are dead. Omar has the van now.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.07,0:03:33.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你需要我做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you need me to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.73,0:03:35.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们本来应该去拿触发器的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They were supposed to pick up the trigger.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.00,0:03:39.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-去哪里拿  -马尔科工作的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where is it? - At the place where Marko worked.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.82,0:03:43.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在他的储物柜里  伯班克的R&J木材公司\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In his locker. R & J Lumber in Burbank.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.91,0:03:46.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-有密码吗  -没有  需要钥匙开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Is there a combination? - No. It requires a key.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.84,0:03:49.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但你必须想办法打开这个储物柜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But you must do whatever you can to gain access to this locker
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.92,0:03:52.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,并尽快把触发器拿给奥马尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and bring the trigger to Omar as soon as possible.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.34,0:03:55.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想让我去做这事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You want me to do this?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.71,0:03:58.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽  我们的任务现在得靠你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Marie, our mission depends on you now.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.15,0:04:00.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我指望着你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm counting on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.27,0:04:04.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会搞定的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll take care of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.35,0:04:08.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我知道你会的  -到地方见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I know you will. - I'll see you there.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.87,0:04:12.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽  你应该换个造型\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Marie, you should change your appearance.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:12.58,0:04:13.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ok.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.13,0:04:30.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真主保佑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As-Salamu Alaykum.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.66,0:04:32.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真主保佑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alaykum As-Salamu.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.89,0:04:43.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们去清真寺和战术小组汇合之后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As we get to the mosque and work up with the tactical team,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.15,0:04:45.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你需要做的就只是指认赛伊德·阿里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}all we need you to do is identify Syed Ali.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.94,0:04:47.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后我们就送你回反恐组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then we'll transfer you back to CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.08,0:04:51.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你还好吧  -还好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You OK? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.06,0:04:55.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道这事对你来说有多艰难\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I know how difficult this must be for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.51,0:04:57.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.85,0:05:01.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你能告诉我到底发生了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, it would really help me out a lot
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.43,0:05:02.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那才是真的在帮我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}if you could tell me what's going on.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.34,0:05:05.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我恐怕我无权\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm afraid I'm not at liberty
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.30,0:05:07.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉你更多了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to tell you any more than I already have.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.95,0:05:11.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们有权逮捕我父亲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your people took the liberty of arresting my father.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.32,0:05:14.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,赛伊德·阿里有权绑架我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Syed Ali took the liberty of kidnapping me
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.80,0:05:17.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,并在我面前杀了保罗·柯普林\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and killing Paul Koplin in front of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.23,0:05:20.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得我也应该有权知道具体情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think I've earned the right to know what's going on.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.99,0:05:25.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们相信赛伊德·阿里是一起恐怖袭击的主脑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We believe that Syed Ali is at the centre of a terrorist attack
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.62,0:05:27.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,计划将于今天袭击洛杉矶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that's gonna take place in Los Angeles today.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.32,0:05:30.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么恐怖袭击\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What kind of terrorist attack?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.09,0:05:34.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,核弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A nuclear bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.99,0:05:47.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是据我们所知唯一一个见过他的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're the only person we know of that's ever seen him.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.12,0:05:50.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们需要你帮我们指认他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We need you to identify him for us.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.84,0:05:52.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我现在带着你来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The reason why I'm taking you with me now
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.50,0:05:55.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是因为我们没有时间了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is because we're running out of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.28,0:06:03.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我是杰克·鲍尔  -我是乔治\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It's Jack Bauer. - It's George.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.72,0:06:05.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,贝克应该随时都会到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Baker should be on site any minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.77,0:06:08.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,清真寺附近已经设了警戒线\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got a hard perimeter set up around the mosque.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.00,0:06:10.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  我们一到就联系你  乔治\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, I'll get back to you as soon as we get there, George.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.06,0:06:13.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  还有件事我要跟你说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, there's something I gotta talk to you about.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.50,0:06:17.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,刚和纽霍尔的警务部门通过电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This got off the line with the Sheriffs Department at Newhall and
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.10,0:06:19.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们在押送金\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}they were transporting Kim
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.20,0:06:21.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后发生了事故\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and they got into some kind of an accident.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.17,0:06:22.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在说些什么  什么事故\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you talking about? What kind of accident?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.42,0:06:24.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不必担心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, don't worry.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.39,0:06:25.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她没事  没有受伤之类的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean she's all right. She didn't get hurt or anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.81,0:06:27.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她怎么会和当地执法部门在一起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What the hell was she doing with local authorities?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.23,0:06:29.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治  你的人本该接上她的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George, your people were supposed to pick her up.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.45,0:06:32.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的人到警察局的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}By the time our guys got to the station,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.65,0:06:33.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们已经把她转移走了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}they'd already moved her.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.99,0:06:37.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我猜是地方上的什么小官急于立功\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know, I guess some local deputy was trying to be a big shot,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.68,0:06:39.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,接管了谋杀案的指控\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}claiming jurisdiction for a murder charge.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.84,0:06:41.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她现在在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where is she now?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.90,0:06:44.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她在车祸之后就逃走了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She ran off after the accident.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.01,0:06:47.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道她是想躲开当地警方\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know whether she was trying to avoid the local police
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.32,0:06:50.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还是不想被带回洛杉矶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}or whether she was just trying not to get brought back to LA.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.33,0:06:52.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,该死的  乔治  你说你会搞定的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Damm it, George. You told me you would take care of this.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.89,0:06:54.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你跟我保证了的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You gave me your word.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.97,0:06:57.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托  一定要找到我女儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please, please find my daughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.94,0:07:00.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  这么说或许能让你安慰一点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, if it's any consolation,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.88,0:07:03.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她在估计的爆炸范围之外\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}she is outside the projected blast radius.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.36,0:07:05.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,找到她  乔治\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just find her, George.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.92,0:07:10.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What was that about?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.46,0:07:15.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我女儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My daughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.95,0:07:19.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-她也跟这事有关吗  -不是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Is she involved in this somehow? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.67,0:07:23.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不过她的确有麻烦了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's in some kind of trouble, though.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.95,0:07:30.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也说不好  希望不是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know yet. I hope not.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.93,0:07:37.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  我会告诉他的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, I'll tell him.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.75,0:07:39.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,司法部达成了一致意见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The consensus at Justice is that
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.19,0:07:41.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,针对斯坦顿的证据还不足以实施逮捕\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the evidence against Stanton isn't actionable.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.84,0:07:44.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们还想要多少\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How much more do they need?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.51,0:07:47.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们已经在斯坦顿和击落鲍尔飞机的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We've established a direct link between Stanton
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.42,0:07:49.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,变节雇佣军之间找到了直接联系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and the rogue mercenaries that shot down Bauer's plane.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.96,0:07:52.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个联系仍是间接的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That connection is still circumstantial.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.01,0:07:55.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他今天一整天都在阻碍我们找到核弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's been sabotaging our efforts to find the bomb all day.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.56,0:08:00.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不能也不会允许他继续领导国安局\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I cannot and I will not allow him to continue heading up NSA.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.28,0:08:02.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是说要找到法官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm only saying it's going to take time
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.43,0:08:04.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,批准逮捕令还需要时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to get a judge to issue a warrant.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.32,0:08:05.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们没有时间了  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We don't have time, Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.71,0:08:08.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那就别管什么罪名了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then don't worry about a pretext.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.00,0:08:09.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在就踢他出局\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Take him out of play now
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.36,0:08:12.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们明天再来解决合法性问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and we'll deal with the legal ramifications tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.36,0:08:17.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雪莉说得没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sherry was right.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.76,0:08:21.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有自己人在密谋推翻我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My own people working against me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.14,0:08:26.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,斯坦顿不会轻易开口的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stanton won't be easy to break.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.00,0:08:30.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,至少在我们仅有的时间里不会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not in the time we have.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.41,0:08:33.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们可能需要放宽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We may need to expand the limits
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.00,0:08:36.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你过去的底线\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}of how far you've been willing to go in the past.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.99,0:08:40.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你什么意思  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you saying, Mike?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.91,0:08:43.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,意思是你需要用尽一切手段\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That you do whatever it takes to find out
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.33,0:08:46.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,找出斯坦顿对这个核弹都知道什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}what Stanton knows about this bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.76,0:08:52.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  帕尔默女士  我不能现在打断他们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry, Mrs. Palmer. I can't disturb them right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.46,0:08:56.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大卫发现斯坦顿的事全靠我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, David only found out about Stanton because of me,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.11,0:08:59.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他完全没有理由把我挡在门外\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and it makes no sense that he's keeping me out of the loop.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.35,0:09:01.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不太确定你觉得我能改变什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not sure what you think I can do about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.71,0:09:04.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不如你告诉我他对斯坦顿的事怎么处理的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why don't you just tell me what he's doing about Stanton?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.68,0:09:07.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他还没告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He hasn't let me in on it yet,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.30,0:09:09.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以我也不知道结果是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so I don't know what's been decided.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.41,0:09:11.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你就不能去问出来吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can't you find out?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.63,0:09:15.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,帕尔默女士  如果总统想听我们俩的意见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mrs. Palmer, if the president wanted input from either of us,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.39,0:09:17.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我相信他会告诉我们的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sure that he would let us know.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.77,0:09:21.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,林恩  你拿走了我修改大卫演讲的功劳\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lynne, you took credit for my work on David's speech,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.87,0:09:24.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那也没关系  我无所谓\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and that was OK, I was fine with that.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.77,0:09:27.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但现在我唯一的目标\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But right now my only interest
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.54,0:09:30.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就是帮助大卫挺过今天\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is to help David get through this day.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.64,0:09:32.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想这应该也是你的首要目标吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now I assume that's your priority as well?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.84,0:09:34.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会想办法\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll see what I can do.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.58,0:10:00.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-华纳小姐  -她跟我走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Miss Warner. - She stays with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.48,0:10:01.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们可以行动了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're good to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.78,0:10:04.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我这部署了30个人随时等你指令\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've got 30 men deployed ready to move on your order.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:04.26,0:10:05.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,清真寺里有多少人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How many people in the mosque?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.83,0:10:07.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,100到125人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Between 100 to 125,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.72,0:10:09.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们会把男性分成十人一组的目标小组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we'll divide the men into target groups of 10 each.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.51,0:10:11.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们暂时还不进去  -长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- We're not going in, not yet. - Sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.77,0:10:14.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们现在进去  就需要控制整个人群\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We go in hot, we're gonna have a crowd control situation
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.06,0:10:15.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这就会给赛伊德·阿里足够时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and it'll give Syed Ali enough time
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.33,0:10:17.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在凯特指认出他之前自尽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to take his own life before Kate can identify him.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.29,0:10:19.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我们怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's the alternative?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.14,0:10:21.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们等到祷告结束\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We wait for the prayer service to end.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.44,0:10:25.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他和其他人一起出来  凯特指认出他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He comes out with everybody else, Kate identifies him,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.06,0:10:26.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们就直接逮捕他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}then we'll take him out surgically.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.58,0:10:28.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迅速活捉  他死了对我们就没用了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fast and alive. He's no good to us dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.87,0:10:30.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,万一外面有人先发现我们怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What if someone out here spots us first?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.88,0:10:32.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们打电话通知阿里  我们就失去了先机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They phone Ali, we lose our surprise.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.76,0:10:34.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这还是在假设他在里面的情况下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's assuming he's even inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.85,0:10:36.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们只是在靠微弱的直觉行动  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're working on a weak hunch here, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.60,0:10:37.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他可能在其他清真寺\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He might be at some other mosque.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.93,0:10:40.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们只能赌一把  就在这里等\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna have to take that chance. We're waiting this out.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.58,0:10:45.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我可以进去  看看他在不在里面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I could go in. See if he's inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.62,0:10:53.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我可以围个头巾  遮住脸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll wear a hijab, hide my face.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.45,0:10:54.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他看不到我的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He wouldn't see me.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.17,0:10:58.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对不起  我不愿意让你置身这种险境中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry, I don't feel comfortable putting you in that kind of a position.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.21,0:11:03.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听你刚才说的  我们全都处于险境\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}From what you've told me, we're all in a pretty bad position.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.24,0:11:07.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我能帮忙  我非常想有这个机会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If I could help, I'd really like the chance.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.05,0:11:18.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你真的觉得你能做到吗  -对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You really think you can do this? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.46,0:11:24.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给我拿清真寺的平面图  我要看看内部结构\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get me the schematics to the mosque. I'll look at the floor plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.85,0:11:47.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fay-0.04\fax0.1\pos(159,64.8)}{\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs15\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H1E0920&}登录失败
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.23,0:11:53.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fay0.03\fax-0.1\pos(207,60.8)}{\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H1E0920&}登录失败
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.24,0:12:02.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-一切就绪了  总统先生  -行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Everything's in place, Mr. President. - Do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.40,0:12:04.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir. Let's move.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.74,0:12:30.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么回事  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's going on, Mike?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.32,0:12:33.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,史坦顿先生  根据总统命令\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Stanton, by order of the president,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.60,0:12:36.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要以密谋背叛美利坚合众国罪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm placing you under arrest for conspiracy
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.01,0:12:38.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,逮捕你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to commit treason against the United States of America.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.95,0:12:41.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What the hell are you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.92,0:12:46.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,手拿开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hands off.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.58,0:12:51.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要求和总统谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I demand to speak to the president.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.00,0:12:55.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,肯定会有机会的  先生  走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sure you'll get your chance, sir. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.66,0:13:36.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请进\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come in.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.61,0:13:44.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先生  帕尔默夫人过去半小时一直在联系你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, Mrs. Palmer's been trying to reach you for the last half-hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.84,0:13:45.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.26,0:13:49.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她现在在七号线上等您\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's on line seven waiting right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.57,0:13:53.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-如果想推掉我可以帮您  -不  我来接\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I can put her off if you'd like. - No, I'll take it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.97,0:13:58.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-谢谢  -是  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Thank you. - Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.03,0:14:14.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-雪莉  怎么了  -大卫  谢天谢地\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yes, Sherry. What is it? - David, thank God.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.61,0:14:18.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想知道你决定怎么处置罗杰了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was just wondering what you'd decided to do about Roger.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.26,0:14:20.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我正在派人拷问他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm having him questioned.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.99,0:14:25.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他承认下令击落杰克·鲍尔的飞机了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Has he admitted to ordering Jack Bauer's plane shot down?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.42,0:14:26.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.52,0:14:29.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我们并没比一小时前知道得更多\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then we don't know any more than we did an hour ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.36,0:14:30.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想说什么  雪莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What is your point, Sherry?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.46,0:14:34.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想说我觉得你应该\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My point is I think you should have waited
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.10,0:14:35.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等更确凿的证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}for something more concrete.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.66,0:14:38.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我做决定不用请示你  雪莉  不再需要了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't run my decisions past you, Sherry, not any more.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.55,0:14:42.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你做决定依据的一大部分情报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A large part of the intelligence
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.36,0:14:45.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都是我提供的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you're basing your decisions on came from me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.56,0:14:47.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想我应该在此有一席之地了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think I've earned a seat at the table here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.91,0:14:50.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不是我的幕僚之一\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're not a member of my staff.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.75,0:14:52.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你也不是政府职员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're not a government employee.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.43,0:14:53.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你也不是我妻子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And you're not my wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.88,0:14:55.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是你的决定  不是我的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That was your decision, not mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.18,0:14:59.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雪莉听我说  不管你今天在这里演什么角色\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sherry listen to me, whatever role you're playing here today
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.63,0:15:01.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都要听我的  跟我的时间走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is on my terms, my timetable.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.97,0:15:05.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,继续你的工作  我过一会联系你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Continue doing what you're doing. I'll speak to you soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.84,0:15:06.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.44,0:15:21.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们需要一个可以配合的人在这  不是三个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We need one person here that we can coordinate with, not three.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.95,0:15:24.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这件事我们解决了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, we got that sorted out.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.53,0:15:27.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让他联系杰克·鲍尔  他是主管\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You have him contact Jack Bauer. He's running point for us.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.72,0:15:28.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.53,0:15:36.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,联调局的人  他们要派个代表去清真寺\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}FBI. They want a representative at the mosque,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.78,0:15:38.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但他们自己搞混了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but they've got their wires crossed.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.39,0:15:44.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们刚刚谈的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen, what we were talking about before...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.53,0:15:46.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对  我很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.66,0:15:50.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不该把你置于那种境地\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I shouldn't have put you on the spot like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.40,0:15:54.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  其实我很高兴你这样做了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, actually, I'm glad you did.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.55,0:15:58.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-真的吗  -对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You are? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:59.52,0:16:03.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在这里工作之后我们之间一直有某种东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's been something hanging between us since you started here.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.84,0:16:07.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对  确实有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Yeah, there has.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.72,0:16:11.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很久之前就决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I made a decision a while ago
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.34,0:16:14.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尽量让工作和私人事务互不干涉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to try to keep personal and professional stuff separate.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.30,0:16:18.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但现在我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But now I...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.62,0:16:24.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔·德斯勒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle Dessler.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.54,0:16:26.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉阿尔梅达华纳情绪不稳\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell Almeida Warner's getting agitated.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.44,0:16:27.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  我会转达\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, I'll tell him.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.35,0:16:31.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-七号审讯室有情况  -鲍勃·华纳吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- There's a problem in room seven. - Bob Warner?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.39,0:16:32.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对  他情绪激动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, he's getting violent.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.22,0:16:42.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,放开你的手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get your hands off of me!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.19,0:16:45.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们不能把我关在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You can't keep me here!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.95,0:16:49.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么回事  -他要喝水\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What's going on? - He asked for water.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.18,0:16:51.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我带他去厕所  他冲出了大门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I brought him to the restroom he bolted out the door.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.45,0:16:52.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么我不能见律师\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why can't I see my lawyer?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.79,0:16:55.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让他坐下  冷静点  华纳先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sit him down. Calm down, Mr. Warner!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.42,0:16:59.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不会冷静  我要有人听我说话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I won't calm down. I want someone to start listening to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.21,0:17:00.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要你冷静\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need you to calm down!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.09,0:17:05.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不过雷扎告诉你什么  他都在撒谎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Whatever Reza told you, he's lying.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.04,0:17:07.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你这样对你的案子没有帮助  懂吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You are not helping your case here. You understand me?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.49,0:17:09.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You wanna have a conversation,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.68,0:17:11.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还是想让我关你一晚上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}or do you want me to lock you up for the rest of the night?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.99,0:17:21.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我女儿们呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where are my daughters?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.95,0:17:25.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雷扎被带去你办公室后五分钟玛丽也走了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Marie left here five minutes after Reza was taken to your office.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.93,0:17:27.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about Kate?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.82,0:17:33.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么了  凯特出什么事了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What? Has something happened to Kate?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.51,0:17:36.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她和我们的一位探员在一起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's with one of our agents.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.02,0:17:39.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们一位探员  为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}One of your agents? Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.78,0:17:42.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你得相信我们  华纳先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're gonna have to trust us, Mr. Warner.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.90,0:17:45.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她不会有事的  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's gonna be fine, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.00,0:17:48.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,相信\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Trust?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.29,0:17:52.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里是人们祈祷的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is where the men pray,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.76,0:17:53.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在前面  离入口最近\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}in front, closest to the entrance.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.99,0:17:56.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,穿过他们  经过这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You walk by them as you pass through here
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.79,0:17:58.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,直到后面的女性祈祷区\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}down to the women's prayer area in the back.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.97,0:18:00.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你只有一次机会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You've got one shot.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.03,0:18:03.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你经过他们之后  就只能看到他们的后背了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Once you pass them, their backs'll be to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.05,0:18:05.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,确保看清整个房间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So make sure you get a clean look at the whole room.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.52,0:18:09.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果看到阿里  穿过女性祈祷区\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you spot Ali, go past the women's prayer area here,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.10,0:18:11.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,上去到火灾紧急出口\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}up here to this fire-exit door.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.72,0:18:13.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你进去之后我们会关闭警铃\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll disable the alarm while you're inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.50,0:18:15.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们在巷子里等你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll be waiting for you in the alley.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.54,0:18:18.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-明白了吗  -明白\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Are you clear? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.21,0:18:21.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你们的人就位了吗  -是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Are your men in place? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.00,0:18:24.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.34,0:18:38.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  你确定吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate, you sure about this?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.69,0:18:40.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,确定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.72,0:18:44.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  拿着这个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK. Take this.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.61,0:18:47.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果阿里看到你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If Ali sees you,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.96,0:18:50.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,或者你觉得有危险  按这个按钮\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}or you feel like you're in danger, press that button.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.22,0:18:52.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这会给我的步话机发射求救信号\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It'll send a distress signal to my walkie-talkie
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.73,0:18:54.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们马上就冲进去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and we'll be in immediately.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.08,0:18:58.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,小心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Be careful.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.32,0:19:35.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她进去了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's in.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.34,0:19:40.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真主保佑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As-Salamu Alaykum.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.83,0:19:42.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真主保佑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alaykum As-Salamu.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.09,0:19:43.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,祈祷已经开始了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The prayers have already begun.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.97,0:19:47.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不好意思  我迟到了  路上堵车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry I'm late. There was traffic.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.32,0:19:50.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你以前和我们祈祷过吗  -有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Have you prayed with us before? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.24,0:19:54.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是有一段时间以前了  我离开了一段时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's been a while, though. I've been away.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.25,0:21:29.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是杰克  你没事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's Jack. You're all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.20,0:21:31.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他在里面  赛伊德·阿里  他在里面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's in there. Syed Ali. He's in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.53,0:21:47.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,史坦顿最后一个电话打给弗吉尼亚州\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stanton's last call was to Virginia.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.74,0:21:49.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,通话时间不够确定全部的号码\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He wasn't on long enough to get a complete number,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.93,0:21:52.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我们知道是中情局的前缀号码\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but we know it's a Langley prefix.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.29,0:21:56.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,中情局\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}CIA.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.85,0:21:59.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,中士\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sergeant.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.07,0:22:12.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,坐下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sit down.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.18,0:22:23.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们掌握了一切  罗杰\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have it all, Roger.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.40,0:22:31.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你用机密命令重启了奥普康网络\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You reactivated OPCOM with an eyes-only order.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.36,0:22:33.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你使用它在仅仅两小时前\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You used it to communicate
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.98,0:22:36.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,联络了塞缪尔斯上校\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}with Colonel Samuels as recently as two hours ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.79,0:22:42.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而我们已经把塞缪尔斯直接联系到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And we've connected Samuels directly to the mercenaries
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.32,0:22:43.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,试图杀死杰克·鲍尔的雇佣军\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that tried to kill Jack Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.94,0:22:46.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道  罗杰\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know, Roger.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.27,0:22:50.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这看起来几乎就像是你想要这个炸弹今天爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It almost seems as if you want this bomb to go off today.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.81,0:22:58.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我跟你说  如果有人牺牲  罗杰\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I'll tell you this: if people die, Roger,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.31,0:23:01.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你会被处决\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you'll be executed.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.70,0:23:04.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而即便我们能及时发现炸弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And even if we find the bomb in time,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.68,0:23:09.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你还是会被判终身监禁不得保释\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you'll still get life without the possibility of parole.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.49,0:23:13.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我只想要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But all I want...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.17,0:23:17.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,及时找到炸弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is to find the bomb in time.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.09,0:23:22.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以我有个交易给你考虑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's why I have a deal for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.58,0:23:27.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你告诉我一切  我是说一切情报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You tell me everything, I mean everything
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.61,0:23:30.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我可以抹掉你的罪名\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and I'll bury this.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.38,0:23:36.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你可以因为身体原因辞职\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You resign, due to health reasons.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.66,0:23:39.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你可以领到养老金\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You'll collect your pension.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.09,0:23:42.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你会住在乡下的漂亮房子里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You'll retire in a nice house, somewhere in the country.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.93,0:23:48.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你还会得到书面无罪保证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You'll be given a written grant of immunity.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.77,0:23:52.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有人会知道这件事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And nobody will ever know anything about this.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.22,0:23:59.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你同意吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do we have a deal?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.24,0:24:16.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道你在说什么  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know what you're talking about, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.53,0:24:20.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我什么都没做错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've done nothing wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.33,0:24:25.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也和你一样不知道关于炸弹的更多信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know any more about the bomb than you do.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.35,0:24:48.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你负责巷子里的两个后门出口\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you to cover these two back exits from the alley.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.32,0:24:51.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要抓的是年近四十的中东男子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're looking for a Middle Eastern man, late 30s.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.33,0:24:53.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,黑色上衣  银色口子  黑色裤子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Black shirt, silver buttons, black pants.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.18,0:24:56.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,华纳小姐和我负责正门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Miss Warner and I will cover the main entrance.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.75,0:24:59.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一旦人群开始离开清真寺\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As soon as the crowd starts to leave the building,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.50,0:25:01.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她就会指认阿里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}she'll identify Ali.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.12,0:25:03.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会把他的位置通知贝克探员  他会下令\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll relay his position to Agent Baker. He will give the go.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.74,0:25:05.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在那之前不要轻举妄动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No one moves before that happens.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.07,0:25:06.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们不能让他跑了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The last thing we want is to lose him.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.50,0:25:08.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你需要开枪  不要取他性命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you fire your weapon, shoot to wound only.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.55,0:25:11.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有十九分钟祈祷结束\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're looking at 19 minutes before the service is over.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.90,0:25:15.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大家听懂了吗  我们不能有闪失\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is everybody clear? We cannot afford any mistakes here.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:15.59,0:25:16.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.30,0:25:38.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-给你  长官  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- There you are, sir. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.22,0:25:51.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,用中间的旋钮控制对焦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Control the focus with the centre dial here.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.41,0:26:05.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在清真寺为我们所做的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What you did for us in the mosque,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.99,0:26:09.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得十分勇敢  谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I thought it was really courageous. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:11.78,0:26:14.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在说笑吗  我还在发抖呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're kidding me. I'm still shaking.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.83,0:26:16.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你做得很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You did great.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.78,0:26:23.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,祈祷还有十七分钟结束\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The prayer service lets out in 17 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.07,0:29:08.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你要见我吗  先生  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You wanted to see me, sir?  - Yes, i did.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.29,0:29:10.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-多谢你能谨慎行事  -应该的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Thanks for keeping this discreet. - Of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.73,0:29:14.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,泰德  你在特工处工作几年了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ted, how long have you been with the Secret Service?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.62,0:29:15.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,五年半了  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Five and a half years, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:18.47,0:29:21.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我了解到你参加过特殊行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I understand you have a background in Special Ops.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:21.75,0:29:23.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,陆军特种部队  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Green Berets, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.23,0:29:24.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迈尔斯堡第七小队  87级\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Unit seven out of Fort Myers, '87.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:21.75,0:29:24.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}美国陆军特种部队的绰号=Special Forces
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.28,0:29:29.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-有没有学以致用  -去过波斯湾  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Ever have a chance to put your training to use? - The Gulf, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.21,0:29:31.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有其他地方吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Anywhere else?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.20,0:29:36.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还参加过一些秘密行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There were some other... covert ops.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.37,0:29:41.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是中情局指挥的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Under the directorate at the CIA?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:45.50,0:29:48.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事  泰德  我没想审讯你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's all right, Ted. I'm not on a witch-hunt here.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:49.05,0:29:50.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我需要你回答我的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I do need you to answer the question.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:52.55,0:29:55.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  先生  是中情局指挥的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir. For the CIA.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:56.52,0:30:01.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  你知道当前形势的严重性吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good. You understand the gravity of today's situation?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:01.75,0:30:02.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,知道  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:04.15,0:30:05.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我猜你已经听说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I guess you've heard by now
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.51,0:30:09.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,罗杰·斯坦顿已经不是国安局的负责人了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that Roger Stanton's no longer functioning as the head of NSA.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:09.55,0:30:12.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我听说他被捕了  -没错  我下的命令\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I heard he was arrested. - He was, under my authority.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.89,0:30:17.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我现在要你做的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What I'm about to ask you to do
Dialogue: 0,0:30:17.95,0:30:21.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不在你特工处的工作范围内\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}falls outside the parameters of your charge of Secret Service.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:21.82,0:30:23.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有我的授意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You won't be able to tell anyone about this
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.42,0:30:24.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不能跟任何人讲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}without my direct consent.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:26.95,0:30:28.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你意下如何  泰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you still with me, Ted?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:29.63,0:30:31.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你需要我怎么做  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What would you like me to do, sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.28,0:30:36.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,从罗杰·斯坦顿那里获取情报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Extract information from Roger Stanton.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:39.88,0:30:40.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我明白了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I see.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.00,0:30:46.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果他负隅顽抗  我能采取多重的手段\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If he resists, how far am I permitted to go?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:48.69,0:30:49.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不惜一切代价\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Whatever you need to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:54.51,0:30:55.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,明白  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.30,0:31:08.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼  理查兹和马加比中枪了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony. Richards and Maccabee were shot.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:08.91,0:31:10.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雷扎·纳耶尔也是  他们都死了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So was Reza Naiyeer. They're all dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:10.46,0:31:12.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么  -对  清洁工发现了他们的尸体\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What? - Yeah, a janitor found their bodies.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.38,0:31:14.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我刚刚和洛杉矶警局通过电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just got off the phone with the LAPD.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.16,0:31:16.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有嫌疑人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are there any suspects?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.46,0:31:19.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我上次和马加比谈话时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Last time I talked to Maccabee,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.85,0:31:22.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她说玛丽·华纳刚到那里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}she said that Marie Warner had just got there.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:22.55,0:31:24.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她想和雷扎谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She wanted to talk to Reza.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:24.93,0:31:28.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽·华纳  发生枪击时她在那里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Marie Warner? She was there during the shootings?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:28.06,0:31:30.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错  安全摄像头显示过去四十分钟内\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, security cameras show she was the only one
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.16,0:31:32.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只有她一人离开过大楼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to leave the building in the last 40 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:45.84,0:31:47.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-鲍尔  -杰克  是我  托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Bauer. - Yeah, Jack. It's Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:47.48,0:31:50.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你那边什么情况  -我们还得等十分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How's it going over there? - We got about 10 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.29,0:31:54.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你还和凯特·华纳在一起吗  -在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Are you still with Kate Warner? - Yes, I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.13,0:31:57.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得给你说一些情报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I gotta give you some information,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:57.23,0:31:59.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是你不能告诉别人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but you need to keep this conversation one-sided.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:59.49,0:32:01.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你能做到吗  -可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Can you do that? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:04.12,0:32:06.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,理查兹和马加比中枪死掉了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Richards and Maccabee have been shot and killed.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:06.45,0:32:07.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雷扎·纳耶尔也是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So was Reza Naiyeer.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:11.90,0:32:15.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们有确凿证据表明枪手是华纳姐妹之一\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have strong evidence that Marie Warner/Kate Warner was the shooter.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:17.88,0:32:19.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  我知道了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:20.46,0:32:23.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特·华纳过去半小时和别人联系过吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Has Kate Warner been contacted by anybody in the last half-hour?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.67,0:32:28.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有  她一直和我在一起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, she's been with me the entire time.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:29.46,0:32:32.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  我觉得你应该提防着点她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, I think you have to treat her as an unknown.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.30,0:32:35.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,据我们所知  她和她妹妹共事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For all we know, she's working with her sister.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:36.74,0:32:37.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得不是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.91,0:32:41.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果不是我们出现  阿里的人已经把她杀了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ali's men would've killed her if we hadn't shown up.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.49,0:32:42.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果凯特的妹妹涉嫌其中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If Kate's sister's part of this,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:42.77,0:32:44.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,或者如果她是恐怖分子的一员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}or if she's one of the terrorists,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:45.57,0:32:47.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我真觉得凯特对此并不知情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I really don't think Kate knows about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:48.77,0:32:50.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  你自己拿主意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, that's your call.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.08,0:32:53.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我就是把情报告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just wanted to give you the information.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.50,0:32:54.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:57.69,0:32:58.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你办公室的电话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Was that your office?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.10,0:33:01.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:03.08,0:33:06.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我父亲在他们那里吗  -在  他很安全\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Are they still holding my dad? - Yes, your dad's safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:06.91,0:33:10.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我妹妹呢  她还好吗  有人有她的消息吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about my sister? Is she OK? Has anyone heard from her?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:10.73,0:33:11.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:46.82,0:33:49.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,打扰了  比尔告诉我你是这里的负责人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Excuse me. Bill told me you're the guy in charge.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:50.46,0:33:51.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是这儿的领班\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm the foreman.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.95,0:33:54.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这听着有点荒谬  但我需要帮助\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's sounds a little crazy, but I need a favour.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.70,0:33:56.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得从我男朋友储物柜里拿点东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need to get something out of my boyfriend's locker.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:57.04,0:33:59.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你男朋友是谁  -马尔科·哈塔米\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Your boyfriend? - Marko Khatami.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:00.86,0:34:02.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你和马尔科在约会吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You go out with Marko?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:02.73,0:34:05.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错  昨晚我们大吵一架\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I did. We got into a fight last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:05.30,0:34:06.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说来话长\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a long story,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:06.13,0:34:08.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想说的是我们已经分手了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but the point of it is we're not going out any more.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:09.30,0:34:12.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-所以他今天才没来上班  -我想是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- That why he didn't show up for work today? - I guess.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:13.06,0:34:14.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当时吵得挺凶的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was a pretty bad fight.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:16.70,0:34:19.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他储物柜里有我的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And he's got something in his locker that belongs to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:21.04,0:34:22.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不能乱开别人的储物柜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't go opening people's lockers.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:23.00,0:34:24.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你得和马尔科谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You'll have to work it out with Marko.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.93,0:34:26.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道你对马尔科了解多少\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know how well you know Marko,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:26.64,0:34:29.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但如果我能和他说清楚  也不用来这儿了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but if I could've worked it out, I wouldn't be asking.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:30.59,0:34:32.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托  它对我非常重要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please. It's really important.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.33,0:34:36.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不好意思  我无能无为\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry. I can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:39.41,0:34:40.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不能还是不想\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can't or won't?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:46.67,0:34:49.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会向你表达谢意的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'd really show my appreciation.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:53.07,0:34:54.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而且我会先表达我的谢意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I'd show it to you first.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:58.89,0:34:59.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:01.18,0:35:03.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这是你的办公室吗  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Is this your office? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:04.68,0:35:06.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,它能上锁吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Does it have a lock?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:35.56,0:35:37.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,时间紧迫  斯坦顿先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Time is of the essence, Mr. Stanton.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:38.38,0:35:40.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,随着问题提问次数的增加\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Intensity and duration of the electrical current
Dialogue: 0,0:35:40.74,0:35:44.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会加大电流强度和持续时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}will increase substantially each time I repeat a question.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:46.06,0:35:48.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  规矩我懂  西蒙斯探员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, I know the drill, Agent Simmons.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:48.72,0:35:51.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有什么打算  斯坦顿先生  还有谁参与\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What is your agenda, Mr. Stanton, and who else is involved?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.87,0:36:11.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有谁知道炸弹在哪儿  斯坦顿先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who else knew about the bomb, Mr. Stanton?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:12.65,0:36:14.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在跟谁合作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who have you been working with?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:17.25,0:36:19.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我对炸弹的事一无所知\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know anything about the bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.97,0:36:27.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在跟谁合作  斯坦顿先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who are you working with, Mr. Stanton?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:36.31,0:36:38.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托  阿尔梅达先生  告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please, Mr. Almeida, just tell me
Dialogue: 0,0:36:38.16,0:36:40.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我女儿凯特怎么样了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}what is going on with my daughter Kate.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:40.16,0:36:42.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我告诉过你  华纳先生  她没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I already told you, Mr Warner. She's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:42.01,0:36:44.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她和你们的探员在干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What is she doing with one of your agents?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:49.57,0:36:51.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雷扎·纳耶尔死了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Reza Naiyeer is dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:54.65,0:36:55.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天呐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, God.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:58.04,0:36:59.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们刚刚得知\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We just found out.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:59.82,0:37:02.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他和我们的两位探员在你办公室被枪击毙命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He and two of our agents were shot and killed at your office.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.34,0:37:16.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽怎么样了  她没事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about Marie? Is she OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:17.77,0:37:19.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请告诉我玛丽是安全的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please tell me Marie is OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.34,0:37:23.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听我说...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:24.74,0:37:26.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很抱歉的告诉你  华纳先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry to have to tell you this, Mr Warner,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:29.19,0:37:31.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我们觉得是玛丽干的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but we believe Marie committed the murders.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:41.50,0:37:45.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,小把戏  我知道这是小把戏  你们想耍我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a trick. I know it's a trick. You're trying to trick me.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:59.37,0:38:00.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了  他们出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK. Here they come.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:01.15,0:38:03.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所有人  注意了  他们出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All teams, be alert. They're coming out now.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:11.64,0:38:13.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你看到他了吗  -没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Can you see him yet? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:16.21,0:38:18.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-等等  -是他吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Wait a minute. - Is that him?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:21.06,0:38:23.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那三个人后面那个可能是他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It could be the one behind those three men.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:23.62,0:38:25.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,慢慢来  凯特  一定要确定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just take your time, Kate. Be sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.26,0:38:28.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我看不到他的脸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't see his face.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:42.13,0:38:44.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  不是他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, it's not him.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.55,0:38:54.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没看到他  我没看到他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't see him. I don't see him!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:54.07,0:38:56.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,继续观察  他应该在人群中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Keep looking. He's gotta be in the crowd.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:00.87,0:39:03.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那个是接待员  通常他是最后一个出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's the greeter. Normally he'd be the last one out.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:04.23,0:39:06.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,该死  后面出口有情况吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Damm it. Anything on the back exits?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:06.96,0:39:09.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没有  没人进出  -该死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Negative. No one's gone in or out. - Damm it!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:09.94,0:39:12.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  你如果看到他你会告诉我的  对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate, you would tell me if you saw him, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:13.10,0:39:15.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当然了  你这话是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course I would. What do you mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.65,0:39:19.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你为什么用这种眼神看着我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why are you looking at me like that,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.34,0:39:21.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把我当嫌犯一样  我没看到他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}as if I'm suspicious? I didn't see him!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:21.29,0:39:23.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别紧张\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just relax.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:23.88,0:39:25.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在清真寺的时候他肯定认出你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He must have made you when you were inside the mosque.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:25.47,0:39:26.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,跟我来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:26.76,0:39:28.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,贝克探员  他没有出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Agent Baker, he didn't come outside.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:28.74,0:39:30.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉手下  守好大楼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Give the word to go. Secure the building.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:30.58,0:39:33.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再次重申  告诉手下  守好大楼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I repeat, Give the word to go. Secure the building.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:33.11,0:39:34.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,打开大门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Open the gate.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:37.62,0:39:38.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,冲  冲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go! Go!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:40.19,0:39:41.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么回事  -联邦探员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What's going on? - Federal agent.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:41.81,0:39:43.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我有搜查令\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've got a warrant.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:50.45,0:39:52.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是这里的阿訇  有什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I am the imam here. What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:50.45,0:39:52.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}伊斯兰教生活的导师
Dialogue: 0,0:39:52.52,0:39:54.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,冷静  先生  冷静点  我们是联邦探员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Calm down, sir. Just clam down. We're federal agents.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:54.67,0:39:57.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,十五分钟前  我们收到确切消息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}fifteen minute ago, We received positive identification
Dialogue: 0,0:39:57.02,0:39:59.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,国际恐怖分子曾在你的清真寺\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}of an international terrorist here in your mosque.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:59.10,0:40:00.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们得找到他  而且要快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We need to find him. We need to find him now.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:00.99,0:40:03.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们有搜查令吗  我们有  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you have a search warrant? Yes, I do, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:05.48,0:40:08.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,靠后点  让她靠着墙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get back here. Keep her against the wall.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:09.13,0:40:11.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你能看到里面情况吗  -没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Can you see anything? - Clear.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:18.61,0:40:19.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Damm it!
Dialogue: 0,0:40:29.37,0:40:30.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拿条毯子盖住他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Put the blanket on him!
Dialogue: 0,0:40:45.24,0:40:46.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,从衣着上看应该是他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The clothes match the description.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:48.78,0:40:51.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,A小队和B小队按兵不动  我们找到阿里了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Teams A and B maintain positions. We've got Ali.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:53.22,0:40:55.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他死了  杰克  -该死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- He's dead, Jack. - Son of a bitch!
Dialogue: 0,0:40:57.66,0:40:59.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天呐  天呐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.08,0:41:04.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,洛杉矶反恐组  -我是杰克·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}CTU. - This is Jack Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:04.18,0:41:04.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让梅森接电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get Mason on the line.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:05.36,0:41:06.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿里自杀了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ali has killed himself.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:32.37,0:41:33.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我去找你一趟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna have to get back to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:39.05,0:41:40.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些衣服不是这个人的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}These clothes don't belong to this man.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:42.46,0:41:44.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看这些裤子  短了有三英寸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look at the pants. They're three inches too short.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:46.46,0:41:49.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,守住出口  守住出口\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Maintain secure exits. Maintain secure exits.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:49.20,0:41:50.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿里还在大楼之中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ali is still in the building.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:50.47,0:41:52.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,重复一遍  阿里还在大楼之中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Repeat, Ali is still in the building.

