[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,1,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.69,0:00:10.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(197.4,200.557)}{\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs25\b1\bord0\shad0\c&H78BDE7&\fad(0,808)}24小时\N\N{\fs15}第二季  第十七集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.11,0:00:13.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(189.6,121.6,193.8,105.6,0,356)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad3\3c&H2F2F2F&\4c&H336D99&}{\fs10}{\t(0,356,\fs20)\fn方正正中黑简体}前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.93,0:00:14.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听我说  我知道托尼在主管\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I know Tony's running things,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.00,0:00:16.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也不想多嘴  但是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and I don't want to speak out of turn, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.53,0:00:16.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs4\c&H449BA1&\pos(315,237.353)}米歇尔·德斯勒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.58,0:00:16.62,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(284.4,221.353)}米歇尔·德斯勒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.62,0:00:16.66,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(253.2,203.753)}米歇尔·德斯勒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.66,0:00:16.70,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(222,187.753)}米歇尔·德斯勒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.70,0:00:16.74,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(190.8,170.953)}米歇尔·德斯勒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.74,0:00:16.78,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(160.8,154.953)}米歇尔·德斯勒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.78,0:00:18.87,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(129,140.553)\fad(0,309)}米歇尔·德斯勒
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.78,0:00:18.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道还能跟谁讲了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know who else to talk to.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.31,0:00:19.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,关于什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}About what?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.42,0:00:21.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我认为总统正在谋划一场军事行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think the president's planning a major military action
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.80,0:00:24.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,缘由是他们在阿里家里发现的一段录音\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}based on a recording that was found at Ali's apartment.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.24,0:00:25.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿里说这是假的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ali claims it was a fake.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.86,0:00:26.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而你相信他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And you believe him.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.38,0:00:29.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  杰克·鲍尔找您\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, it's Jack Bauer for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.17,0:00:30.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(285,217.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.22,0:00:30.26,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(253.8,197.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.26,0:00:30.30,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(220.2,179.753)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.30,0:00:30.34,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(186.6,159.2)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.34,0:00:30.38,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(153.6,139.753)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.38,0:00:32.42,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(121.8,122.953)\fad(0,345)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.33,0:00:31.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  我很遗憾地告知您\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, I regret to inform you,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.21,0:00:33.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,赛伊德·阿里刚刚被暗杀了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Syed Ali has just been assassinated.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.10,0:00:34.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我认为这与\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think it has to do with
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.07,0:00:36.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在塞浦路斯录下的对话有关\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the conversation that was recorded in Cyprus.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.54,0:00:38.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我认为那段录音不可信\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't believe it's genuine.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.20,0:00:39.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  我知道他否认\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, I'm aware of his denials.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.91,0:00:41.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  我在担心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, I'm just worried that
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.82,0:00:43.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有人会试图操纵您\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}someone is trying to manipulate you
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.22,0:00:44.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去采取一些我能设想到的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}into taking the kind of military action
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.92,0:00:46.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,某些军事行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that I assume you're about to take.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.04,0:00:49.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我和你说过我有钱  我不是来偷东西的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I told you I had money. I didn't come here to steal.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.90,0:00:48.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(279,213.353)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.94,0:00:48.99,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(244.8,190.153)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.99,0:00:49.03,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(211.8,170.153)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.03,0:00:49.07,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(177,147.753)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.07,0:00:49.11,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(142.8,126.153)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.11,0:00:51.15,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(108.6,106.153)\fad(0,307)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.38,0:00:51.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不想伤害任何人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I didn't want to hurt anyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.23,0:00:56.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把枪给我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Give me the gun.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.64,0:01:00.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不  -你已经被我们包围了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- No. - We've got the store surrounded.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.38,0:01:04.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不  不  -放下枪  高举双手走出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Oh, no. No. - Put the gun down and come out with your hands up.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.48,0:01:06.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.96,0:01:06.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(64.2,218.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.01,0:01:06.05,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(96,202.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.05,0:01:06.09,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(128.4,186.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.09,0:01:06.13,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(160.2,170.153)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.13,0:01:06.17,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(194.4,152.553)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.17,0:01:06.21,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(226.8,135.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.21,0:01:08.25,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(259.2,120.553)\fad(0,306)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.34,0:01:08.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你可能还没搞清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The recording they found in Ali's apartment,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.08,0:01:10.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们在阿里公寓里找到的录音是伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}in case you haven't figured it out already, is bogus.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.50,0:01:12.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你怎么知道  -因为此事正是我捏造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How do you know that? - Because I'm the one who planted it.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.85,0:01:15.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你想怎样  -凯特·华纳\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What do you want? - Kate Warner.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.16,0:01:17.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有三十分钟的时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You got 30 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.09,0:01:19.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,带她去那间仓库  就你们两个人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bring her to the warehouse, just the two of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.89,0:01:22.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你到底要去哪里  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where the hell you think you're going, Jack?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.62,0:01:23.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没时间解释\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't have time to explain.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.15,0:01:26.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那就腾出时间  -把枪放下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Let's find the time. - Put the gun down.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:29.38,0:01:32.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  来  我们赶快走  快走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate, come on, we gotta go. Now. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.60,0:01:35.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.03,0:01:41.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs15\t(696,6577,\fs16)\c&H4BAAAD&\fad(1697,1183)\pos(187.2,191.79)}以下故事情节发生在午夜0点到凌晨1点之间
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.08,0:01:48.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.64,0:01:52.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等  杰克  告诉我到底怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wait, Jack. Tell me what's going on.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.54,0:01:56.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你信任我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you trust me?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.38,0:02:02.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-凯特  你信任我吗  -信任\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Kate, do you trust me? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.48,0:02:03.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我到车里再跟你解释\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I will explain everything to you in the car,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.90,0:02:05.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我们现在必须得走了  快来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but we've gotta go now. Come.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.03,0:02:14.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-凯莉  -托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Carrie! - Tony!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.35,0:02:17.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-发生了什么  -是杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What happened? - It was Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.96,0:02:20.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想阻止他带着凯特·华纳离开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I tried to stop him from taking Kate Warner out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.23,0:02:23.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么了  -我的脚踝\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What is it? - My ankle.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.39,0:02:24.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我去叫医生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll get the medic.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.00,0:02:27.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先通知警卫  让他们必须拦下杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Call security first. Make sure they stop Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.62,0:02:28.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.77,0:02:47.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,警卫处\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Security.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.51,0:02:51.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等  他就在门口\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hold on. He's at the gate.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.58,0:02:55.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-拦住那辆车  -停车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Stop that vehicle! - Hey! Stop!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.81,0:03:03.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你没事吧  -没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You OK? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.12,0:03:05.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  我刚刚不是有意要吓你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry, I didn't mean to frighten you back there.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.46,0:03:07.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会试着跟你解释这一切\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me try and explain everything to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.01,0:03:10.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,此刻  美国正准备就今晚的事件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right now the United States is preparing to retaliate
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.35,0:03:12.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对中东国家进行回击\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}against the Middle East for what happened tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.66,0:03:14.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,几个小时之后  我们就会全面卷入战争\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In the next few hours, we're gonna be involved in a full-scale war
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.93,0:03:17.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这场战争将影响世界上所有国家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}which'll affect every country on this planet.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.09,0:03:18.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这跟我有什么关系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What does that have to do with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.25,0:03:21.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,十分钟前有个人打电话给我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ten minutes ago a man called me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.69,0:03:23.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我他能证明\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Told me he had proof that the evidence that
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.24,0:03:26.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统做出决策所基于的证据是伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the president was using to base his decisions on was forged.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.68,0:03:27.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他不愿再告诉我别的信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He wouldn't give me any other information
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.92,0:03:29.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,除非我带你去见他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}unless I brought you to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.56,0:03:32.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这个人是谁  -我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Who is this man? - I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.94,0:03:34.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这就是问题所在  凯特  我不知道他是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's the problem, Kate. I don't know who he is.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.61,0:03:39.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他要我干什么  -这就要靠我们去查了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What would he want with me? - That's what we've gotta find out.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.95,0:03:42.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我能向总统提供确凿的证据证明\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If I can provide the president with concrete proof
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.19,0:03:45.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,塞浦路斯录音是假的  就能阻止一场战争\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that the Cyprus recording was fake, we can stop a war.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.81,0:03:47.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会竭尽全力保护你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I will do everything I can to protect you,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.34,0:03:48.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但你必须现在就做出决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but you have to make a decision now.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.29,0:03:51.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你需要决定你愿不愿意冒这个险\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You have to decide whether or not you want to accept the risk.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.64,0:03:56.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你真的觉得我们能做到吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you really think we can do this?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.64,0:04:01.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不想骗你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not gonna lie to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.59,0:04:04.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这件事非常  非常危险\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is very, very dangerous.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.77,0:04:08.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很抱歉  我不知道还能怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry, I don't know what else to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.09,0:04:10.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我快没时间了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm running out of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.81,0:04:20.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-拦住他了吗  -他直接开车冲出了大门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Did they stop him? - He drove right through the gate.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.29,0:04:23.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-哪里伤了  -脚踝\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What's the problem? - My ankle.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.07,0:04:25.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我来看看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's take a look.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.39,0:04:27.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你通知洛杉矶警方了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did you call LAPD?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.91,0:04:30.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,通知了  还通知了联调局  他们都在找他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. And the FBI. They're all looking for him.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.79,0:04:32.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可能是韧带拉伤  也可能是扭伤了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Could be a torn ligament, maybe a sprain.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.88,0:04:34.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,应该没有骨折\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't think it's broken.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.17,0:04:36.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你得去拍个片子  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- We've gotta get you an X-ray. - Great.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.49,0:04:38.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我去拿医疗箱  马上回来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll be right back with a first-aid kit.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.60,0:04:40.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你刚刚说杰克带走了凯特·华纳  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You said Jack took Kate Warner with him? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.86,0:04:44.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我觉得他不是单独行动  -什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I don't think he was working alone. - What do you mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.02,0:04:46.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,原本是贝克看着凯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Baker was keeping an eye on Kate.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.91,0:04:49.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但就在我找到你前几分钟  米歇尔支开了他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle distracted him just a few minutes before I found you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.39,0:04:52.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么支开的  -她让他去弄什么文书\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Distracted him how? - She called him away on some paperwork.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.67,0:04:54.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那杰克可能刚好利用了这个空窗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So Jack could just been using that as a window.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.61,0:04:55.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不意味着他们就是一伙的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Doesn't mean they were working together.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.17,0:04:57.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得就是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think it does.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.05,0:04:59.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔在去找贝克之前就在跟杰克谈话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle was talking to Jack right before she went to Baker.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.42,0:05:01.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他可能是故意嫁祸给她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He might have been setting her up.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.34,0:05:03.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看起来不是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It didn't appear that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.75,0:05:10.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,副总统在华盛顿等待与您通话  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The vice president's in Washington ready for your call, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.84,0:05:12.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他什么时候见英国大使\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When's his meeting with the British ambassador?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.80,0:05:14.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在跟您通完电话之后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right after he speaks with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.68,0:05:15.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.46,0:05:27.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,副总统肯定想让你授权他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The vice president is going to want you to authorise him
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.07,0:05:29.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,将我们的部署告诉大使\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to inform the ambassador of our deployment.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.92,0:05:34.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他告诉你的吗  -你也知道他的立场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- He told you that? - You have to know where Jim stands on this.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.20,0:05:36.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他巴不得让所有人都知道我们即将卷入战争\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's gonna want to let everyone know we're on a war footing.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.41,0:05:37.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尤其是英国人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Especially the British.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.52,0:05:40.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,您怎么想  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's your position, sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.71,0:05:44.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一旦我们告诉了盟友\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Once we bring our allies in on this,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.88,0:05:47.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要召回轰炸机就会困难许多\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it could make it much harder to recall those planes.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.53,0:05:52.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-接过来  -总统可以跟他通话了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Put him through. - The president is ready to speak with him now.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.72,0:05:54.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-马上  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Right away. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.09,0:05:59.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你好  吉姆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hello, Jim.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.00,0:06:03.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\fad(319,352)\pos(192,240.553)}华盛顿特区
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.16,0:06:02.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,英国方面对加州的核弹爆炸是什么反应\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's the British reaction to the California bombing?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.21,0:06:03.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所有人都很震惊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Everyone over there is stunned.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.71,0:06:05.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们已经命令军队进入高度警戒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They placed their military on high alert.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.92,0:06:08.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-英国大使呢  -他在等我们的消息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- The British ambassador? - He's waiting to hear from us.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.70,0:06:11.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就我的理解  我们谈完之后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I take it that after this conversation,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.20,0:06:14.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我就能告诉他隐身轰炸机的事情了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm free to inform him about the stealth bombers?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.05,0:06:17.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先别急  吉姆  时机还未成熟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not just yet, Jim. It's still premature.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.12,0:06:18.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  那些战机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, those planes are due to drop
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.63,0:06:20.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在四个多小时之后就要投下炸弹了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}their payloads in a little over four hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.20,0:06:23.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们需要暂缓通知盟友\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're holding off notifying our allies
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.14,0:06:24.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为我们有可能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}because there's a possibility
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.09,0:06:27.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不会执行这次袭击\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that we may not go through with the attack.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.52,0:06:29.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不明白\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.84,0:06:32.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我有理由相信  牵扯了三个目标国家的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have reason to believe that the Cyprus audio that implicated
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.61,0:06:35.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,塞浦路斯录音有可能是伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the target countries was fabricated.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.44,0:06:37.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们不是已经分析并证明它是真的了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I thought we analyzed it and proved it was real.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.49,0:06:38.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我原本也这么以为\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As did I.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.84,0:06:41.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但洛杉矶反恐组正在搜集\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But CTU Los Angeles is in the process of
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.20,0:06:43.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可能证明录音是伪造的证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}obtaining intelligence that may show otherwise.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.85,0:06:44.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,正在搜集\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In the process?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.61,0:06:48.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-就是说他们还没有任何证据  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Meaning they don't have any proof yet. - Correct.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.13,0:06:50.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你问过中情局了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did you run it by CIA?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.28,0:06:52.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有迹象表明这东西是伪造的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did they have any indication this thing's a fraud?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.53,0:06:54.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,暂时没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not as of yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.59,0:06:58.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  你授权了这次军事行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, you authorised this military action,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.10,0:07:00.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,理由充分\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and justifiably so.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.32,0:07:05.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,恕我直言  现在再犹豫太晚了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}With all due respect, it's too late for second thoughts.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.93,0:07:09.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们不能根据伪造或不完整的信息而开战\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We will not start a war on false or incomplete information.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.90,0:07:14.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么都不要和大使说  -是  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Say nothing to the ambassador. - Yes, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.02,0:07:23.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  我知道你心里信任杰克·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President... I know you trust Jack Bauer implicitly,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.91,0:07:28.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但因为一个人的保留意见我们就对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but to equivocate our response in a matter of this importance
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.87,0:07:33.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,重大事件的回应闪烁其词  这让我很不安\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}because of one man's reservations makes me very uncomfortable.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.12,0:07:37.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这件事我恐怕要同意麦克  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm afraid I'm with Mike on this one, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.40,0:07:40.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,知道了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Noted.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.31,0:07:51.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是雷恩斯副警长  加西亚先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is Deputy Raynes. Mr. Garcia,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.91,0:07:54.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里已经被我们包围了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we have officers surrounding the building.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.01,0:07:57.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你唯一的选择就是把武器扔出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your only option is to throw your weapon out
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.70,0:07:59.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把双手放在头顶走出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and come out with your hands on top of your head.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.10,0:08:04.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,坚持住  不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stay with me. No. No!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.60,0:08:08.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我止不住出血  我们得把他送去医院\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't stop the bleeding. We need to get him to a hospital.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.69,0:08:10.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,求求你别让他死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please don't let him die.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.46,0:08:11.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们需要你的回应\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We need you to respond.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.91,0:08:13.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你得和警察说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You need to talk to the police.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.98,0:08:15.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你必须告诉他们你要投降\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You have to tell them that you're gonna give up.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.43,0:08:17.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们必须马上让他们进来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We gotta let them in here right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.68,0:08:19.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  我不想出这种事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, I didn't mean for this to happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.96,0:08:22.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,炸弹爆炸了  战争要爆发了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A bomb went off. There's gonna be a war.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.62,0:08:25.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是想保护我老婆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was just trying to protect my wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.03,0:08:28.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-她怀孕了  -我能理解  我会和警察说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- She's pregnant. - I understand. I will tell the police that.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.76,0:08:32.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们必须出去  -加西亚先生  请回应\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- We gotta get out of here! - Mr. Garcia, please respond.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.71,0:08:36.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,里面有人需要医疗救助吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you have someone in there who needs medical attention?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.09,0:08:38.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这事有办法解决  -坚持住\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- We can work this out. - Stay with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.79,0:08:41.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但首先你必须放下武器走出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But first you have to put the weapon down and come out.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.42,0:08:47.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们出去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's walk out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.19,0:08:51.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  加西亚先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come out, Mr. Garcia.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.39,0:08:54.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拖延只会使事情更糟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're only making things worse by prolonging it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.95,0:08:56.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.76,0:08:59.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这事有办法解决  但你必须配合\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We can work this out, but you have to work with us.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.45,0:09:00.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,求求你别死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, please don't die.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.98,0:09:04.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-求求你别让他死  -请回应\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Please don't let him die. - Please respond.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.90,0:09:12.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在反恐组  他们为什么不帮你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why won't they help you, back at CTU?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.00,0:09:15.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼·阿尔梅达刚当上主管\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony Almeida's just been put in charge there.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.27,0:09:16.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他压力很大\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's under a lot of pressure.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.24,0:09:17.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他不认为录音是伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He doesn't think the tape is a forgery,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:17.67,0:09:19.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以在按规矩办事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so he's following the proper protocol.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.29,0:09:20.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他在做他认为正确的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's doing what he thinks is right.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.80,0:09:25.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要去哪儿见这个人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where are we supposed to meet this man?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.93,0:09:27.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,影视城的一个小仓库\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A small warehouse in Studio City.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.87,0:09:37.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么了  -我们被跟踪了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What is it? - We're being followed.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.02,0:09:40.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你认为是谁  -不知道  坐稳了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Who do you think it is? - I don't know. Hold on.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.74,0:10:01.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,熄火\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Turn the ignition off!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.11,0:10:02.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把双手放在方向盘上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Put your hands on the wheel!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.73,0:10:04.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把双手放在方向盘上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Put your hands on the wheel!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.47,0:10:08.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-就你一个人  -对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You alone? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.78,0:10:11.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么从反恐组跟踪我  优素福\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yusuf, why did you follow me from CTU?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.66,0:10:13.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,自从我来了  没人给我提供过任何信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Since I arrived no one's given me any information.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.87,0:10:16.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在反恐组告诉过你  我的国家被牵连了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I told you at CTU that my country is being implicated.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.38,0:10:17.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道能相信谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know who I can trust.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.79,0:10:21.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我见你撂倒了托尼·阿尔梅达  你的上司\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I saw you take out Tony Almeida, who's in charge there.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.00,0:10:22.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就是说不赞同他们在做的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Which means you're not on board with what they're doing.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.63,0:10:24.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不想让你的国家入侵我的国家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't want your country to invade mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:24.17,0:10:25.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的目的不是帮助你的国家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My agenda is not to help your country.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.83,0:10:28.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的职责是确保\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My responsibility is to make sure the President of
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.90,0:10:30.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,美国总统依据事实作出决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the United State makes his decisions based on fact.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.32,0:10:32.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的国家与这个炸弹无关\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My country's not responsible for this bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.14,0:10:36.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也许如此  但赛伊德·阿里是你国公民\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Maybe, but Syed Ali is a citizen of your country.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.82,0:10:38.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而且他是从国家运行恐怖主义网络\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And he runs his terrorist network from there.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.45,0:10:40.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对  所以他对你我两国的政府来说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, which means he's a criminal to my government
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.69,0:10:42.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都是罪犯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}just as much as yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.90,0:10:44.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的国家为什么要故意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why would my country deliberately
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.10,0:10:46.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,挑起一场最终会毁灭我们的战争\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}provoke an attack that would eventually decimate us?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.59,0:10:49.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,百害而无一利\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have everything to lose, nothing to gain.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.36,0:10:57.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想怎样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you want?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.10,0:11:00.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你逃出去时  就孤立了自己\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When you broke out, you isolated yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.77,0:11:02.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不管你在做什么  你都需要帮助\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Whatever you're doing, you'll need help.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.25,0:11:08.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.84,0:11:09.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,医生怎么说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What did the doctor say?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.95,0:11:13.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不知道  他们觉得我是韧带撕裂了之类的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know, they think I tore a ligament or something.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.79,0:11:18.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  凯莉告诉我  杰克把凯特·华纳\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look... Carrie told me that she saw you talking to Jack,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.47,0:11:20.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,从反恐组带走前  她看到你俩在说话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}right before he took Kate Warner out of CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.76,0:11:24.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对  有问题吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Is that a problem?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.37,0:11:25.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,得看你们是在说什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It depends what you were talking about.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.95,0:11:29.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们说了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What were you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.36,0:11:32.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是在审问我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you interrogating me?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.84,0:11:40.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你帮助杰克带走了凯特·华纳吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did you help Jack take Kate Warner out of here?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.45,0:11:42.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当然没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course not.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.15,0:11:46.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯莉是这么和你说的吗  我和杰克串通一气\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is that what Carrie told you? That I'm in collusion with Jack?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.39,0:11:49.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-是的  -我不知道怎么和你说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yeah. - I don't know what to tell you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.33,0:11:51.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她不知道自己在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She doesn't know what she's talking about.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.41,0:11:54.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, Michelle.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.08,0:11:58.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你觉得杰克是对是错都不重要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It doesn't matter whether you think Jack is right or wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.54,0:12:01.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,事实是  这里由我指挥\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The fact is, this is my command,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.11,0:12:03.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里发生的事是我的责任\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and what happens here is my responsibility.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.55,0:12:07.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我知道  -所以我需要你实话实说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I know that. - So I need you to be honest with me now.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.71,0:12:11.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是故意把贝克探员从凯特·华纳身边引开吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did you intentionally draw Agent Baker away from Kate Warner?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.00,0:12:18.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  我没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. I did not.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.46,0:12:20.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那凯莉为什么要这么说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So why would Carrie tell me you did?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.48,0:12:23.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为她想看我走人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because she'd like to see me out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.64,0:12:24.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And why's that?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.97,0:12:27.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为我不喜欢她  而她也知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because I don't like her, and she knows it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.69,0:12:33.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你想说说吗  -不怎么想\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You wanna tell me about it? - No, not really.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.95,0:12:37.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果这影响了你的工作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you got a problem that's interfering with your work...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.04,0:12:38.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有影响我的工作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's not interfering with my work.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.77,0:12:41.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's not.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.62,0:12:45.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK. Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.67,0:13:13.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,加西亚先生  我们用电话联系你  请接听\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Garcia, we are contacting you by phone. Please answer.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.85,0:13:18.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我做了什么啊  我要烂死在监狱里了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What have I done?! I'm going to prison for the rest of my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.92,0:13:22.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不一定的  -我杀了人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You don't know that. - I killed a man!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.57,0:13:24.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是个意外  我看到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was an accident. I saw it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.74,0:13:27.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你现在自首  他们会考虑这一点的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you turn yourself in now, they'll consider that.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.32,0:13:29.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,否则  只会变得更糟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you don't, it'll only get worse.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.45,0:13:30.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得离开这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've got to get out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.42,0:13:37.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不许碰电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey! Don't touch that phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.73,0:13:47.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-喂  -加西亚先生  我是雷恩斯副警长\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yeah. - Mr. Garcia, this is Deputy Raynes.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.50,0:13:50.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  不管问题是什么  我们都能解决\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, whatever the problem is, we can work this out.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.74,0:13:53.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-有谁和你在一起吗  -顾客  一个女孩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Now, who's in there with you? - A customer. A girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.96,0:13:55.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  她受伤了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, is she hurt?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.48,0:13:58.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有  是店主\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. It's the owner.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.70,0:14:00.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  我们得把他弄出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, we have to get him out of there.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.75,0:14:05.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,太迟了  我不是故意的  那是个意外\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's too late. Look, I didn't mean it. It was an accident.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.24,0:14:08.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没关系  让我们谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, that's OK. Let's talk about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.17,0:14:11.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都是因为那个炸弹  听着  要开战了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's because of the bomb. Look, there's gonna be a war.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.68,0:14:13.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我试图带我老婆出城\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm trying to get my wife out of this city.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.70,0:14:15.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能理解  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You understand that, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.75,0:14:17.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的妻子就在这里  加西亚先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your wife is right here, Mr. Garcia.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.71,0:14:18.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她很担心你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's worried about you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.99,0:14:20.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  把电话给她  我要和她讲话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. Put her on the phone. I wanna talk to her.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.60,0:14:27.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雷蒙  你没事吧  你为什么还在里面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ramon, are you OK? Why are you still in there?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.27,0:14:35.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-亲爱的  我杀了人  -不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Mija... I killed a man. - No!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.71,0:14:38.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是个意外  但他们不会相信我的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was an accident, but they won't believe me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.64,0:14:41.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你和孩子必须马上离开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You and the baby have to leave now.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.40,0:14:44.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在城里不安全\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's not safe to be in the city.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.31,0:14:49.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雷蒙  亲爱的  出来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ramon, mijo, come out.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:49.78,0:14:50.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不行  还不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, not yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.56,0:14:52.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要让警察\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, look, I'm gonna tell
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.35,0:14:54.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把你带去安全的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the police to take you where you'll be safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.22,0:15:00.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我爱你  -我也爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I love you. - I love you, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.30,0:15:08.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  加西亚先生  你跟你妻子谈过了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, Mr. Garcia, you talked to your wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.57,0:15:09.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你可以出来了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'd like you to come out.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.12,0:15:12.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可以  但是我要你先为我做一件事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, but I want you to do one thing for me first.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.93,0:15:13.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's that?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.89,0:15:18.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,送她去蒙特利  她有个姐姐在那里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Take her to Monterey. She's got a sister there.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.57,0:15:21.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她到那里后  我就放了这姑娘\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When she gets there, I'll let the girl go,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.47,0:15:23.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那时候我就出去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and then I'll come out.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.35,0:15:52.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要我怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you want me to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.73,0:15:55.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要你待在这  我要进去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you to stay here. I'm going in.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.86,0:15:56.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你要联系我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you need to get in touch with me,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.88,0:15:58.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,中控那里有手机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}there's a cellphone in the centre console.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.68,0:16:00.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,按1号键就行  快速拨号设好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Press one. It's on speed dial.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.67,0:16:03.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate, you OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.40,0:16:08.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,记住  我会竭尽全力保护你  知道吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't forget, I will do everything I have to to protect you, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.08,0:16:12.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好的  -留在这里别动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yeah. - Just stay put.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.26,0:17:16.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,放下武器  放下武器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Drop the weapon. Put the weapon down!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.64,0:17:18.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.71,0:17:26.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的武器在桌子上  我现在没有武器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My weapons are there on that table. I'm unarmed.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.67,0:17:27.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,双手放在脑后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Put your hands behind your head,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.80,0:17:29.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,十指交叉  你知道程序\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}interlock your fingers. You know the drill.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.33,0:17:38.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果是邓禄普的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If that's a Dunlop,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.87,0:17:42.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那就可以测到我胸腔内的一片弹片\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it'll pick up a piece of shrapnel that's still in my rib cage.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.88,0:17:44.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对了  看到没\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yep, see?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.70,0:17:53.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,坐下来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Take a seat.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.97,0:17:57.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.92,0:18:02.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,第七轻型装甲侦察营的乔纳森·华莱士中尉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jonathan Wallace, Captain, 7th Light Armoured Reconnaissance Battalion,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.23,0:18:03.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,海军第三分局\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Third Marine Division,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.28,0:18:05.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,本宁堡军事基地的特种部队\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Special Ops Detachment Delta, Fort Benning.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.73,0:18:10.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,慢慢地抬起右手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Slowly... raise your right arm.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.27,0:18:13.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给我看你的手前臂内侧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Show the inside of your forearm to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:23.46,0:18:25.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-珊瑚蛇小组  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Coral Snake Unit. - That's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.32,0:18:28.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以你是第七个队员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So you're the seventh man.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.46,0:18:31.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你撤了你们小组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You took out your unit that was
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.79,0:18:33.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不去追踪炸弹  他们就阻止不了爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}tracking the bomb so they couldn't stop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.64,0:18:34.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.45,0:18:37.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我负责两件事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was responsible for two things:
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.36,0:18:39.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一  确保炸弹爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}making sure the bomb went off,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.66,0:18:42.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,二  伪造录音  栽赃三国\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}planting the recording to blame the bomb on the three countries.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.58,0:18:43.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,目的呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}To what end?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.74,0:18:46.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有什么  杰克  发动战争\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What else, Jack? To start a war.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.73,0:18:49.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最终目的一直都是引发美国袭击中东\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The end game was always to get the US to attack the Middle East.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.05,0:18:50.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.53,0:18:54.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们没说  但是也不用说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They didn't tell me, but they didn't have to.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.52,0:18:56.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些人控制着里海的石油\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}These men control the oil in the Caspian Sea.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.68,0:18:58.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果发生战争\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If there's a war,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.39,0:19:00.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们的财富可以翻四番至少达十年\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}their holdings quadruple in value for at least a decade.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.91,0:19:04.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,代价是在洛杉矶市中心引爆核弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}At the cost of detonating a nuclear device in the centre of LA?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.19,0:19:05.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你说对了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.23,0:19:08.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要凯特·华纳做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you want with Kate Warner?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.08,0:19:11.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大概一小时前\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}About an hour ago,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.80,0:19:14.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我老板想要我死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the people who hired me tried to have me killed.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.85,0:19:16.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,显然他们失败了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Obviously, they didn't succeed,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.92,0:19:18.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是他们断了我的交通渠道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but they took out my transport team.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.76,0:19:22.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要另想个办法离开这个国家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need an alternate way out of the country.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.84,0:19:25.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,华纳公司有国防部的关系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Warner Industries has DOD variance.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.00,0:19:26.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她可以授权我离开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She can authorise a departure.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.67,0:19:28.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要用证明塞浦路斯录音是假的的证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, evidence against the Cyprus
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.93,0:19:31.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来换逃跑的机会  是这样吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}recording for your departure. That's the deal?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.51,0:19:34.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yep.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.29,0:20:04.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别出声  下车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Keep your mouth shut and get out of the car.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.49,0:20:08.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,打开门  现在打开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Unlock the door. Do it now!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.96,0:20:11.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,过来  下车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, get out of the car!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.93,0:20:21.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.56,0:20:30.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-华纳家的女孩呢  -等我们完事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- So where's the Warner girl? - When we're done.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.07,0:20:32.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我那个证据怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Talk more about the evidence.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.03,0:20:34.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么证明录音是伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How does the evidence prove the recording was forged?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.34,0:20:36.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我有源录音\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have the source recordings.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.39,0:20:38.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是伪造假录音剪辑之前的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Before they were mixed down to create the fake tape.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.68,0:20:43.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是我  -杰克  还有一个人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. - Jack, there was another guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.81,0:20:44.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我打昏他了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I took care of him.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.72,0:20:45.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他在那边吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is he there?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.48,0:20:50.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,找你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.63,0:20:59.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谁啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.47,0:21:01.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你派来抓凯特·华纳的人昏迷了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The man you sent to pick up Kate Warner is unconscious.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.90,0:21:02.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他昏过去了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He'll be out for a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.60,0:21:04.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你说谎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're lying.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.91,0:21:06.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他六英尺二  深色头发\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's six-two, dark hair,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.96,0:21:08.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,脸上有明显的疤\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}pretty nasty scar on his face.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.46,0:21:14.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  这改变不了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK. It doesn't change anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.68,0:21:16.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还拿着你要的证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got what you need
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.85,0:21:19.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你不给我凯特·华纳  我是不会给你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and I won'tgive it to you until you give me Kate Warner.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.48,0:21:20.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可以  我带你去找她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fine, I'll take you to her.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.86,0:21:22.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们会安排你走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll arrange your charter.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.03,0:21:23.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  不  不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, no, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:24.23,0:21:25.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她不能授权一架临时飞机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She can't authorise a non-scheduled charter
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.94,0:21:27.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,除非有公司合伙人在机上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}unless one of the partners of the company is on board,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.63,0:21:30.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在你的人又抓了鲍勃·华纳\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and right now your people have Bob Warner in custody.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.86,0:21:32.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以她要跟我走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So she's coming with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.23,0:21:36.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你到了目的地后打算怎么处理她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you plan to do with her when you reach your destination?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.89,0:21:38.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只能干掉她  你知道的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have to dispose of her. You know that.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.13,0:21:42.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我决不允许\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't let that happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.35,0:21:45.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我们没得谈了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're done here.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.10,0:22:02.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.94,0:22:13.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,优素福  你能听到吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yusuf, do you copy?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.21,0:22:15.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们在呢  杰克  你要我怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're here, Jack. What do you want me to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.68,0:22:17.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,带她进来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bring her in.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.13,0:22:45.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\fad(399,389)\pos(196.2,222.153)}洛杉矶\N地区总部
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.33,0:22:51.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,林恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lynne.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.87,0:22:57.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-麦克  -我怎么才能找到杰克·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yeah, Mike? - How do I get ahold of Jack Bauer?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.52,0:23:01.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我之前听说他在反恐组汇报  怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Last I heard, he was debriefing at CTU. Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.40,0:23:03.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统只因为跟鲍尔通过电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The president's hesitating with this operation,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.97,0:23:06.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就开始对这次行动犹豫不决\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}based solely on a conversation he had with Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:06.29,0:23:08.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想亲自跟他谈一谈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wanna to talk to him myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.34,0:23:10.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,背着总统去吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Behind the president's back?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.06,0:23:15.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,麦克  那非常危险\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mike, that is so dangerous.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.98,0:23:18.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我能得到一些具体的信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If I can get some concrete information,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.88,0:23:21.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我就能更有效地支持总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can support the president more effectively.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:21.19,0:23:22.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要是得不到呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And if you can't?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.83,0:23:24.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我就有信心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then I'll have the conviction
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.08,0:23:25.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可以说服他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to talk him through the situation.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.69,0:23:27.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在我在暗处\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right now, I'm in the dark.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.89,0:23:32.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我没把握  -林恩  这是我的决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'm not sure. - Lynne... Lynne, this is my call.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.41,0:23:36.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很认同你建议不要围着总统转\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your recommendation not to go around the president is duly noted.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.01,0:23:51.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.89,0:24:00.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿尔梅达先生  麦克·诺维克的电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Almeida, Mike Novick,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:00.87,0:24:03.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他是总统的幕僚长\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the president's chief of staff, is on the line.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.41,0:24:09.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,诺维克先生  我是托尼·阿尔梅达\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Novick, this is Tony Almeida.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.33,0:24:12.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼你好  我需要找到杰克·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hi, Tony. I need to reach Jack Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.07,0:24:15.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,长官  我们也正在找他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, well, we're trying to locate him ourselves, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.64,0:24:18.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么意思  发生什么事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you mean? What's the problem?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:19.08,0:24:21.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克早先来过这  汇报当天的事务\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack was here earlier, debriefing from the day's events,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.39,0:24:23.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他找到了一个重要证人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}when he grabbed a material witness
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.76,0:24:25.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,并非法带她离开了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and took her off the premises illegally.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.53,0:24:28.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他还攻击了反恐组的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He also assaulted CTU personnel.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.54,0:24:30.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他为什么这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why would he do that?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.52,0:24:31.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克的直觉认为\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack's working on a hunch
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.61,0:24:33.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,塞浦路斯的录音是伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that the Cyprus recording was fabricated.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.03,0:24:36.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也想和他谈谈此事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is what I wanted to talk to him about.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.02,0:24:39.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,除非鲍尔那边有消息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The president is not giving his complete support
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.76,0:24:42.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,否则总统对军事行动不会给予完全支持的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to the military action until he hears from Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.54,0:24:45.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我懂了  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I understand, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.65,0:24:48.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他带走的那个人是什么情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, what about the witness he's taken?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.58,0:24:51.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-她怎么会牵涉其中  -她叫凯特·华纳\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How does that factor in? - Her name is Kate Warner.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.49,0:24:54.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她妹妹玛丽和"第二波"的恐怖分子有联系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Her sister Marie was involved with the Second Wave terrorists.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.51,0:24:55.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们还在试图理清脉络\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're trying to connect the dots.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.72,0:24:58.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这也是我们要找到杰克的原因之一\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's the other reason we need to find Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.08,0:25:01.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一旦你联系到了鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The second you make contact with Bauer,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.11,0:25:04.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你让他和我讲  我们在分区\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you put him through to me. We're at District.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.41,0:25:05.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:15.46,0:25:16.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-特纳  -凯莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Turner. - Carrie.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.06,0:25:19.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么事  -你过来一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What's up? - Yeah, I need to see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.00,0:25:20.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.46,0:25:40.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么事  托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, Tony?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.15,0:25:43.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们在哪些地方设置了监视点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where are we guarding on Jack?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.20,0:25:45.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,卫星没有监控到他的去向\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}His exit wasn't picked up on satellite.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.91,0:25:48.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而且目前为止他还没联系过别人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And he hasn't initiated contact with anyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.36,0:25:50.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特·华纳那边怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about Kate Warner?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.98,0:25:53.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她家和她父亲的公司都有人在监视\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Her house and her father's company are being watched,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.22,0:25:54.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,以防他们过去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}in case they go there.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.45,0:25:56.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.74,0:26:01.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你找米歇尔谈过了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Have you talked to Michelle?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.91,0:26:03.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谈过了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.09,0:26:08.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,事实上  我想就此事和你聊聊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In fact, I wanted to talk to you about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.44,0:26:11.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,和米歇尔一起工作你有什么意见吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you have a problem working in the same office with Michelle?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.31,0:26:16.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你这么想吗  觉得我是因为和她工作不和\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is that what you think? That I'd be making up stories
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.33,0:26:18.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,才编造这些瞎话的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}because I have a problem working with her?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.00,0:26:23.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她在杰克带走凯特·华纳前和他交谈过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She and Jack were talking before he took Kate Warner.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.17,0:26:25.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们可不是在交换食谱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They weren't trading recipes.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.71,0:26:28.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是场阴谋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was conspiratorial.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.52,0:26:37.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.15,0:26:46.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  我需要你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I need you to put a filter
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.45,0:26:48.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对米歇尔所有通讯活动进行监视筛选\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}on all of Michelle's communications.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.13,0:26:50.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,电子邮件  通话记录  开放通道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}E-mails, phone calls, open channels.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.32,0:26:53.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果杰克联系她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you to let me know
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.04,0:26:55.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,务必让我知道  行吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}when Jack tries to contact her, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.55,0:26:57.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Done.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.93,0:27:23.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,外面现在什么情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's going on out there?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.77,0:27:25.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们要把我妻子送到安全的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're taking my wife where she'll be safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:26.30,0:27:27.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And then what?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.86,0:27:37.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你会放我走的  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're gonna let me go, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.45,0:27:40.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别逼我  是你让我落得如此下场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't push me. You got me into this.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.21,0:27:44.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这不是我造成的  -你用这把枪指着我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I didn't get you into this. - You pointed this gun at me.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.23,0:27:47.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是整件事情的导火索\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's how this whole thing started.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.75,0:27:50.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,话说你带着枪要干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What were you doing with a gun anyway?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.05,0:27:57.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说啊  你准备抢劫这里吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What?! Were you gonna rip this place off?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.24,0:27:57.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.57,0:28:03.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你毁了我的生活  都怪你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You ruined my life. It's all your fault.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.94,0:28:06.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  我不应该拿出这把枪的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry, I shouldn't never have taken out that gun.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:06.13,0:28:08.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是吗  你之前为何要拿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah? Well, why did you?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.54,0:28:10.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很害怕\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was afraid.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.89,0:28:14.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,害怕  有什么让你害怕的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14} Afraid. What do you have to be afraid of?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.57,0:28:17.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,回答我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Answer me!
Dialogue: 0,0:28:20.54,0:28:22.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我爸今晚过世了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My daddy died tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.44,0:28:24.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,炸弹爆炸时  他就在那里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The bomb that went off, he was there.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.27,0:28:48.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:48.20,0:28:50.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,加西亚先生  你妻子在去蒙特利的路上了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alright, Mr. Garcia. Your wife's on her way to Monterey.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:50.72,0:28:52.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,里面没事发生吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Everything cool in there?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:52.12,0:28:54.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  有事  你只要确保我妻子平安到达\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, it's not cool. You just make sure my wife gets there.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.87,0:28:57.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没必要隔五分钟就打电话来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't need to call every five minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.15,0:28:59.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  雷蒙  你冷静点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, Ramon, you need to stay calm.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:59.50,0:29:01.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们会完全按照你的要求来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, we're doing exactly what you said.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:01.62,0:29:03.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是你要想清楚了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But you got to think this through.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:03.30,0:29:05.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不久后你会被羁押起来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You'll be in custody soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.19,0:29:08.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我没想要蓄意杀人  -我们知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I didn't mean to kill anybody! - We know.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.70,0:29:10.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但如果你把那位年轻小姐放出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But what would help your case
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.14,0:29:13.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对你的案子会大有裨益\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is if you'd let the young lady out now.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:13.55,0:29:14.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别当我是傻子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not stupid!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.05,0:29:17.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,正是因为她你们才不敢向这里开枪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's the only reason you haven't shot your way in here yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.71,0:29:19.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还就告诉你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I'll tell you something.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.16,0:29:21.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,若我看到你们进来  我会杀了她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If I see you coming in, I'll kill her!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:21.85,0:29:23.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你最好把这话当真\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You better believe that!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:24.17,0:29:26.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不是杀人犯  雷蒙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're not a killer, Ramon.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.41,0:29:29.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你没有案底  别冲动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You've got no record. Be smart.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.30,0:29:31.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我别冲动  你们才别冲动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll be smart. You be smart.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:31.87,0:29:32.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Damn it!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:36.15,0:29:37.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给我回来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get back here!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.82,0:29:40.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  不要  开门啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No! No! Open the door!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:41.41,0:29:44.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,开门  开门啊  快开门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Open it! Open the door! Open it!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:44.51,0:29:47.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,救命  快救救我  我在后门  快救救我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Help me! Hurry, I'm at the back door! Help! Please!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:48.48,0:29:50.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不想伤害你  你别逼我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't wanna hurt you, but I will!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:52.02,0:29:53.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,加西亚先生  里面什么情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Garcia, what's going on in there?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.00,0:29:58.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天呐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.10,0:30:01.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-加西亚先生  快接电话  -不要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Mr. Garcia, pick up the phone. - No!
Dialogue: 0,0:30:01.23,0:30:01.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:30:05.90,0:30:08.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快接电话  加西亚先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please respond, Mr. Garcia.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:15.09,0:30:16.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,除了你还有别人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is there anyone else besides you?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:21.50,0:30:22.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  看看那边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate, look the other way.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.47,0:30:26.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没  没有  没有别人  没别人了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, no. No one else. There's no one else.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.45,0:30:33.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-走吧  -等等  仓库在那边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Come on. - Wait, the warehouse is that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.16,0:30:34.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-杰克  -说吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Jack. - Yeah, go ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:35.09,0:30:37.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我用迂回的方式进来  要花上几分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna approach in a sweep pattern. It'll take a few minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:38.38,0:30:39.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,收到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Copy that.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.84,0:30:44.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们还得五分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're gonna be five minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:44.81,0:30:46.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我们只能干等着了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And here we are without a deck of cards.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:50.52,0:30:51.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,知道吗  塞缪尔斯有意招募你时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, I was down at Benning
Dialogue: 0,0:30:51.55,0:30:53.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还在本宁堡军事基地\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}when Samuels tried to recruit you.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:54.96,0:30:55.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.90,0:30:58.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你拒绝了他让他真的很难过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He was real disappointed you turned him down.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:02.76,0:31:04.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他说你是天生的杀手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He said you were a born killer.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:08.10,0:31:08.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is that true?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:41.88,0:31:43.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8f\fs15\b1\bord0\shad0\fn方正黑体简体\pos(112.8,50.4)}错误信息
Dialogue: 0,0:31:42.04,0:31:43.17,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord0\shad0\b1\fs15\pos(114.6,118.4)}系统故障
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.31,0:31:56.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8f\fs15\b1\bord0\shad0\fn方正黑体简体\pos(191.4,74.4)\frz0\fad(0,57)}错误信息\N\N\N系统故障
Dialogue: 0,0:31:57.35,0:31:58.43,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an8f\fs15\b1\bord0\shad0\fn方正黑体简体\frz0\fad(25,96)\pos(191.4,68.8)}错误信息\N\N\N系统故障
Dialogue: 0,0:31:58.85,0:31:59.27,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an8f\fs15\b1\bord0\shad0\fn方正黑体简体\frz0\fad(68,0)\pos(195.6,75.2)}错误信息\N\N\N系统故障
Dialogue: 0,0:32:11.09,0:32:13.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-特纳  -我收到备份服务器一个提示信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Turner. - I just got an alarm conditional on the backup server.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:13.84,0:32:14.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有遇到吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you have one?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:14.73,0:32:17.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  我没有  应该是你那边路由器的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, i don't. Must be on your side of the router.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:17.93,0:32:20.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,需要我接个信号过去测试一下连接情况吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Want me to patch a band and check out the connections?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:20.07,0:32:23.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不用  你需要权限  还是我来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, you need C-clearance for that. I'll have to do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:23.59,0:32:24.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  我忘了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right, I forgot.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:49.57,0:32:51.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-能帮我把这个给汤普金斯吗  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Will you give this to Thomkins for me? - Sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.58,0:33:03.08,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an8\fs13\bord0\shad0\b1\c&H000000&\frz0.02539\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\move(255.6,90.4,227.4,82.4,0,1192)}系统级别
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.58,0:33:03.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fs12\bord0\shad0\b1\frz358.7\c&H000000&\move(321.6,150.4,293.4,142.4,0,1109)\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK}用户账号\N\N互联网\N\N局域网\N\NA服务器访问\N\NC服务器访问
Dialogue: 0,0:33:07.29,0:33:09.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fs13\bord0\shad0\b1\c&H000000&\frz0.02539\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\move(252,99.2,288,7.2,30,1781)}应用级别
Dialogue: 0,0:33:07.29,0:33:09.09,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an4\fs11\bord0\shad0\b1\frz358.7\c&H000000&\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\move(299.4,162.4,333.6,70.4,30,1781)}ASCI文本\N\N数据库请求\N\N电子邮件\N\N电子邮件附件\N\N网络电话\N\N编码表
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.34,0:33:12.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fs13\bord0\shad0\b1\c&H000000&\frz0.02539\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\move(247.8,33.6,249.6,19.2,25,1610)}硬件级别
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.34,0:33:12.97,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an4\fs11\bord0\shad0\b1\c&H000000&\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\frz357.5\move(304.8,85.6,307.8,71.2,22,1610)}内部总线\N\N声音管理\N\N视频显示器\N\N键盘
Dialogue: 0,0:33:22.24,0:33:22.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:24.84,0:33:27.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-总统先生  打扰下  -什么事  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Mr. President, may I? - What is it, Mike?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:30.70,0:33:32.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克·鲍尔从反恐组带走重要证人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack Bauer took a material witness
Dialogue: 0,0:33:32.62,0:33:36.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,与此同时还打伤一名探员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}from CTU and assaulted an agent in the process.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:36.98,0:33:39.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道他为国做了很大贡献  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know how much this country owes him, sir,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.83,0:33:43.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但他感情上明显受到严重创伤\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but he's obviously suffered some kind of emotional collapse.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:43.44,0:33:46.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鉴于所发生的一切  这也合情合理\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It would be understandable, given everything he's been through.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:47.62,0:33:48.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我们也说不准\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But we don't know that.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:50.24,0:33:53.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当时的情况可能让他别无选择\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What he did might have been necessary under the circumstances.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.68,0:33:58.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们已经有中情局的铁证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We already have incontrovertible proof from Langley
Dialogue: 0,0:33:58.46,0:34:00.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,塞浦路斯的录音是可信的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that the Cyprus recording is authentic.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:00.95,0:34:03.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就算找到杰克·鲍尔也改变不了这点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Finding Jack Bauer isn't going to change that.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:03.69,0:34:05.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,国家需要你把精力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The country needs your energy and
Dialogue: 0,0:34:05.62,0:34:09.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,放在爆炸之后的事情上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}attention on what happens after those bombs are dropped.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:09.41,0:34:11.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要为接下来的战斗做准备\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We need to prepare for this war.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:12.27,0:34:14.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果这份录音是伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If this recording's not authentic,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:15.92,0:34:18.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果杰克·鲍尔是对的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and Jack Bauer turns out to be right,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:19.56,0:34:21.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那这将是一个历史性的错误\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it'd be a mistake of historic proportions.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:21.93,0:34:23.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-总统先生  -我想说的就是这些  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Mr. President... - That's all, Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:26.80,0:34:28.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,找到杰克·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Find Jack Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:42.25,0:34:45.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她随时都会到  证据在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She'll be here any minute. Where's the evidence?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.85,0:34:47.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,接下来的计划是这样的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, here's how it's gonna go down.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:48.68,0:34:51.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我带凯特一起走  她安排飞机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I take Kate with me. She sets up the plane.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:51.56,0:34:53.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我来选择离开的机场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It picks us up at an airport of my choosing.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:53.95,0:34:55.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等我上了飞机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When I'm on that plane,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.44,0:34:57.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会打电话告诉你证据在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll call and tell you where the evidence is.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:57.57,0:34:59.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么保证你会给我打电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What assurances do I have you'll even call?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:00.41,0:35:01.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}None.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:02.39,0:35:02.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这就是那种\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's one of those things
Dialogue: 0,0:35:02.89,0:35:04.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你只能相信我的话的时刻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}where you're just gonna have to trust me.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:05.12,0:35:06.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不相信你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, I don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:09.38,0:35:11.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  这世上我最不想\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, you're the last person in the world
Dialogue: 0,0:35:11.88,0:35:13.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让你跟踪我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want tracking me down.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:25.09,0:35:27.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, what's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:27.81,0:35:29.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们俩要一起走一趟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You and I are going on a little trip.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:31.04,0:35:31.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:37.03,0:35:38.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要跟他走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You have to go with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.28,0:35:41.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那你呢  -杰克不跟我们一起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What about you? - Jack's not coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:49.93,0:35:51.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你答应过我的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You gave me your word.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:52.68,0:35:54.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  我必须要怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry it has to be done like this.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:58.39,0:35:59.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,放开我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let go of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.46,0:36:00.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,跟她谈谈  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Talk to her, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:00.25,0:36:02.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不然我就要来硬的了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Otherwise, i'm gonna have to do this differently.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:04.24,0:36:06.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  记住我在车里对你说的每一句话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate, remember everything I said to you in the car.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.15,0:36:11.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,照他说的做  我向你保证  你不会有事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do what he says, and I promise you, you will not get hurt.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:15.42,0:36:17.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是不是想放弃我了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're giving me up, aren't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.90,0:36:47.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我是反恐组的德斯勒  -是我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- CTU, Dessler. - Hey. Hey, it's me.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:48.13,0:36:49.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,丹尼  你怎么打电话来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Danny, what are you doing up?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:49.79,0:36:52.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我睡不着  你确定这里安全吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't sleep. Are you sure it's safe here?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:52.97,0:36:54.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  我认为很安全\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. As far as I know, it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:54.81,0:36:55.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你认为\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As far as you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:55.93,0:36:58.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么叫"我认为"\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What the hell does that mean? "As far as I know"?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:59.44,0:37:01.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,丹尼  你知道我的工作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Danny, you know my situation.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.08,0:37:03.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的工作糟透了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what, your situation sucks.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:03.86,0:37:05.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在说的可是我的生命安全\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're talking about my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:05.32,0:37:08.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,至少告诉我你知道的信息吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The least you could do is tell me what you know.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:08.26,0:37:09.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没什么好告诉你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's nothing to know.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:09.39,0:37:10.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在那里好好待着  睡一觉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stay where you are. Get some sleep.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.88,0:37:11.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我明天就过去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll come over tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:11.51,0:37:13.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别哄我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't you patronise me!
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.72,0:37:15.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别哄我  我只想要答案\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't you patronise me, cos I want answers.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:15.66,0:37:17.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一颗核弹爆炸了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A nuclear bomb just went off.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:17.67,0:37:20.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想知道继续留在洛杉矶是不是安全\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wanna know if it's safe to stay here in LA.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:21.23,0:37:23.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,孩子们怎么样  你难道不关心他们吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about the kids? Don't you care about them?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:23.67,0:37:26.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我当然关心  如果有什么需要你知道的消息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course. If there was anything to know,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:26.15,0:37:26.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会告诉你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'd tell you.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:26.86,0:37:28.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是吗  炸弹的事情你就没告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is that right? You didn't tell me about the bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:26.86,0:37:28.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:28.81,0:37:30.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是忘了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did it slip your mind?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:30.66,0:37:31.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我已经向你解释过了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I already explained it to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.58,0:37:33.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不能告诉任何人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wasn't allowed to tell anyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:35.16,0:37:38.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要不我给凯莉打电话吧  她会告诉我的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what? Maybe I should call Carrie. She'd tell me.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:39.07,0:37:40.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还以为你们俩不联系了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I thought you two weren't speaking.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:40.84,0:37:42.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们是不联系了  她就是个贱人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're not. She's a bitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:42.53,0:37:44.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-丹尼  我会照顾好  -算了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Danny, I will take care... - Forget it.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:00.00,0:38:03.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(144.6,55.2,145.2,70.4,0,1071)}{\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs11\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H000000&}录音记录
Dialogue: 0,0:38:03.13,0:38:05.47,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(189,63.2,130.8,40,819,2237)}{\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs11\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H000000&}录音记录
Dialogue: 0,0:38:04.13,0:38:05.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(280.2,125.6,237.6,112.8)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs12\b1\bord0\shad0\fax0.1\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H000000&}是否从主数据库中删除该条目  删除
Dialogue: 0,0:38:20.45,0:38:21.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别射我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't shoot me!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:23.10,0:38:27.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,求你们了  我很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please! I'm sorry!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.99,0:38:30.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把武器从前门扔出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Throw the weapon out the front door,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:30.75,0:38:33.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,双手放在头后走出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and come out with your hands behind your head.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:33.54,0:38:35.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  再给我点时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No! I need more time!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.52,0:38:41.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我老婆会安全的  对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My wife's gonna be safe, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:42.59,0:38:45.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雷蒙  你现在必须 合作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, Ramon, you gotta cooperate now.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.61,0:38:47.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,里面没人了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You got nobody left in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:55.07,0:38:57.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有人看到嫌疑人了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Anybody have a visual on the suspect?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:57.85,0:39:00.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看不到  他不出来  我们还要待命吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. He's not coming out. Should we hold position?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:00.29,0:39:02.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  自从炸弹袭击以来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. Ever since the bomb,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:02.19,0:39:03.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们每十分钟就会接到报案\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we got a new call every ten minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:03.56,0:39:04.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里得赶快收工了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We gotta be done here.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:05.10,0:39:07.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别这样  再给他点时间  他会自己走出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please don't. Give him time. He'll come out on his own.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:08.02,0:39:10.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了  各单位  行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, all units go. Go now, go!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:13.07,0:39:14.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,放下武器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Drop your weapon!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:14.88,0:39:15.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.96,0:39:22.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,四号行动  请派医疗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Code 4. Send medical...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:22.50,0:39:24.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,医疗队  行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Medical team, go!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:33.15,0:39:34.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-谢谢你  -没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Thank you. - All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:35.36,0:39:38.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-准备好了吗  -好了  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- We ready? - Yes, we are, Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:42.13,0:39:44.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,副总统先生  目前这里只有我和林恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Vice President, you're on with me and Lynne
Dialogue: 0,0:39:44.83,0:39:47.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为总统先生正在听莱恩·查普尔做简报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}because the president is being briefed by Ryan Chappelle.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.27,0:39:50.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他让我们先开始\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He asked that we go ahead without him.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:51.07,0:39:54.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好吧  -英国大使那边怎么样了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Fine. - How did it go with the British ambassador?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:54.91,0:39:55.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不太好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not well.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:56.90,0:39:58.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他知道我们计划组织一场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He knows that we're planning a retaliation
Dialogue: 0,0:39:58.45,0:39:59.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对中东的报复行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}against the Middle East,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:59.33,0:40:02.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是他因为我们不合作而感到沮丧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but he's frustrated because we're not coordinating with them.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:02.28,0:40:05.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我确定等他知道真相的时候  他会理解的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sure he'll understand once he gets the facts.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:05.24,0:40:06.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么真相  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are the facts, Mike?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:07.70,0:40:08.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不管我们承不承认\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We've got planes in the air.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:08.65,0:40:10.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们已经派出了飞机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Either we're committed or we're not.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:11.20,0:40:16.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果证据显示塞浦路斯的录音是伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If the evidence shows that the Cyprus recording was falsified,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:17.09,0:40:20.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统想要把那些飞机召回来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the president wants the option of calling those planes back.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:21.43,0:40:22.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道这是什么意思吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what it sounds like to me?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:23.74,0:40:25.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一个取消行动的借口\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}An excuse to call this off.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:31.20,0:40:32.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你相信总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you believe the president's
Dialogue: 0,0:40:32.30,0:40:34.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有能力做这件事吗  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}capable of doing the hard thing, Mike?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:38.93,0:40:39.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,做正确的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The right thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:44.54,0:40:45.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  我相信\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir, I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:47.12,0:40:49.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他全身心投入了这次行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's committed to this action.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:49.51,0:40:53.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他只是想要考虑到方方面面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All he's doing is making sure every base is covered.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:54.81,0:40:55.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,希望吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I hope so.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:57.96,0:40:59.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一有消息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The president will be contacting you
Dialogue: 0,0:40:59.94,0:41:01.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统就会联系您的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}as soon as anything develops.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.60,0:41:03.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:16.82,0:41:17.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:23.03,0:41:25.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你觉得副总统说的对  是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You think the vice president is right, don't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:27.93,0:41:30.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果总统因为一位反恐组特工的不实猜测\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If the president turns those planes around,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:31.12,0:41:35.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就把那些飞机召回的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}based on the unconfirmed speculation of a single CTU agent,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:37.05,0:41:38.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那就真的是个灾难了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it'll be a disaster.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:47.83,0:41:49.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以我们该怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So what do we do about it?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:54.18,0:41:55.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:06.00,0:42:08.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你要带我去哪  -进去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where are you taking me? - Get in.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:10.13,0:42:11.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不会逃跑的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not gonna try and escape.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:14.15,0:42:15.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我说了  进去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I said, get in.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:15.33,0:42:19.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  为了你自己的安全  进后备箱吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate. Get in the trunk, for your own safety.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:03.74,0:43:06.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,追踪器安装好了  已经启动了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The tracker's in place. It's been activated.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:06.14,0:43:06.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:07.74,0:43:10.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  跟你交易真愉快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, it's been a real pleasure.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:13.57,0:43:14.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会联系你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll be in touch.

