[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,1,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.69,0:00:10.86,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(197.4,200.557)}{\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs25\b1\bord0\shad0\c&H78BDE7&\fad(0,808)}24小时\N\N{\fs15}第二季  第四集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.15,0:00:13.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(189.6,121.6,193.8,105.6,0,356)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad3\3c&H2F2F2F&\4c&H336D99&}{\fs10}{\t(0,356,\fs20)\fn方正正中黑简体}前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.10,0:00:16.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你查我给你的护照信息了吗  -查了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Did you check the passport information I gave you? - I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.49,0:00:16.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(167.4,129.353)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.53,0:00:16.58,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(163.2,128.553)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.58,0:00:16.62,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(159,125.353)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.62,0:00:16.66,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs15\c&H449BA1&\pos(154.2,122.153)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.66,0:00:16.70,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(148.8,118.153)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.70,0:00:16.74,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(144.6,116.553)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.74,0:00:18.70,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(141,112.553)\fad(0,347)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.27,0:00:20.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,证实了雷扎·纳耶尔和赛伊德·阿里有过接触\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It confirms Reza Naiyeer has had contact with Syed Ali.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.42,0:00:23.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我妹妹就要跟一个和恐怖分子合作的人结婚了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My sister is marrying someone who works for terrorists
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.92,0:00:25.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你居然要我表现得正常一点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and you expect me to act normal?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.49,0:00:26.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你表现出有什么问题的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You could endanger yourself
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.89,0:00:29.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你和你的家人都会有危险\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and your family if you let on anything is wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.46,0:00:30.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我懂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.56,0:00:33.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治  我们需要你去检查山谷里的一座仓库\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George, we need you to check out a warehouse in the valley.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.59,0:00:31.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(219.6,130.953)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.63,0:00:31.67,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(227.4,129.353)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.67,0:00:31.72,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(234,125.353)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.72,0:00:31.76,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs15\c&H449BA1&\pos(242.4,120)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.76,0:00:31.80,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(247.2,117.353)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.80,0:00:33.68,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(255.6,113.353)\fad(0,312)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.96,0:00:43.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你吸入的物质是钚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The substance you inhaled is Plutonium.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.35,0:00:43.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(192,37.6)\fax-0.3\frz359}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&}危险\N放射性物质
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.20,0:00:44.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还能活多久\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How much time do I have?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.56,0:00:47.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,多则一周少则一天\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As much as a week or as little as a day.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.96,0:00:49.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,外面什么情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's going on out here?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.08,0:00:53.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克·鲍尔说沃尔德的手下准备炸掉反恐组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack Bauer says that Wald's crew is planning to blow up CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.36,0:00:50.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(131.4,141.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.41,0:00:50.45,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(133.2,136.553)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.45,0:00:50.49,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(132.6,132.553)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.49,0:00:50.53,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs13\c&H449BA1&\pos(132,128.8)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.53,0:00:50.57,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs15\c&H449BA1&\pos(133.8,121.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.57,0:00:50.61,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(135,116.553)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.61,0:00:50.65,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(136.8,113.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.65,0:00:50.69,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(137.4,109.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.69,0:00:52.57,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(137.4,104.553)\fad(0,350)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.15,0:00:56.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你给反恐组打过电话了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Have you contacted CTU?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.16,0:00:57.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鲍尔还没抓到沃尔德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bauer hasn't gotten to Wald yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.85,0:00:59.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我们阻止沃尔德手下行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If we stop Wald's crew,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.08,0:01:01.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们可能会意识到是鲍尔告的密\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}they may realise Bauer turned them in.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.23,0:01:03.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,立刻联系反恐组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Contact CTU immediately.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.51,0:01:05.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不会让他再伤害到你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I’m never gonna let him hurt you again.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.92,0:01:05.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(177,130.153)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.96,0:01:06.01,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(173.4,128.553)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.01,0:01:06.05,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(172.2,126.153)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.05,0:01:06.09,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs15\c&H449BA1&\pos(169.2,122.153)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.09,0:01:06.13,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(166.2,120.553)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.13,0:01:06.21,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(163.2,118.153)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.21,0:01:08.09,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(156,113.353)\fad(0,313)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.04,0:01:08.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要报告一起儿童绑架事件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Dispatch said you're reporting a child abduction?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.00,0:01:08.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她带走了我女儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She took my daughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.82,0:01:11.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-描述一下嫌疑人  -她叫金柏莉·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Describe the suspect for me. - Her name's Kimberly Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.63,0:01:13.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,事情有点麻烦  警察在追捕我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's kinda messed up. I have the police after me.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.27,0:01:17.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你能带她来反恐组吗  -我觉得可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Can you get her to CTU? - Yeah, I guess so.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.66,0:01:19.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是金柏莉·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My name's Kimberly Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.11,0:01:20.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要见托尼·阿尔梅达\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony Almeida is expecting us.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.80,0:01:22.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你真觉得用三组炸药就足以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You really think you're gonna take that building down
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.24,0:01:23.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,炸掉那栋大楼吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}with three charges?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.02,0:01:23.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(162,130.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.07,0:01:23.11,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(157.2,130.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.11,0:01:23.15,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(151.8,126.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.15,0:01:23.19,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs15\c&H449BA1&\pos(150,123.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.19,0:01:23.23,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(144.6,121.353)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.23,0:01:23.27,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(141.6,120.553)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.27,0:01:23.31,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(138.6,117.353)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.31,0:01:25.23,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(135,116.553)\fad(0,394)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.42,0:01:25.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你为什么以反恐组为目标\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What made you target CTU anyway?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.18,0:01:27.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你怎么这么多问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why are you asking so many questions?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.00,0:01:36.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们成功了  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We did it, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.07,0:01:38.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,干得好  艾迪  干得好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good job, Eddie. Good job.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.95,0:01:45.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs15\t(696,6577,\fs16)\c&H4BAAAD&\fad(1697,1183)\pos(187.2,191.79)}以下故事情节发生在上午11点到12点之间
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.13,0:01:59.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,墙就要倒塌了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The walls are coming down.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.21,0:02:02.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,楼里还有56人  没有反应\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}56 remain in the property and no responding.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.23,0:02:05.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,A区有7名人员死亡  你们呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have seven DOAs in the alpha zone. What's your count?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.28,0:02:07.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,目前10名\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ten so far.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.24,0:02:08.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,北侧入口需要急救队支援\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We need more EMT support at the north entrance.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.95,0:02:13.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,消防和救援队正在途中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fire and rescue teams are on way.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.20,0:02:40.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.24,0:02:43.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.23,0:02:52.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有人能来这里搭把手吗  需要一些帮助\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can we get some help over here? A little help.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.13,0:02:54.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.56,0:02:56.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.51,0:03:01.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你空出一块三角区  带上卢克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need you to set up a triage. And take Luke with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.02,0:03:05.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,卢克  我在这呢  是米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Luke, I've got you. It's Michelle.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.17,0:03:07.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我看看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me see that.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.50,0:03:09.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,宝拉  宝拉  能听到吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Paula? Paula, can you hear me?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.73,0:03:11.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,发  发生了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What... What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.88,0:03:14.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不必说话  如果能听到就眨眨眼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't have to speak. Just blink your eyes if you can hear me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.36,0:03:17.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  我们会把你弄出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. We're gonna get you outta there.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.54,0:03:19.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,撑住了  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just hang tight. All right?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.04,0:03:21.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她伤的很严重  伙计\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's bad, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.60,0:03:25.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们得现在找个起重机或是液压升降机之类的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We gotta get a crane or a hydraulic lift or something in here now.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.66,0:03:26.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们得小心处理\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have to be careful.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.53,0:03:27.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果拿错了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If we pull out the wrong piece,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.54,0:03:28.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,整个物体会倒向她  砸毁她的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the whole thing could come down on her and crash her.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.65,0:03:31.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们得一块一块来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have to do this brick by brick.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.45,0:03:33.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那得花好长时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That could take for ever.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.46,0:03:36.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  开始吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, let's do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.30,0:03:41.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事的  我们会没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's OK. We're gonna be all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.47,0:03:45.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你真的非常勇敢  非常...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're being real brave. Real...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.15,0:03:48.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-抱抱  -我觉得不太舒服\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Ssh, ssh, come on. - I don't feel very well.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.83,0:03:49.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们会没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna be OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.54,0:03:52.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们很快就离开这里  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna be out of here soon, OK? All right?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.58,0:03:55.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅根  梅根\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Megan! Megan!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.78,0:03:59.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快来人帮帮我  拜托  我需要帮助\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Somebody help me! Please, I need some help!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.56,0:04:01.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-把她放下  -她怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Hold her down. - What's wrong with her?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.95,0:04:02.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把她放下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hold her down.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.96,0:04:03.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's the matter?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.67,0:04:05.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅根\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Megan!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.63,0:04:08.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-梅根  -她在痉挛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Megan! - She's seizing.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.74,0:04:10.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们得立刻送她去急诊室\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We've gotta get her to the ER right away.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.78,0:04:11.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's wrong with her?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.97,0:04:12.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,送你去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.41,0:04:16.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统  我们尽力了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, we did everything we could do.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.95,0:04:20.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果鲍尔再早点打电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If only Bauer had called earlier,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.36,0:04:24.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,即使只有几分钟  我们也能救下这些人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}even a few minutes, we could've saved those people.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.72,0:04:26.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在我们了解更多之前  我想\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Until we know more, I'd like to
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.17,0:04:29.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再过一遍洛杉矶的疏散计划  在你桌上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}go over my evacuation plan for LA. It's on your desk.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.78,0:04:32.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-等我准备好看再打给你  -谢谢  总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'll call you when I'm ready to meet on it. - Thank you, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.52,0:04:43.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那些人都是因你而死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Those people are dead because of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.28,0:04:47.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我想要告诉总统的  -但是你没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I wanted to tell the president. - But you didn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.58,0:04:49.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都是因为你  艾瑞克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because of you, Eric.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.88,0:04:51.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你确保我无法顺利告诉他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You made sure that I couldn't get through to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.94,0:04:53.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就我所知  鲍尔就没打电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As far as I know, Bauer never called.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.93,0:04:55.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是那个和他通话的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're the one who spoke to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.91,0:05:00.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你在威胁我吗  -我是在保护总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Are you blackmailing me? - I'm protecting the president.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.51,0:05:03.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,林恩  不管你知道或者自以为知道什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lynne, whatever you know or think you know,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.35,0:05:05.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我建议你不要声张\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I suggest you keep it to yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.69,0:05:19.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你车里的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Everything in your car,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.66,0:05:21.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我都清理干净并放进救护车了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I had it cleared out and put into the ambulance.So...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.88,0:05:24.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你什么时候准备好去医院都可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}whenever you're ready to go to the hospital.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.77,0:05:28.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我会怎么死掉  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- So how's it gonna happen? - Excuse me?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.45,0:05:30.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你说过我可能活不到明天了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You said I might be dead by tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.78,0:05:31.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是好奇的想知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm just kind of curious to know
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.81,0:05:33.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,剩下的日子还有什么可指望的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}what to expect for the rest of the day.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.76,0:05:39.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在潜伏期内你基本上没有症状\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's a latent period where you'll be mostly asymptomatic.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.81,0:05:42.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,即使是在最严重的辐射中毒病例中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Even in the most extreme cases of radiation poisoning,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.50,0:05:44.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,潜伏期会持续一阵\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it can last a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:44.89,0:05:45.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是多久\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's a while?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.05,0:05:49.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最多12小时  可能更长\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Up to 12 hours, maybe longer.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.06,0:05:50.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你现在感觉怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How do you feel now?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.90,0:05:53.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想呕吐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wanna puke.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.04,0:05:56.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我可以给你点药物控制住恶心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can give you something to control the nausea.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.17,0:05:58.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,多谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thanks, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.60,0:06:01.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,至少在症状更为显著前\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}At least until the symptoms are more acute.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.01,0:06:03.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  具体表现是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, like, like what?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.89,0:06:07.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的头发会开始脱落\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your hair will start to fall out.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.69,0:06:09.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我过去也这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm used to that.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.60,0:06:14.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你会开始表现出胃肠道出血\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You'll start to manifest gastrointestinal haemorrhaging,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.13,0:06:18.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,皮肤损伤  口鼻出血\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}skin lesions, bleeding from the mouth and the nose.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.33,0:06:21.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ok.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.56,0:06:22.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会如何死去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So how am I gonna die?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.19,0:06:29.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的  你的意识功能会开始\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your... your mental functioning will begin
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.20,0:06:32.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,退化  接着你会陷入昏迷\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to deteriorate and then you'll lapse into a coma...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.64,0:06:33.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅森先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Mason.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.85,0:06:35.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-等会  -是托尼·阿尔梅达\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Not now. - It's Tony Almeida.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.81,0:06:37.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-等会再说  -他说很紧急\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Not now! - He said it's urgent.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.06,0:06:37.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.98,0:06:41.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼  什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony, what is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.06,0:06:43.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们袭击了我们  乔治  他们炸了反恐组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They hit us, George. They bombed CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.36,0:06:46.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,损害严重吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What kind of damage?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.02,0:06:47.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,损坏报告还在跟进\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Damage reports are still coming in
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.61,0:06:49.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是目前为止我们的人员有19名死亡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but so far we got 19 of our people dead,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.43,0:06:50.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,20名受伤  7名失踪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}20 wounded and seven missing.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.52,0:06:54.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们这里伤亡严重  乔治\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, we're bleeding bad here, George.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:55.07,0:06:57.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,与核武器有关的信息都损毁了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All of our intel on the nuke was destroyed.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.55,0:06:59.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,信息在国安局服务器上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, it's on the NSA server,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.72,0:07:02.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但解密代码是宝拉写的  她状况很糟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but Paula wrote the decryption code and she's in bad shape.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.24,0:07:04.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那就想尽办法恢复数据吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just do whatever you have to to retrieve it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.90,0:07:06.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错  我在想办法\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, Well, I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.92,0:07:07.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以才打给你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's why I called you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.16,0:07:09.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,指挥系统  记得吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Chain of command, remember?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.46,0:07:11.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,打给国安局系统的人  让他们去弄\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Call NSA systems people. Get them on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.81,0:07:14.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我已经打过了  乔治  -很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I already did, George. - Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.23,0:07:15.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你什么时候回来这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, when are you coming back here?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.46,0:07:17.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不确定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I... I'm not sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.29,0:07:19.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,越早越好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, the sooner the better.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.17,0:07:24.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  事实上我可能不回去了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, the truth is I may not be coming back.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.29,0:07:24.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why not?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.99,0:07:27.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为我现在的处境帮不到忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because I'm not really in a position to help out right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.16,0:07:29.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.06,0:07:33.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天有一个待爆炸的核装置被安置在洛杉矶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, a nuclear device is set to go off some time today in Los Angeles.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.51,0:07:34.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们刚刚失去了半数的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We just lost half the people
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.70,0:07:36.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们可都是为了阻止事情发生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}who were in position to keep it from happening,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.33,0:07:38.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别和我说你还要顾你自己\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so don't tell me you're still trying to cover your own ass!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.45,0:07:40.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想办法吧  托尼  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just deal with it, Tony, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.74,0:07:42.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想想办法  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just deal with it, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.06,0:07:42.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, right.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.63,0:08:04.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  你和我来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, you come with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.33,0:08:11.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  点着火  我们就离开这\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, light her up. Let's get outta here.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.36,0:08:18.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔  搞定了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Joe. It's done.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.84,0:08:21.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.79,0:08:25.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Yeah, I can do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.98,0:08:27.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我地址\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Give me the address.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.14,0:08:32.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I know where it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.79,0:08:35.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.13,0:08:40.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  再见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. Out.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.91,0:08:44.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-是乔吗  -是的  走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Was that Joe? - Yeah. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.27,0:08:50.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把火柴给我  艾迪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Give me the matchbook, Eddie.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.76,0:08:53.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你他妈要干什么  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What the hell are you doing, Jack?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.40,0:08:55.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是联邦探员  你被拘捕了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm a federal officer. You're under arrest.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.31,0:08:56.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把火柴板给我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now give me the matchbook.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.85,0:09:03.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,安炸放弹你也有份  还把戈伦的头砍了下来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You helped plant those bombs and cut Goren's head off.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.20,0:09:04.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道我都干什么了  艾迪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know what I did, Eddie.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.59,0:09:07.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把你的右手放到方向盘上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Put your right hand on the steering wheel.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.24,0:09:15.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,慢一点  用你的左手把你的枪给我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And very slowly, with your left hand, pass me your gun.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.62,0:09:22.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  乔要是知道这事  你就死定了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, Jack, when Joe finds out about this, you're a dead man.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:23.91,0:09:25.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,闭嘴  艾迪  下车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shut up, Eddie. Get out of the car.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:28.57,0:09:29.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那个狗娘养的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That son of a bitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.02,0:10:56.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是托尼·阿尔梅达的电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony Almeida's line.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.49,0:10:58.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你是谁  -米歇尔·德斯勒  你是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Who's this? - Michelle Dessler. Who is this?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.28,0:11:01.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔  我是杰克·鲍尔  出什么事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle, this is Jack Bauer. What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.80,0:11:04.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,20分钟前发生了一场爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There was an explosion 20 minutes ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.79,0:11:06.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,21人身亡  数字还在上升\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}21 casualties, the number's growing.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.22,0:11:10.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-反恐组怎么没疏散  -根本没时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Why wasn't CTU evacuated? - There wasn't any time.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:10.32,0:11:14.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,时间不够是什么意思  梅森没事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you mean there wasn't enough time? What about Mason, is he all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:14.45,0:11:15.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他不在这\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He wasn't here.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.42,0:11:19.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-托尼·阿尔梅达呢  -他在帮着救助同事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How about Tony Almeida? - He's helping the rescue workers.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.59,0:11:21.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好吧  你能处理一个情况报告吗  -能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Fine. Can you handle a situation report? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.90,0:11:27.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, go ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.83,0:11:30.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我定位了约瑟夫·沃尔德  正赶往那里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've located Joseph Wald. I'm on my way there now.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.26,0:11:33.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-沃尔德的手下呢  -他们都死了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What about Wald's crew? - They're all dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.83,0:11:34.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,死了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Dead?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.65,0:11:37.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你就告诉梅森我正赶往沃尔德的住处就行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just let Mason know I'm on my way to Wald's house.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.45,0:11:41.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,地址是西米谷市峡谷路221号\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The address is 221 Canyon View Road in Simi Valley.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.34,0:11:43.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会派支援的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, I'll send backup.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.83,0:11:45.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK. Oh, Michelle,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.76,0:11:48.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉梅森我跟金通话了  她离开市里了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}let Mason know I talked to Kim. She is leaving the city.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.96,0:11:51.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她也给这打电话了  跟托尼说的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She called here too and she spoke to Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.37,0:11:53.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是吗  她说什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She did? What did she say?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.34,0:11:55.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也不清楚  我回头查一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not sure. But I'll look into it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.44,0:11:56.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,查完找我  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, get back to me. Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.88,0:12:03.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,宝拉  宝拉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Paula! Paula!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.60,0:12:05.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她没事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is she OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.50,0:12:07.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.92,0:12:10.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's up?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.42,0:12:14.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-刚跟杰克·鲍尔通过电话  -他在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Just got off the phone with Jack Bauer. - Where is he?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.08,0:12:16.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去见沃尔德的路上  他想让梅森知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}On his way to see Wald. He wanted Mason to know.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.31,0:12:17.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅森不在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, Mason's checked out.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.08,0:12:20.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把信息直接给国安局就行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just get the information directly to NSA.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:21.39,0:12:23.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他还问起了他的女儿  金\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And he asked about his daughter, Kim.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.22,0:12:26.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-糟糕  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Oh... Oh, no. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.95,0:12:28.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她往这边赶来着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She was on her way here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.15,0:12:31.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能看一下安全日志  看她在不在楼里吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can you check the security logs, see if she was in the building?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.76,0:12:33.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.96,0:12:38.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-梅根没事吧  -会没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Is Megan all right? - She will be.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.02,0:12:41.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她的癫痫是由颅内压力引起的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Her seizure was caused by pressure on the brain
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.32,0:12:43.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再加上颅骨骨折\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}compounded by a skull fracture.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.68,0:12:45.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是我们爆炸前就出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But we got out in time,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.17,0:12:46.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她不是在爆炸中受伤的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}she wasn't injured in the explosion.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.32,0:12:48.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道  据我们所掌握的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know. From what I've seen,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.06,0:12:50.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她的头部是很可能是在大爆炸之前受伤的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}her head injury most likely occurred before the blast.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.37,0:12:55.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅根的X光片显示多处其他的伤痕\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Megan's X-rays indicate other prior injuries
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.69,0:12:58.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,手腕骨折  几处手指骨折未得到医治\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}a fractured wrist, several fingers that were never treated.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.65,0:12:59.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的意思是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you saying?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.85,0:13:02.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些伤可能是生理虐待的迹象\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}These injuries suggest a possible pattern of physical abuse.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.45,0:13:12.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不会认为是我吧  你认为我伤害了她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't think I did this? You don't think I hurt her?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.55,0:13:15.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会让警方来调查清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna let the police sort that out.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.29,0:13:21.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,比尔  他们正在限制权限\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bill, they're limiting access.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.28,0:13:23.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们只知道就在刚才\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All we know is that a short time ago,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.10,0:13:27.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一个大型爆炸将这栋洛杉矶的政府大楼炸开了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}a major explosion ripped through this government building in Los Angeles.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.46,0:13:31.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尽管早期推断包含恐怖分子涉足其中的传闻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No statement has been issued about the cause of the explosion,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.55,0:13:32.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但到目前为止\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}although early speculation
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.87,0:13:35.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还没有针对此次爆炸发表的任何声明\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}has included rumours of terrorist involvement.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.70,0:13:40.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就我看来  这个结果支持疏散城市\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As far as I'm concerned, this tips in favour of evacuation.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.48,0:13:41.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我估计大家已经都读了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I assume you've all read
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.86,0:13:44.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,埃里克建议疏散洛杉矶的报告\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Eric's report recommending the evacuation of LA.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.86,0:13:47.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反恐组爆炸事件还只是个开始\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The CTU bombing is just the beginning.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.14,0:13:50.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,问题变成传言  传言再引发大型恐慌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's only a matter of time before the questions become rumours,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.73,0:13:53.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是时间早晚的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and the rumours set off a mass panic.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.64,0:13:55.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,疏散就不会造成恐慌了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wouldn't the evacuation itself cause panic?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.97,0:14:00.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们可以悄然逐步行事  已经准备好了托辞\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We can do this discreetly in stages. We've prepared cover stories.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.19,0:14:02.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对于九百万的人口来说不是容易事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's a tough sell for nine million people.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.54,0:14:04.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,普勒斯顿将军向我保证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}General Preston assures me
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.28,0:14:07.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,军方可以控制任何民间骚乱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that the military can contain any civilian unrest.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.13,0:14:09.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"控制"听着挺委婉的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Contain" Sounds like a euphemism.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:09.95,0:14:11.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,更不用提宪法问题了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not to mention the Constitutional issues.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.92,0:14:13.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我并不是说此事易如反掌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't claim this'll be a cakewalk.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.02,0:14:19.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里也没用提到现实问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's also a practical issue not being addressed here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.87,0:14:20.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么情况  林恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's that, Lynne?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.12,0:14:22.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们的情报确定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Our intelligence is specific
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.88,0:14:26.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天将会引爆核武器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}about this nuclear device being detonated today.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.32,0:14:27.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的报告说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your report says
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.53,0:14:30.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,疏散至少需要一周的时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it would take at least one week for this evacuation.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.21,0:14:31.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的职责是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's my job to protect as
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.41,0:14:34.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尽可能地保护更多的美国公民\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}many citizens of the United States as I can.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.35,0:14:35.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我能把百分之二十的人口\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If I get even 20% of the
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.74,0:14:38.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,疏散到辐射区外  那就算成功了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}population outside the blast radius, that's a win.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.55,0:14:40.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们连炸弹在哪里都不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We don't know where the bomb is.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.00,0:14:42.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那要从哪开始疏散\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where do we begin the evacuation?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.31,0:14:45.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的手下列出了十个可能性最高的目标区域\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My staff has ranked ten high probability target areas.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.98,0:14:47.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这还不够\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's not good enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.52,0:14:55.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道你们的准备时间很仓促\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I realise you've only had a short time to prepare this,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.83,0:14:58.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是我很不满意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I have some real reservations.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.02,0:15:02.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  底线就是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bottom line, Mr. President,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.40,0:15:05.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,从政治上保护你  如果炸弹引爆了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it protects you politically. If the bomb goes off...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.46,0:15:07.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果炸弹引爆了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If the bomb goes off,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.18,0:15:09.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就有比我再次竞选更重要的事情需要担忧的了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we'll have more important concerns than my re-election.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.35,0:15:18.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你还有什么需要补充的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you have anything else to add?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.97,0:15:21.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.10,0:15:23.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,散会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then we're done.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.38,0:15:26.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,除非我们有关于炸弹地点的可靠情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Until we have reliable intelligence about where the bomb is located,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.73,0:15:28.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不然就别提疏散这码事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}there will be no evacuation.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.38,0:15:33.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉达文罗斯将军我可以见他了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let General Davenlos know I'm ready for him,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.71,0:15:35.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,叫泰德和伊丽丝开会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and conference in Ted and Elyse.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.46,0:15:36.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.23,0:15:49.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是杰克·鲍尔  我有急事找总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is Jack Bauer. I need to speak to the president, it's urgently.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.62,0:15:51.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,稍等  鲍尔先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}One moment please, Mr. Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.13,0:15:53.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你确认这些报告\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need you to confirm
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.93,0:15:56.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后放到诺维克的办公桌上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}these reports and get them on Novick's desk immediately please.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.04,0:15:59.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-林恩·柯瑞斯基  -杰克·鲍尔在八号线\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Lynne Kresge. - I have Jack Bauer on line eight.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.04,0:16:02.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他坚持要跟总统通话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He insists on speaking to the president.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:02.05,0:16:03.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,接进来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Put him through, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.50,0:16:07.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鲍尔先生  我是林恩·柯瑞斯基\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Bauer, this is Lynne Kresge.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.28,0:16:09.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要跟总统通话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I asked to speak to the president.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.36,0:16:12.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  他现在没空  也许我能帮忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry, he's unavailable. Perhaps I can help.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.49,0:16:14.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们这帮人在搞什么鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What the hell are you doing over there?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.44,0:16:17.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大楼被炸之前我给了你们30分钟的警报时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I gave you a 30-minute warning before that building was hit.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.96,0:16:20.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们有充足的时间疏散员工的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You had plenty of time to evacuate the personnel.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.39,0:16:23.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鲍尔先生  有些情有可原的情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Bauer, there were extenuating circumstances.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.24,0:16:24.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我确实试图告知总统了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I did try to tell the president.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.97,0:16:28.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是情况比我一时能解释的更复杂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's more complicated than I'm able to explain at this time.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.67,0:16:32.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-很遗憾  这还不够  -我的能力有限\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'm sorry. That's not good enough. - It's all I can offer you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.43,0:16:34.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-柯瑞斯基女士  对吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Ms. Kresge, right? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.50,0:16:36.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要为丢掉性命的众多无辜百姓负责\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're responsible for killing a lot of innocent people today.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.54,0:16:38.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的同事  我的朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}People I work with, friends of mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.50,0:16:39.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I realized that.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.63,0:16:41.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在你是我们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right now you are the best
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.63,0:16:43.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拦截核武器的最佳人选了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}chance we have of intercepting that nuclear weapon.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.40,0:16:46.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我建议你做好分内的事  -我会做好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- So I suggest you do your job. - I'll do my job.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.99,0:16:48.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们这帮人最好开始做好你们分内的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You people better start doing yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.97,0:17:00.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.66,0:17:04.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,打扰一下  我需要跟你谈谈  很重要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry to interrupt, I need to talk to you. It's important.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.34,0:17:06.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  亲爱的  稍等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sure. Sure, honey. Just a second.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.66,0:17:10.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这场婚礼要把我弄破产了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This wedding's gonna break me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.30,0:17:14.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有什么大事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, what's the big emergency?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.15,0:17:17.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,上个月我查看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Last month I was going over
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.36,0:17:21.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,第三季度损益表的时候发现有不一致的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the P&Ls for the 3rd Quarter and I found some inconsistencies.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.94,0:17:24.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要是生意上的事  我们周一再谈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If this is business, we'll deal with this on Monday.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.97,0:17:27.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-爸  这跟雷扎有关  -雷扎怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Dad, it's about Reza. - What about Reza?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.03,0:17:34.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我以为丢钱的事可能就是他干的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I thought he might have been responsible for the missing money
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.40,0:17:36.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以我就雇了调查员做了个审计\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so I hired an investigator to do an audit.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.12,0:17:39.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你雇人调查雷扎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You hired someone to spy on Reza?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.78,0:17:41.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我以为他偷你的钱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I thought he was stealing from you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.09,0:17:42.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是他偷的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And is he?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.82,0:17:48.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是  但是发现了其他的事情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. But something else came up.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.84,0:17:50.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,更可怕的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Something a lot worse.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.98,0:17:52.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.43,0:18:02.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雷扎可能跟一个恐怖分子掺和到了一起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Reza may be involved with a terrorist.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.64,0:18:03.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.43,0:18:06.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很显然他一直跟一个资助\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Apparently he's been in contact with someone
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.64,0:18:09.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,恐怖行动的人联系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}who finances terrorist operations.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.39,0:18:11.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一个叫赛伊德·阿里的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A man named Syed Ali.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.37,0:18:14.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他有什么证据吗  -我不确定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What kind of proof does he have? - I'm not sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.61,0:18:15.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不确定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're not sure?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.28,0:18:18.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他只在一小时前给我打了电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He only called me about this an hour ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.43,0:18:21.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,叫我不要告诉任何人  但我得告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He told me not to tell anyone, but I had to tell you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.66,0:18:25.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不管他发现了什么  都是可以解释的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Whatever this investigator found, there's an explanation for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.58,0:18:29.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你雇人去挖他的丑事  他就一定能挖出东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Honey, you hire a man to dig up dirt, he's gonna dig up dirt.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.90,0:18:31.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们就是这样维持生计的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's how these guys stay in business.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.69,0:18:34.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-如果你是错的呢  -我没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What if you're wrong?  - I'm not.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.67,0:18:35.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你怎么知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How do you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:40.36,0:18:42.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为我自己已经查了雷扎的身份\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because I had Reza checked out myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.92,0:18:46.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,查得比你找的人仔细多了  相信我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And a lot more thoroughly than the guy you hired. Belive me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.08,0:18:50.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  雷扎不是恐怖分子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate, Reza is not a terrorist.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.98,0:18:55.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是一个商人  凯特  一个厉害的商人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I am a businessman, Kate. A damn good one.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.84,0:18:58.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的女儿是我最宝贵的财产\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My daughters are my most precious assets.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.21,0:19:00.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不进行一番详尽的调查\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wouldn't let either one of you
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.21,0:19:02.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是不会允许你们结婚的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}get married without performing a due diligence.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.28,0:19:08.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在  我希望你能放下这件事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, I want you to drop this nonsense
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.05,0:19:10.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,像对待家人一样对待雷扎  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and start treating Reza like a member of the family, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.94,0:19:12.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-各位  -嘿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Hey, guys. - Hey!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.86,0:19:19.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得我的表哥对你有感觉  凯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think my cousin's got a little crush on you, Kate.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.37,0:19:21.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,回酒店的路上他一直在谈论你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He wouldn't stop talking about you on the way back to hotel.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:22.02,0:19:24.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他看起来很不错  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- He seems nice. - Yeah, he is.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.80,0:19:29.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我向玛丽保证我会去取午餐  我得出发了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, I promised Marie I'd pick up lunch. I'd better get going.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:29.16,0:19:32.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-让我送你去吧  -没事  我一个人可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Let me take you. - It's OK, I can handle it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.69,0:19:34.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当你看到她点了多少菜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When you see how much she's ordered,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.47,0:19:36.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就会知道你需要人帮忙的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you'll need another pair of hands.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.21,0:19:37.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真的  我可以的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Really, I can do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.63,0:19:39.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.35,0:19:42.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,出发吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.90,0:20:17.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,三号车  这里是调度站\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mobile 3, this is Dispatch.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.54,0:20:21.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是三号车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is mobile 3.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:22.06,0:20:25.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反恐局的托尼·阿尔梅达需要联系乔治·梅森\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have Tony Almeida at CTU for George Mason.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.62,0:20:28.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-长官  -我知道了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Sir... - Yeah, I heard.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.33,0:20:35.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-托尼  -乔治\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Tony? - George.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.06,0:20:37.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我说了这事你自己处理\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I told you to handle this yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.71,0:20:40.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我不用给你打电话  我会很高兴的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Truth is right now if I didn't have to talk to you again I'd be happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.98,0:20:44.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但技术部门需要进入宝拉之前工作的数据流\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But IT people need to access the data stream Paula was working on.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.29,0:20:46.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在你的系统上  需要你的密码\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's on your system. We need your password.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.26,0:20:47.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我的密码  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- My password? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.77,0:20:50.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,Hendrix\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hendrix.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.14,0:20:54.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-带X吗  -要不然你怎么拼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- That's with an "X"? - How else would you spell it?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.68,0:20:56.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  谢谢  乔治\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right. Thanks, George.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.59,0:20:58.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-托尼  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Tony? - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.96,0:21:02.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,宝拉怎么样了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How's Paula doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.24,0:21:06.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不好  他们正努力救她出来  但她没反应\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not good. They're trying to dig her out, but she's unresponsive.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.15,0:21:07.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得挂了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I gotta go.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.13,0:21:09.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ok.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.84,0:21:13.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.61,0:21:21.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会传染别人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Am I contagious?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.56,0:21:24.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.42,0:22:25.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔  我是杰克  让我进去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Joe, it's Jack. Let me in.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.88,0:22:30.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-艾迪呢  -他死了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where's Eddie? - He's dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.62,0:22:32.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,克里斯和斯科特呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about Chris and Scott?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.96,0:22:35.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们也死了  乔  快让我进去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're dead, too. Come on, Joe. Let me in.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.40,0:22:41.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我半小时前才和艾迪通过话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just talked to Eddie half an hour ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.23,0:22:44.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔  我得先进去再和你解释\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Joe, we gotta do this inside. Let me in.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.44,0:22:53.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,艾迪之前说一切都进展顺利\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Eddie said the job went off without a hitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.56,0:22:54.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在又是怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What happened between then and now?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.16,0:22:57.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我把他们杀了  因为拒捕\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I killed them, for resisting arrest.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.53,0:23:01.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也会杀了你的  把枪放在桌上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll kill you, too, Joe. I mean it. Put it down on the table.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.23,0:23:05.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把枪放下  放在桌上  快点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Put it down! On the table, now.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.61,0:23:09.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,坐到沙发上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Have a seat on the couch.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.36,0:23:17.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你杀了戈伦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You killed Goren.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.60,0:23:20.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为了找到你我做了我该做的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I did what I had to to find you.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.83,0:23:22.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  你到底想干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, Jack. What do you want?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.99,0:23:25.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是谁命令你今天袭击反恐组的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who told you to hit CTU today?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.48,0:23:29.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么你觉得是别人叫我做的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What makes you think anyone told me to do anything?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.52,0:23:30.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为在洛杉矶某个地方还有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because there's a nuclear device
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.99,0:23:33.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一个核弹预计今天会爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}somewhere in Los Angeles set to go off today.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.20,0:23:36.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊  乔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's right, Joe.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.28,0:23:39.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反恐组是次要目标\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}CTU was a secondary target.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.69,0:23:41.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样做能阻止我们接近核弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A way of stopping us from getting to the bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.23,0:23:45.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,无论谁叫你这么做的  他们利用且陷害了你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Whoever got you to do this job, they used you, they set you up.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.75,0:23:47.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在说谎  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're lying, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.32,0:23:49.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  这次我说的是事实\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, this time I'm telling you the truth.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.56,0:23:51.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要不然你觉得我是如何联系上戈伦的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How else do you think I got to Goren?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.47,0:23:54.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔  你不傻  好好想想吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, Joe you're not stupid. Think about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.89,0:23:57.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你今天为什么袭击反恐组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why did you hit CTU today?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.52,0:24:01.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有这么多天可以选择  为什么选择今天袭击\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of all the days you could have, why did you hit CTU today?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.19,0:24:05.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不仅知道袭击哪里  还知道何时袭击\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You weren't just told where to hit, you were told when.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.09,0:24:07.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这才是真相  乔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's the truth, Joe.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.14,0:24:10.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我最后再给你一次机会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, I'm gonna give you one last chance.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.34,0:24:13.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谁命令你今天袭击反恐组的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who told you to hit CTU today?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.86,0:25:14.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,开门  乔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Open the door, Joe.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.38,0:25:17.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,开门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Open the door.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.17,0:25:23.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,开门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Open the door!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.55,0:25:35.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你无路可走了  乔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's no other way outta here, Joe.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.01,0:26:09.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-喂  -卡拉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Hello? - Carla.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.94,0:26:12.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-金  你在哪  -急诊室\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Kim, where are you? - The emergency room.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.93,0:26:16.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-梅根呢  -她在  医生在救治她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where's Megan? - She's here Carla. She's in with the doctors.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.79,0:26:18.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的天  她怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, my God, what happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:18.38,0:26:19.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她晕倒了  全身发抖\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She collapsed, she started shaking.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.89,0:26:20.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,医生说由于颅内压的升高\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The doctors said she had a seizure
Dialogue: 0,0:26:20.97,0:26:22.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,诱发了癫痫的发作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}because of pressure on her brain.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.27,0:26:26.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在哪里  哪个医院\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where are you? What hospital?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.55,0:26:27.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你先听我说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}First listen to what I have to say.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.81,0:26:29.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  你听我说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, you listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.31,0:26:31.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你绑架了我的女儿  攻击我的丈夫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You kidnapped my daughter and you attacked my husband.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.79,0:26:33.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道不是那样的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know that's not true.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.62,0:26:35.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅根受伤是加里造成的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's Gary's fault that Megan is here.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:35.79,0:26:38.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,医生说是头部受伤造成了癫痫的发生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The doctor said she had a seizure because of a head injury.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.63,0:26:40.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,加里把梅根推倒了  梅根撞到了头\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Gary threw her down and Megan hit her head.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:41.55,0:26:42.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是个意外  金\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was an accident, Kim.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:43.10,0:26:46.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别再为他找借口了  别再否认事实了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stop making excuses for him, stop denying what's happening.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.24,0:26:48.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这不关你的事  金\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This isn't your problem, Kim.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.43,0:26:50.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们还发现了些别的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They found other things on Megan's X-rays.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.58,0:26:52.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们认为她受到了虐待  我也这样认为\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They think she's been abused. I think so, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.41,0:26:59.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,卡拉  你在吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Carla, are you there?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.35,0:27:03.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I'm here.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.63,0:27:05.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,医院联系了警方  他们已经在路上了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The hospital called the police. They're on their way.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:06.53,0:27:08.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你也应该过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You should be here when they come.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:10.45,0:27:13.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你在哪里  -圣维吉尔急诊室\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where are you? - St Virgil's Emergency Room.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:13.79,0:27:15.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我二十分钟就到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm 20 minutes away.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:58.86,0:28:01.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有一个战术小队就要到了  乔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A tactical team's on its way, Joe.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:02.19,0:28:03.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你无路可走了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's nowhere for you to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.65,0:28:11.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那些给你反恐局信息的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The people who gave you the information for CTU,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:11.80,0:28:14.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,示意图  还有所有的访问代码\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the schematic, all the access codes,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.11,0:28:17.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我希望你明白他们的目的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you to know what they're trying to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.17,0:28:22.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们想毁掉整个国家  从洛杉矶开始\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They wanna destroy this entire country, starting with Los Angeles.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.29,0:28:24.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这真是你想要的吗  乔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is that really what you want, Joe?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.58,0:28:33.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我以为你希望把权利重新交给人民\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I thought you wanted to give the power back to the people.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:34.28,0:28:35.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那不是你过去常说的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Isn't that what you used to say?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:37.27,0:28:39.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你觉得哪些人会处于爆炸中心  乔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who do you think's gonna be at ground zero, Joe?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:40.68,0:28:42.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你并不是在和联邦政府作斗争\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're not fighting the federal government.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:43.21,0:28:45.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这事关无辜的群众\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're talking about innocent people.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.72,0:28:49.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天有多少人要死于你的手下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How many of them are gonna have to die for you today?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:50.27,0:28:52.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,十万人  二十万人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A hundred thousand? Two hundred thousand?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:53.18,0:28:54.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  我不这样认为\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, I don't think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:55.60,0:28:57.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我估计有接近一百万人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think it's gonna be a lot closer to a million,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.93,0:28:59.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果包括辐射造成的影响的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}once you factor in the radiation.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:00.82,0:29:02.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是你想要的遗产吗  乔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is that what you want your legacy to be, Joe?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.17,0:29:08.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔  开门吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, Joe. Just open the door.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:10.97,0:29:12.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去你妈的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Son of a bitch!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:13.50,0:29:15.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这就是你这种人的可笑之处  乔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's the funny thing about people like you, Joe.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:16.56,0:29:18.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你把你人生中的一切差错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You wanna blame the rest of the world
Dialogue: 0,0:29:18.20,0:29:19.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都怪在这个世界其他人的头上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}for everything wrong with your life.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:21.39,0:29:24.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,政府太强大  他们的权力过大\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The government's too big. They're too powerful.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.38,0:29:28.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这就有点讽刺了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, here's a bit of irony for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.11,0:29:31.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在权力都在你的手上  乔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You got all the power now, Joe.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:34.08,0:29:35.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,权力都在你的手上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You got all the power.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:36.19,0:29:37.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,问题是  你要怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Question is, what are you gonna do with it?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:38.65,0:29:40.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你会让那些人死去吗  乔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You gonna let all those people die, Joe?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:42.32,0:29:45.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,该死  乔  没时间了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Damm it, Joe! You are running out of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.41,0:29:49.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们没时间了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We are all running out of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:09.00,0:30:09.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You, uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:12.51,0:30:14.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不是很喜欢我  是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}don't really like me very much, do you?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:17.66,0:30:18.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这真疯狂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:20.34,0:30:22.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我为你的父亲已经工作三年了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've been working for your father for three years now.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:22.45,0:30:24.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,和玛丽约会两年了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've been dating Marie for two.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:27.07,0:30:31.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但你和我  我们一直没机会了解对方\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But you and I, we never really got to know each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.51,0:30:35.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊  我们没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, no, we haven't.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:37.46,0:30:38.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以  你不了解我的为人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, you don't know who I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:43.60,0:30:45.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道我的妹妹爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know my sister loves you.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.86,0:30:47.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, she does.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.55,0:31:00.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等  你在往哪里开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wait, where are you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:01.38,0:31:02.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这不是去餐厅的方向\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's not the way to Brent's.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:02.68,0:31:04.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想先给你看点东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want to show you something first.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:04.89,0:31:05.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:06.99,0:31:08.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只要几分钟就好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It'll only take a few minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.07,0:31:18.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要去哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where are we going?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.34,0:31:20.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要告诉你一个秘密\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna let you in on a secret.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:21.61,0:31:23.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,本着相互了解的精神\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In the spirit of getting to know each other better.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:33.78,0:31:35.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你要带我去哪  雷扎  -你会知道的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where are you taking me, Reza? - You'll find out.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:36.15,0:31:38.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-现在就说  否则就停车  -是一份惊喜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Tell me now or stop the car. - It's a surprise.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:38.59,0:31:40.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-停车  雷扎  -马上就到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Stop the car, Reza. - We're almost there.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.64,0:31:42.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我说了停车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I said stop the car!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:46.51,0:31:47.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:48.19,0:31:50.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你为什么不告诉我要去哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why won't you tell me where we're going?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:53.40,0:31:54.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想带你来看看这房子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wanted to show you the house.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:55.54,0:31:56.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么房子  -那房子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What house? - The house...
Dialogue: 0,0:31:58.68,0:32:00.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我刚刚买下来  要送给玛丽做结婚礼物\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just bought for Marie as a wedding present.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:03.06,0:32:04.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我希望你第一个看到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wanted you to be the first one to see it.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:16.03,0:32:17.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,退后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stand back.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.03,0:32:19.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  站到一边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, step aside.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:20.83,0:32:22.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们准备量血压\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's get ready to get blood pressure.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.89,0:32:29.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:31.57,0:32:34.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,高压80  低压50  马上给她吊点盐水\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}BP's 80 over 50. Get some saline into her stat.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:34.39,0:32:36.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-她没事吧  -她体内大出血\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Is she all right? - She's haemorrhaging internally.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:36.41,0:32:37.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大梁骨止住了流血\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The girder staunched the bleeding,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.20,0:32:39.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但只要我们一抽掉  就彻底挡不住了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but once we lifted it off, the dam broke.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:40.48,0:32:41.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能止住吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can you stop it?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.43,0:32:43.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我们不送她去急诊室  她就会流血而死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If we don't get her to the ER, she'll bleed to death.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.63,0:32:44.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,准备好了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ready?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:45.39,0:32:47.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,慢点  小心她的脖子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Easy. Watch her neck there.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:49.47,0:32:51.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,动作快点  把她抬出去  各位\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, let's go. Let's get her out, guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.11,0:32:52.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-抬好了  -嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Got it. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:52.02,0:32:53.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一二三\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}One, two, three.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.36,0:32:56.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  慢点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.89,0:32:57.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把她放下来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, set her down.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.15,0:33:01.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们快走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's go, let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.54,0:33:24.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, so...
Dialogue: 0,0:33:24.94,0:33:28.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,立即打电话找个建筑工程师过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}get a structural engineer on the phone and get him over here now.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.04,0:33:29.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,同时  我得让大家继续在这做事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}At the meantime, I have to keep people working at this range.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:29.68,0:33:30.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,出什么事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's going on here?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:30.75,0:33:32.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也正想问你  乔治\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I should ask you the same question, George.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:32.11,0:33:33.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不是不回来了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I thought you weren't coming back here.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:33.33,0:33:35.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我改变主意了  -是吗  为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I changed my mind. - You did? Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:35.58,0:33:37.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不必回答你的问题  你这个态度可以省了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't have to answer to you, so drop the attitute.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:37.35,0:33:38.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她的情况有多严重\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How bad is she?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:38.58,0:33:40.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,情况很严重  她正在内出血\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's bad. She's bleeding internally.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:40.14,0:33:42.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在医院能做的事  在这里也能做吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Anything you can do for the hospital, you can do here, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.05,0:33:43.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不行  她需要做手术\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. She needs surgery.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:43.39,0:33:44.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在外面做不了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We can't do that in field.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:44.38,0:33:46.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你要给她打麻醉药吗  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Are you gonna put her under anaesthesia? - That's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:46.43,0:33:47.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要干什么  乔治\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What you doing, George?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:47.09,0:33:48.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-她会昏迷多久  -几个小时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How long will she be under? - Couple hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:48.83,0:33:50.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那她要留在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, then she stays here.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:50.00,0:33:51.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治  我们不能让她留在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George, we can't keep her here.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:51.19,0:33:52.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们所有在核武器上的资料都被毁了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Everything we have on this nuke has been destroyed.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.99,0:33:56.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在我们只剩下宝拉发给国安局的数据库\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All we have is the database Paula sent to the NSA
Dialogue: 0,0:33:56.12,0:33:57.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是他们没拿到代码\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and they didn't get the code.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:57.45,0:33:59.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我们就派其他的技术部人员去取回的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, then we'll assign other IT people to retrieve it.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:59.79,0:34:01.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她是唯一能破解这些文件的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's the only one who can decrypt the files.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:01.56,0:34:02.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你知道的  -那好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You know it. - All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:02.25,0:34:04.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们派一名和她一起困在里面的程序员去拿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll send a programmer that trapped with her to get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:04.18,0:34:07.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们没时间了  我要她神智清醒待在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We don't have time. I need her here and I need her lucid.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:07.52,0:34:09.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,几分钟就好  我不管你要做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just for a few minutes. I don't care what you have to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:09.75,0:34:10.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能让她醒过来吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can you get her conscious?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:11.87,0:34:15.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我可以注射肾上腺素  暂时让她的血压上升\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can administer epinephrine, maybe get her BP up temporarily.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:15.14,0:34:16.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你疯了  乔治  你疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're out of your mind, George. You're crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:16.75,0:34:18.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果这样能让你好过点  你就自我安慰吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell yourself that if it makes you feel better.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:19.25,0:34:20.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这姑娘应该有活下去的机会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This girl deserves a chance to live.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:22.65,0:34:23.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,弄醒她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wake her up.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.26,0:34:24.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,立刻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:44.45,0:34:45.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我  我们安全了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell me we're clear.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:47.25,0:34:50.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好  我很快会再联系你  拜拜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good. I'll speak to you soon. Bye-bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:50.63,0:34:52.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,长官  这是珍妮对媒体发表的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, this is Jenny's statement to the press
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.97,0:34:54.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反恐组爆炸案声明\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}about the CTU bombing.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:54.86,0:34:55.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我大致看了一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I took a quick pass
Dialogue: 0,0:34:55.68,0:34:58.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有空时  我们可以再看一遍\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but we can go over it whenever you get a chance, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:00.64,0:35:01.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你打算要告诉我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Were you ever gonna tell me?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:09.56,0:35:12.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克·鲍尔打来电话大概三十分钟之后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}About the 30 minutes after Jack Bauer called,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:13.59,0:35:15.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最后你终于警告了反恐组的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and the time you finally warned CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:20.76,0:35:23.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,林恩  我是美国总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lynne, I am the president of the United States.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:25.28,0:35:27.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你真的以为我不会知道吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did you really think I wouldn't find out?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:31.83,0:35:33.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你到底是出于什么原因\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What possible reason could you have
Dialogue: 0,0:35:34.01,0:35:35.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不告诉我这些信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}had for keeping this information from me?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:35.86,0:35:38.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-长官  我试过告诉你  -不够尽力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Sir, I tried to tell you. - Not hard enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.07,0:35:41.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,长官  杰克·鲍尔打来时  你在对付媒体\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, when Jack Bauer called, you were with the press.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:41.84,0:35:43.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想尽一切办法把话带给你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I desperately tried to get a message to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.02,0:35:48.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好  在我们发现反恐组遇袭之后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good. Now, after we found out that CTU had been hit,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:49.11,0:35:52.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你依然不告诉我  你比我早三十分钟知情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you still kept from me the fact that you knew 30 minutes earlier.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:08.48,0:36:10.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,长官  你说得对  没有理由可言\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, you're right. There's no excuse.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:11.65,0:36:12.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,完全没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}None.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:19.32,0:36:21.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在杰克·鲍尔打来后  你有和其他人说过吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}After Jack Bauer called, did you tell anyone else?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:29.23,0:36:30.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你和雷本恩说了是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You told Rayburn, didn't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:32.66,0:36:35.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是他叫你瞒着我的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And he was the one that wanted you to keep it from me.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:36.08,0:36:37.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以你们俩之前在争吵\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's why you two were arguing earlier.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:39.66,0:36:41.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,长官  我想在这种情况下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, I think, under the circumstances,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:42.27,0:36:44.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我最好递交辞呈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it would be best if I tendered my resignation.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:44.19,0:36:45.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我来决定什么是最好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll decide what's best.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:46.65,0:36:47.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当然了  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, of course, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:49.43,0:36:51.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,虽然我很感激你这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As much as I appreciate the gesture,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:52.51,0:36:54.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是我没时间安抚你的内疚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't have time to appease your guilty conscience.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:02.51,0:37:04.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是我依然相信你  林恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I still trust you, Lynne.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:05.94,0:37:08.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我相信你会告诉我所有发生的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I trust you'll tell me everything that happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:11.32,0:37:13.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,出什么事了  她怎么在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's going on? Why is she here?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:14.47,0:37:15.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:17.51,0:37:18.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,宝拉为什么还在这\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why is Paula still here?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:19.32,0:37:20.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是梅森的决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's Mason's call.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:20.70,0:37:23.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我们不立即送她去医院  她就要没命了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She has almost no chance if we don't get her to a hospital now.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:23.98,0:37:24.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:25.17,0:37:27.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-梅森不是不会回来了吗  -他回来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I thought Mason wasn't even coming back. - Well, he's back.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:28.37,0:37:29.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他想要宝拉苏醒得够久\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's trying to revive Paula long
Dialogue: 0,0:37:29.76,0:37:32.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好取得她发送给国安局的信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}enough to access the information she was sending NSA.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:32.90,0:37:34.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以他就这样让她死吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So he's just gonna let her die?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:35.54,0:37:37.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也不确定梅森到底错没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not so sure Mason made the wrong call.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:39.82,0:37:41.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只有宝拉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, Paula is the only person
Dialogue: 0,0:37:41.29,0:37:42.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,才能取回那些信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that can retrieve that information.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:02.58,0:38:04.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm-I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:05.33,0:38:06.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry, Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.41,0:38:13.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是...  是我把她带来反恐组的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's just, I'm the one that brought her to CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:15.37,0:38:16.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我雇了她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I hired her.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.46,0:38:21.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这份工作正是她想要的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This job is all she ever wanted to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:25.29,0:38:26.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她甚至没机会去做了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She never even got a chance to do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:28.69,0:38:29.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她有过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She did.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:38.17,0:38:39.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们还是回去工作吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'd better get back to work.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:57.38,0:38:58.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请跟我们走  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please come with us, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:00.64,0:39:01.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,跟你们去哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come with you where?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:02.35,0:39:03.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统想见你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The President wants to see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:29.68,0:39:30.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:33.38,0:39:35.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你被撤职了  艾瑞克  立即生效\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're out, Eric. Effective immediately.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:36.37,0:39:37.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  如果这是为了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, if this is about...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:37.34,0:39:39.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道是为了什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know exactly what this is about.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:40.38,0:39:41.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你骗了我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You lied to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:42.31,0:39:43.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,林恩是这么跟你说的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's that what Lynne told you.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:43.71,0:39:45.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,林恩什么也不必和我说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lynne didn't have to tell me anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:45.87,0:39:47.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你现在不能撤我的职  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You can't dismiss me now, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.01,0:39:49.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在不行  尤其是发生危机的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not now. Not in the middle of a crisis.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:49.73,0:39:50.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你需要我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You need me here.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:50.93,0:39:52.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要一个我能信任的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need someone I can trust.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:53.60,0:39:56.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我做出一个你无法做出的决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I made a decision that you couldn't make.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:56.11,0:39:58.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只有我才能做出这些决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm the only one who could make it.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:58.81,0:40:00.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在27人死亡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And now 27 people are died.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:00.57,0:40:02.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是附带损伤  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Collateral damage, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:02.43,0:40:04.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,令人遗憾  但却势在必行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Regrettable but necessary,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:04.61,0:40:08.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样鲍尔就能抓到约瑟夫·沃尔德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so that Bauer could get to Joseph Wald.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:13.54,0:40:14.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把他带出去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get him out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:15.17,0:40:16.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿莫斯先生在等着和他谈话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Armus is waiting to talk to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:31.30,0:40:33.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔  接下来的情况是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, Joe, this is how it lays out.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:33.61,0:40:36.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,战术小组两分钟之内就会到达这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tactical team's gonna be here in less than two minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:37.84,0:40:39.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这件事只有两种结束方式\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This thing's gonna end in one of two ways.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:40.50,0:40:41.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要么你死掉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're gonna either be dead
Dialogue: 0,0:40:42.66,0:40:44.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要么你就一辈子在监狱里渡过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}or you're gonna spend the rest of your life in prison.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:45.96,0:40:48.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在我给你最后一次机会做正确的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm giving you one last chance to do the right thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:49.47,0:40:50.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,开门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Open the door.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:52.22,0:40:55.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只要知道是谁叫你去袭击反恐组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just need to know who told you to target CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:59.12,0:41:00.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔  我没时间了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Joe, I'm out of time!
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.68,0:41:04.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔  开门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Joe, open the door!
Dialogue: 0,0:41:07.00,0:41:08.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你个混蛋  乔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're a son of a bitch, Joe.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:52.61,0:41:53.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,放下武器  乔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Drop the weapon, Joe.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:58.57,0:42:00.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把袭击反恐组计划告诉我的女人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The woman who gave me the plans to CTU,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:01.74,0:42:03.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只见过她两次\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I only met her twice.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:05.38,0:42:08.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,第二次  艾迪在街口处拍了些照片\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The second time Eddie took some pictures from down the block.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:09.59,0:42:10.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,放下武器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Drop the weapon!
Dialogue: 0,0:42:12.34,0:42:13.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,结束了  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's over, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:16.04,0:42:17.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不能回去坐牢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't go back to jail.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:18.55,0:42:19.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No!

