[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,1,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.65,0:00:10.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(197.4,200.557)}{\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs25\b1\bord0\shad0\c&H78BDE7&\fad(0,808)}24小时\N\N{\fs15}第二季  第二十三集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.11,0:00:13.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(189.6,121.6,193.8,105.6,0,356)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad3\3c&H2F2F2F&\4c&H336D99&}{\fs10}{\t(0,356,\fs20)\fn方正正中黑简体}前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.93,0:00:16.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,普莱斯考特还要关我到什么时候\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How long will Prescott detain me?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.06,0:00:17.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,到新闻发布会之后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Until after the press conference.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.91,0:00:15.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(126,217.353)}大卫·帕尔默
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.96,0:00:16.00,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(145.2,198.153)}大卫·帕尔默
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.00,0:00:16.04,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(166.2,183.753)}大卫·帕尔默
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.04,0:00:16.08,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(186.6,164)}大卫·帕尔默
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.08,0:00:16.12,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(207.6,147.753)}大卫·帕尔默
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.12,0:00:16.16,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(228.6,130.953)}大卫·帕尔默
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.16,0:00:18.16,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\fad(0,346)\pos(249,110.953)}大卫·帕尔默
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.70,0:00:20.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,两个小时内他会宣布美国对核弹袭击的回应\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In two hours he'll announce our response
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.68,0:00:23.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,以及他就任总统的消息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to the bomb and his ascension to president.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.21,0:00:27.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我受够鲍尔了  他在白费功夫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've done with Bauer. He's chasing a trail that leads nowhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.50,0:00:27.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(294,216.553)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.54,0:00:27.58,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(260.4,195.753)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.58,0:00:27.63,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(226.8,173.353)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.63,0:00:27.67,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(192.6,153.353)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.67,0:00:27.71,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(158.4,131.753)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.71,0:00:29.80,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(126,106.953)\fad(0,353)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.78,0:00:30.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们有其他事要做  你被调职了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're onto other things. You've been reassigned.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.66,0:00:32.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不能现在调我走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You can't reassign me now.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.55,0:00:36.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你让自己变成了我承受不了的负担\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You have made yourself a liability I can't afford.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.05,0:00:39.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是金·鲍尔  我要找我爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is Kim Bauer. I need my dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.86,0:00:42.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-宝贝  怎么啦  -我在马西森家里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What's wrong? - I'm at the Mathesons' house.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.81,0:00:39.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(304.2,222.953)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.85,0:00:39.90,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(274.2,203.753)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.90,0:00:39.94,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(244.8,185.353)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.94,0:00:39.98,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(215.4,166.953)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.98,0:00:40.02,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(184.8,147.753)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.02,0:00:40.06,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(156.6,130.153)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.06,0:00:42.10,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(126.6,111.753)\fad(0,349)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.93,0:00:44.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,加里在这里  他有枪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Gary's here. He has a gun.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.61,0:00:47.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他杀了带我来这里的那个警官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He killed the policeman that brought me.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.04,0:00:48.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要你现在拿枪瞄准他的胸口\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you to point the gun at his chest
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.36,0:00:49.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后扣动扳机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and pull the trigger now.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.07,0:00:53.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他死了吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Is he dead? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.88,0:00:55.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我现在派人去接你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll send someone to pick you up.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.18,0:00:56.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,到楼下去等着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go downstairs and wait for them.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.47,0:00:58.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你能做到吗  --可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Can you do that? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.27,0:01:02.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  我确定塞浦路斯录音是被伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, I can tell you for certain the Cyprus audio has been forged.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.20,0:01:04.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,编造录音的人现在在我手上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have in custody the man who engineered it.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.37,0:01:03.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(308.4,225.353)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.42,0:01:03.46,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(285,211.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.46,0:01:03.50,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(262.2,196.553)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.50,0:01:03.54,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(240.6,182.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.54,0:01:03.58,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(218.4,167.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.58,0:01:03.62,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(195.6,154.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.62,0:01:03.66,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(174.6,139.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.66,0:01:03.71,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(150.6,126.153)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.71,0:01:05.58,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(129,112.553)\fad(0,264)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.48,0:01:06.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很快就把他带过去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll bring him in soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.06,0:01:06.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么展示\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How's it gonna work?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.92,0:01:09.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要给他们做一段录音  当场制作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll make a recording for them, on the spot.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.52,0:01:11.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,调整一下  片段重组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shift it around, reframe segments,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.25,0:01:12.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,和塞浦路斯的参数相同\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}same specs as Cyprus.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.70,0:01:14.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你要去哪里  -这样太慢了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where are you going? - This is taking too long.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.24,0:01:15.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不再相信你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't trust you any more.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.30,0:01:16.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们是唯一可以帮你的人了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're the only ones who can help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.55,0:01:18.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有我们  你一点机会都没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Without us, you don't stand a chance.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.57,0:01:21.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚历克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alex!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.00,0:01:29.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚历克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alex!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.36,0:01:36.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs15\t(696,6577,\fs16)\c&H4BAAAD&\fad(1697,1183)\pos(187.2,191.79)}以下故事情节发生在早晨6点到早晨7点之间
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.01,0:01:38.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.33,0:01:42.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,查普尔怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How's Chappelle doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.29,0:01:44.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还在昏迷中  但是他已经开始颤抖了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Still unconscious, but he's starting to stir.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.10,0:01:46.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我给他的药药效很短\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The drug I gave him is short-acting.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.63,0:01:48.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他还需要更多的药\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He may need more.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.61,0:01:50.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能让他保持昏迷多久\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How long can you keep pumping him full?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.96,0:01:54.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只要等杰克把休伊特送来了就行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We only have to keep him on ice long enough for Jack to deliver Hewitt.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.46,0:01:55.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,直升机的事怎么样了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How are we coming on the chopper?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.66,0:01:57.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,十分钟内就该到达休伊特家了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It should land at Hewitt's in ten minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.83,0:02:00.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-一个半小时之内就能把他带来  -很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- We should have him here in half an hour. - Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.21,0:02:02.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯莉问起查普尔的事了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is Carrie asking about Chappelle?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.82,0:02:03.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not yet, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.52,0:02:06.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,图像处理会让她忙上一段时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Image processing should keep her busy for a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.96,0:02:08.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,打扰一下  阿尔梅达先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Excuse me, Mr. Almeida?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:09.26,0:02:11.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,分局的布拉德·汉蒙德想找到查普尔先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Brad Hammond from Division wants Mr. Chappelle.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.99,0:02:13.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道他在哪吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you know where he is?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.19,0:02:14.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,交给我吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, I'll take it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.01,0:02:18.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是托尼·阿尔梅达  有什么可以帮忙的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is Tony Almeida. How can I help you, sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:18.55,0:02:21.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-莱恩人呢  -我不清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where's Ryan? - Uh, I'm not sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.51,0:02:24.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,办公室的人说他三小时之前就到反恐组了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}His office says he arrived at CTU three hours ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.42,0:02:27.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没有人找到他  -他肯定是出去了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- None of your people can find him. - He must have stepped out.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.73,0:02:31.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有他出门的记录  他有说过要去哪吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He didn't log out. Did he say where he was going?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.19,0:02:34.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没跟我说过  我找到他会立刻告诉您的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not to me, sir, but I'll let you know as soon as I find him.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.56,0:02:37.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  阿尔梅达先生  告诉我发生了什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, Mr. Almeida, you'll tell me what's going on over there.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.53,0:02:41.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道莱恩·查普尔要做情况评估\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know Ryan Chappelle was going to assess the situation.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.18,0:02:42.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想不出他为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I cannot think why
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.28,0:02:45.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要在国家危机的时候失去联系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}he would be out of contact during a national crisis.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:45.05,0:02:46.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,汉蒙德先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Hammond,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.03,0:02:48.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  我所知道的情况已经全部告诉您了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry, I've told you all that I know, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.85,0:02:51.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等莱恩回来一定让他联系您\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll make sure Ryan calls when he returns.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.14,0:02:53.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-就这样吧  -谢谢  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You do that. - Thank you, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.31,0:03:00.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么样  -分局知道出事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What's goin' on? - Division knows something's up.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.87,0:03:02.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们该怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So what are we gonna do?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.60,0:03:05.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要尽快把亚历克斯·休伊特带过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, we got to get Alex Hewitt here as quickly as possible.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.47,0:03:09.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚历克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alex!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.06,0:03:20.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚历克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alex!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.43,0:03:26.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚历克斯  如果你不跟我走的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alex, if you don't come with me,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.98,0:03:29.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金斯利会杀了你的  你知道的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kingsley will kill you. You know that!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.11,0:03:35.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是按他们说的做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just did what they told me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.24,0:03:37.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道会发生什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I didn't know what was gonna happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.15,0:03:47.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你唯一的出路就是让我把你带回反恐组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your only way outta this is to let me take you into CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.58,0:03:51.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你可以和当局做笔交易  出来作证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You can cut a deal, testify!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.35,0:03:55.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚历克斯  你必须要相信我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alex, you're gonna have to trust me!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.86,0:04:01.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚历克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alex!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.73,0:04:21.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚历克斯  别跑了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alex! Stop running!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.41,0:04:31.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚历克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alex!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.63,0:04:35.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚历克斯  听我说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alex, listen to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.68,0:04:37.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,接我们去反恐组的直升机马上就到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A chopper's on its way to take us to CTU,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.82,0:04:39.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那里没人会伤害你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}where no one can hurt you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.02,0:04:42.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,求你了  亚历克斯  帮我结束这张战争\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please, Alex. Help me stop this war
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.54,0:04:44.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会保护你安然无恙的  我保证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and I will help you stay alive, I promise.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.27,0:04:46.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,求你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.03,0:04:50.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚历克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alex!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.25,0:04:52.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,停下  妈的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stop, damn it!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.66,0:05:24.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道昨天港股市场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know the oil stocks closed
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.08,0:05:27.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,石油股票涨停了  马克斯  但是记住\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}high in Hong Kong last night, Max, but remember,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.09,0:05:29.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一旦总统宣布战争开始\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}once the president announces the war,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.96,0:05:31.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,市场马上就会急剧变化\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the margins will change dramatically.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.90,0:05:33.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,价格会立刻上升\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Prices will spike immediately.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.70,0:05:36.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是仍然值得购入所有可购股票\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's still worth acquiring any available shares.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.20,0:05:39.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们的问题处理了吗  -会处理好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Do we still have our problem? - That'll be taken care of.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.64,0:05:42.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-一定要干净利落  -马克斯  放心吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- This must go smoothly. - Max, don't worry about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.53,0:05:45.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我要挂了  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I have to go. - OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.11,0:05:50.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-找到了什么  -所有的录音和数据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What'd you get? - All the recordings and data.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.36,0:05:52.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是没有休伊特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But no Hewitt?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.45,0:05:57.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们尽快赶到  但是我没有时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We got there as soon as we could, but I had no lead time.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.65,0:05:59.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,记住  所有东西  包括休伊特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Remember, everything, including Hewitt,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.45,0:06:01.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,昨天晚上都应该消失\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}was meant to have been vaporised last night.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.11,0:06:03.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不想让那群满脸包的技术宅\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I won't let some pimply-faced
Dialogue: 0,0:06:03.91,0:06:06.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,毁了我们的计划\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}techie ruin everything that we've planned.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.97,0:06:08.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果他被带回去做了证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If he gets brought in and testifies,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.60,0:06:12.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们就无处可逃了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}there's gonna be no place for any of us to hide.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.83,0:06:17.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚历克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alex!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.56,0:07:07.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚历克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alex!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.65,0:07:10.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你没地方可去了  结束了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's nowhere left to run. It's over.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.29,0:07:19.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  你能保证我是安全的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. You... you promise I'll be safe?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.93,0:07:21.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我向你保证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I give you my word.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.77,0:07:28.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚历克斯  把枪放下  放下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alex, drop the gun! Drop the gun!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.23,0:07:30.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你对我开枪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you try to shoot me,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.37,0:07:33.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也对你打回去  而且我肯定不会打偏\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I will have to shoot you back, and I promise I won't miss.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.21,0:07:35.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而我不想这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I don't wanna do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.12,0:07:39.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有你  我们无法阻止这场战争\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't stop this war without you,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.65,0:07:41.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚历克斯  拜托把枪放下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alex. Please, drop the gun.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.87,0:07:43.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托了  把枪放下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please, drop the gun.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.44,0:07:46.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚历克斯  你是个聪明人  好好想想吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alex, you're a smart guy. Think this through.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.60,0:07:50.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是唯一一个能帮你活着度过这一切的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I am the only guy that can get you through this alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.59,0:07:52.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托了  把枪放下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please, drop the gun.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.76,0:07:56.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把枪放下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Drop the gun.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.86,0:08:04.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-亚历克斯  -你打伤了我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Alex... - You shot me!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.13,0:08:07.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你打伤了我  -会没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You shot me! - It's gonna be all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.09,0:08:09.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.19,0:08:20.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚历克斯  亚历克斯  你能听到吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alex, Alex... Can you hear me?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.20,0:08:23.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,冷静点  别动  你会没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, stay calm. Don't move. You're gonna be all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.36,0:08:24.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,千万别动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just don't move.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.07,0:08:26.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么回事  -你摔下来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What happened? - You fell.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.90,0:08:33.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚历克斯  听我说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alex, stay with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.88,0:08:35.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一定要睁着眼睛  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you to keep your eyes open, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.85,0:08:37.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把眼睛睁开  好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just keep your eyes open. OK...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.05,0:08:43.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.11,0:08:46.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,子弹没有伤到动脉  直升机马上就到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The bullet didn't hit an artery. The chopper should be here soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.54,0:08:49.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你不会因为出血过多而死的  -好疼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You're not gonna bleed to death. - It really hurts.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.75,0:08:50.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只要我们一上直升机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna get you something
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.34,0:08:52.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我马上帮你找东西止疼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}for the pain as soon as we get on the chopper.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.97,0:08:59.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你全身上下除了腿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is there any other part of your body
Dialogue: 0,0:08:59.20,0:09:01.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有什么地方疼吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}besides your leg that still hurts?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.57,0:09:04.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没  没有了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, not really.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.86,0:09:10.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  看起来你很幸运  你会没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, good. It looks like you got lucky. You're gonna be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.26,0:09:13.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的头  好像湿了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My head... feels wet.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.80,0:09:19.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,放轻松  放轻松\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just relax. Try and relax.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:26.82,0:09:28.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把头放下来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just put your head down.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.67,0:09:32.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ok.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.50,0:09:52.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我打个电话  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I gotta make a phone call, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.54,0:09:56.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我哪都不去  坚持住\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not goin' anywhere. Stay with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.16,0:10:01.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快接啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.63,0:10:06.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是阿尔梅达\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Almeida.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.56,0:10:07.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是杰克  休伊特受伤了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's Jack. Hewitt's been hurt.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.90,0:10:11.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我现在在屋顶需要紧急医疗救助\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need medical assistance on the roof now.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.27,0:10:12.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,直升机上没有医疗人员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's no EMT on the chopper,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.69,0:10:15.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是有急救箱  你可以吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but there's a med kit. Can you handle it?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.66,0:10:18.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道  希望吧  我要挂了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know. I hope so. Look, I gotta get back to this.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.11,0:10:19.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-等等  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Wait. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.73,0:10:22.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这之后你可能联系不到我了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You may not be able to contact me after this.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.88,0:10:25.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-为什么  -查普尔找我麻烦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Why? - Chappelle became a problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:25.90,0:10:28.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我把他麻晕了  他们盯上我了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I had to take him out of play, and they're onto me.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.38,0:10:32.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他们马上就会带我走的  -我该找谁帮忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- So it's only a matter of time before they take me out. - Who do I contact if I need help?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.75,0:10:35.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我派米歇尔去外面建立一个区外站点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sending Michelle out to the filed to set up an off-site station.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.52,0:10:37.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她可以通过远程访问提供帮助\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She'll do what she can by remote access.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.70,0:10:41.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她有闭路电话  B频道  节点12-12\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She'll be on her closed cell, channel B, node 12-12.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.98,0:10:43.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,B频道12-12  我知道了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}B, node 12-12. I got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.55,0:10:44.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,祝好运  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good luck, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.29,0:10:45.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.79,0:10:48.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚历克斯  你怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alex, how you doin'?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.14,0:11:00.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个能带你上货车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This'll get you into the van.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.92,0:11:03.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要怎么通过防火墙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How will I breakthrough the firewall?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.34,0:11:06.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有几个数据块\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This has a range of a few blocks.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.22,0:11:08.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,用的是霍夫曼编码  能帮你登录\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's Huffman encoded. It'll get you in.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.65,0:11:11.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,准备好了记得给我打个电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Give me a call when you're set, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:18.01,0:11:19.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-米歇尔  -你好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Michelle. - Hi.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.71,0:11:23.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你要去哪  -我要去找我的车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where are you going? - I'm going out to my car.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.16,0:11:25.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你要离开吗  -没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Are you leaving? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.58,0:11:28.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是想去拿点东西再回来  有问题吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm just getting something and come back. Is there a problem?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.42,0:11:31.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你见到查普尔了吗  -没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Have you seen Chappelle? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.50,0:11:35.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我所有地方都找过了  还是没有找到他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've looked everywhere and I can't find him.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.23,0:11:38.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我看到他  会告诉他你在找他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If I see him, I'll tell him you're looking for him.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.03,0:11:42.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你没见到他呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And if you don't see him?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.11,0:11:45.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你这是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's that supposed to mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.40,0:11:50.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的工作是监视这周围的联络\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My job is to monitor communications around here.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.68,0:11:52.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你以为我不知道发生了什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't think I know what's goin' on?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.33,0:11:54.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不如你告诉我吧  凯莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why don't you tell me, Carrie?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.22,0:11:58.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你把查普尔带过来见卢丁  我跟卢丁谈过了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You called Chappelle in to see Rudin. I just talked to Rudin.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.82,0:12:00.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他什么都不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He doesn't know anything about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.27,0:12:03.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他当然会这么说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, of course he told you that.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.66,0:12:06.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他的系统不能顺利加载都是因为你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}His system wasn't loaded properly and it was your fault.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:07.80,0:12:10.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他想找查普尔抱怨你的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He wanted to see Chappelle to complain about you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.46,0:12:15.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别瞎管闲事  凯莉  这样你才能好好工作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stay out of my business, Carrie. You'll do a better job.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.87,0:12:31.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,布莱恩  你怎么发现我的事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Brian. How did you find out about me?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.88,0:12:34.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,司法部长说你想让我做你的律师\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The Attorney General said you'd want me for your counsel.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.85,0:12:36.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们告诉你什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What have they told you?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.02,0:12:37.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你因为第二十五号修正案\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You'd been removed from office by the cabinet
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.31,0:12:40.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,被内阁弹劾了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}under the capacity closet of 25th Amendment.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.83,0:12:44.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他们的做法是合法的吗  -准确来说是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Is what they did legal? - Technically, yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.42,0:12:47.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,宪法准许内阁可以宣布总统失职\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The Constitution gives the cabinet the right to declare the president incompetent
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.11,0:12:50.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不用进一步的解释或说明\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}without further definition or clarification.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.98,0:12:53.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这也给了我上诉的权力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That also gives me the right to appeal that decision.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.53,0:12:55.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  我会全力以赴\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, which I will do vigorously.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.17,0:12:58.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不幸的是  这过程很花时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Unfortunately, it's a lengthy process.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.23,0:12:59.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们没有时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We don't have time.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.94,0:13:01.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道如何加快进程  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know how to make it go any faster, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.06,0:13:04.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  那些法律都不重要  布莱恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, none of those legalities matter, Brian.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.95,0:13:06.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,基于我现在确信是错误的证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This country's about to go to war
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.14,0:13:08.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个国家即将开战\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}based on evidence that I am now convinced is false.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.82,0:13:11.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是在这间屋子以外没有人会相信\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Except no one outside this room believes that.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.89,0:13:15.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,证据被一个叫彼得·金斯利的家伙篡改了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The evidence was manipulated by a man named Peter Kingsley.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.57,0:13:17.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你竭尽所能调查他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need you to find out everything you can about him.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.22,0:13:20.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你得明白  麦克·诺维克在约束我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You have to understand Mike Novick's tying my hands.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.57,0:13:23.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想尽办法摆脱他的束缚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get him to untie them, whatever you have to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.04,0:13:25.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.04,0:13:31.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-阿尔梅达  -是我  我已就位\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Almeida. - It's me, I'm in place.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.63,0:13:33.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你在哪里  -我在北边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where are you? - I'm in the North lot.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.00,0:13:37.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,15A号车  托尼  凯莉盯上我们了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Van 15 A. Listen, Tony, Carrie's onto us.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.56,0:13:40.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-她在找夏普尔  -你怎么跟她说的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- She was asking about Chappelle. - What did you tell her?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.55,0:13:42.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我说  我不知道她在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That I didn't know what she's talking about,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.69,0:13:44.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我们需要摆脱她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but we need her out of the way.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.36,0:13:45.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,分散她的注意力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Keep her occupied.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.36,0:13:47.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  我会处理  你准备好联系杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, I'll handle it. Look, set up and get ahold of Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.53,0:13:49.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得挂了  汉蒙德来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I gotta go. Hammond's here.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.69,0:13:54.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-汉蒙德先生  -托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Mr. Hammond. - Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:54.92,0:13:56.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有什么事吗  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you doing here, sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.33,0:13:57.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在电话里跟你说过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I told you on the phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.88,0:14:01.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想这里有问题  莱恩·查普尔在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think there's a problem here. Where's Ryan Chappelle?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.28,0:14:05.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我还没有见到他  先生  -我明白了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I haven't seen him yet, sir. - I see.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.22,0:14:07.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们两个去查这边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Two of you take this side.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.74,0:14:10.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好好查这个区域\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want this section covered.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.35,0:14:11.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.22,0:14:13.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你在干什么  -我要封锁你们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What are you doin'? - I'm locking you down.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.21,0:14:15.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,封锁我们吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Locking us down?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.56,0:14:16.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先生  我们正在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, we're in the middle of
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.40,0:14:18.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为这场战争做反应准备\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}preparing a domestic response to this war.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.37,0:14:19.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我听到的并非如此\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's not what I heard.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.89,0:14:20.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我听说你们在违反分局的命令\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I heard you were supporting
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.69,0:14:23.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,支持一个不听命令的探员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}a rogue agent against division orders.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.25,0:14:26.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你从哪里听说的  -你们的一个内部人员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where'd you hear that? - One of your own people.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.02,0:14:30.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,走  查清楚这里的每一个角落\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's go. Cover every square inch of the place!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.67,0:14:44.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  先生  我知道了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes sir, I'm aware of that.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.34,0:14:46.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们需要那个至关重要的领空飞越\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That flyover space is critical.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.09,0:14:48.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-大卫会帮我们吗  -我不知道  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Do you think David will help us? - I don't know, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.39,0:14:49.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.97,0:14:53.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们可能很难与他沟通\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't see us having much success with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.76,0:14:55.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们需要他的帮助  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We need this, Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.07,0:14:56.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  先生  我会努力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir, I'll try.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.98,0:14:58.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How is he?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.96,0:15:00.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大卫仍然确信他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}David remains convinced that his decision
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.57,0:15:02.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,推迟轰炸的决定是正确的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to hold off on the bombers was the correct one.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.87,0:15:05.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他将对免职进行强烈上诉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And he'll vigorously appeal his removal from office.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.32,0:15:06.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,第二十五修正案让他有了这个权力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The 25th Amendment gives him that right.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.53,0:15:07.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为他的上诉  我们会证明\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thanks to that appeal, we'll prove
Dialogue: 0,0:15:07.75,0:15:08.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们是被利用参战的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we're being manipulated into this war
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.91,0:15:11.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,塞浦路斯的录音是被伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and that the Cyprus recording was falsified,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.69,0:15:14.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而且我们现在知道是谁伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}plus we now think we know by whom.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.24,0:15:19.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你说说看  -一个叫彼得·金斯利的家伙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'm listening. - A man named Peter Kingsley.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.70,0:15:22.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他与国内外的石油利益都有联系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's got ties to oil interests both here and abroad.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.12,0:15:24.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有找到任何证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Have you found anything to
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.24,0:15:26.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,将他与塞浦路斯的录音\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}connect him to the Cyprus recording,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.15,0:15:27.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,或是轰炸联系起来吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}or the bomb for that matter?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.66,0:15:29.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有  我们进不去情报数据库\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. We won't be able to
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.27,0:15:31.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以没法找联系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}without access to the intelligence database.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.99,0:15:33.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大卫会被封锁直至\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}David's locked down until
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.31,0:15:35.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们公开军事行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we've gone public with the military action.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.87,0:15:38.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那个时候太迟了  -我很遗憾\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- By then it'll be too late. - I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.40,0:15:40.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,麦克  等等  等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mike, wait. Just hold on a second.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.59,0:15:41.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还记得20多年前你报名参加\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I remember when you signed up for
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.54,0:15:44.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大卫的第一次参议员竞选\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}David's first run at the Senate over 20 years ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.57,0:15:49.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不能就这样不念旧情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's... that's a lot of history to just throw out the window.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.67,0:15:54.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托了  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.43,0:15:58.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道你只是在做你认为是正确的事情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know you just did what you thought was right,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.02,0:16:00.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但让他试着证明他的立场吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but let him try to prove his case.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.78,0:16:03.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是你欠他的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You owe him that.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.34,0:16:15.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会让科琳为你准备一个工作站\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll have Colleen set up a computer station for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.91,0:16:19.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你无法向外发送信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You won't be able to transmit outgoing messages.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.62,0:16:20.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这够公平了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's fair enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.05,0:16:25.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里面是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's in here?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.82,0:16:28.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是我们的两间拘留室之一  现在没人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}One of our two holding rooms. No one's in there right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:30.31,0:16:31.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.63,0:16:45.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这间呢  -这是另一间拘留室\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- And this? - The other holding room.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.23,0:16:49.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,它不该被锁着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It shouldn't be locked.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.08,0:16:56.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么回事  -肯定有人重置了密码\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What's wrong? - Someone must have reconfigured the lock.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.30,0:17:05.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,救命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Help.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.07,0:17:16.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快  亚历克斯  继续跟我讲话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, Alex. Keep talking to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.99,0:17:21.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一切都...有点模糊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Everything's... a little blurry.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.78,0:17:24.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's happening to me?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.61,0:17:29.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事  你撞到头了  会没事的  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nothing. You just banged your head. It's gonna be all right, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.96,0:17:31.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,坚持住\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You just hang in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.56,0:17:39.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚历克斯  我听到了  他们正在过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alex, I can hear 'em. They're coming, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.10,0:17:41.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,救援马上就来  坚持住  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Help's on the way. Just hang in there, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.99,0:17:55.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,夏普尔先生  我已找到托尼·阿尔梅达\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Chappelle, I've located the CTU chopper
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.11,0:17:56.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给杰克·鲍尔派去的反恐组直升机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that Tony Almeida sent to Jack Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.79,0:17:59.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们正在降落  你想让他们拘留鲍尔吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're landing now. Would you like to have them to detain Bauer?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:59.70,0:18:03.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  我不想再在他身上浪费任何资源了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, I don't wanna waste any more resources on him.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.52,0:18:05.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让直升机回来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just get the chopper back here.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.85,0:18:09.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  保罗  夏普尔先生要你们马上回来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah Paul, Mr. Chappelle wants you to come back now.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.24,0:18:11.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们正准备降落  -我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- We're about to land. - Yeah, I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.11,0:18:12.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我能看到他...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can see him...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:12.01,0:18:13.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不用管他  照我说的做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It doesn't matter. Just do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.44,0:18:24.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们在等什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you waiting for?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.65,0:18:26.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我在降落  -不  取消降落\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'm putting her down. - No, cancel that.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.70,0:18:30.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,马上降落直升机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Land the chopper now!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.48,0:18:36.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们在干什么  快降落\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you doing?! Land the damn chopper!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.59,0:18:42.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的证人要死了  快降落\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My witness is gonna die! Land!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.63,0:18:52.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们是受令来接我们的  快下来接我们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your orders are to pick us up! Pick us up now!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.78,0:18:55.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Damn it!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.08,0:19:00.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是德斯勒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Dessler.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.52,0:19:02.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔  到底发生什么事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle, what the hell is going on here?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.35,0:19:03.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,直升机不肯降落来接我们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The chopper won't pick us up.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.71,0:19:04.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们召回了直升机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They recalled the chopper.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.90,0:19:06.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-汉蒙德封锁了我们  -我不管\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Hammond's locked us down. - I don't give a damn!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.96,0:19:09.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让直升机回来  休伊特快不行了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get me that chopper back! Hewitt is dying!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:16.63,0:19:17.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚历克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alex.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.85,0:19:39.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,需要我来处理阿尔梅达吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Want me to deal with Almeida?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.63,0:19:42.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不用了  布拉德  谢谢  我自己处理他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, Brad, thanks. I'll take care of him myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.30,0:19:47.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-米歇尔  是我  -杰克  你在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Michelle, it's me. - Jack, where are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.37,0:19:49.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在回休伊特住所的路上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm on my way back to Hewitt's loft.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.78,0:19:53.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要你准备好与他的电脑对接\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you to set up and be ready to interface with his computer.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.12,0:19:57.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-休伊特怎么样了  -他没挺过来  死了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What about Hewitt? - He didn't make it. He's dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.58,0:19:58.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  我很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.52,0:20:00.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,准备好就打给我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Call me when you're ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.34,0:20:11.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么事  -我要跟你谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yes? - I need to speak with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.24,0:20:14.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这事关国家安全\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It concerns national security.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:14.75,0:20:16.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我已不再是总司令\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As I am not the commander in chief any more,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.77,0:20:18.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不明白这事跟我有什么关系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't see how that could be relevant.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.56,0:20:20.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们跟土耳其政府有点问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have a problem with the Turkish government.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.15,0:20:23.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们的隐身轰炸机已接近他们的领空\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Our stealth bombers are nearing their airspace,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.13,0:20:25.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不幸的是  几分钟前  轰炸机被\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}unfortunately, one of their fighter patrols
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.13,0:20:27.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们的一架巡逻战斗机发现了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}spotted them a few minutes ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.03,0:20:30.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那就向他们的首相申请飞过领空\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So ask the prime minister for the flyover.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.17,0:20:31.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他应该会同意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He should agree.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.13,0:20:33.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,国务卿已跟他谈过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The secretary of state has spoken to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.63,0:20:36.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他说需要一个条件才能同意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And he said he would grant us this under one condition.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.48,0:20:37.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么条件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's the condition?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.77,0:20:41.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他需要总统的个人请求和保证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He wants a personal request and assurances from the president.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.88,0:20:45.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,首相还不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The prime minister hasn't been told
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.39,0:20:46.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我已被免职\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that I've been removed from office.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.19,0:20:49.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他不能比美国人民更先知道  不可能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That couldn't happen not before the American people. No
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.83,0:20:52.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对  现在这样做不合适  是吗  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, that wouldn't be right now, would it, Mike?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.35,0:20:55.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,既然现在轰炸机已被发现\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now that the bombers have been spotted,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.83,0:20:56.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那它们就更得\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it's more critical than ever
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.96,0:20:59.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,迅速到达目标\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that they get to their targets quickly.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.66,0:21:02.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,任何绕道都会让他们进入地方领空\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Any detour will take them over unfriendly skies.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.38,0:21:06.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以你想让我假装我还是总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So you want me to speak to the prime minister,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.36,0:21:10.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去跟首相谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}under the pretence that I'm still the president?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.80,0:21:11.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:13.00,0:21:16.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,轰炸机的任务无论如何都将继续执行  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This mission is going to continue regardless, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.45,0:21:18.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不管这通电话有多令人厌恶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This phone call, no matter how distasteful,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.52,0:21:21.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能防止那些轰炸机被袭击\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you could prevent those planes from being attacked.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.61,0:21:24.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们只有几分钟的时间  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We only have minutes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.04,0:21:40.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你为什么丢下我这副模样不管  我被捅伤了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why did you leave me like this? I've been stabbed!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.28,0:21:42.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我看看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me look at it.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.64,0:21:45.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,小心点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Be careful.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.72,0:21:49.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你很幸运  伤口很浅\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're lucky. The wound's superficial.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.08,0:21:51.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,已经止血了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The bleeding's already stopped.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.06,0:21:53.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我给你拿干净的绷带\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll get you a clean bandage for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.19,0:21:59.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-亚历克斯在哪里  -他摔下楼顶  死了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where's Alex? - He fell. He's dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.82,0:22:02.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天呐  现在怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, my god. What happens now?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.91,0:22:05.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要帮我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You are going to help me.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:06.40,0:22:08.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,用绷带压住这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just put this right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.10,0:22:12.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-帮你干什么  -我们还有最后一种办法\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Help you do what? - We got one last play.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.74,0:22:15.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-找出金斯利  -不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- To deliver Kingsley. - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.67,0:22:20.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他太危险了  你没法接近他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's far too dangerous, and you'll never get close to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.45,0:22:23.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你说得对  我做不到  但你可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're right. I won't, but you will.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.10,0:22:26.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金斯利不知道休伊特已经死了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kingsley doesn't know Hewitt's been killed.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.04,0:22:27.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你如果说你可以交出休伊特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you say you can deliver him,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.73,0:22:29.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,应该会引起他的注意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that should get us his attention.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.34,0:22:30.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.05,0:22:31.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金斯利有证据可以证明我有罪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kingsley has evidence that will implicate me.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.86,0:22:33.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我绝不会这样做...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There is no way I'm gonna do this...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.32,0:22:34.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,帕尔默女士  你要...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mrs. Palmer, you're gonna...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.55,0:22:39.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.45,0:22:43.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没什么  我没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's nothing. I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.17,0:22:47.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别跟我说没事  发生什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't tell me it's nothing. What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.84,0:22:56.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金斯利的人在审我时  我的心脏骤停了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My heart stopped when Kingsley's men were interrogating me.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.17,0:23:00.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的心脏可能受到了损伤  你得去看医生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your heart could be damaged. You need to get to a doctor.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.79,0:23:02.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们得先找到金斯利\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We need to get Kingsley first.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.96,0:23:07.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,帕尔默女士  你要帮我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mrs. Palmer, you are going to help me.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.34,0:23:09.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你别无选择\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not gonna give you another choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.76,0:23:12.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不敢伤害我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You wouldn't dare hurt me.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.92,0:23:16.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别误会  我会不择手段\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Make no mistake about it. I will do what I have to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.30,0:23:23.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要我做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you want me to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.23,0:23:26.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要你告诉金斯利  你会用休伊特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you to tell Kingsley that you'll exchange Hewitt
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.91,0:23:29.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,换取他能证明你有罪的任何证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}for any evidence that he has incriminates you.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.01,0:23:31.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他会要我证明休伊特在我手上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He'll want proof that I have Hewitt.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.61,0:23:34.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没问题  -怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- He'll get it. - How?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.09,0:23:37.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,休伊特会跟他说话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hewitt's gonna talk to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.54,0:23:42.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,目前  我们可以推断\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}At this point, we can assume
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.97,0:23:45.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,包含源录音的芯片\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the chip containing the source recordings
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.01,0:23:47.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还没有落入政府之手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}has not landed in government hands.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.58,0:23:49.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你拦截了那个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did you intercept the federal agent
Dialogue: 0,0:23:49.52,0:23:51.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,持有芯片的联邦探员吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to who was in possession of the chip?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.63,0:23:55.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有  但既然轰炸机还在规定路线上飞行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. But since the bombers are still on course,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.94,0:23:59.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那就能推断  他没能将芯片交给总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we can assume that he wasn't able to deliver it to the president.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.72,0:24:02.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因此休伊特就是最后的漏网之鱼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Which leaves Hewitt as the last remaining loose end.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.97,0:24:04.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,找他的事进展如何\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where are we on finding him?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.22,0:24:07.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我派出了几队人马去找他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have several teams out looking for him.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.65,0:24:11.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他绝不能走漏风声\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He cannot be allowed to talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.19,0:24:13.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在不能  将来也不能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not now, nor ever.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.30,0:24:17.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们会找到休伊特并除掉他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hewitt will be found, and he'll be eliminated.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.44,0:24:18.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,斩草除根  彼得\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Clean this up, Peter.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.98,0:24:30.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再检查一遍  即使你需要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go over it again, even if you
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.67,0:24:33.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,找几个探员来帮你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}need to pull a couple of agents in to help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.69,0:24:48.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不必告诉你  你被逮捕了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't need to tell you you're under arrest.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.38,0:24:50.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔·德斯勒在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where's Michelle Dessler?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.99,0:24:52.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她对此一无所知\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She didn't know nothing about this.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.91,0:24:55.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她把我叫进了那间屋子让你给我下药\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She called me to the room where you drugged me.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.17,0:24:56.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她不知道我要这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She didn't know what I was gonna do.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.66,0:25:01.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要发逮捕令  联系当地警方  发布通知\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need to issue a warrant. Contact local police, issue a memo.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.01,0:25:04.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我能找到她  -怎么找\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I can find her. - How?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.65,0:25:07.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这一切都是为了帮助杰克·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This whole thing's been about helping Jack Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.69,0:25:11.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她不在这里  是因为她在外面的某处帮他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's not here because she's doing that somewhere off-site.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.06,0:25:14.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-要怎么找到她  -反追踪她的访问代码\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How do we find her? - Back track her access code.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.11,0:25:16.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看看她是否登录了反恐组的计算机网络\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}See if she's logged onto the CTU computer network.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.03,0:25:19.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-就这么办吧  -马上去做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Then do it. - Right away.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.85,0:25:23.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,带他去二号拘留室\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Put him in holding 2.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.81,0:25:46.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-喂  -杰克  我连上休伊特的电脑了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yeah? - Jake, I'm connected to Hewitt's computer.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.78,0:25:49.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只要你按退出  我就能操控了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just need you to press "Escape" and I can take control.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.24,0:25:52.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好了  -休伊特和你说了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Done. - What did Hewitt tell you?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.05,0:25:54.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他和我说他编了一个程序\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He told me he invented a program
Dialogue: 0,0:25:54.29,0:25:55.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能再现任何人的声音\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that could recreate anybody's voice.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.89,0:25:57.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只要有那个人的声音样本\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As long as you have sample with that voice,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.30,0:25:59.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想让程序说什么都行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you could get it to say anything you wanted.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.29,0:26:02.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他说他把所有的音频文件都在放一个主文件里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He told me he kept all the audio files in a main file.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:06.46,0:26:07.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我好像找到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, I think I've found it.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:11.30,0:26:12.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我头一回看到这种东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've never seen this before.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.64,0:26:14.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所有的样本都跟合成器连在一起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All the samples connect through an integrator.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.78,0:26:17.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只需要有休伊特声音的音频就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, all I need is anything with Hewitt's voice on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.23,0:26:18.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, hold on.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:22.18,0:26:24.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要伯克利和威尔克一起出席那顿午餐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna need Berkeley and Wilkerson at that lunch.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:24.46,0:26:26.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我得改到一点钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have to change to 1 o'clock then.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.13,0:26:28.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-是他吗  -不是  该死的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Is that him? - No, damn it.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.65,0:26:30.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里有上百个文件  等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's hundreds of files. Hold on one second.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.97,0:26:33.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,帕尔默夫人  你什么时候打给休伊特的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mrs. Palmer, when did you call Hewitt?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.87,0:26:36.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,昨晚半夜左右  怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Last night, around midnight. Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:37.53,0:26:38.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他也许录了音\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He might have recorded it.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.93,0:26:39.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.10,0:26:42.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能根据时间和日期筛选音频文件吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}can you filter through the audio files by time and date?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.74,0:26:43.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我看看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me see...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.68,0:26:45.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.60,0:26:48.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你看看能不能找到一个音频文件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, see if you can put an audio file that was recorded
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.06,0:26:50.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是在昨晚或是凌晨  大约午夜时分录下的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the late last night or early this morning, right around midnight.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.63,0:26:54.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,肯定是这个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This must be it.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.02,0:27:00.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-喂  -是亚历克斯·休伊特吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Hello? - Alex Hewitt?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:00.48,0:27:02.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你是哪位  -是他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Who's this? - That's him.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.15,0:27:03.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是雪莉·帕尔默\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sherry Palmer.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.60,0:27:05.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-必须让音频播放  -总统的前妻吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- We have to let it run. - President's ex-wife?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.63,0:27:06.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你打给我有什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you calling me for?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:07.73,0:27:11.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道你和彼得·金斯利的关系  亚历克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know all about your relationship with Peter Kingsley, Alex.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.93,0:27:13.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不认识叫彼得·金斯利的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know anyone named Peter Kingsley.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:13.74,0:27:17.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还知道你录下了他所有的手机通话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I also know you that had all his phone conversations recorded.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.04,0:27:19.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我问问你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me ask you.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:19.52,0:27:23.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是为了自保  还是为了勒索他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Was that to protect yourself or to blackmail him?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.99,0:27:25.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事的  亚历克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's OK, Alex.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.30,0:27:29.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我是来帮你的  -谁说我需要帮忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'm here to help you. - Who says I need help?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.39,0:27:32.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,彼得以为你今天会和所有人一起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Peter thought you would die in Los Angeles
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.81,0:27:33.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,死在洛杉矶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}with everybody else today.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.23,0:27:35.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,既然你没死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now that you haven't,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.99,0:27:37.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他会来找你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}he's gonna come after you.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:38.70,0:27:42.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听我说  我可以保护你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So listen to me, and I can protect you.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:42.29,0:27:44.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,程序显示我们已经有足够的材料\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, program says we have enough material
Dialogue: 0,0:27:44.17,0:27:45.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来创建语音模板\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to create a phonetic template.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.33,0:27:46.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好  我们要怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, good. What do we do?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.98,0:27:48.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只要打开生成文件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All we have to do is open up a Gen file
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.29,0:27:50.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,输入我们想要说的话就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and type in the phrases we want voiced.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.43,0:27:53.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么叫打开生成文件  米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you mean, open a Gen file, Michelle?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.91,0:27:56.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他创建了一个单独的回放程序模块\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He created a separate program module for playback.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.06,0:27:57.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只要找出模块下面的选项单就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All we have to find out what menu it's under.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.21,0:28:01.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我要找的是什么  -这辆没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What am I looking for? - It's not here.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:02.48,0:28:04.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,找一个叫做序幕的子程序\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Try a subroutine called Prologue.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:05.88,0:28:06.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就是这辆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's this one.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.09,0:28:08.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们找到我了  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They've found me, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.42,0:28:10.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,正在加载\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, it's loading.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.82,0:28:12.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我现在要找什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What am I looking for now?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.34,0:28:14.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一个像回放图形界面的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Something that looks like a playback graphic interface.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.46,0:28:15.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们就快进来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're almost here.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.25,0:28:16.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-下车  -等等  米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Come out of the van! - Hold on, Michelle.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:17.49,0:28:18.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hold on.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:21.03,0:28:22.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,女士  双手离开键盘\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ma'am, hands off the keyboard.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.76,0:28:24.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-明白吗  -我找到了  米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- See? - OK, I've got it. Michelle!
Dialogue: 0,0:28:24.09,0:28:25.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-要我她带回去吗  -米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Do you want me to take her in? - Michelle!
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.83,0:28:26.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,知道了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.33,0:28:30.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,确认  中央调度  我们已经将她扣押\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, affirmative, Central. She's in custody.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.71,0:28:34.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请讲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:01.19,0:29:03.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你好  希瑟  -总统先生好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Hello, Heather. - Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.18,0:29:06.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.72,0:29:07.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没关系  希瑟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's all right, Heather.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.64,0:29:23.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-总统先生  我们准备好了  -大卫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Mr. President, we're ready. - David.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:24.52,0:29:27.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道这种情况很尴尬\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I realise how awkward this is.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.61,0:29:29.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,希望麦克和你说了  我们非常感谢你帮忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I hope Mike has told you how much we appreciate your help.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.92,0:29:32.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不要搞错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Make no mistake.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.20,0:29:35.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我认为你们正在犯下严重的悲剧性错误\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I believe you're making a gross and tragic error.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.27,0:29:39.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我这么做是为了飞机上的那些人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm doing this for the men in those planes.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.82,0:29:47.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.35,0:29:49.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们这边准备好了  你可以接通总理电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're ready here, you can patch in the prime minister.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:49.27,0:29:49.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:53.97,0:29:56.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-总理先生  -你好  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Mr. Prime Minister. - Hello, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:56.92,0:29:59.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我一直想和你联系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've been trying to reach you for some time.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.59,0:30:07.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kim?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:12.60,0:30:13.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kim!
Dialogue: 0,0:30:24.40,0:30:25.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:36.05,0:30:36.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:41.43,0:30:42.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kim?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:53.15,0:30:53.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kim?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.81,0:31:15.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你是什么人  -我叫凯特·华纳\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Who are you? - I'm Kate Warner.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.24,0:31:17.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你父亲叫我来接你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your father sent me to come get yeou.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.17,0:31:20.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我怎么知道真假\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How do I know that?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:21.88,0:31:22.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:24.08,0:31:26.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你开枪打死了进屋袭击你的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You shot a man who came in here to attack you.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:27.13,0:31:28.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是自卫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was self-defence.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.50,0:31:32.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你父亲杰克·鲍尔打电话给我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your father, Jack Bauer, called me,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:32.64,0:31:34.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,叫我来接你  带你去反恐组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}asked me to come get you, take you to CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.31,0:31:38.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不然我怎么会知道那些事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How else would I know all of that?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:42.63,0:31:44.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你怎么认识我爸的  你在反恐组工作吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How do you know my dad? Do you work at CTU?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:45.87,0:31:49.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不在  我家人和今天的发生的事有关\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. My family was involved with what happened today.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:51.01,0:31:54.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我爸为什么会叫一个他刚认识的人来接我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why would my dad send someone he'd just met to come get me?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:57.91,0:31:59.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他信任我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He trusts me.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.76,0:32:03.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托  金\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, Kim.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:05.71,0:32:06.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:16.33,0:32:16.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们越早离开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The sooner we leave,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:16.94,0:32:21.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你和你爸就越早能团聚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the sooner you and your dad can be together, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.44,0:32:57.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你觉得他们会以什么罪名起诉我们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you think they'll charge us with?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:59.67,0:33:01.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果他们想  要冠上叛国罪都行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They could push for treason if they wanted to.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:03.86,0:33:04.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你觉得他们会吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Think they will?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:05.78,0:33:08.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,取决于他们有多想拿我们来以儆效尤\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Depends on how big of an example they wanna make of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:12.99,0:33:14.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, Michelle...
Dialogue: 0,0:33:15.45,0:33:16.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没人能证明\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}no one can prove
Dialogue: 0,0:33:16.12,0:33:18.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道我要对查普尔采取行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that you knew anything about what I was gonna do to Chappelle.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.56,0:33:20.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会和他们说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And now I'm just gonna tell them
Dialogue: 0,0:33:20.64,0:33:24.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是我下令让你去帮杰克的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you were helping Jack under my orders, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:27.59,0:33:28.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:30.23,0:33:31.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么叫不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you mean, no?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:32.69,0:33:34.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我做了我觉得是正确的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I did what I thought was right.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:35.43,0:33:36.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我现在还坚信这点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I still believe that.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:38.84,0:33:40.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不会让你替我撒谎的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I won't let you lie for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:19.19,0:34:20.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大卫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}David...
Dialogue: 0,0:34:23.43,0:34:27.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你  我知道这对你来说有多不容易\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you. I know how difficult it must have been for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:29.91,0:34:32.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,普莱斯考特还要把我关在这里多久\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How much longer will Prescott keep me here?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:32.40,0:34:34.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,直到记者招待会之后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Until after the press conference.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.15,0:34:35.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我已经要求尽快释放你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've requested you be released sooner,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.97,0:34:38.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我能做的事有限\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but there's only so much I can do.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.37,0:34:44.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我见过布莱恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I spoke to Brian.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:44.74,0:34:48.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他代表你要求了一些低安全性访问权\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He requested some low-security access on your behalf.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.04,0:34:50.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想你知道我同意了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wanted you to know I granted it.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:30.85,0:35:33.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你和我爸是怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So what's going on with you and my dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:34.02,0:35:34.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Excuse me?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:37.45,0:35:39.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他有这么多人可以找  但是他却找了你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Out of everyone he could have called, he called you.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:41.61,0:35:43.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,肯定是有原因的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's gotta be a reason.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:45.40,0:35:47.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得他信任的人不多\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't think he trusts very many people.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:51.19,0:35:52.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是他信任你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He trusts you.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:57.06,0:35:58.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们真的只是今天认识的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is it true you guys just met today?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:00.10,0:36:03.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,其实是昨天  但是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yesterday really, but yeah, it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:07.79,0:36:10.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我并不是生气  我只是...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't resent it or anything. I just...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:12.23,0:36:13.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,希望他开心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}want him to be happy.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:14.98,0:36:17.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他很久都没开心过了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's been a long time.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:19.89,0:36:21.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,自从你母亲过世后吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Since you lost your mother?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.04,0:36:26.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.53,0:36:32.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我母亲也过世了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I lost my mother too.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:34.89,0:36:36.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我当时和你一样大\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When I was about your age.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.58,0:36:46.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我真的觉得我做不了  -你可以的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I really don't think I can do this. - You'll do fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:46.00,0:36:48.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把我和你说的话都告诉他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just tell him everything I told you to say.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:49.26,0:36:50.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,打电话吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Make the call.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:57.25,0:36:58.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,明白\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Understood.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.41,0:37:03.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还是没有找到休伊特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Still no sign of Hewitt.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:11.29,0:37:12.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,喂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:12.93,0:37:14.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是雪莉·帕尔默  彼得\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's Sherry Palmer, Peter.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:16.20,0:37:19.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-通话安全吗  -当然安全\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Are we on a secure line? - Of course we are.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:20.05,0:37:22.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要你录下我们对话的带子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want the tapes that you made of our conversation,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:23.04,0:37:24.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要原始的数字录音带\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want the original DATs.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:25.59,0:37:27.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我为什么会同意把带子交给你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And why would I agree to give you those?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:27.91,0:37:30.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为作为交换  我会交出亚历克斯·休伊特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because I'll give you Alex Hewitt in return.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.58,0:37:34.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你找到休伊特了  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You've found Hewitt? - That's right.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:36.83,0:37:37.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where is he?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:39.02,0:37:41.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别侮辱我的智商  彼得\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't insult my intelligence, Peter.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:41.17,0:37:42.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,同意做交换\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Agree to the exchange,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:42.43,0:37:44.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后他就交给你随意处置\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}then you can do whatever you want with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:48.51,0:37:49.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要和他说两句\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want to talk to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:50.84,0:37:51.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你要等等了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You'll have to hold on.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.96,0:37:54.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的保镖把他关在隔壁房间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My bodyguard has him restrained in the next room.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:01.05,0:38:02.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\frz358.8\move(170.4,84,176.4,90.4)}{\fn方正准圆_GBK\fs12\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H848D7C&}音频文件已生成
Dialogue: 0,0:38:04.15,0:38:05.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚历克斯  你可以说话了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, Alex, you can talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.39,0:38:10.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金斯利先生  事情不是你想的那样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Kingsley, it's not what you think.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.22,0:38:13.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们拿着枪进来  威胁说要杀了我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They came in here with guns and threatened to kill me.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:13.07,0:38:15.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的事我什么也没和他们说  我发誓\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I didn't tell them anything about you, I swear, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:16.77,0:38:18.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谁去过那里  亚历克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who's been there, Alex?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:18.78,0:38:20.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你都和谁说过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who have you told about this?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:20.57,0:38:22.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你到底同不同意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, do we have a deal or not?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:22.53,0:38:24.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,除非我搞清楚到底是怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not until I know what's going on there.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:25.67,0:38:27.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我再和亚历克斯说话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Give me Alex back.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.82,0:38:30.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是不会一直和你通着电话的  彼得\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not gonna keep this call going on, Peter,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:30.01,0:38:30.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好让你能追踪到我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so that you can trace it.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:31.51,0:38:33.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是同意还是不同意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is it yes or no?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:33.25,0:38:37.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最后通牒  帕尔默夫人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, this is an ultimatum, Mrs. Palmer.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.57,0:38:41.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再让亚历克斯听电话  否则谈话到此结束\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You put Alex back on, or this conversation is ended.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:41.50,0:38:45.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要是逼我  我就会保证休伊特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You force my hand and I'll make sure Hewitt tells his story
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.86,0:38:48.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把事情告知天下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to as many people as possible.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:48.19,0:38:50.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是你最后的机会  帕尔默夫人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's your final chance, Mrs. Palmer.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:56.02,0:38:57.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那就再见吧  彼得\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then it's goodbye, Peter.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:03.77,0:39:04.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:06.11,0:39:07.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那就交换吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:08.04,0:39:10.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-找个中立的地方  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Neutral ground. - All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:10.42,0:39:14.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,洛杉矶体育场  18号门  30分钟后见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}L.A. Coliseum, gate 18, 30 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:14.67,0:39:18.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-只有你和亚历克斯两个人  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Just you and Alex. - All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:21.08,0:39:22.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,非常好  帕尔默夫人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Very good work, Mrs. Palmer.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:24.35,0:39:25.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们出发\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:29.86,0:39:31.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,休伊特在雪莉·帕尔默手上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sherry Palmer has Hewitt.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:32.89,0:39:34.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她想怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What does she want?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:36.95,0:39:39.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我有种被人下套的感觉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I get this feeling I'm being set up.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:42.84,0:39:46.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们只是用休伊特把我引出去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hewitt's just the bait to draw me out into the open.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.17,0:39:48.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你打算怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So what are you gonna do?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:49.39,0:39:51.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我别无选择  必须照约定去见他们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't have any choice. I have to play this out.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:51.94,0:39:54.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,斯科特会让枪手准备就位\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Scott'll have shooters in place.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:54.73,0:39:58.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雪莉·帕尔默以及涉及此事的那个人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sherry Palmer and whoever else she's involved with in this
Dialogue: 0,0:39:58.18,0:40:00.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不能活着离开那里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}won't leave there alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:01.81,0:40:05.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后  我要出国\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And then... I'm heading outta the country.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:07.83,0:40:10.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是时候结束这里了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Time to roll things up around here.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:11.07,0:40:12.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,暂时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For now.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:13.24,0:40:14.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有什么我能做的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is there anything I can do for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:15.52,0:40:17.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你已经做了很多\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You've already done so much.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:18.42,0:40:20.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,下周我们在葡萄牙首都里斯本见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll see you in Lisbon next week.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:37.87,0:40:40.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,感激不尽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I am enormously grateful.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:57.76,0:40:59.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反恐组会如何开始支援你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What kinda support will you begin to get from CTU?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:00.15,0:41:01.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在完全没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As of now, none.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:01.17,0:41:01.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wait a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:01.70,0:41:04.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不是打算亲手除掉金斯利吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't expect to take Kingsley down by yourself?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:04.70,0:41:05.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's insane!
Dialogue: 0,0:41:05.87,0:41:08.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只要金斯利一自首  反恐组就会支援我们的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Soon as Kingsley incriminates himself, CTU will give us backup.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:08.96,0:41:12.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那时就太迟了  -抱歉  现在只能这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- By then it'll be too late. - Sorry, that's how it's gonna be.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:12.02,0:41:14.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金斯利身边会有手下跟着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kingsley will have people with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:14.00,0:41:15.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那些人一发现休伊特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}People who will kill us
Dialogue: 0,0:41:15.21,0:41:17.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不在我们这里  他们就会杀了我们的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the moment they realise we don't have Hewitt.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:19.97,0:41:21.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你还好吧  -我很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You OK? - I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:22.33,0:41:24.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你不好  停车  杰克  -没时间了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- No, you're not. Pull over, Jack. - We don't have time.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:24.80,0:41:27.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不  停车  -不能停车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- No, pull-pull over. - We've gotta keep moving!
Dialogue: 0,0:42:08.62,0:42:11.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack? Jack!
Dialogue: 0,0:42:13.11,0:42:14.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack!

