[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,1,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.69,0:00:10.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(197.4,200.557)}{\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs25\b1\bord0\shad0\c&H78BDE7&\fad(0,808)}24小时\N\N{\fs15}第二季  第十五集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.53,0:00:13.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(189.6,121.6,193.8,105.6,0,356)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad3\3c&H2F2F2F&\4c&H336D99&}{\fs10}{\t(0,356,\fs20)\fn方正正中黑简体}前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.38,0:00:16.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼  有时间吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony, got a second?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.70,0:00:14.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(120.6,243.753)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.74,0:00:14.78,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(141,223.753)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.78,0:00:14.83,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(162,202.953)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.83,0:00:14.87,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(181.2,182.4)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.87,0:00:14.91,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(201.6,162.953)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.91,0:00:14.95,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(220.8,142.153)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.95,0:00:16.91,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(238.8,123.753)\fad(0,309)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.08,0:00:17.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.05,0:00:18.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想我该退下了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think it's time I stepped down.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.06,0:00:20.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.10,0:00:21.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's this?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.18,0:00:23.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反恐组和分局的登入密码\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Access codes to CTU and Division.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.84,0:00:25.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你就是新的反恐组主管  托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're the new CTU director, Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.46,0:00:28.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你现在要放我出去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me out of here right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.46,0:00:27.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(118.6,249.886)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.50,0:00:27.55,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(138.4,226.953)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.55,0:00:27.59,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(159.2,205.62)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.59,0:00:27.63,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(177.8,183.753)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.63,0:00:27.67,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(197.4,163.486)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.67,0:00:27.71,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(217,143.486)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.71,0:00:29.76,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(238.8,122.42)\fad(0,355)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.35,0:00:30.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道炸弹没爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know the bomb didn't go off.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.01,0:00:31.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是想有人陪我而已\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just wanted some company, that's all.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.60,0:00:33.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你在这里干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then what are you doing out here?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.59,0:00:34.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我属于这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is where I belong.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.05,0:00:36.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不属于这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.81,0:00:38.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给  拿着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here. Take it.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.56,0:00:40.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,外面有美洲狮\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's cougars out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.77,0:00:42.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你遇到  就向空中鸣枪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you see one, fire a shot in the air
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.83,0:00:43.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,它们就会跑掉了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and it'll take off.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.79,0:00:45.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我刚和罗杰·斯坦顿聊了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just spoke with Roger Stanton.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.29,0:00:47.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他承认炸弹的事他已经知道好几周了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He confesses that he's known about the bomb for weeks.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.06,0:00:45.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(249.2,212.02)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.11,0:00:45.15,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(227.4,190.953)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.15,0:00:45.19,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(209.4,170.953)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.19,0:00:45.23,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(186.8,152.8)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.23,0:00:45.27,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(167.4,130.42)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.27,0:00:45.31,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(145.4,112.82)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.31,0:00:47.27,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(133.6,91.753)\fad(0,305)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.62,0:00:49.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你必须要相信我  大卫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You have to trust me, David.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.42,0:00:51.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的总统地位岌岌可危\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your presidency is in jeopardy.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.46,0:00:53.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我帮你吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.20,0:00:55.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不用了  你现在就走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. You'll leave now.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.75,0:00:57.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你以任何方式反抗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you resist in any way,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.53,0:01:00.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我别无选择  只能逮捕你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll have no choice but to place you under arrest.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.45,0:01:01.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给我你的证件  凯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You gotta give me your badge, Kate.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.87,0:01:04.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  我不信你会开枪打我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. I don't believe you'd shoot me.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.25,0:01:02.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(273.4,237.886)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.29,0:01:02.34,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(250,215.753)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.34,0:01:02.38,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(226,194.953)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.38,0:01:02.42,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(203.6,169.62)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.42,0:01:02.46,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(180,148.02)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.46,0:01:02.50,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(154.4,126.42)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.50,0:01:04.58,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(132,104.553)\fad(0,390)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.57,0:01:10.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽  炸弹在哪  真正的炸弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where's the bomb, Marie? The real bomb?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.78,0:01:12.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你去死吧  混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You can go to hell, you bastard.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.16,0:01:13.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我什么也不会说的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not telling you anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.20,0:01:16.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你为什么希望我和我的队员这么快离开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why do you want me and my team to leave here so fast?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.39,0:01:16.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(274.8,220.82)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.44,0:01:16.48,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(253.8,203.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.48,0:01:16.52,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(231.8,187.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.52,0:01:16.56,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(211.4,171.486)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.56,0:01:16.60,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(188.8,152.02)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.60,0:01:16.64,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(169.4,135.486)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.64,0:01:16.68,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(147.8,120.02)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.68,0:01:18.68,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(128,102.686)\fad(0,392)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.98,0:01:18.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,炸弹还在这里是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The bomb's still here, isn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.86,0:01:22.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在机场外围做网格搜索\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Initiate a grid search on every outbuilding at the airport,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.88,0:01:25.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,从北面开始往南搜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}starting at the north end, headed south.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.21,0:01:28.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,炸弹就在这里  我重复  炸弹就在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The bomb is on-site. I repeat: the bomb is on-site.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.08,0:01:30.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-保险已拔  -我们还剩多少时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It's armed. - How much time have we got?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.38,0:01:33.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说不准  有可能随时会爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't tell. It could be any second.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.57,0:01:40.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs15\t(696,6577,\fs16)\c&H4BAAAD&\fad(1697,1183)\pos(187.2,191.79)}以下故事情节发生在晚上10点到11点之间
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.81,0:01:48.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,通知所有人我们会在12号机库拆解炸弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let everyone know we'll be working on the bomb in hangar 12.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.84,0:01:50.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,收到  我们这里随时待命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roger that. We're on standby here.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.71,0:01:52.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有任何需要就叫我  鲍尔探员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Anything you need, Agent Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:52.24,0:01:53.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,收到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Copy that.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.82,0:01:55.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了  放这里就可以了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alright, guys. Right here should be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.52,0:02:02.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要一个继电器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay I need a relay here.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.61,0:02:06.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我看看电路板\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me get a look at the circuit panel.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.17,0:02:11.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们改了电路\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They redirected the circuit.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.58,0:02:13.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,准备好旁路\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bypass be ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.94,0:02:17.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当心点  当心点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Easy, easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.91,0:02:19.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没问题  继续吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got it, I got it. Go ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.17,0:02:22.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看看里面的定时器开关\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's get in there and check out that timer switch.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.44,0:02:25.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等  调整一下电路的盖子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hang on. Adjust the flash cap.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.94,0:02:30.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有点紧  快好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a little tight. Almost there.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:31.55,0:02:34.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好了  怎么样  -等等\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Got it. How's that? - Wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:39.65,0:02:40.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把盖子拿下来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Cap it off.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.80,0:02:44.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把旁路给我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need the bypass.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.73,0:02:51.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-成功了  情况良好  -很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It worked. We're in good shape. - Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.77,0:03:05.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治  你来这里干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George? What are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.74,0:03:08.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就是这东西害死了我  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is the thing that killed me, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.35,0:03:10.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们拆解它的时候我比较想在现场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I kind of like to be here when they lay it to rest.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.43,0:03:11.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,已经拆掉了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Got it diffused yet?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.15,0:03:14.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还没有  他们说大概还要十分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. Not yet. They're looking at about ten minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.41,0:03:15.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有定时器吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is there a timer?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:15.42,0:03:17.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在里面  他们还看不到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's internal. They haven't been able to read it yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.55,0:03:19.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以理论上炸弹随时都可能爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So theoretically it could detonate any minute?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.24,0:03:21.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治  他们已经控制住局面了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George, they've got it under control.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.22,0:03:24.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别这样  你肯定还有别的想去的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on. There's gotta be somewhere else you'd rather be.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.55,0:03:27.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我向自己保证过  我要跟进到最后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I promised myself I was gonna see this through to the end.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.92,0:03:29.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也打算这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's what I'm gonna do.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.55,0:03:38.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.88,0:03:40.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还好  我吃点药就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. I'll just take something.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.66,0:03:45.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,该死的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Damn it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.70,0:03:50.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等我一下  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just give me a minute, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.10,0:04:01.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有问题吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is there a problem?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.11,0:04:03.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,触发器有防破坏机制\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The trigger's tamper-proofed.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.17,0:04:07.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我本该看出来的  但它被伪装起来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I should've seen it, but it was disguised.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.58,0:04:11.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果它被拆解了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If it's dismantled
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.63,0:04:14.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,或者脱离了整个装置  炸弹就会爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}or disconnected from the main casing, it'll detonate.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.15,0:04:20.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是在告诉我这个炸弹没有办法拆除吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you telling me that there is no way to disarm this bomb?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:21.10,0:04:22.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我就是这个意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's what I'm telling you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.96,0:04:25.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,古德里奇\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Goodrich.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.97,0:04:31.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们没有办法拆除炸弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They are not gonna be able to diffuse this bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.69,0:04:32.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们得开飞机把它运走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna have to fly it out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:32.91,0:04:35.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道这个机场里没有喷气式飞机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now I know this airport doesn't accommodate jets,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.06,0:04:37.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以我需要你去找速度最快的飞机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so I need you to find me the fastest plane you can
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.19,0:04:38.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但必须稳定可靠\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but it's got to be reliable.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.76,0:04:43.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  三号机库前面有一架赛斯纳"大篷车"\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right there's a Cessna Caravan in front of hangar three.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.14,0:04:45.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,非常可靠  巡航时速340公里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's rock solid, cruises at 210.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.36,0:04:46.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-去开过来  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Get it. - All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.72,0:04:56.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,西北战区\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Northwest Regional?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.96,0:04:57.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是杰克·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is Jack Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.77,0:04:59.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我找总统  非常紧急\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need to speak with the president. It's urgent.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.71,0:05:01.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.79,0:05:07.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们看到定时器了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did you get a look at the timer?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.71,0:05:08.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.78,0:05:12.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们还有多少时间  -55分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How much time have we got? - 55 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.16,0:06:03.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要搭车吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Need a ride?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.02,0:06:08.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你去哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where are you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.16,0:06:09.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要去哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where are you trying to get to?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.14,0:06:11.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,圣何塞\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}San Jose.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.07,0:06:12.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真的假的  我也要去那\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No kidding. That's right where I'm headed.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.83,0:06:14.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,其实是去圣克拉拉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Santa Clara, actually.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.89,0:06:16.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,离圣何塞就几分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's just a few minutes past San Jose.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.46,0:06:25.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还是算了  不用了  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what? That's OK. I'm fine, thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.18,0:06:27.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别害怕\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't be scared.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.99,0:06:30.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我没害怕  -那就上车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'm not. - Then get in.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.68,0:06:32.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大半夜的在这里游荡做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's no point wandering around here in the middle of the night.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.92,0:06:33.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.55,0:06:36.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,刚刚你还想搭车去圣何塞  现在就不想了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}One second you need to get a ride to San Jose, the next you don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.91,0:06:38.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  你能停车我很感激\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry. It's really nice that you pulled over.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.73,0:06:39.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是我...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's just that I...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.53,0:06:42.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,回车里去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get back in the car now.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.41,0:06:50.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你都不知道怎么用那东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't know how to use that thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.64,0:06:54.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,回车里去  开车走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get back in the car and keep driving.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.93,0:07:03.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,婊子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bitch!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.49,0:07:15.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先生  您什么时候能作出决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, when will you have a decision?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.05,0:07:17.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们正在分析  飞机什么时候能准备好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We are analyzing now. When will the plane be ready?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.85,0:07:19.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,十分钟  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ten minutes, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.54,0:07:21.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会在那之前给你消息的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll get back to you before then.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.22,0:07:24.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,与此同时  准备好我们刚刚说的两种可能性\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In the meantime, prepare for the two possibilities we discussed.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.96,0:07:28.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-再跟联邦航空局协调一下  -是  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- And coordinate with the FAA. - Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.23,0:07:30.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要两种方案的地图和航海图\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want maps and charts for both scenarios.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.47,0:07:32.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-太平洋的放这里  沙漠的放这里  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Pacific Ocean here, desert here. - All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.78,0:07:34.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了  杰克  我们准备开会了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, Jack, we're ready to assemble.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.22,0:07:35.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我几分钟之后再打给你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll get back to you in a couple of minutes
Dialogue: 0,0:07:35.99,0:07:37.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉你最终的决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}when we have a final decision.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.11,0:07:38.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.29,0:07:40.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很想说我对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wish I could say I had more faith
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.69,0:07:42.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些提案的可靠性有信心  但...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}in the reliability of these recommendations but...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.75,0:07:44.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-尽你所能就行  麦克  -是  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Best you can, Mike. - Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.41,0:07:45.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会陈述在太平洋引爆一颗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll discuss the consequences of
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.88,0:07:48.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一万吨爆炸当量核弹的后果\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}a 10-kiloton detonation in the Pacific Ocean.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.34,0:07:50.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,林恩会陈述在莫哈维沙漠引爆的后果\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lynne will do the same for the Mojave Desert.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.34,0:07:50.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}加州东南部沙漠
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.77,0:07:52.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在允许的时间内\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In the time available,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.16,0:07:54.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,飞机可以飞离海岸线大约130公里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the plane can get roughly 80 miles offshore.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.77,0:07:57.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果在爆炸前几分钟投下核弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If it splashes down a few minutes before detonation,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.34,0:07:59.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,炸弹就会在水里爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the bomb will go off underwater.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.19,0:08:01.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,海洋会吸收大部分的核辐射\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The ocean will absorb a large portion of the radiation.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.96,0:08:06.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但盛行风会将一定程度的放射尘\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}However, prevailing winds would blow a moderate level of fallout
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.78,0:08:09.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,吹回到洛杉矶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}back over the city of Los Angeles.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.78,0:08:12.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,随着时间推移  癌症和其他辐射导致的疾病\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Over time, there would be a high incidence of cancer
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.73,0:08:15.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,病发率将会大幅提高\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and other radiation-related diseases.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.20,0:08:17.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但至少不会立即有人死亡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But at least there'll be no immediate casualty.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.17,0:08:19.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不能确定  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We can't be certain, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.24,0:08:21.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,进入洛杉矶港的航道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The shipping lanes into the port of Los Angeles
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.30,0:08:22.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,非常繁忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}are extremely busy.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:23.26,0:08:25.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在洛杉矶海岸方圆130公里内\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In the 80 square miles off the coast of LA,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.77,0:08:28.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,海岸警卫队说有24艘货船\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the Coast Guard counts two dozen freighters
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.49,0:08:30.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,挂着世界各国的国旗在航行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}flying flags from around the world,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.12,0:08:32.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,何况还有不知数量的未登记的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}plus an unknown number of unregistered
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.48,0:08:34.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,渔船和游轮\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}fishing or pleasure vessels.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.58,0:08:36.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很有可能它们中的一艘或几艘\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's likely that one or more of them
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.11,0:08:39.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会因为爆炸的冲击沉没或倾覆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}would be sunk or capsized by the effect of the blast.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.05,0:08:40.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对环境有哪些影响\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's the impact on the environment?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:41.49,0:08:46.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爆炸会使生物多样性大幅下降\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The blast will wipe out a substantial pocket of biodiversity.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.02,0:08:48.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,关键种会灭绝\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Keystone species would be exterminated,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.48,0:08:50.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,食物链会被污染\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the food chain would be contaminated,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.52,0:08:54.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,地区生态基础设施会被彻底摧毁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and the regional ecological infrastructure would collapse.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.38,0:08:57.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,诸如海上钻井  捕鱼业\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Marine resources such as offshore drilling,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.46,0:09:01.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,甚至是海滩休闲等海洋产业\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}commercial fishing, even recreational beach usage
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.46,0:09:05.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在很多年内都会是有害的或是根本无法进行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}would become hazardous or impossible for many years.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.51,0:09:07.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,生态和经济损失\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The ecological and economic effects,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.74,0:09:10.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  无可估量\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, would be devastating.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.99,0:09:12.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那沙漠呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about the desert?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.54,0:09:15.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们可以在莫哈维沙漠指定一个核弹爆炸点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We can designate a ground zero, in the Mojave.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.53,0:09:16.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,由于该地区被政府隔开了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's officially isolated,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:16.48,0:09:18.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以居民区不会马上受到影响\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so that the inhabited areas won't be immediately affected.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.97,0:09:21.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当地城镇在爆炸后几小时内就能撤离\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Local towns could be evacuated within hours of the blast
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.16,0:09:19.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs12\frz357.8\c&H020409&\fad(0,352)\move(135.2,74.667,108,76.8,233,692)}核弹  沙漠爆炸
Dialogue: 0,0:09:19.66,0:09:20.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs12\c&H424448&\move(159.6,64.8,108,65.6,25,651)\fad(234,0)}无人区
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.87,0:09:22.83,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an8\fn方正黑体_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs12\c&H424448&\move(108,65.6,169.8,68.8,0,1193)}无人区
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.75,0:09:25.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而不会有严重的长期后果\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}without any serious long-term effects.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.00,0:09:29.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是我们不能排除有零散野营和登山的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}However, we can't rule out the possibility of isolated campers and hikers,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.12,0:09:32.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们会被炸死或是受到辐射\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}who would be killed or contaminated by the blast.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:32.16,0:09:36.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果风向在接下来的几个小时明显变化的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If the wind shifts substantially during the next few hours,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:36.32,0:09:38.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,放射尘可能会到达拉斯维加斯上空\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it could blow fallout over Las Vegas.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.17,0:09:41.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最好的气象预报指出\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The best meteorological projections indicate that
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.83,0:09:44.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这种可能性微乎其微\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that is a very, very slight possibility.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.55,0:09:45.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,长期影响呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Long-term effects?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.83,0:09:50.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爆炸点方圆几公里的范围\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}An area of a few square miles around ground zero
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.69,0:09:53.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会多年持续高辐射\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}would be highly radioactive for decades,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.35,0:09:55.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但事实是我们并不依靠沙漠\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but the truth is we don't get food
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.64,0:09:58.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,提供食物或是其他重要的资源\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}or any significant resources from the desert anyway.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.54,0:10:02.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以总体来讲对健康的威胁相对较小\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So the overall health risk is relatively small.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.83,0:10:08.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看来沙漠是我们最好的选择了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sounds like the desert's our best option.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.23,0:10:10.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  先生  我们同意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir, we do agree with that.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.34,0:10:13.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但还有一点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But there is one more thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.21,0:10:16.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,沙漠里的爆炸点必须是特定的位置\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In the desert, ground zero has to be a precise location.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.84,0:10:20.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一个群山环绕且低于海平面的盆地\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A depression, below sea level and surrounded by mountains,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.03,0:10:22.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样才有希望防止放射尘扩散\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so it could hopefully contain the fallout.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.91,0:10:26.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在正在寻找可选的地点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Potential target sites are being researched as we speak.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.75,0:10:28.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  问题是  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. Point is, Mr. President,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.57,0:10:31.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那架飞机并不是军用飞机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the airplane isn't a military craft.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.35,0:10:33.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,它没有准确运送炸弹到指定地点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It doesn't have any of the equipment needed
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.34,0:10:35.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所需的一切仪器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to deliver a payload accurately.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.25,0:10:38.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为了确保坠落地点足够准确\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}To ensure the necessary level of precision,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:39.36,0:10:42.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,必须有飞行员随飞机坠毁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}a pilot will have to go down with the plane.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.63,0:10:44.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是个自杀式任务\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a suicide mission.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:44.28,0:10:47.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么不能从飞机侧门丢出去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why can't we push it out the side door?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.24,0:10:50.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那样太不准确了  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's too imprecise, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.03,0:10:54.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果飞行员为了保证地点准确而低空飞行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If the pilot is flying low enough to ensure accuracy,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:54.49,0:10:56.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他就会被爆炸炸死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}he would be killed by the blast.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:56.60,0:10:58.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,用一个人的生命  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}One man dies, Mr. President,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:59.34,0:11:02.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来确保百万人的安全\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to ensure the safety of millions.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.65,0:11:13.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-杰克  -总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Jack? - Mr. President?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.90,0:11:15.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-去沙漠  -是  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- The desert. - Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.39,0:11:19.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  我的幕僚说必须有一名飞行员牺牲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, my people tell me that the pilot has to die.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.10,0:11:20.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反恐组也得出了同样的结论\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}CTU came to the same conclusion.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.76,0:11:24.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先生  炸弹必须在特定的坐标引爆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, the bomb has to be put down on specific coordinates.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.20,0:11:26.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很抱歉  总统先生  但没有其他的办法了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry, Mr. President, but there isn't another way.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:26.78,0:11:28.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谁来做这个飞行员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do we know who the pilot will be?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.93,0:11:31.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们有几位志愿者  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have a few volunteers, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.41,0:11:32.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,全都很可靠\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All of them good men.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.70,0:11:36.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不管是谁  告诉他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Whoever it is, tell him
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.19,0:11:39.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,全国所有人民都会永远感激他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}he has the undying gratitude of every citizen of this country.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.90,0:11:42.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉他我们会负责\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And tell him we will take care
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.81,0:11:44.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他的全部家人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}of whatever family he leaves behind.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.67,0:11:46.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  先生  我会照办\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir. I will.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.52,0:11:48.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我随时待命  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll be standing by, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.86,0:11:50.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,飞机起飞后给我打电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Call me back when the plane's in the air.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.57,0:11:51.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.20,0:12:01.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有趣  我可没看到什么志愿者\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Funny, I don't see any volunteers.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.32,0:12:04.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你上次开飞机是什么时候\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When was the last time you flew a plane?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.07,0:12:06.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我能驾驶它  并操纵它坠毁  乔治\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can get it in the air and put it down, George.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.85,0:12:10.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也能  我现在没事  我也会驾驶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So can I. I'm current, I'm instrument-rated,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.92,0:12:12.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而且我今天之后本来就要死了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and I'm gonna be dead by the end of the day anyways.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.69,0:12:14.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,问题是  你随时都可能会死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Problem is, you could be dead any minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.93,0:12:17.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我能再撑半个小时  这就够了不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can hang on for another half-hour, that's all we need, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.25,0:12:18.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治  如果你失去知觉  飞机没到沙漠前\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George, if you blacked out and it went down
Dialogue: 0,0:12:18.84,0:12:19.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就坠毁的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}before it got to the desert,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.82,0:12:22.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很多人会因此丧命  我知道你也不想这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}a lot of people will die. I know you don't want that.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.55,0:12:23.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行了  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.73,0:12:25.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道你想做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know what you're trying to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.06,0:12:28.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我必须拒绝你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I gotta say no.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.65,0:12:30.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,古德里奇探员  我是鲍尔  他们选了沙漠\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Agent Goodrich, this is Bauer. They chose the desert.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.45,0:12:34.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你清空航线并立即开始组织撤离\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you to clear air space and start immediate evacuation now.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.47,0:12:37.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,各位  把炸弹装上飞机  要行动了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Gentlemen! Load this bomb. We are a go!
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.55,0:13:03.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这没有显示加急\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's not rated as a priority.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.35,0:13:05.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不管分局加不加急  照办就行了  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't care what the Division's priority is. Just do it, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.81,0:13:06.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-是  长官  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yes, sir. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.57,0:13:09.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了  奥达先生  在这等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, Mr. Auda. Wait here a second.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.78,0:13:10.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们马上就来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll be right with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.45,0:13:15.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,格拉夫斯探员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Agent Graves.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.60,0:13:17.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼·阿尔梅达  我们在等你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony Almeida. We've been expecting you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.34,0:13:18.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们告诉你箱子里装了什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They told you what's in the case?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.77,0:13:21.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿里的安全屋里的个人物品吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Personal effects from Ali's safe house?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.52,0:13:22.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who's he?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.30,0:13:24.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他叫优素福·奥达\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}His name is Yusuf Auda.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.93,0:13:27.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他的政府派他来做情报联络员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}His government assigned him as an intelligence liaison.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.33,0:13:30.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们提供给我们安全屋的情报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They gave us information that got us in the safe house.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.26,0:13:32.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们不得不带他过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We couldn't refuse to bring him.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.73,0:13:33.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你信任他吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you trust him?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.77,0:13:36.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在吗  我不信任任何人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right now? I don't trust anyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.73,0:13:39.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  带上箱子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Take the case
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.21,0:13:41.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去转角过去那个会议室\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and bring it into that conference room around the corner.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.16,0:13:42.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- OK. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.80,0:13:46.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,奥达先生  托尼·阿尔梅达  反恐组主管\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Auda. Tony Almeida, Director of CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.14,0:13:47.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-欢迎你  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Welcome. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.31,0:13:48.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你可是远道而来啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Must have had some trip.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.05,0:13:50.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天早晨你还在一万多公里之外呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You were 10,000 miles away this morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:50.77,0:13:52.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我准备好工作了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm ready to get back to work.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.45,0:13:55.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我理解你们要分析\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I understand analysis needs to be done on things
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.53,0:13:57.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,从赛伊德·阿里的公寓搜出的物品\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}seized from Syed Ali's apartment.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.94,0:14:02.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  我们的分析室需要先做些初步分析\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Our lab needs to do some preliminary work first.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.47,0:14:04.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我让人给你拿点咖啡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll have somebody get you coffee.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.90,0:14:06.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我一会就回来  好吗  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll be with you in a moment, OK? Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.24,0:14:16.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-刚确认分析室可以开始解码了  -很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I checked with the lab, they are ready for decryption. - Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.35,0:14:20.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  我需要一个人去拖延他一会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I might need somebody to do a little handholding here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.42,0:14:22.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他叫优素福·奥达\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That gentleman's name over there is Yusuf Auda.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.98,0:14:25.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,纸面上看  他是需要我们全力合作的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Officially, he's a visiting intelligence agent
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.40,0:14:27.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,访问情报员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}entitled to full cooperation.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.46,0:14:28.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,纸面下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Unofficially,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.60,0:14:31.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不能让他看到任何他不需要看到的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't want him to see anything he doesn't need to see.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.82,0:14:34.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,确保你派的人明白这点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Make sure anybody you assign to this understands this.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.37,0:14:35.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没问题  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Sure. - OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.27,0:14:40.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我亲自去应付奥达先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna deal with this Mr. Auda myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.37,0:14:43.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你需要帮手  叫雅各布  他会帮你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you need any help, call Jacobs. He will give you a hand.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.86,0:14:46.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼让你派个人去看着奥达\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony told you to assign someone to Auda.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.44,0:14:47.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我亲自去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm assigning myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.44,0:14:50.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你还是不愿意跟我一起工作  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're still not comfortable working with me, are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.68,0:14:53.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,做好你自己的事  凯莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just do your job, Carrie.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.61,0:15:03.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有什么发现\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, what have we got?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.77,0:15:05.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,多数文件都正常\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Most of it's pretty innocuous.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.05,0:15:06.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是有一点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There is one thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.82,0:15:08.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个被藏得很深  我们几乎没找到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This was well-concealed, we almost didn't find it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.90,0:15:11.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这显然对于阿里来讲很重要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Obviously it was of great importance to Ali.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.41,0:15:14.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们需要读取  但它编了密码\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We tried to read it, but it's encrypted with a Z-Q function.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:14.46,0:15:16.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们这里技术不足以破解\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We don't have that technology in the field.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:16.38,0:15:18.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  我现在就派我的人帮忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK. I'll get our people on it right away,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:19.69,0:15:20.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看他们能查到什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}see what they can find.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.95,0:15:21.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.27,0:15:23.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-谢谢  -没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Thanks. - Sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.32,0:15:32.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿尔梅达\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Almeida.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.07,0:15:33.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼  我是杰克  找到金了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony, it's Jack, have you found Kim yet?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.79,0:15:35.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有  我们还在找\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. We're still working on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.34,0:15:37.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要没时间了  我现在就要跟她说话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm running out of time I need to speak to her now.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.80,0:15:40.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我理解你的感受  杰克  但我们这里很忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I understand how you feel Jack, but we got our hands full here.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.60,0:15:42.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你能等飞机起飞后再说...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you could wait until the plane takes off...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.15,0:15:45.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-托尼  我就是驾驶员  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Tony, I'm flying it. - What?!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.40,0:15:49.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想趁着还有时间和女儿说说话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'd like to speak with my daughter while I still got time.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.08,0:15:51.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总会有别人可以驾驶的吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's gotta be somebody else to fly that plane.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.50,0:15:53.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,找个没有家人  或者至少没有孩子的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Somebody that doesn't have a family or at least no kids. Come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.63,0:15:56.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没时间做人口普查了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I didn't have time to take a census.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.86,0:15:58.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不能命令任何人去做这件事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't order anyone to do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.44,0:16:00.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托了  托尼  你得找到她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please, Tony, you've gotta find her.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.81,0:16:07.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我会找到她的  -托尼  还有一件事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- All right. I'll find her. - Tony, one other thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.55,0:16:08.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:09.89,0:16:12.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的公寓里有个保险箱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In my apartment, there's a safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.20,0:16:13.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,里面是我的遗嘱和一旦我出事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Inside is my will and a letter
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.43,0:16:15.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我写给金的一封信\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wrote to Kim in case something ever happened to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.28,0:16:19.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会确保她拿到信的  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll make sure she gets it, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.50,0:16:23.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-谢谢  -等下联络\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Thanks. - I'll get back to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:51.50,0:16:55.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你还好吗  亲爱的  -我需要搭车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You all right, honey? - I could use a lift.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.46,0:16:57.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在这荒郊野外做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you doing way out here?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.31,0:17:02.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我跟一个人约会  我们到了这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was on a date and we parked.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.25,0:17:05.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他开始不安分  所以我跑了出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He got a little out of hand, so I got out.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.85,0:17:08.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快进来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hop in.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.97,0:17:24.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你  真的很感谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you. I really appreciate this.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.48,0:17:26.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想去哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where would you like to go?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.54,0:17:30.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在圣何塞有个阿姨\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have an aunt in San Jose.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.28,0:17:32.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你来赴约  约会不成\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You were on a date, it didn't work out,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.65,0:17:34.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你就要去圣何塞找你的阿姨\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so you're going to your aunt's in San Jose.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.85,0:17:38.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亲爱的  你的事是你的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Honey, your business is your business,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.53,0:17:40.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我也不傻  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I'm not an idiot, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.76,0:17:44.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道  这事太疯狂了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know. It's just been crazy,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.79,0:17:45.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而且说来话长\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and it's a long story,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.90,0:17:47.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也遇到点小麻烦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and I'm kind of in a little bit of trouble.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.42,0:17:49.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你有手机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you have a cellphone,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.39,0:17:51.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我非常需要打个电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I actually really need to make a call.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.05,0:17:54.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-打给谁  -我爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- To whom? - My father.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.82,0:18:07.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们把这个表和炸弹的计时器同步了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We synchronised this with the timer on the bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.65,0:18:08.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.05,0:18:28.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,祝你好运\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good luck.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.80,0:18:37.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以飞机有自动驾驶功能吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So the plane has some automatic pilot thing?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.19,0:18:38.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,并没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Actually, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.04,0:18:41.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,必须有人驾驶它飞到一个特定的地点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It'll have to be flown out to a very precise location.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.15,0:18:43.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以飞行员就...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So the pilot...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.67,0:18:48.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天哪  谁来驾驶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, my God. Who's it gonna be?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.84,0:18:51.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.03,0:19:03.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.09,0:19:07.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对不起  沃纳小姐  你不能离开这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry, Miss Warner, but you're gonna have to stay here.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.69,0:19:39.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,塞斯纳47福克斯请求立刻起飞\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Cessna 47 Fox requesting immediate takeoff.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.96,0:19:42.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,47福克斯  3号跑道可以起飞\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}47 Fox, you're clear on runway three.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.16,0:19:43.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,收到  塔台\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roger that, tower.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.48,0:19:45.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.47,0:20:31.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先生  这是你明天演讲的初稿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, here's your preliminary draft for your statement tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.88,0:20:34.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes. Right. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.27,0:20:36.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,飞机飞行情况如何  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How's the plane doing, Mike?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.53,0:20:38.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  现在飞行高度是3000英尺\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr.President, it's at 3,000 feet
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.26,0:20:38.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,飞机仍在爬升\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and climbing.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:38.99,0:20:39.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们出城了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Out of the city yet?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.94,0:20:41.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没呢  先生  还早着呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, Sir, it's too soon for that,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.28,0:20:44.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是十分钟内就要让人口密集区域撤离了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but they'll clear the main population centres in ten minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.23,0:20:48.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,目前看起来不错  不过我想再过一遍\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is a good start, but I want to go over it again.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.13,0:20:50.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,同时  打电话给戴维斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In the meantime, call Davis.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.66,0:20:53.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要他把空军一号尽快备好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want him to get Air Force One ready as soon as possible.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.69,0:20:55.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.06,0:21:01.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我可以问下您要去哪里吗  -洛杉矶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Do you mind if I ask where you're going? - Los Angeles.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.06,0:21:05.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  请恕我直言\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, if I may speak frankly,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.36,0:21:09.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这恐怕不是个好主意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not sure that's a good idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.70,0:21:13.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不得不说这恐怕有点太"亲力亲为"了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It may be a little too "Hands-on", for lack of a better term.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.20,0:21:16.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,人们更愿意看到你掌握着大局\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The people want to feel that you're managing events,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.56,0:21:18.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而不是深陷其中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}not caught up in them.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.35,0:21:19.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,无论如何  我甚至怀疑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And, in any case, I doubt
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.97,0:21:23.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,特勤局会不会同意这件事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}if the Secret Service will even hear of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.39,0:21:25.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,特勤局是听命于我的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Secret Service works for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.30,0:21:26.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是我听他们的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't work for them.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.51,0:21:27.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.45,0:21:33.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先生  我很同意麦克的看法\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, I do agree with Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.94,0:21:36.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一旦这枚炸弹爆炸的消息传出去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Once word gets out that this bomb has gone off,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:37.00,0:21:39.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,肯定会引起一定程度的局势动荡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}there's bound to be certain amounts of civil unrest.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.35,0:21:42.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得你不能牵涉其中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't think you should be associated with that.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.37,0:21:45.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,全国上下都会因为这枚炸弹的消息震动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The whole country will be traumatised by the news of this bomb,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.25,0:21:47.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尤其是洛杉矶的居民\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}especially the people in Los Angeles.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.61,0:21:49.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会尽我所能向他们保证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna do everthing I can to reassure them
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.45,0:21:51.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一切尽在掌控之中  明白了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that everything is under control. Understood?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.95,0:21:54.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  先生  我立刻打给戴维斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir. I'll call Davis immediately.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.65,0:21:57.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢  我们立刻去机场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you. We'll leave for the airport now.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:59.16,0:22:02.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,麦克  最后谁来开飞机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mike, who ended up flying the plane?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.31,0:22:03.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道他名字吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did you get a name?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.61,0:22:05.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.69,0:22:08.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.30,0:22:12.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我本该早点告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'd have told you sooner,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:12.51,0:22:15.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我想你的事儿已经够多了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I figured you had enough on your mind already.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.68,0:22:33.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,塞斯纳47福克斯  飞机爬升到一万英尺\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Cessna 47 Fox, climb to 10,000 feet,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:33.03,0:22:34.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,0-8-9\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}0-8-niner.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:34.53,0:22:37.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,收到  0-8-9  高度一万英尺\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roger. 0-8-niner. 10,000 feet.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.72,0:22:40.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,五分钟后等待最后航线指令\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Expect final vectors in five minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.22,0:22:41.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,收到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I copy.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.35,0:22:47.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鲍尔特工  我打通托尼·阿尔梅达的电话了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Agent Bauer, I've got Tony Almeida.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.57,0:22:49.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我把他转接过来  请稍等\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm patching him through. Hold on one second.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.85,0:22:51.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  你能听到吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, can you hear me?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.92,0:22:53.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可以 我听到了  托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I can hear you, Tony
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.48,0:22:56.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我找到金了  她在线上呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We found Kim. She's on the other line.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.17,0:22:58.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你  托尼  干得漂亮\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you, Tony. Good work.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.41,0:23:00.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你跟她说了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Have you told her anything?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.60,0:23:03.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有  我不知道你想不想让我说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. I didn't know if you'd want me to.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.78,0:23:05.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ok.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.23,0:23:09.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-把她电话转接过来吧  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Put her through, will ya? - All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.75,0:23:12.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kim?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.07,0:23:15.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸爸  总算接通了  天啊  你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Dad! Finally. Oh, my God, are you OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.71,0:23:17.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很好  亲爱的  你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm OK, sweetheart. Are you all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.93,0:23:19.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  我很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:19.93,0:23:22.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢天谢地  你过了糟糕的一天  不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank God. You've had a hell of a day, haven't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.89,0:23:25.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊  什么声音啊  你在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. What's that noise? Where are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.23,0:23:27.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在飞机上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm in a plane.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.55,0:23:30.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,飞机  为什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A plane? Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.38,0:23:32.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亲爱的  有些事我得跟你说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sweetheart, there's something I've gotta tell you.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.89,0:23:36.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你听了可能会很难过  但是我需要你的支持\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It'll be hard for you to hear, so I need you to stick with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.53,0:23:40.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们找到炸弹了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We found the bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.05,0:23:44.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,炸弹排线的方法根本拆不开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was wired in a way that made it impossible to diffuse it.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:44.59,0:23:46.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们需要有人把炸弹运到沙漠里去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We needed someone to fly it over the desert,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.03,0:23:48.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样它爆炸就不会伤到人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so when it exploded nobody would get killed.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.28,0:23:52.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而我就是那个开飞机的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That someone turned out to be me.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.21,0:24:00.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你怎么逃离飞机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How are you getting off the plane?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.85,0:24:07.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没打算逃离  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not, sweetheart.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.34,0:24:10.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,飞机必须在特定的区域扔掉炸弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The bomb has to be dropped in a very specific area.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.52,0:24:12.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有其他选择了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There was no other choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.19,0:24:14.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.59,0:24:20.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可是  爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But... Dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.51,0:24:27.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-爸爸  不要  你不能这么做  -金\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Dad, no! No, you can't do this to me! - Kim.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.61,0:24:29.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,肯定还有人可以去的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There has to be somebody else!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.22,0:24:31.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没得选了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I didn't have any other choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.33,0:24:33.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金  你听我说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kim, I need you to listen to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:33.64,0:24:36.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对不起  对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.25,0:24:37.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亲爱的  你为什么说对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sweetheart, what are you sorry for?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.11,0:24:40.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天啊  为所有的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, God, everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.61,0:24:45.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我一直那么对你那么凶  态度很差\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've been so mean and so bad to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:46.30,0:24:48.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,宝贝  我们之间发生的一切\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Honey, anything that ever happened between us,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.85,0:24:51.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都不能怪你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it was never your fault.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.60,0:24:55.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我爱的就是你现在的样子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I love you just the way you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.52,0:24:58.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不想你改变  你能理解吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't ever want you to change, you understand that?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.88,0:25:01.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我爱你胜过这世上的一切\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I love you more than anything in the world.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.60,0:25:08.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金  你还能听得见吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kim, can you still hear me?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:09.41,0:25:10.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.45,0:25:14.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,宝贝  我要你过自己的人生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Honey, I want you to live your life.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.72,0:25:18.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要你幸福  这是我唯一想要的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you to be happy. That's all I've ever wanted for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.85,0:25:23.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要你努力  成长为一个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you to try and grow up and be the kind of person
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.76,0:25:28.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让你妈妈为之骄傲的人  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that would have made your mom proud, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.63,0:25:29.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,哦  天啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, God.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.07,0:25:33.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,答应我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Promise me that.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.64,0:25:37.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我答应你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I promise.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.83,0:25:46.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,宝贝  我得开始关注我手上的事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Honey, I've gotta start focusing on what I'm doing up here.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.17,0:25:47.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,时间不多了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm running out of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.71,0:25:51.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只能跟你说再见了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna have to say goodbye.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:54.06,0:25:55.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我爱你胜过这世上的一切\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I love you more than anything in the world
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.59,0:25:57.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会一直和你在一起  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and I will always be with you, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.30,0:25:59.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,记住这一点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Remember that.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.29,0:26:07.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我为你骄傲  我爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm proud of you... and I love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.74,0:26:14.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我也爱你  亲爱的  -不要啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I love you, too, sweetheart. - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.30,0:26:18.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Goodbye.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.20,0:26:47.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很难过  宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.81,0:26:49.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you want to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:52.00,0:26:53.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得离开这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I gotta get out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.11,0:26:54.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么意思  为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you mean? Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:54.37,0:26:55.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我本该离开洛杉矶的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was supposed to get out of LA,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.77,0:26:57.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但现在都不重要了  我要一个人待着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but it doesn't matter any more. To be alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.15,0:26:59.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  等一下  这太疯狂了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, wait a minute. This is crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.94,0:27:02.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等  等一下  给其他人打个电话吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wait. Just wait. Call someone else.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.12,0:27:04.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不行  我可以的  我要一个人待着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't. I'm OK. I need to be alone.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.30,0:27:19.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You oK?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:22.87,0:27:23.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们找到金了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We found Kim.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.96,0:27:27.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-杰克有机会跟她说再见吗  -说了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Jack get a chance to say goodbye? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.23,0:27:30.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有什么发现\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So what'd you find?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:31.17,0:27:33.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们解码了阿里的硬盘\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We decrypted Ali's hard drive...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.79,0:27:37.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,里头记录了发生在四个月前的一个对话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a recording of conversation that took place four months ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:38.12,0:27:39.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谁和谁的对话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Conversation between who?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.70,0:27:41.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,赛伊德·阿里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Syed Ali
Dialogue: 0,0:27:42.75,0:27:45.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,和这三个国家的政府高层官员之间的对话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and high-ranking government officials from these three countries.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.76,0:27:55.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那意思就是说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So what we're saying is
Dialogue: 0,0:27:55.58,0:27:58.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这三个国家不仅知道炸弹的存在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that these three countries not only knew about the bomb,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:58.91,0:28:01.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们还付钱买了并把它给了赛伊德·阿里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but they bought it and supplied it to Syed Ali?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:02.06,0:28:03.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  看起来是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. That's what it looks like.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.43,0:28:06.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对这个说法我们有几分把握\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How sure are we about this translation?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:06.86,0:28:08.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,时间很赶  我们还要再确认\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We were rushed, it needs to be refined,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:08.72,0:28:10.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是其中的信息是准确的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but the substance of it is accurate.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.06,0:28:18.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们还需要对这四个人进行声音鉴定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll need voice authentication on all four of these men.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.78,0:28:20.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,已经派人去做了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've already got people working on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:20.31,0:28:21.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也报送给分局\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get Division involved as well.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.17,0:28:30.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里是西北分局\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Northwest Regional?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.31,0:28:32.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是反恐局的托尼·阿尔梅达\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thi is Tony Almeida at CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.38,0:28:35.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就今天的恐怖袭击事件我需要和总统先生通话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need to speak to the president about today's terrorist attack.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:35.29,0:28:36.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,情况紧急\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's urgent.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.15,0:28:37.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我帮你转接\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll transfer you.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.98,0:28:48.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么事  阿尔梅达先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What is it, Mr. Almeida?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:48.31,0:28:50.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  我们有录音证据表明\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr.President, we have a recording of Syed Ali
Dialogue: 0,0:28:50.83,0:28:52.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,赛伊德·阿里勾结\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}collaborating with high-ranking officials
Dialogue: 0,0:28:52.44,0:28:54.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,三个中东国家的政府高官们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}from three Middle Eastern countries
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.06,0:28:56.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,策划了了今天的恐袭\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}in preparation for today's terrorist attack.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.85,0:28:58.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,多久之前知道到这个情况的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How long ago did this come to our attention?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:58.92,0:29:00.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就几分钟前\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just within the last few minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:01.11,0:29:02.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有谁知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who else knows?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.83,0:29:04.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们分局总部  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Our Division headquarters, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:04.67,0:29:06.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们跟其他单位有联系  包括五角大楼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They have ties to the other agencies, including the Pentagon,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.11,0:29:08.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也就是说每个人都知道了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}which means everybody knows.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.91,0:29:11.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我把它标为四级安全级别  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I tagged it with a section-four security, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.67,0:29:13.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我认为我们必须\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I did think it was important
Dialogue: 0,0:29:13.01,0:29:16.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尽快进行声音鉴别\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to get going on the authentication process as quickly as possible
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.09,0:29:18.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那需要多长时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How long will that be?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:18.29,0:29:21.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一个小时内应该可以初步确认\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We should have initial confirmation in an hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:21.11,0:29:23.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿尔梅达先生  还有一个问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me ask you another question, Mr. Almeida.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:24.40,0:29:26.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,首先为什么赛伊德·阿里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why would Syed Ali
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.01,0:29:28.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要把这样的对话录下来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}record a conversation like this in the first place?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:28.31,0:29:30.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  多半时候  这些人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, half the time these people
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.61,0:29:33.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,彼此间的信任并不超过对我们的信任\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}don't trust each other any more than they trust us.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.00,0:29:36.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我猜阿里需要一些弹药来保护自己\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My guess is Ali wanted some ammunition to protect himself,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:36.29,0:29:39.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,以防这三个国家有谁跟他翻脸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}in case any of these three countries ever turned against him.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.44,0:29:41.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:41.56,0:29:42.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢  阿尔梅达先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you, Mr. Almeida.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:42.69,0:29:45.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我就不打扰你工作了  干得漂亮\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll let you get back to work. Good job.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.02,0:29:48.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请替我向你的其他同事表达谢意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please pass on my appreciation to the rest of your staff.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:48.93,0:29:50.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-多谢夸奖  总统先生  -谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Thank you, Mr. President. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:54.76,0:29:58.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有证据表明炸弹背后可能牵涉三个中东国家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's evidence three governments in the Middle East may be behind this bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:58.58,0:30:00.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错  先生  我猜到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir. I gathered that.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:09.72,0:30:11.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,战争可能一触即发  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We could be at war soon, Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.42,0:30:16.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一旦战争打响...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And once it begins...
Dialogue: 0,0:30:17.33,0:30:20.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,牵涉的可不一定只有这三个国家了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}there's no guarantee it'll be limited to these three countries.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:26.66,0:30:27.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我一整天都在想\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've been thinking all day
Dialogue: 0,0:30:27.73,0:30:30.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,林肯在美国内战时的讲话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}about something Lincoln said during the Civil War.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:31.88,0:30:34.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"我无法掌控生活中的不如意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"I don't claim to have controlled events
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.97,0:30:38.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我愿意承认事情已经掌控了我"\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but confess plainly that events have controlled me."
Dialogue: 0,0:30:42.46,0:30:43.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有人想往这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's bad enough
Dialogue: 0,0:30:43.15,0:30:46.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,走私核武器就已经够糟糕了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that someone tried to smuggle a nuclear weapon in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.06,0:30:47.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,更糟的是他们的奸计得逞\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Worse that they succeeded.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:48.40,0:30:50.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是一旦炸弹真的引爆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But once this bomb actually goes off,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:51.47,0:30:54.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的选择将少之又少\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}my options will narrow very, very quickly.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:08.37,0:31:09.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里是赛纳斯47福克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is Cessna 47 Fox.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:09.93,0:31:12.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我已经抵达沙漠的低空区域\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have just crossed over to the low desert.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:12.55,0:31:13.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快要达到目标地点了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm on final line to target.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:13.70,0:31:15.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,需要更改当前坐标吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Any change in my coordinates?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.58,0:31:17.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不需要  和预期坐标一致\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Negative. They're confirmed as given.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.60,0:31:21.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,收到  自动驾驶仪坐标为0-8-9\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Copy that. Confirming autopilot 0-8-niner.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:21.79,0:31:25.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-坐标已锁定  -收到  结束通话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Coordinates are now locked. - Roger. Over.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:43.24,0:31:45.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-别动  -别激动  别激动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Don't move! - Hey, hey, hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:45.32,0:31:46.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这架飞机的服务已经够差了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The service is bad enough for this flight.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:46.84,0:31:48.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没必要再把我打死吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't have to shoot me.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:48.84,0:31:50.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治  你在这里干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George, what the hell are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:50.98,0:31:52.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想着搭个便车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I felt like taking a ride.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.75,0:31:54.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是怎么上的这架飞机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How the hell did you get on this plane?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:55.08,0:31:56.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也没那么难\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wasn't that hard.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.62,0:31:58.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们还把我当成是反恐组的老大\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}To them, I'm still head of CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:59.66,0:32:01.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你个混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Son of a bitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:04.17,0:32:05.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给你带了点东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Brought something for ya.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.17,0:32:10.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是个降落伞\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a parachute.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:10.62,0:32:11.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我看出来了  乔治\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can see what is it, George.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:11.62,0:32:13.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我告诉过你  我来驾驶这架飞机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I already told you, I'm taking this plane in.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.78,0:32:18.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在地上时这样做或许没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That might have made sense back on the ground,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.53,0:32:20.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但坦白讲  杰克  最难的时刻已经过去了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but let's face it, Jack, the hard part's over.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:21.35,0:32:23.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你驾着飞机  远离城市\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You took off, cleared the city.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:24.00,0:32:26.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,剩下就只是平稳飞行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's left but flying straight and level
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.42,0:32:28.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,之后再进行俯冲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and taking it into a dive?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:29.54,0:32:30.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没说错吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Am I right?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.72,0:32:35.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,除非你一心求死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Unless of course maybe you wanna die.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.96,0:32:40.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你这话是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:42.03,0:32:44.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,自从特里死后你求生意志就不强\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You've had a death wish since Teri died.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:44.78,0:32:47.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看看你去年的所作所为\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The way things have been going for you the past year,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.28,0:32:50.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在做出这种结果也未尝是坏事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}this probably doesn't look like such a bad idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:50.73,0:32:52.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你将流芳百世\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You get to go out in a blaze of glory,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.07,0:32:55.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,成为受万人敬仰的英雄\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}one of the greatest heroes of all time.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.43,0:32:58.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,烦心事丢一边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Leave your troubles behind.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.75,0:33:02.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这种结果也不错  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This could be the easy way out, huh?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:08.19,0:33:09.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你还有你的人生  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You still got a life, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:10.16,0:33:12.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想当真英雄  那你就这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You wanna be a real hero, here's what you do.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:13.15,0:33:16.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你离开这里  振作起来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You get back down there and you put the pieces together.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:17.26,0:33:20.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对于你妻子的遭遇要学会放手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Find a way to forgive yourself for what happened to your wife,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.13,0:33:23.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要和女儿好好相处\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you make things right with your daughter,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.42,0:33:25.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,并且继续为国效力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and you go on serving your country.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:27.02,0:33:28.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这都需要勇气去面对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That'd take some real guts.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.36,0:33:43.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快  杰克  你有12分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go on, Jack. You got 12 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:43.09,0:33:46.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的决定是什么  想活还是想死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's it gonna be? You wanna live or not?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:56.76,0:34:00.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你真觉得你没问题  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You really think you can do this? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:01.33,0:34:05.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你百分百确定你做得到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You are absolutely sure you can do this?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:05.94,0:34:08.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  这就是我应该做的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, I'm supposed to do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:19.40,0:34:22.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你按当前的方向和速度飞就行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You need to maintain this heading and this airspeed.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:22.94,0:34:25.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只要定时器读数到一分半钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The second the LAD reads a minute and a half,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:25.68,0:34:28.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你就立刻按三十度角俯冲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you initiate a dive at a 30-degree angle.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:32.60,0:34:34.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样我不会提早冲进沙堆吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Won't that get me in early?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.00,0:34:35.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就是要这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's the point.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.45,0:34:37.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你必须保证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You have to be absolutely certain
Dialogue: 0,0:34:37.05,0:34:40.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,炸弹在引爆前就已经进入沙堆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that the bomb is already in the depression before it goes off.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:41.30,0:34:42.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,明白了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:53.46,0:34:54.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢  乔治\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you, George.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:58.65,0:34:59.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:21.51,0:35:24.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快点  杰克  带好降落伞赶快离开这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on. Jack. Get your chute on and get the hell outta here.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:24.51,0:35:26.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要尽量多陪你一会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm staying with you as long as possible.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:27.17,0:35:29.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我精神不错  杰克  我没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got it together. Jack. I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:29.10,0:35:31.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治  别和我讨价还价\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Geogre. This is not negotiable.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:31.08,0:35:33.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等引爆前4分钟我再行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm bailing out four minutes before impact.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:33.47,0:35:36.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那点时间应该够我跑的远远的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That should get me far enough away from the blast.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:36.13,0:35:37.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是杰克·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is Jack Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:37.16,0:35:38.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,帮我接通反恐组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Patch me through to CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:38.86,0:35:40.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  长官  马上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir. Right away.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:41.28,0:35:44.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我是阿尔梅达  -托尼  是我杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Almeida. - Tony, this is Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.18,0:35:46.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你立刻从空军调一架直升机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14} I need you to get a helicopter in the air immediately.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:46.33,0:35:47.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,计划临时有变\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We got a change of plans here.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:47.93,0:35:48.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我退出了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm bailing out.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:48.85,0:35:50.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治要接手飞机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George is taking the plane down.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:50.78,0:35:52.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治在那里干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's George doing there?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:52.35,0:35:55.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,每个声音需要至少三位人员来进行辨识\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We need authentication from at least three independent sources for each voice.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:55.82,0:35:58.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,部长们发表过公开讲话  分局有存档\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Division has public speeches from ministers.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:58.18,0:36:00.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看看你能否从电话窃听器听出他的声音\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}See if you can get his voice on phone taps.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:01.17,0:36:02.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:05.52,0:36:07.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想让你派架直升机跟踪杰克位置\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you to send a chopper to trail Jack's plane.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:07.78,0:36:09.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅森在飞机上  别问原因\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mason got on board. Don't ask how.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.79,0:36:11.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,飞机接下来由他接手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He'll take the plane the rest of the way.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:11.32,0:36:13.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克要离开那里  我们得派架直升机去接他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack's bailing out. We need that chopper to pick him up.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.96,0:36:15.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我稍后解释\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll explain later.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:16.85,0:36:20.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿尔梅达先生  能告诉我硬盘有什么发现吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Almeida, may I know what you found on the hard drive?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:20.56,0:36:23.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有安全许可不便透露  奥达先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm afraid you don't have security clearance. Mr. Auda.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:23.43,0:36:24.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿尔梅达先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Almeida.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.13,0:36:28.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我和我的国家出于好意帮助你们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I and my country have shown good faith in helping you
Dialogue: 0,0:36:28.16,0:36:31.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,寻找赛伊德·阿里的安全屋...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to find Syed Ali's safe house in the first place...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:32.07,0:36:33.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我希望你们能知恩图报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm asking you to do the same
Dialogue: 0,0:36:33.21,0:36:35.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我们现在是什么情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}by giving me some idea of what's going on.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:35.86,0:36:37.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很抱歉  但我现在不能告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry, but I can't tell you at this time.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:37.98,0:36:39.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们美国人啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You Americans.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:42.45,0:36:46.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们美国人怎么了  -没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- We Americans what? - Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:04.52,0:37:05.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请进\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:06.87,0:37:08.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先生  鲍登将军要见你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, General Bowden's here to see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:09.00,0:37:10.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  让他进来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course. Show him in.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.88,0:37:15.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-总统先生  -鲍登将军\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Mr. President. - General Bowden.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:16.25,0:37:18.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道炸弹现在在莫哈韦上空\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I understand the bomb is over the Mojave now.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:18.49,0:37:21.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,引爆后不会造成过多伤亡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It may detonate without causing many immediate loss of life.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:21.12,0:37:24.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-希望如此  -这太好了  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- That is our hope. - That's wonderful news. Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:24.39,0:37:26.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,非常佩服您的英明决断\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Congratulations on your truly remarkable achievement.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:26.82,0:37:28.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,多谢夸奖  将军\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you, General.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:28.53,0:37:29.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在  或许是时候\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, perhaps it's appropriate
Dialogue: 0,0:37:29.96,0:37:32.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,讨论一下反击策略了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to begin discussing the matter of retaliation.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:32.84,0:37:35.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-说吧  -好的  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Go on. - Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:35.09,0:37:37.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就在刚刚  参谋首长认定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}After now, the Joint Chiefs have been assuming
Dialogue: 0,0:37:37.12,0:37:40.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,炸弹是名为"第二波"的恐怖组织所为\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the bomb was the work of terrorist group called Second Wave.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:40.65,0:37:43.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在看来此恐怖组织背后至少有三个国家参与\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, it appears Second Wave had the backing of at least three governments.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:43.69,0:37:45.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在还犹未可知  将军\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's not definite yet, General.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:45.25,0:37:47.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  先生  我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, sir. I understand that.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:47.52,0:37:50.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但为了方便部署  我们还是要假定成这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But for planning purposes, we should proceed as if it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.10,0:37:53.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我请求授权启动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I request authority to activate plans
Dialogue: 0,0:37:53.29,0:37:54.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,入侵可疑国家的计划\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to invade the countries in question.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:54.98,0:37:56.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,启动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Activate?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:56.72,0:37:58.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,已经有相应的计划了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There are plans already in existence?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:58.95,0:38:02.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对于各种可预见性问题我们都有相应措施\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have plans for every conceivable contingency, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:03.03,0:38:04.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我懂了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I see.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:04.93,0:38:07.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你说的启动具体是指什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So what exactly do you mean by activate?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:07.47,0:38:09.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让相关军队警戒起来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Putting the relevant military units on alert,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.26,0:38:12.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,开始进行后勤行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}beginning logistical operations,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.47,0:38:17.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在美军入侵时多方协调\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}coordinating sources regarding the probable level of resistance
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.08,0:38:19.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可能遇到的各种敌对力量\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to an invasion by American forces.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:20.15,0:38:22.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谈论入侵还言之过早\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Talk of an invasion is premature.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:22.28,0:38:23.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我同意  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I agree, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:23.32,0:38:25.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些都还在计划阶段\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is in the planning stages only.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:30.51,0:38:32.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,启动你的计划吧  将军\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Activate your plan, General.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:32.98,0:38:34.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是没有我的亲口授权\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But take no steps to implement
Dialogue: 0,0:38:34.48,0:38:36.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不准采取任何实质措施\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}without my direct authorisation.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:36.44,0:38:37.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,遵命  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.18,0:38:46.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,林恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lynne.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.38,0:38:51.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,第三次世界大战可能要打响了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We may be talking about World War III.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:09.14,0:39:10.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  我好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK. I'm set.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.21,0:39:15.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治  你还有什么要嘱托的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George, is there anything you want me to take care of?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.09,0:39:19.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说来也怪  我觉得我把事情都处理好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oddly enough, I think I got everything squared away.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:20.79,0:39:22.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我甚至和我儿子还相处片刻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I even got to spend a little time with my son.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:24.09,0:39:25.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我都不知道你有个儿子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I didn't even know you had one.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:29.22,0:39:32.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我很高兴你们见了面  -是啊  我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'm glad you got to see him. - Yeah. Me, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:32.87,0:39:35.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得他可能并不高兴  可是...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't think he was particularly, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:35.86,0:39:39.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,其实  你能去看看他就更好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Actually, I wouldn't mind if you checked in on him.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:40.67,0:39:41.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course I will.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:00.09,0:40:01.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,时间到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's time.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:02.85,0:40:03.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:46.31,0:40:47.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:55.30,0:40:56.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:57.53,0:40:59.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在飞机的高度  应该能从\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}At this altitude, the explosion
Dialogue: 0,0:40:59.90,0:41:02.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,东方的地平线看到爆炸情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}should be visible on the eastern horizon.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.58,0:41:04.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道您想不想看一眼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know if you want to take a look.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:50.29,0:42:53.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,四  三  二...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Four, Three, two...

