[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,1,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.69,0:00:10.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(197.4,200.557)}{\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs25\b1\bord0\shad0\c&H78BDE7&\fad(0,808)}24小时\N\N{\fs15}第二季  第六集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.40,0:00:13.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(189.6,121.6,193.8,105.6,0,356)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad3\3c&H2F2F2F&\4c&H336D99&}{\fs10}{\t(0,356,\fs20)\fn方正正中黑简体}前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.96,0:00:15.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,罗杰  很高兴见到你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roger, it's good to see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.00,0:00:18.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想跟你说说这次会面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'd like to talk to you about this meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.95,0:00:17.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(291.6,192.553)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.00,0:00:17.04,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(289.2,186.953)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.04,0:00:17.08,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(284.4,182.153)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.08,0:00:17.12,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(281.4,175.2)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.12,0:00:17.16,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(277.2,168.553)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.16,0:00:17.20,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(275.4,163.753)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.20,0:00:17.24,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(270.6,157.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.24,0:00:17.28,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(268.2,152.553)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.28,0:00:17.33,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(265.2,146.153)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.33,0:00:17.37,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(261.6,139.753)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.37,0:00:17.41,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(258,134.153)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.41,0:00:17.45,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs13\c&H449BA1&\pos(253.8,130.953)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.45,0:00:17.49,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(252.6,124.553)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.49,0:00:17.54,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(249.6,117.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.54,0:00:17.58,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs15\c&H449BA1&\pos(245.4,112.553)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.58,0:00:17.62,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(244.2,106.153)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.62,0:00:17.66,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(238.8,101.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.66,0:00:17.70,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(236.4,98.153)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.70,0:00:19.16,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(234,90.953)\fad(0,432)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.57,0:00:19.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不信任大使\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't trust the ambassador.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.95,0:00:21.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们不能忽视一点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We can't ignore the possibility that
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.83,0:00:23.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他的国家可能在支持"第二波"\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}his country's supporting Second Wave.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.85,0:00:26.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们想阻止这个事件发生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We want to prevent this incident.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.78,0:00:28.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们需要查阅你们档案的权限\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We need access to your files.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.95,0:00:31.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你监控他们如何使用我们的信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you to monitor how they use our intel.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.22,0:00:36.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是大使的直升机  刚起飞就坠毁了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's the ambassador's chopper. It crashed just after takeoff.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.91,0:00:39.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这里有个人想和你谈谈  -什么人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- There's a man here who needs to talk to you. - Who is he?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.10,0:00:39.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(118.2,193.353)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.14,0:00:39.19,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(132,185.353)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.19,0:00:39.23,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(144.6,175.753)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.23,0:00:39.27,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs15\c&H449BA1&\pos(155.4,166.153)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.27,0:00:39.31,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(167.4,158.953)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.31,0:00:39.35,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(182.4,149.353)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.35,0:00:39.39,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(192,138.153)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.39,0:00:39.43,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(205.2,132.553)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.43,0:00:39.47,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(216.6,122.153)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.47,0:00:41.23,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(230.4,113.353)\fad(0,313)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.26,0:00:43.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他是政府的人  一个反恐机构\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's from the government, a counter-terrorism Agency?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.07,0:00:45.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我说过了  我不认识什么赛伊德·阿里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I told you before, I do not know a Syed Ali.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.07,0:00:46.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你怎么解释\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then how do you explain the fact
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.49,0:00:49.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他的名字出现在了你的个人电脑文件里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that his name is in your personal computer files?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.10,0:00:52.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,洛杉矶有一颗核弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's a nuclear bomb in Los Angeles.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.02,0:00:54.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,照我说的做  立刻离开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do what I tell you. Go now.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.49,0:00:52.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(228,194.153)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.53,0:00:52.58,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(221.4,187.753)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.58,0:00:52.62,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(212.4,182.153)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.62,0:00:52.66,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs15\c&H449BA1&\pos(204,175.753)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.66,0:00:52.70,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(196.2,167.753)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.70,0:00:52.74,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(189,162.953)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.74,0:00:52.78,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(180.6,157.353)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.78,0:00:52.82,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(171.6,150.153)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.82,0:00:52.86,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(163.2,143.753)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.86,0:00:52.90,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(152.4,136.553)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.90,0:00:52.95,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(145.2,129.353)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.95,0:00:52.99,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(136.2,122.153)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.99,0:00:54.70,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(127.2,117.353)\fad(0,395)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:54.84,0:00:56.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米格尔  过来找我吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Miguel, get over here, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.39,0:00:58.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他说城市里有一颗核弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He said there's a nuclear bomb in the city.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.11,0:01:01.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们赶快走吧  -不行  得带上梅根\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Let's get outta here. -No, we can't, not without Megan.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.66,0:01:02.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治  我审问了沃尔德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George, I got to Wald.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.74,0:01:05.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我找出了是谁让他袭击反恐组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I found out who commissioned him to take out CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.42,0:01:05.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(179.4,200.553)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.47,0:01:05.51,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(188.4,188.553)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.51,0:01:05.55,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(197.4,176.553)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.55,0:01:05.59,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs15\c&H449BA1&\pos(206.4,163.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.59,0:01:05.63,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(215.4,152.553)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.63,0:01:05.67,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(225,139.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.67,0:01:07.71,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\fad(0,354)\pos(234,127.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.69,0:01:07.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-谁  -尼娜·迈尔斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Who was it? - It was Nina Myers.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.90,0:01:08.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尼娜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nina?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.90,0:01:11.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尼娜杀了你的妻子  我不想让你接近她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nina killed your wife. I don't want you anywhere near her.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.39,0:01:13.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要为她提供庇护\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have to grant her a shadow asylum.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.18,0:01:16.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要赦免她吗  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That sounds like a pardon, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.34,0:01:18.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她有信息  能够帮助我们找到这颗核弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She has information that could help us find this bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.45,0:01:21.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么了  -他们要放她走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What is it? - They're gonna let her go.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:22.84,0:01:24.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治  我知道你今天早上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George, I know you were exposed to
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.19,0:01:27.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,接触到了高浓度的放射性物质\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}high levels of radioactive materials this morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.60,0:01:24.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(98.4,207.753)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.64,0:01:24.68,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(115.2,198.953)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.68,0:01:24.73,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(131.4,191.753)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.73,0:01:24.77,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs15\c&H449BA1&\pos(147.6,182.4)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.77,0:01:24.81,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(162.6,173.353)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.81,0:01:24.85,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(177.6,164.553)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.85,0:01:24.89,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(194.4,156.553)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.89,0:01:24.94,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(210,145.353)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.94,0:01:26.81,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(227.4,138.953)\fad(0,306)}乔治·梅森
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.06,0:01:28.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想知道你要怎么应对尼娜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wanna know what your plans are for Nina.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.77,0:01:31.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要接手此事  我了解她的心思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want the case. I know how she thinks.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.49,0:01:32.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你不这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you don't do this,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.03,0:01:34.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我就把你的情况告诉局里面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll tell District about your condition.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.04,0:01:36.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,分分钟让你走人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They'll have you replaced within minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.99,0:01:41.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs15\t(696,6577,\fs16)\c&H4BAAAD&\fad(1697,1183)\pos(187.2,191.79)}以下故事情节发生在下午1点到2点之间
Dialogue: 0,0:02:22.86,0:02:23.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,帕尔默刚签了特赦令\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Palmer just signed the pardon.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.93,0:02:28.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,东西一到就开始审问\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, as soon as it gets here, we'll start the interrogation.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.07,0:02:46.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-尼娜的档案  -我不需要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Nina's file. - I don't need it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.92,0:03:06.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The President's here.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.78,0:03:23.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.30,0:03:25.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  您能告诉我们一些\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, can you give us any details
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.36,0:03:26.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,直升机坠毁的细节吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}about the helicopter crash?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.68,0:03:30.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谁在飞机上  有人生还吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who was on the aircraft? Are there any survivors?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.78,0:03:33.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这和洛杉矶的爆炸案有关吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is it related to the bombing in LA?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.32,0:03:37.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在遇难者家属得到通知前\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We can't disclose any more information about the crash
Dialogue: 0,0:03:37.88,0:03:40.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们不能透露更多有关坠机的信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}until the families of the victims have been notified.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.08,0:03:42.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我可以向你们保证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I can promise you,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.67,0:03:45.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会展开仔细  全面的调查\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}there will be a careful and thorough investigation.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.31,0:03:47.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-总统先生...  -走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Mr. President... - Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.99,0:03:50.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托大家  一旦解决了这些问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Everyone please, we will be putting out a formal statement
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.60,0:03:52.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们就会发表正式声明\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}as soon as we get those issues resolved,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:52.70,0:03:56.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我请各位在那之前不要妄加揣测\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and I ask everyone to refrain from speculation until that time.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.47,0:04:00.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,除了珍尼以外  没人就坠毁一事发表看法\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No one besides Jenny releases a statement on the crash.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.33,0:04:03.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有名字  没有推测  严密封锁信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No names, no speculation. And keep the lid on tight.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.50,0:04:04.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没问题  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Absolutely, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.61,0:04:20.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你好  大卫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hello, David.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.09,0:04:24.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有我的授权你是怎么进来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How did you get in here without my authorization?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.14,0:04:26.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们结婚很多年了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We were married for many years.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.40,0:04:28.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很多人尊重这个事实  即使你不在意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Many people respect that, even if you don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.65,0:04:33.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得和你聊聊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need to talk to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.21,0:04:34.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们没什么可聊的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have nothing more to talk about.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.07,0:04:37.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不再是我妻子了  雪莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're not my wife any more, Sherry.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.37,0:04:40.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不是我们的事  -那是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It's not about us. - Then what?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.44,0:04:48.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在这不方面  我要和你单独说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not here. I need to be alone with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.40,0:04:49.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.37,0:04:52.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,即使我对你要说的话感兴趣\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Even if I were interested in what you had to say,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.52,0:04:54.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天也不可能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}today is impossible.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.49,0:04:56.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不该来这\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You shouldn't have come here.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.21,0:05:01.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-事关你的政府  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It's about your administration. - What about it?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.37,0:05:04.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我只需要五分钟  -我现在没空\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Just give me five minutes. - I don't have time now.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.52,0:05:06.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是你下令让军事人员撤离\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did you order an evacuation of military personnel
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.96,0:05:08.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,洛杉矶的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}out of Los Angeles?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.50,0:05:29.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谁和你说的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who told you that?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.23,0:05:34.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就五分钟  大卫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Five minutes, David.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.26,0:05:38.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在这等着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wait here.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.60,0:05:40.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会叫你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll call you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:48.93,0:05:52.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们知道军事行动人员撤离洛杉矶吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do we know about the military moving personnel out of LA?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.26,0:05:56.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  总统  您特别要求不要撤离\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. Sir, you specifically requested there be no evacuation.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.16,0:05:59.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-确认一下  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Check into it. - I certainly will.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.85,0:06:03.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在和一个众所周知的恐怖分子交易\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're doing business with a known terrorist,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.12,0:06:05.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你现在要一本正经的坐在那里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and you're gonna sit there with a straight face
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.93,0:06:07.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,和我说你不知道怎么回事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and tell me you don't know what's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.67,0:06:14.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在伦敦长大\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I grew up in London.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.76,0:06:18.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我娶了一个美国姑娘  一个新教徒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm marrying an American girl, a Protestant.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.09,0:06:24.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你要用种族定性那一套\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, if you're going to racially profile me,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.72,0:06:28.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,至少找对方向\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you should at least get it right.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.75,0:06:33.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你听过芬斯伯里公园清真寺吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You ever hear of the Finsbury Park Mosque?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:36.59,0:06:38.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,它被认为是西方伊斯兰恐怖分子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's considered to be one of the main recruitment centers
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.95,0:06:41.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,主要的招募中心之一\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}for Islamic terrorists in the West.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.72,0:06:45.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们的主要目标是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Our main targets are European Muslims
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.24,0:06:49.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,接受西方教育  持有西方护照\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}with western educations, passports,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.83,0:06:52.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,具有融入西方社会潜力的欧洲穆斯林\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and the potential to blend into western society.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.18,0:06:58.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道那所清真寺的位置吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And do you know where that mosque is located?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.22,0:07:06.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的家乡  伦敦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your hometown... London.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.97,0:07:12.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来说说  雷扎  我的种族定性现在如何\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So tell me, Reza, how's my racial profiling going now?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.58,0:07:15.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要一名律师\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want a lawyer.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.90,0:07:18.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.91,0:07:25.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-找倒黑匣子了吗  -还没有  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Did they find the black box yet? - Not yet, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.25,0:07:28.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可恶  罗杰  怎么会发生这样的事呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Damn it, Roger, how could something like this happen?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.49,0:07:29.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不知道  总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.51,0:07:31.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我已经展开了一场多机构调查\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've opened a multi-agency investigation.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.74,0:07:33.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,国家交通安全局正在路上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}NTSB is on the way.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.67,0:07:37.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,林恩  安排与首相的通话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lynne, schedule a call with the Prime Minister.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.74,0:07:39.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:39.18,0:07:41.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要在流言四起之前和他通话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wanna talk to him before rumours start.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.96,0:07:44.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是我担心他们也快接近真相了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I'm afraid they may not be far from the truth.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.63,0:07:46.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这不是意外\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This was not an accident.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.31,0:07:49.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也是这么想的  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm thinking along the same lines, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.02,0:07:52.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,首相可能因大使与我们的合作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The Prime Minister may not have been happy
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.89,0:07:55.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而感到不满\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}about the ambassador's cooperation with us.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:56.64,0:07:58.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有一种可能  罗杰\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's another possibility, Roger.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.82,0:08:01.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没听明白  总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not following you, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.23,0:08:06.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-是我们制造的事故  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- That we did it. - Correct.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.54,0:08:09.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这似乎不大可能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That hardly seems likely.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.33,0:08:11.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大使当时正将机密情报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The ambassador was taking classified information
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.16,0:08:12.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,带回他的国家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}back to his government.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:13.26,0:08:15.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们俩都对这个决定存疑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Both of you thought it was a questionable call.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.50,0:08:17.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我们要在这里讨论这个问题  总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And if we were talking about it here, sir,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.76,0:08:19.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,华盛顿肯定有一些人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you can bet there are others back in DC
Dialogue: 0,0:08:19.48,0:08:20.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对此反应更强烈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}who feel even more strongly.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.28,0:08:24.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,设一个独立的调查人员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Set up an independent investigator.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.97,0:08:27.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我们看看到底是谁在主使\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's find out exactly who was in the loop.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.17,0:08:28.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.27,0:08:40.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  就这个  开始吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, this is it. Here we go.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.78,0:08:44.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我给她看这个  我会让她开口\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll show her this, I'll let her start talking.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.61,0:08:46.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我能套出你想要的信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then I'll get you everything you want
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.97,0:08:49.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,即使她不想我们知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}even the stuff she doesn't want us to know.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.34,0:08:52.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得提醒你  上次我让你审问人时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have to remind you the last time I let you interrogate somebody,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.01,0:08:53.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你可是击中了他的心脏\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you shot him in the heart.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.01,0:08:57.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我可以让你去做  希望这不是个错误的决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can do this, but I hope I'm not making a mistake.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.40,0:08:58.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是错误  乔治\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No mistake, George.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.70,0:09:02.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  好运\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. Good luck.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.74,0:10:01.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,开门见山吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's keep this simple.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.54,0:10:02.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你想阻止爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you wanna stop the bomb,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.51,0:10:05.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就必须让我立刻坐飞机去维萨利亚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need to be on a plane to Visalia now.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.88,0:10:08.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你选择维萨利亚是有原因的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did you pick Visalia for a reason,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.27,0:10:11.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还是爆炸区以外的任何地方都可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}or would anywhere outside the blast zone work?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.58,0:10:15.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我的接头人在维萨利亚  -谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- My contact is in Visalia. - Who is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.29,0:10:17.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,唯一能告诉我们炸弹位置的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The only person who can tell us where the bomb is.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.07,0:10:21.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们到那之前我是不会供出这个人的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not gonna tell you who it is till we get there.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.45,0:10:26.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  那你就坐在这里等着爆炸吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fine. Then you can sit here and wait for the blast to hit.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.17,0:10:29.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别浪费时间了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stop wasting time.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.22,0:10:31.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,摆在我眼前的可是总统签字的文件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sitting here looking at the President's signature.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:31.87,0:10:34.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在这我说得算  不是他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm here. He's not.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.68,0:10:37.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在我相信你之前我是不会采取行动的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I'm not gonna make a move until I believe you're credible.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.54,0:10:40.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只有阻止爆炸才能得到豁免\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll only get the pardon if I stop the bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.76,0:10:42.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我有什么好保留的呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why wouldn't I do everything I can?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:43.18,0:10:45.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为你还不如一个叛徒  尼娜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because you're worse than a traitor, Nina.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.40,0:10:49.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你连个信条都没有  毫无信仰\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't even have a cause. You don't believe in anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.81,0:10:52.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但你会把任何人任何事出卖给价码最高的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But you would sell anyone and everything out to the highest bidder.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:52.76,0:10:56.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别浪费我的时间了  把名字告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So stop wasting my time! Give me a name!
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.06,0:11:02.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,省省吧  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't even bother, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.29,0:11:06.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要是敢动我一下  这案子你就办不了了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you lay a hand on me, you'll be taken off the case.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.87,0:11:30.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你只能按我的意思行事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're just gonna have to follow my lead.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.71,0:11:44.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要把知道的一切都告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're gonna tell me everything I wanna know.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.41,0:11:45.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-开门  -否则我发誓\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Open it. - Or I swear to God,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.98,0:11:49.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谁也拦不住我狠狠地折磨你再杀了你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I will hurt you before I kill you and no one will stop me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:49.32,0:11:51.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-听明白了吗  -杰克  放开她  快点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Do you understand? - Jack, let her go! Now!
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.89,0:12:13.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-够了  你出去  -为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- All right, you're done. Get outta here. - Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:13.98,0:12:16.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么  因为你失控了  就因为这个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why? Because you've lost it! That's why.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.32,0:12:20.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治  现在她以为中了大奖  尽在掌控\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George, right now she thinks she's won the lottery. She's in control.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.45,0:12:23.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想让她说实话  就不能让她有这个想法\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You want her to tell the truth, you take that away from her.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.13,0:12:24.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杀了她吗  那倒是有效果\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}By killing her? That'll work.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.90,0:12:28.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给她一个管事的人  一个她怕的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}By giving her someone to answer to, someone to be afraid of.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.68,0:12:29.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,得让她相信\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She has to believe that
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.53,0:12:32.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我愿意把她的复仇凌驾于找到炸弹之上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'd be willing to put her revenge over finding this bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.19,0:12:34.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是说你不想这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And you're telling me you're not.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.45,0:12:36.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治  戏要演得像那么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George, it had to look like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.36,0:12:40.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看着我  这里面没有个人恩怨\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look at me. There's no emotion here.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:41.64,0:12:42.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看看她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now look at her.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:44.97,0:12:46.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,目前你说得还算有道理\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's say for the time being you've made your point.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.73,0:12:47.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你下一步打算怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What would your next move be?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.77,0:12:49.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你得允许我回到屋子里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You need to let me go back in there,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.09,0:12:52.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让她知道我有权利想把她怎样就怎样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}show her that I have the power to do anything I want to her.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.53,0:13:03.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果让你回去的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If I let you go back in there,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.45,0:13:06.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你要...  -乔治  给我五分钟就行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- you've got... - George. All I need is five minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.28,0:13:11.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谁都别进来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just don't let anyone in that room
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.59,0:13:13.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再把空调调高十度\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and raise the thermostat ten degrees.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.36,0:13:17.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能给我五分钟时间吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you gonna let me have five minutes?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.81,0:13:22.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:24.21,0:13:25.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.41,0:13:40.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,上次的播报中  总统要求\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In the latest update, we have Mr. President requesting...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:53.01,0:13:54.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们得谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We need to talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.94,0:13:58.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我让你离开了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I told you to leave.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.71,0:14:03.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not leaving.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.31,0:14:06.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是你姐姐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm your sister,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.77,0:14:10.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你可以继续生我的气\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and you can stay angry with me,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.46,0:14:12.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是我们得想办法接下来该怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but we need to figure out what we're going to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.39,0:14:15.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do about what?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.27,0:14:18.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,婚礼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The wedding.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.61,0:14:25.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们可能要取消了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We may have to cancel.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.42,0:14:30.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那就正中你的下怀了  不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That would make you happy, wouldn't it?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.52,0:14:33.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这不是你一直期待的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Isn't that what you wanted all along?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.78,0:14:36.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是的  不是悔婚  玛丽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. Not the marriage, Marie.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.51,0:14:38.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是婚礼而已\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just the wedding.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.02,0:14:44.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们今天办不了了  我来帮你解决\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We can't do it today. Let me help you take care of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.58,0:14:47.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你总是假装你想要帮我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You are always pretending you wanna help me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.75,0:14:48.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,假装\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Pretending?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.03,0:14:54.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,咱妈去世后我为了照顾你辍学在家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I dropped out of school when Mom died to take care of you,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.57,0:14:57.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好让一家人继续生活\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to keep this family together.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.05,0:14:59.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以你就有不谈婚论嫁的理由的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So you'd have an excuse for not having a relationship.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.73,0:15:02.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"爸爸需要我  玛丽需要我"\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Dad needs me. Marie needs me."
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.27,0:15:04.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在我再也不需要你了  你管不了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now I don't need you any more, you can't handle it!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.83,0:15:06.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我做出了牺牲  因为...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I made sacrifices because...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.40,0:15:08.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不用再牺牲了  妈妈早就没了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then stop! Mom died a long time ago!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:08.89,0:15:11.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,过好你自己的日子  少来掺和我的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So get your own life and stay outta mine!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.41,0:15:14.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个婚礼不能取消\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We are not cancelling this wedding!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.55,0:15:20.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她不在重症监护室  也不在东配楼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's not in intensive care she's not the east wing.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.52,0:15:21.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她肯定在这边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's gotta be up here.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.26,0:15:24.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们有多长时间来对付这个核武器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How much time do we have to this nuke?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.71,0:15:28.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不知道  -要是梅根不想跟我们走怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I don't know. - What if Megan doesn't wanna come with us?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.55,0:15:30.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.44,0:15:34.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就是他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's him.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.83,0:15:43.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,马西森先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Matheson?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.72,0:15:51.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,核磁共振和体检结果确认了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The MRI and the physical exam confirmed that
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.86,0:15:53.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,头部的压力是脑震荡的造成的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the pressure on the brain was the result of the concussion.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.83,0:15:55.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Meaning?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.26,0:15:57.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,马西森先生  在我们查明她的伤源之前\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That we won't release her, Mr. Matheson, until questions
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.80,0:16:01.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是不会允许她离开这里的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}regarding the sources of her injuries are resolved.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:03.11,0:16:04.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.95,0:16:07.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我所做的一切都是为了我的女儿好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen, I just wanna do what's best for my little girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:08.09,0:16:11.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我临下班之前再来看看她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good. I'll check in on her at the end of my rounds.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.82,0:16:16.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,马西森先生  医院里不允许使用手机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And, Mr. Matheson, no cellphones in the hospital.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.66,0:16:18.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,它们会干扰医疗设备\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They interfere with the equipment.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.03,0:16:21.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course. Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:29.40,0:16:31.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸爸  你还生我的气吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Daddy, are you still mad at me?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.67,0:16:36.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  宝贝  没事  爸爸就是累了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, sweetie, no. Everything's fine. Daddy's just tired.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.26,0:16:38.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你得换衣服  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You need to get dressed, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.23,0:16:42.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-马西森先生办公室  -切尔西  是我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Mr. Matheson's office. - Chelsea, it's me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.38,0:16:45.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在帮我个忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen, you gotta do something for me right away.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.18,0:16:47.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给我订两张最近一班去墨西哥城的机票\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Book me two seats on the next flight to Mexico City.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.64,0:16:48.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是你有会...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But you have a meeting...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.89,0:16:50.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, I know about the meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.99,0:16:52.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是让你取消会议\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm asking you to cancel it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:52.34,0:16:54.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那五点钟的呢  -全都取消\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What about your five o'clock? - Cancel everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.75,0:17:09.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在维萨利亚的那个人是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who is the man in Visalia?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.35,0:17:17.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在维萨利亚的那个人是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who is the man in Visalia?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.18,0:17:21.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,马穆·法海因  在维萨利亚的马穆·法海因\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mamud Faheen. The man in Visalia is Mamud Faheen.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.63,0:17:23.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这不算新线索  这个人我们知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's not news! We've got his name!
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.31,0:17:26.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是你们不知道他在哪  我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But you don't know where he is. I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.28,0:17:29.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们之间什么关系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's the history of the relationship?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.58,0:17:31.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他把我介绍给了沃尔德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He introduced me to Wald.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:31.45,0:17:33.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以沃尔德能买到反恐组的图纸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So that Wald can buy a schematic for CTU
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.70,0:17:36.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后把它炸掉分散核武袭击的注意力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and blow it up as a diversion for a nuclear strike?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.06,0:17:38.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我并不知道这是更大的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I didn't know it was part of a larger plan
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.59,0:17:40.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,引爆核武器计划的一部分\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to detonate a nuclear device.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.68,0:17:43.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你为什么笃定法海因参与了其中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then why are you so sure Faheen's involved?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.42,0:17:44.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为在我被捕之前\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because before I was arrested,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.74,0:17:47.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我听说他参与了洛杉矶的一些事情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I heard hints that he was involved in something in Los Angeles.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.21,0:17:49.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,像是大事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Something substantial.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.05,0:17:59.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在他在维萨利亚的哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where is he in Visalia now?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.17,0:18:04.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们到那之前我是不会告诉你他的准确位置的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not gonna give you his location until we get there.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.09,0:18:09.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要是找得到他的话  你就不需要我了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you knew how to get to him, you wouldn't need me any more.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.05,0:18:11.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要是死了对我没什么好处\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And the deal I made wouldn't do me much good if I'm dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.19,0:18:30.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,联系维萨利亚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get me Visalia.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.85,0:18:56.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.83,0:19:00.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雪莉说得对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sherry was right.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.30,0:19:03.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大概一小时之前有军事人员和资源开始撤离\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}An evacuation of military personnel and resources began
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.36,0:19:06.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也就是说  这一步早就策划好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}about an hour ago, which means destage is well under way.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.61,0:19:08.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,知道是谁下的命令吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do we know where this order came from?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.17,0:19:10.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,知道  总统  罗杰·斯坦顿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, we do, sir. Roger Stanton.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.83,0:19:15.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,传达我的命令  取消撤离\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Countermand the evacuation on my authority.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:15.90,0:19:18.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所有行进中的部队\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All forces already in the process of moving
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.04,0:19:19.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,立即返回到各自的基地\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}are to return to their bases immediately.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:19.98,0:19:20.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:23.27,0:19:25.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,罗杰  到我办公室来一趟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roger. My office, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.66,0:19:27.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,珍尼特  我是林恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Janet? Hi, this is Lynne.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.54,0:19:30.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要一下基地的联系方式\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna need contacts for the following bases:
Dialogue: 0,0:19:31.03,0:19:33.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,穆古角  彭德尔顿营\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Point Mugu, Camp Pendleton.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.88,0:19:39.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,罗杰  我刚刚听说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roger, I just got word
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.32,0:19:41.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,军事资源正在撤离洛杉矶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that military resources were being moved out of LA.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.59,0:19:43.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-是的  总统先生  -你下的令\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yes, Mr. President. - On your order.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:43.78,0:19:47.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  我在实施计划\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes. I was implementing the plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.68,0:19:49.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我以为是你下令的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I assumed you authorized it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.77,0:19:53.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  我告诉雷伯恩不许采取任何撤离\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, I told Rayburn not to trigger any evacuation.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.25,0:20:00.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我应该在采取行动之前反复核查\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I should have double-checked everything Rayburn told me
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.97,0:20:02.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雷伯恩跟我说的所有事情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}before I took any action.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.85,0:20:08.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  我无可辩驳  我负全部责任\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, it's inexcusable. I take full responsibility.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.77,0:20:10.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们待会再处理这个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll worry about that later.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.10,0:20:13.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我刚刚告诉林恩撤销撤离的命令\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just told Lynne to countermand the evacuation order.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.21,0:20:19.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-确保立刻执行  -好的  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Make sure it happens immediately. - Right away, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.90,0:20:28.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,需要帮助吗  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can I help you, Mr. President?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.11,0:20:32.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有  告诉雪莉我们要在二十分钟内见面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes. Tell Sherry I'll meet her in 20 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:32.31,0:20:33.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,收到  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.41,0:20:35.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道爸爸有多爱你  不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know how much Daddy loves you, don't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.05,0:20:40.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你也知道我的小天使受伤后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And you know how sorry I am
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.20,0:20:43.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我有多抱歉  对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that my little angel ever got hurt, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.40,0:20:55.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  我们现在需要离开了  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen, pal, we're leaving now, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.94,0:20:58.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果有人和你说话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So if anybody tries to talk to you,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:58.40,0:21:01.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你一个字也别说  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you just... you don't say a word. OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.18,0:21:05.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,假装睡着了  你可以做到的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just pretend you're asleep. You can do that, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.46,0:21:07.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好的  -很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Ok. - Ok.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.41,0:21:09.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,马西森先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Matheson?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.99,0:21:13.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有你的电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's a call for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.43,0:21:15.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A call?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.40,0:21:20.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你可以在护士站接\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You can take it at the nurse's station.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.54,0:21:21.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么不能在这里接\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why can't I take it in here?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.62,0:21:25.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为病房里没有电话  除非你来买\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because we don't have phones in the rooms unless you order one.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.87,0:21:33.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,待在这里  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You stay there, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.37,0:21:38.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅根  别动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Megan, don't move.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.92,0:21:45.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-她应该没事了  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Looks like she'll be fine. - OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.78,0:21:48.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吗  还需要做几项检查\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK? Just running a few other tests.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.79,0:21:50.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会花很长时间吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is it gonna be much longer?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.25,0:21:51.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,电话就在里面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The phone's right in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.79,0:21:53.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们一起去看看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So let's go take a look, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:58.34,0:22:01.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我是 加里·马西森  -马西森先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- This is Gary Matheson. - Mr. Matheson?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.57,0:22:03.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  你是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, who is this?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.05,0:22:04.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是医院财务部的特雷·威廉姆斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is Trey Williams in Accounts Receivable.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:05.81,0:22:07.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们的电脑似乎出了些故障\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It seems that our computers crashed,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.35,0:22:09.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,导致我们遗失了您的很多账务信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and we lost a lot of your billing information.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.89,0:22:11.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我们可以再过一遍\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So if we could just go over it again...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.05,0:22:15.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可以改天吗  拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can we do this another time, please?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.12,0:22:17.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们现在就需要  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, we need it now, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.59,0:22:20.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你需要  我可以派人去你女儿的病房\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you like, I can send someone up to your daughter's room.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.76,0:22:24.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不用了  你需要哪些信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. What do you need?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.75,0:22:32.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-嗨  金  -嗨  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Hi, Kim. - Hi, sweetie.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.04,0:22:39.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-听着  你相信我吗  -相信\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Listen, do you trust me? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.63,0:22:43.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要带你离开这里  但来不及解释原因\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need to get you outta here, and I can't explain why.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.10,0:22:44.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我能告诉你的就是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All I can tell you is I'm doing this
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.30,0:22:48.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的所作所为都是因为我爱你  希望你安全\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}because I love you and I want you to be safe. OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.04,0:22:58.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ok.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.83,0:23:00.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.03,0:23:05.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-失效日期  -2007年三月  行了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- The expiration date? - It expires March 2007, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.87,0:23:09.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好  如果我们可以过一遍你的账单地址\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Great. Now if we could just go over your billing address.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.93,0:23:12.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样吧  我待会再打过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what? I'll come down later.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.57,0:23:13.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,马西森先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Matheson?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.71,0:23:28.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅根\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Megan?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.41,0:23:38.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我女儿不见了  -厕所找了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- My daughter's gone. - Did you try the bathroom?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.46,0:23:42.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-找了  不在  -她可能被带去放射科了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yes. She's not there. - She might have been taken to radiology.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.65,0:23:44.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,找到她在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, find out where she is.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.48,0:23:46.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当然了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:51.63,0:23:56.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,夏皮罗医生  请到2262病房\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Dr. Shapiro, 2262. Dr Shapiro, 2262.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.31,0:24:17.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要去哪儿  金\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where are we going, Kim?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:17.90,0:24:19.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没有时间解释  你得相信我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I told you I don't have time to explain, you have to trust me.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.18,0:24:23.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我刚刚挂掉电话  快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just got off the phone. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.77,0:24:26.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我改变主意了  我不想走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I changed my mind. I don't wanna go.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.21,0:24:27.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的爸爸会变得很生气\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My daddy's gonna get really mad,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.61,0:24:31.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他会打我的  我不想走了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and then he's gonna hurt me. I don't wanna go.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.97,0:24:34.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就是因为他会伤害你  所以我们得赶快离开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We need to get out of here because your dad is hurting you.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.71,0:24:37.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你妈妈尝试阻止他  但是失败了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And your mom is trying to stop him, but she can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.84,0:24:39.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,除非你现在跟我们一起走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's gonna keep hurting you
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.86,0:24:41.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,否则他会一直伤害你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}unless you leave with us right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:41.25,0:24:43.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是阻止他的唯一办法\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's the only way anyone is gonna stop him.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:43.10,0:24:44.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你明白吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you understand me?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.19,0:24:45.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,唯一的办法\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The only way.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.86,0:24:47.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们给科室都打了电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We called all the departments.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.30,0:24:48.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都没有看到你女儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your daughter's not with any of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.14,0:24:49.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那她还会在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then where the hell is she?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.14,0:24:51.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也在努力找呢  马西森先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm trying to figure that out, Mr. Matheson
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.62,0:24:52.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有看到任何人进入她的病房吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did you see anyone go in her room?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.61,0:24:54.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有  联系安保人员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No! Call security!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.64,0:24:56.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,找看门的  找到我的女儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get somebody on the door. Find me my daughter!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:57.03,0:25:00.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅根  深呼吸  平静下来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Megan, I need you to breathe and calm down
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.48,0:25:03.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别再哭了  我们就可以离开了  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and stop crying, so we can leave now. OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.10,0:25:05.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.56,0:25:09.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想妈妈了  我要妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I miss my mom. I want my mom!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:09.51,0:25:12.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我明白  跟我走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know. Come on with me. I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.47,0:25:22.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,寻找一个九岁的金发女孩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look out for a nine-year-old girl with blonde hair,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.03,0:25:24.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,穿条纹衫  蓝色牛仔裤\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}striped top and blue jeans.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.93,0:25:27.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我守着第三长廊  西门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've got Third Street, west door covered.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.41,0:25:33.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,进去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In there.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.34,0:26:00.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,刚刚收到一个维萨利亚小队的消息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just got a team on the ground in Visalia,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.27,0:26:01.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有更多来自弗雷斯诺的消息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and more coming in from Fresno.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.36,0:26:04.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,国防部借用了一些人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Division's loaned us some men,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.30,0:26:06.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我派米勒和你一起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so I'm sending Miller along with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.61,0:26:08.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我一个人就可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can handle her myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.54,0:26:10.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我所担心的不是这个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's not what I'm worried about.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.11,0:26:15.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你觉得我真的会为了杀她的一时之快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you think I'd really sentence millions of people to death
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.44,0:26:17.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而置百万人的安危不顾吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}just for the satisfaction of killing her?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:22.78,0:26:24.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会做好我该做的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll do my job.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:25.03,0:26:27.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我派米勒一起去只是确保你这样做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm just sending Miller along to make sure of that.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.48,0:26:58.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你应该和家人待在一起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You should go be with your family.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:00.20,0:27:01.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你该登机了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You should get on a plane.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.58,0:27:07.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们登机后再联系你  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'll call you when we're in the air. - Yeah. Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.92,0:27:15.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大卫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}David...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:15.35,0:27:17.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是怎么知道军队撤离的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How did you find out about the military evacuation?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:18.78,0:27:20.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我打了一些电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I made some phone calls.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.48,0:27:22.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是想确认一下传闻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just following up on a rumour.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:22.99,0:27:24.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我能说的只有这些\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't tell you any more than that.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.47,0:27:27.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你会告诉我的  我不会再问你另一遍\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You will tell me more, and I will not ask you again.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.84,0:27:34.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我又不是你的职工  大卫  我是你妻子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I am not a member of your staff, David. I am your wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.46,0:27:36.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,前妻  你会告诉我的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ex-wife, and you will tell me
Dialogue: 0,0:27:36.66,0:27:38.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为这个国家的安全\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}because the safety and security of this country
Dialogue: 0,0:27:38.87,0:27:41.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,比你的任何权利游戏都重要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is more important than any of your power plays.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.50,0:27:45.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尽管出了这么多事  但我还是爱你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, despite everything that's happened, I love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:45.74,0:27:48.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-拜托了  -我永远都会爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Oh, please. - No, I always will.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:48.42,0:27:49.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不管你是否相信\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Whether you want to believe it or not,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:49.80,0:27:53.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我所做的一切都是为你的利益着想\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}everything that I have done has been in your best interest.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.02,0:27:59.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你心里不愿意给我第二次机会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you won't give me a second chance at your heart,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.28,0:28:02.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那让我在力所能及的范围内帮助你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}let me help in the ways you know I can.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.59,0:28:04.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而我帮不到你  大卫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I can't help you, David,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.91,0:28:08.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,除非你给我描述一下你面对着什么危机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}unless you give me some idea of what you're facing.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.37,0:28:15.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我能发现这些事情  而你自己的职工却不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was able to find something your own staff couldn't find.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.87,0:28:19.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没有必要警告你  我是自愿来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I didn't have to warn you. I came here on my own accord.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:26.53,0:28:29.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有恐怖分子准备对洛杉矶实施恐怖袭击\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Terrorists have planned a strike against Los Angeles.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:30.47,0:28:32.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,国安局认为就在今天\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}NSA thinks it'll be today.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.82,0:28:34.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么样的袭击\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What kind of strike?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:35.32,0:28:36.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,核弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nuclear.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:37.39,0:28:38.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的天\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, my G...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:40.03,0:28:41.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的天\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:45.12,0:28:46.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我  雪莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Talk to me, Sherry.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.92,0:28:50.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:51.89,0:28:55.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是从国防部的一个人那里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got the information about the military evacuation
Dialogue: 0,0:28:55.01,0:28:58.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,得到军队撤离消息的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}from someone inside the defence department.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:58.40,0:28:59.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:59.79,0:29:03.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一个高级官员  局内人  他欠我一个人情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A high-level staffer. He's in the loop. He owed me a favour.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.05,0:29:07.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但还有更重要的事情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But there's something more important.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:07.68,0:29:08.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他还告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He also told me that
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.88,0:29:12.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的政府内部有人联合起来反对你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}there are members of your own administration allying against you.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.95,0:29:15.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想要控制你的权利\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They want control of your presidency.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:16.63,0:29:18.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这就是我今天来的原因\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's why I came here today.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.54,0:29:21.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谁  雪莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who, Sherry?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:22.06,0:29:24.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反对你的政策的那些人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}People who disagree with your policies,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:25.01,0:29:27.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想要以自己的意愿治理国家的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}who want to impose their will on the country.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.20,0:29:30.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,已经有很多私下交易了  大卫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There have been deals made under the table, David.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.32,0:29:31.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,各种幕后承诺\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Back-room promises.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.03,0:29:35.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我可以继续查下去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, I can keep digging, find out.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.08,0:29:38.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你需要我的帮助\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you want my help.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:56.76,0:29:59.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我接受你的帮助  这并不是事关我俩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If I accept your help, it won't be about us.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.76,0:30:02.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这事关整个国家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It'll be about doing what's best for the country.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:03.55,0:30:07.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亲爱的  你怎么说都可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sweetheart, you can call it anything you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:10.20,0:30:11.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会给你安排安全的专线\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll get you a secure line
Dialogue: 0,0:30:12.40,0:30:13.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,和隐蔽的地点  以便你通话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and a private place to make your calls.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:13.94,0:30:16.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我一查到更多信息  就立刻去找你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then I'll come to you as soon as I find out more.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.86,0:30:26.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这最好不是你想操纵我的把戏之一\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This had better not be one of your manipulations.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:27.34,0:30:28.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,赌注太高了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The stakes are too high.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:52.03,0:30:53.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:55.13,0:30:56.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雷扎的父母来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Reza's parents are here.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.95,0:30:58.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我正在和你奶奶讲电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm on the phone to your grandmother.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:58.53,0:30:59.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我马上过去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll be right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:06.63,0:31:07.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're here!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:09.38,0:31:10.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,欢迎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:11.37,0:31:14.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-很高兴见到你  凯特  -请进\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- So nice to see you, Kate. - Come on in.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:14.03,0:31:14.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:16.03,0:31:17.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,房子很漂亮\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The house looks beautiful.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.64,0:31:19.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:20.28,0:31:24.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们肯定累了  我们去客厅吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well... you must be tired. Let's go into the living room.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:24.95,0:31:25.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:28.40,0:31:30.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大家都怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, how is everyone holding up?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:31.31,0:31:32.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not too bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:33.69,0:31:35.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雷扎呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where is Reza?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.59,0:31:39.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们现在有些小问题要处理\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Um, well, there's a small problem we're dealing with.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:39.26,0:31:40.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What kind of problem?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:42.84,0:31:47.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有几个政府的人来找他谈话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Um, some men from the government are here talking to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:48.89,0:31:50.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}About?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.33,0:31:54.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为一起刑事调查\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a criminal investigation.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:54.08,0:31:56.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,刑事调查  我不明白\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Criminal investigation? I don't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.53,0:31:59.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-说来复杂  -凯特  到底怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It's very complicated. - Kate, what is going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:59.97,0:32:02.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最好等雷扎自己告诉你们吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It would be best if Reza told you himself.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.46,0:32:04.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我们什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Told us what?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.11,0:32:08.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们来找雷扎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're talking to Reza
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.10,0:32:12.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说他有可能涉及恐怖活动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}about his possible involvement in terrorist activities.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:13.64,0:32:17.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-简直是荒谬  -肯定是搞错了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- That is absurd! - This must be a mistake.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:17.07,0:32:19.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-所以他们想要查清楚  -看到没\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Well, that's what they're trying to find out. - You see?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:20.17,0:32:24.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们的国家  所谓的宽容和自由\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your country, you talk about tolerance, you talk about freedom,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:24.97,0:32:28.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但你们却把所有的中东人都当恐怖分子来对待\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but you treat every Middle Easterner like he was terrorist!
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.73,0:32:30.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  当然不是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No! No, of course not.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:31.17,0:32:32.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我相信事情会水落石出的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sure it'll all get sorted out.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.85,0:32:34.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,里马  哈桑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Rima, Hassan...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:34.16,0:32:36.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鲍勃  这件事你知道吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bob, Bob, do you know about this?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:36.61,0:32:38.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们一小时前来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They just showed up about an hour ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.84,0:32:40.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我什么也不知道  对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know nothing else. I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.87,0:32:46.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事  应该没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen, don't worry. I'm-I'm sure it's nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:57.69,0:32:59.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在停车场等我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wait for me in the parking lot.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.09,0:33:01.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果超过十分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If it's more than ten minutes,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.97,0:33:02.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说明他们抓到我了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it means they caught me,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:04.56,0:33:06.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以不要等我直接走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so take off without me.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:07.47,0:33:11.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不能让他们抓走你  我们要一起走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You can't let them. We are gonna leave all together.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:13.39,0:33:14.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:20.10,0:33:20.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米格尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Miguel.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.28,0:33:24.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.70,0:33:44.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能自己走吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you OK to walk by yourself?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:45.29,0:33:47.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可以吗  真乖\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah? Good girl.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.73,0:33:54.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有一个西班牙男性  二十出头\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got a male Hispanic, early 20s,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.26,0:33:56.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抢了一台电脑显示器逃跑了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}running out with a computer monitor.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:57.12,0:33:58.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:17.04,0:34:18.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去那边  去那边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go that way! Go that way!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.38,0:35:17.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,艾德  你怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, Ed, how are ya?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:18.61,0:35:19.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不必装了  尼娜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't bother, Nina.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:20.57,0:35:24.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我来是因为不得已  不是因为我是你的朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm here because I have to be, not because I'm your friend.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:25.89,0:35:27.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你来是因为他们认为\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're here because they think,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:27.45,0:35:30.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在我帮忙阻止爆炸案之后  杰克会想要杀我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}after I help stop the bomb, Jack will try to kill me.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:31.47,0:35:32.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他当然会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Which, of course, he will.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:34.57,0:35:36.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但如果你阻止不了他怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And what if you can't stop him?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:37.51,0:35:39.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请别见怪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, no offense,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.71,0:35:43.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但艾德  面对现实吧  你不是杰克的对手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but, Ed, let's face it, you're no match for Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.96,0:35:46.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不够狠\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're just not that ruthless.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:50.56,0:35:52.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以他设法绕过你  扣下扳机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So he manages to get around you and pull the trigger.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:52.41,0:35:54.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后怎么样呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What happens then?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:57.87,0:35:59.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为有特赦  他知道如果他杀了我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because of the pardon, he knows if he kills me,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.55,0:36:01.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他下半辈子都将要坐牢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}he'll spend the rest of his life in jail.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:02.72,0:36:05.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  如果你有我没想到的办法能让她闭嘴\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, if you have some way to shut her up I'm not thinking of...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:06.59,0:36:11.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当然  杰克在想  这也不失为一个好计划\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course, Jack's mind is thinking "That's not such a bad deal."
Dialogue: 0,0:36:15.11,0:36:17.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为他妻子的死报仇  这不过是个很小的代价\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Small price to pay to avenge his wife's death.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:19.37,0:36:23.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但那他的女儿呢  他在考虑他的女儿吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But what about his daughter? Is he thinking about her?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.01,0:36:26.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她已经失去妈妈了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's already lost one parent.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:26.53,0:36:28.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果他杀了我  她就会无亲无故了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If he kills me, she'll have no one.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:34.27,0:36:35.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克知道我说得对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack knows I'm right.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:37.06,0:36:39.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他就该利用我来阻止那场爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He should just use me to stop the bomb,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:39.85,0:36:41.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后回家  回到金身边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and then go home to Kim.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.64,0:36:47.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她需要你  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She needs you, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:09.21,0:37:09.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没有转那笔钱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I didn't transfer that money.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:09.79,0:37:11.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你把钱转到了那个账号上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You transferred it into that account.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:11.53,0:37:12.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没有转那笔钱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I didn't transfer that money.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:12.45,0:37:13.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你把钱转到了那个账号上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You transferred it into that account.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.83,0:37:15.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没有转那笔钱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I didn't transfer that money!
Dialogue: 0,0:37:15.04,0:37:18.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你最好告诉是谁转的  不然我要逮捕你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then you better tell me who did, or I'm taking you in!
Dialogue: 0,0:37:18.68,0:37:20.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你为什么要这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why are you doing this?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:20.84,0:37:21.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Friends of mine...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:24.57,0:37:28.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在尽全力保护这个国家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}who were doing their best to protect the citizens of this country
Dialogue: 0,0:37:28.65,0:37:30.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天被谋杀的公民\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}were murdered today...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.21,0:37:33.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也许凶手就是你提供资金的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}probably by the same people you're funding!
Dialogue: 0,0:37:36.54,0:37:38.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这理由对你来说够吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That a good enough reason for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:39.77,0:37:41.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我之前和你说过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I told you before...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:44.80,0:37:46.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我什么也不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know anything else.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:06.36,0:38:07.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的父母\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your parents.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:16.07,0:38:17.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,站起来  雷扎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, stand up, Reza.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:22.35,0:38:23.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,双手放在头后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Place your hands behind your head.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:30.65,0:38:33.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真是惭愧  这下肯定会伤透他们的心的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a shame. It's gonna break their heart.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:35.50,0:38:37.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得陪你一起从他们身边走过去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have to walk you right past them.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:38.46,0:38:40.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后他们就会看到他们儿子的真面目\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And they're gonna see who their son really is.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.41,0:38:46.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wait!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.53,0:38:54.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我批准了那笔转账  但不是我转的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I confirmed the transfers, but I didn't make them.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:56.23,0:38:58.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是在掩盖记录而已\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was just covering the records.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:00.65,0:39:02.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不想他有麻烦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I didn't want him to get into trouble.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:05.30,0:39:08.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谁  你在替谁掩盖\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who? Who are you covering for?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:11.72,0:39:15.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快说  是谁把钱转到赛伊德·阿里的账户的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, who transferred that money into Syed Ali's accounts?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:23.78,0:39:24.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鲍勃·华纳\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bob Warner.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:28.40,0:39:29.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽的父亲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Marie's father.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.55,0:39:49.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:49.63,0:39:51.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么了  -我觉得很不舒服\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What's the matter? - I don't feel very well.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:51.40,0:39:52.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我抱你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:05.89,0:40:07.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快点  米格尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, Miguel.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:10.51,0:40:11.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,离我们远点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get away from us!
Dialogue: 0,0:40:11.87,0:40:12.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把她交给我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Give her to me,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:12.74,0:40:15.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不然我会保证你坐二十年的牢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}or I will make sure you go to prison for 20 years.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:15.43,0:40:17.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不在乎  我知道她怎么会脑震荡的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't care. I know how she got the concussion.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:17.35,0:40:18.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是个意外\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That was an accident!
Dialogue: 0,0:40:18.46,0:40:20.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,卡拉的瘀青也是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, like Carla's bruises?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:40.56,0:40:42.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没事了  -米格尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It's OK. - Miguel...
Dialogue: 0,0:40:49.41,0:40:50.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's just get outta here.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:55.52,0:40:57.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去拿他的车钥匙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get his car keys.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:21.44,0:41:24.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-雷扎  -亲爱的小天使\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Reza. - Sweetheart, angel.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:27.21,0:41:28.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你没事吧  -没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You OK? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:30.63,0:41:33.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他们知道我什么也没干  -感谢上帝\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- They know I didn't do anything. - Oh, thank God.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:34.59,0:41:36.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天我们可以结婚了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We can get married today.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:36.24,0:41:38.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know, sweetheart.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:40.53,0:41:41.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,华纳先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Warner.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:43.57,0:41:45.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能跟我走吗  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Could you follow me, please, sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:45.92,0:41:48.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这事和我有什么关系  -请跟我走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What does this have to do with me? - Just come with me, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:53.92,0:41:55.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你和他们说了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What did you tell them?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:56.22,0:41:57.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,实话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The truth.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:58.63,0:42:00.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,实话  实话是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The truth? What-what do you mean, the truth?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:00.17,0:42:02.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托  我爸妈已经很难受了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please, my parents are very upset.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:17.60,0:42:18.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hurry.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:35.53,0:42:36.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:37.43,0:42:39.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:40.67,0:42:44.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,小队在维萨利亚集结  会有实战和外勤部队\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The team's assembling in Visalia. We'll have tactical and field units.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:44.43,0:42:46.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能确认他们就位了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have confirmation that they're in place?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:47.63,0:42:48.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也许在空中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Probably in the air.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:52.57,0:42:54.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们会进行空中管制\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll have air traffic, um...
Dialogue: 0,0:42:58.32,0:42:59.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,空中管制优先权吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Air traffic priority?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:01.20,0:43:02.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah...
Dialogue: 0,0:43:03.48,0:43:04.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,管制\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tra...
Dialogue: 0,0:43:05.92,0:43:06.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack...
Dialogue: 0,0:43:06.75,0:43:09.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事的  艾德  没事的  放松点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's all right, Ed. It's all right. Just take it easy.

