[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,1,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.61,0:00:10.82,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(197.4,200.557)}{\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs25\b1\bord0\shad0\c&H78BDE7&\fad(0,808)}24小时\N\N{\fs15}第二季  第十九集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.07,0:00:13.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(189.6,121.6,193.8,105.6,0,356)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad3\3c&H2F2F2F&\4c&H336D99&}{\fs10}{\t(0,356,\fs20)\fn方正正中黑简体}前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.84,0:00:14.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Talk to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.78,0:00:15.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克说得很清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack made it very clear that the
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.74,0:00:14.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(288,238.153)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.78,0:00:14.82,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(259.2,216.553)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.82,0:00:14.87,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(231,195.753)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.87,0:00:14.91,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(201.6,174.953)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.91,0:00:14.95,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(172.2,154.153)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.95,0:00:14.99,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(142.2,133.353)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.99,0:00:16.99,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(117.6,114.153)\fad(0,389)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.73,0:00:17.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想要证实这份录音真假\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}only way to get proof on this tape
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.74,0:00:19.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只有反恐局不参与才可以办到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is if CTU stays out of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.53,0:00:20.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们都不知道他现在是死是活\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We don't know if he's alive!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.98,0:00:22.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他在一条公用线上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's on an open channel.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.63,0:00:24.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你没办法追踪  但可以跟他说话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You won't be able to trace it, but you can talk to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.20,0:00:27.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-米歇尔  -不是  杰克  是托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Michelle! - No, Jack, it's Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.06,0:00:29.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼  总统想要得到证明那份录音\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony, the president asked me to provide him with the
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.41,0:00:31.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是假的的证据  我现在正在努力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}proof that the Cyprus recording was fake.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.98,0:00:35.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那个能提供证据的人只愿意见我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The man who can provide that proof will only deal with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.35,0:00:36.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要怎么知道他不是在利用你  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How do we know he's not using you? Jack
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.09,0:00:38.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为刚有十个突击队员想杀他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because ten commandos just tried to
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.32,0:00:40.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阻止他与我交易\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}kill him to stop him making a deal with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.25,0:00:41.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.55,0:00:44.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  我不行了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack. I'm not gonna make it.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.64,0:00:42.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(238.2,216.553)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.69,0:00:42.73,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(218.4,199.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.73,0:00:42.77,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(199.2,182.153)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.77,0:00:42.81,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(180,166.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.81,0:00:42.85,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(160.8,148.553)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.85,0:00:42.89,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(139.8,131.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.89,0:00:44.94,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(121.8,113.353)\fad(0,353)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.34,0:00:46.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,赶紧告诉我证据在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just tell me where the evidence is now.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.59,0:00:48.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在一个存储芯片上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's on a memory chip.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.76,0:00:52.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,原始录音证明了塞浦路斯录音是伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The source recordings prove the Cyprus audio is a fake.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.75,0:00:54.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,存储芯片在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where's the memory chip?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.97,0:00:57.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Inside...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.75,0:00:59.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在哪里  快说  华莱士\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, Wallace. Inside where?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.75,0:01:02.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,医生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Doctor!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.68,0:01:04.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,病人宣布死亡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.66,0:01:09.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拿到芯片了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We got the chip.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.50,0:01:13.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,目前我们的飞机已经抵达大西洋上空\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Our planes are currently over the Atlantic.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.50,0:01:15.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们将在三个小时之内首先到达目标位置\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The first of them will be reaching their targets just under three hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.76,0:01:14.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(298.8,222.153)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.81,0:01:14.85,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(268.2,203.753)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.85,0:01:14.89,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(239.4,186.153)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.89,0:01:14.93,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(206.4,164)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.93,0:01:14.97,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(178.2,146.153)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.97,0:01:15.01,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(149.4,129.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.01,0:01:17.05,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\fad(0,346)\pos(117,108.553)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.55,0:01:17.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统  我刚和国防部长谈过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, I just got off
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.77,0:01:20.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他想知道你还要给杰克·鲍尔多久\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the secretary of defence. He wants to know how much longer
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.50,0:01:23.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来证明录音是假的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you plan on giving Jack Bauer to disprove that tape.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.71,0:01:25.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要把投弹前的所有时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As far as I concerned, Jack Bauer has up until
Dialogue: 0,0:01:25.49,0:01:27.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都留给杰克·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the time the planes start releasing bombs.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.25,0:01:32.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,部长认为这会限制国防部的行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}From the secretary's point of view, that's tying the DOD's hands.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:32.05,0:01:34.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要利用一切时间做到面面俱到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna utilise every moment we have to be thorough.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.67,0:01:37.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他恐怕不会同意  -那是他的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- He's not gonna like that, sir. - That's his problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.99,0:01:44.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs15\t(696,6577,\fs16)\c&H4BAAAD&\fad(1697,1183)\pos(187.2,191.79)}以下故事情节发生在凌晨2点到凌晨3点之间
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.84,0:01:49.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为了突袭能够取得最佳效果\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In order to exploit the advantages of a surprise attack,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.17,0:01:54.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们从三个本土基地调了十二支轰炸机部队\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we've launched 12 bomb squadrons from three stateside bases.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.38,0:01:55.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但本土基地进行的第一轮空袭\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But initial air strikes will be
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.80,0:02:00.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,将会从这里  这里和这里发起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}launched from our bases in the region here, here and here.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.87,0:02:05.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,长官  这符合您对空袭需要在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, that is consistent with your request was for air strikes
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.27,0:02:07.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,您对民众的演讲之前发起的要求\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to begin before your address to the nation.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.32,0:02:08.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的命令我心里有数\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know what I asked for.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.26,0:02:13.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不是这个意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That came out wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.41,0:02:16.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你和参谋长们在这么短的时间内\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You and the Joint Chiefs have achived a remarkable
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.23,0:02:19.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能够调动起部队  干得很漂亮\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}job mobilising our forces on such short notice.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.54,0:02:20.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.95,0:02:22.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.50,0:02:26.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还能假定你赞成袭击计划吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is it fair to assume that you're still behind the attack?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:26.99,0:02:30.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为我感觉你有点动摇\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Cos I'm sensing some equivocation.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.70,0:02:34.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我告诉过副总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I told the Vice President,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.08,0:02:35.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但还没告诉过你们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I haven't shared this with the rest of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.53,0:02:41.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克·鲍尔  那个反恐组特工\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack Bauer, the CTU agent
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.11,0:02:43.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在找到核弹中立下首功的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}most responsible for finding the nuclear bomb,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.07,0:02:45.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,认为塞浦路斯录音是伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}has reason to believes that the Cyprus audio is fabricated.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.11,0:02:48.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-鲍尔没有实质性证据  -目前没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Bauer has no hard evidence? - Not at this point.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.10,0:02:52.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个战斗计划要求我们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President this battle plan requires our
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.47,0:02:56.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,以压倒性的武力发起突袭\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}surprising the enemy with a strike of overwhelming force.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.90,0:03:00.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再等下去我们就会丧失突袭的优势\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We will lose that advantage if we wait any longer.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.61,0:03:03.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,目标国家将会组织防御\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The target countries will mobilise their defences
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.03,0:03:07.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,并且我们未来的伤亡人数也会上升\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and our casualties will increase over the long term.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:08.22,0:03:11.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-上升多少  -多达两万士兵\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- By how much? - Up to 20,000 troops.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.22,0:03:24.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我们就别无选择\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then we have no choice
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.77,0:03:28.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只能照原计划进行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but to proceed with the plan as stated.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.14,0:03:32.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\frz19.91\move(173.4,66.4,183,39.2,1228,3031)}{\fn方正兰亭粗黑_GBK\fax-0.6\fs25\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H74767D&}急救中心
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.05,0:03:34.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  我明白\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, I understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.37,0:03:35.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我必须要告诉总统的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But what I have to say to the President
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.65,0:03:38.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会对他现在开的会议有直接影响\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}will have a direct impact on the meeting that he's in.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.03,0:03:39.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他目前不能接电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He can't be disturbed at this time.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.64,0:03:41.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行  那至少告诉他我打来了电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fine. Just make sure he knows I called.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.81,0:03:42.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好的  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yes. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.74,0:03:45.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他正在同参谋长们开会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The President is in a meeting with the Joint Chiefs.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.27,0:03:46.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会议结束前都不能被打扰\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They won't interrupt until it's finished.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.30,0:03:52.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,求求你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.57,0:03:59.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-阿尔梅达  -托尼  我是杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Almeida. - Tony, It's Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.44,0:04:00.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  你在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, where are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.64,0:04:02.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼  我听不太清你说话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony, I can barely hear you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.25,0:04:04.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,干扰太厉害  信号很差\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The interferer is big. We got a really bad connection.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.45,0:04:06.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你得把华莱士立即带回来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, Listen I want you to bring Wallace back here now.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:06.69,0:04:07.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼  华莱士死了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony, Wallace is dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.98,0:04:10.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我有证据  能证明塞浦路斯录音是伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I got the evidence that proves Cyprus audio is forged. It's a CPB
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.89,0:04:13.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是一个存有原始录音的芯片\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}memory chip containing the original source recordings.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.12,0:04:17.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你怎么知道是真的  -他为了给我都死了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How do you know it's real, Jack? - Because he died trying to give it to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:17.09,0:04:18.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他把它植入了自己的身体\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and he had it surgically implanted.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.35,0:04:21.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要是那是假的  我不觉得他会花那么大力气\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I hardly think he'd have gotten that kind of trouble that if it wasn't authentic.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.71,0:04:23.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行  你在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fine. Where are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.67,0:04:25.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们在靠近北好莱坞的一个急救中心里面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We are in a Urgent Care center somewhere near North Hollywood,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.86,0:04:27.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大概离反恐组有四十分钟路程\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We are about 40 minutes outside CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.17,0:04:28.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们现在就把芯片带去给你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna bring you the chip now.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.67,0:04:31.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,沿途把路线发过来  我会安排空军护送\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. Call in your route from the road so I'll send an aerial escort.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:31.02,0:04:33.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行  托尼  你得联系总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ok fine, Tony. I need you to get in touch with the President.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.57,0:04:35.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我试着联系过他  他正在和参谋长开会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have tried to get through. He's in middle of a meeting with the Joint Chiefs.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.08,0:04:37.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们不给我转接\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They won't patch me through.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.44,0:04:38.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  在确认你手里东西的真伪之前\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, I'm not calling the president
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.56,0:04:40.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是不会打给总统的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}until I confirm what you're holding is real.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.19,0:04:40.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  到这里来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, come here.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.96,0:04:44.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你起码得告诉他发生了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony, you've got to at least tell him what's going on.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.81,0:04:46.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你在这里  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need you here, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.08,0:04:47.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼  你听得到吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony, can you hear me?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.65,0:04:48.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我听得到  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I hear you, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.77,0:04:51.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得挂了  求你照我说的做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I gotta go. Please just do what I ask.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.63,0:04:54.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么  -我们不能带着这芯片走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What? - We can't go anywhere with this chip.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.09,0:04:55.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why not?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.69,0:04:58.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-看这个  埋在这芯片里的  -那是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Look at this, embedded in the silicon. - What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.58,0:05:01.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,某种被动应答器  作用类似于定位器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Some kind of a passive transponder. It acts like a tracking device.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.52,0:05:02.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你确定  -确定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Are you sure? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.24,0:05:06.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们组织用类似的回路来追踪敏感材料\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Our group uses circuits like this to track sensitive material.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.35,0:05:07.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不懂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't really understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.34,0:05:10.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,被华莱士偷走东西的那个人能定位它\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Whoever Wallace stole the chip from can track it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.24,0:05:11.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们就是这样追着他到了那仓库\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's how they tracked him to the warehouse.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.87,0:05:14.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不先把这个信号中断  他们就会发现我们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They'll find us if I don't disconnect it at first.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.20,0:05:15.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在中断信号同时能不损害录音文件吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can you do it without destroying the audio file?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.81,0:05:18.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我想可以  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I think so. - Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.50,0:05:25.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,丹尼  不能再这样了  我说过你别打过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Danny, you have to stop doing this, Ok? I told you not to call.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.49,0:05:29.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉让你不高兴了  但我没时间说这个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry you're upset, but I don't have time for this right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.07,0:05:31.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么了  出什么事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why? What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.57,0:05:35.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没什么事  别担心  一切都在掌握之中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nothing. Don't worry. We're taking care of things here.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.37,0:05:37.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真的吗  我该怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Really? What am I supposed to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.99,0:05:41.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,坐好  我有空会打给你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just sit tight. I'll call you as soon as I get a chance,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.42,0:05:42.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-但我得挂了  -当我没说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- but I have to go - Forget it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.70,0:05:54.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,电话有问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Something's wrong with the phones.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.91,0:05:57.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,自从核弹的消息泄露后  互联网就炸锅了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The network's been overloaded ever since news of the bomb broke.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.00,0:06:01.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你刚在跟谁说话  -没谁  怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Who were you talking to? - No one. What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:01.95,0:06:02.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克刚刚打来了电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, Jack just called.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.67,0:06:04.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他说他从华莱士那里拿到了证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He says he's got the evidence from Wallace.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.25,0:06:06.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统知道吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Does the president know?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.39,0:06:08.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  我们还没有确认证据的真伪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. We haven't confirmed it's authentic yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.03,0:06:11.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统以录音真实为前提\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony, the president's acting on
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.24,0:06:13.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,正在展开行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the assumption that the recording is real.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.51,0:06:15.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而这份证据有可能证明那不是真的  我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And this evidence may prove that it's not. I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.51,0:06:19.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼  你得打给总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony, you've gotta call the president.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.75,0:06:22.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我正在考虑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm thinking about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.31,0:06:30.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个太大了  我需要更尖一点的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is too big. I need something with a finer point.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.20,0:06:35.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个呢  能用吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about this? Will that work?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.59,0:06:38.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能用\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.61,0:06:47.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-优素福  你还需要多久  -一两分钟吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yusuf, how much longer do you need? - One minute, maybe two.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.06,0:06:48.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一分钟还是两分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Which is one or two?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.05,0:06:49.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要是别烦我就是一分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}One if you stop bothering me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.64,0:06:52.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想夺回芯片的人到这里来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Those people who want their chip back, they are here.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.03,0:06:53.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,定位器在被你和芯片分离后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Will the tracker still function after
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.81,0:06:56.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还能运作吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you seperated it from the chip?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.57,0:06:57.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得摘掉天线  但是它应该还能发射信号\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll have to loose the antenna but yeah the signal should still transmit.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.63,0:07:00.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我能把他们引开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think I can lure them away from here.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.11,0:07:02.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你和凯特把芯片带去反恐组  -我们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You and Kate get the chip over to CTU. - Us?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.61,0:07:05.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别担心  这能行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't worry. This is gonna work.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.36,0:07:10.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  到这里贴着墙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate, move here against the wall.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.94,0:07:23.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好了  -拿过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Got it. - Bring it here.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.20,0:07:25.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,仍旧能锁定目标吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Still locked on target?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.66,0:07:27.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This way.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.32,0:07:33.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们俩在西边几个街区外的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK. I want you to meet me at
Dialogue: 0,0:07:33.09,0:07:35.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,摩尔公园和葡萄园那里同我碰面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Moorpark and Vineland, it's a few blocks west of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:36.09,0:07:37.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要是我十五分钟内没到  你们就别管我了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If I'm not there in 15 minutes, leave without me,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.95,0:07:39.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-带着芯片去找托尼·阿尔梅达  -明白\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- but you get that chip to Tony Almeida. - Got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.94,0:07:44.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-小心点  -我会没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Be careful. - I'll be OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.58,0:07:56.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,信号不稳定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Signal's dropping off.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:59.33,0:08:01.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-等等  他在移动  -往哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Wait. He's moving. - Where?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.76,0:08:04.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,前面  向东入口方向\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just ahead. Toward the east entrance.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.22,0:08:08.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我马上来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll catch up.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.49,0:09:25.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我等到会议结束\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I waited till the meeting broke
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.66,0:09:27.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,才来告诉您州长从萨克拉门托来电\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to tell you the Governor called from Sacramento.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.75,0:09:31.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么了  -上街抗议的人更多了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What's going on? - More people are hitting the streets.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.66,0:09:33.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,州长希望您像在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Governor wants you to dispatch
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.17,0:09:35.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽埃塔一样派遣国民警卫队\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the National Guard like you did in Marietta.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.38,0:09:37.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  反恐组的托尼·阿尔梅达正在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, Tony Almeida from CTU is
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.74,0:09:40.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,紧急卫星网络电话上等您\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}holding for you on the emergency Satcom network.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.13,0:09:41.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么用卫星网络\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why on Satcom?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.21,0:09:43.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,自从新闻报道了炸弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, since news of the bomb got out,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.24,0:09:45.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,通信网络就完全超负荷了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}network circuits have been completely overloaded.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.20,0:09:47.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,几分钟前  90%的系统都瘫痪了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}90% of all systems went down a few minutes ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.44,0:09:51.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果您想的话  我可以跟他谈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can talk to Almeida if you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.24,0:09:52.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不用  接通免提\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, put him on speaker.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.41,0:09:57.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿尔梅达先生  我是帕尔默总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Almeida, this is President Palmer.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:58.54,0:10:01.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一同接听的有麦克·诺维克和林恩·柯瑞斯基\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're also on with Mike Novick and Lynne Kresge.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.59,0:10:02.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.23,0:10:04.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克·鲍尔刚刚电话提供了新信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack Bauer just called with some new information.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.03,0:10:06.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,其实我有些犹豫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The truth is I'm a little conflicted
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.38,0:10:07.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是否要就此联络您\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}about contacting you with this.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.60,0:10:09.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但他声称他有证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But... He claims he has evidence that
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.77,0:10:11.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,证明塞浦路斯录音是伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}proves the Cyprus recording is counterfeit.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.34,0:10:13.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么样的证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What kind of evidence?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.59,0:10:16.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,塞浦路斯音频里每个人的源录音\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Source recordings of each of the men on the Cyprus audio.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:16.59,0:10:18.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,它们被重新剪辑了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They were then re-edited.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.66,0:10:20.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,经过鉴定了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Have these been authenticated?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:20.37,0:10:23.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-还没有  我们很快就会拿到手  -多快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Not yet. We're getting 'em soon. - How soon?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.55,0:10:24.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一小时内  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Within the hour, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.79,0:10:30.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿尔梅达先生  你对杰克·鲍尔的信任很怪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Almeida, your confidence in Jack Bauer is curious.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.14,0:10:33.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一小时前你刚告诉我他袭击了反恐组的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}An hour ago you told me he assaulted CTU personnel
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.47,0:10:36.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后非法带走了一名证人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and took illegal custody of a witness.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:36.93,0:10:40.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先生  情势所迫杰克别无选择\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, Jack had no choice under the circumstances.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.65,0:10:41.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不明白\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't follow.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.77,0:10:42.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果杰克牵扯上反恐组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The man with the evidence would
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.78,0:10:45.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那个人就不会交出证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}not have turned it over had Jack involved CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.94,0:10:50.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那么阿尔梅达  是什么让你确定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So Almeida, what makes you so sure that
Dialogue: 0,0:10:50.50,0:10:52.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这份证据比塞浦路斯录音更可靠\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}this is any more real than the Cyprus recording?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.10,0:10:55.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,问题就在这里  先生  我不确定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's just it, sir. I'm not.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.68,0:10:57.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-但杰克·鲍尔确定  -是的  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- But Jack Bauer is. - Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.81,0:11:04.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你的坦诚  阿尔梅达先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you for your candour, Mr. Almeida.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.49,0:11:07.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会予以考量\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll take this information under advisement.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.43,0:11:08.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢您  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.77,0:11:29.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要取消攻击\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm calling off the attack.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.40,0:11:36.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在这之前  先生  我们应该充分讨论后果\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, before you do that, we should talk through the consequences.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.38,0:11:37.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们讨论得够多了  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We've talked enough, Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.74,0:11:42.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  我理解您对杰克·鲍尔的尊重\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, I appreciate your respect for Jack Bauer. I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.20,0:11:44.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但你了解这个人的声誉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But you know the man's reputation.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.17,0:11:45.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我了解这个人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know the man.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:47.52,0:11:50.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那或许您该想想你自己的声誉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then maybe you better start thinking about your own reputation.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.36,0:11:50.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Meaning?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.29,0:11:55.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一枚核弹在美国领土上被引爆了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A nuclear bomb was detonated on US soil.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.55,0:11:58.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而我们收到了证据显示\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And we've been shown proof connecting
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.08,0:12:00.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,三个中东国家与其有关联\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the weapon to three nations in the Middle East.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:01.14,0:12:02.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可能是虚假的证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Proof that may be false.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.92,0:12:05.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果您不果断回应\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Unless you respond decisively,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.15,0:12:09.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,您的敌人会利用这点称你领导失职\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}your enemies will exploit that as a failure of leadership,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:10.61,0:12:12.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,自身弱点暴露\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}as a sign of personal weakness.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.52,0:12:13.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你想怎样  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So what are you saying, Mike?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.73,0:12:15.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我应该继续军事行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That I should continue with a
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.69,0:12:18.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只为证明我够果断吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}military operation just to prove that I'm decisive?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.17,0:12:22.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果杰克·鲍尔是对的呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What if Jack Bauer's right?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.18,0:12:23.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果他是错的呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What if he's wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.23,0:12:26.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先生  我们都听了五角大楼的评估\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, we have all heard the Pentagon's assessment.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.19,0:12:28.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,停止再重启这次军事行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stopping and restarting military
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.76,0:12:32.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可能会牺牲数万美国士兵的生命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}action could cost tens of thousands of American lives.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.67,0:12:36.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,比起与三个无辜的国家开战\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}An acceptable risk if the alternative
Dialogue: 0,0:12:36.21,0:12:39.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是可接受的风险\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is waging war against three innocent countries.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.41,0:12:42.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  根据过往经验\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, we know from
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.08,0:12:45.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们知道这些国家并不无辜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}past experience these countries aren't innocent.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.95,0:12:51.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我强烈主张您重新考虑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm urging you in the strongest possible terms to reconsider.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.98,0:13:09.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我已经决定了  让格拉茨将军回来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've made up my mind. Now get General Gratz back in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.88,0:13:11.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,并连线参谋长\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And conference in the Joint Chiefs.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.50,0:13:20.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看起来没问题  发去分区\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They look fine. Send them to District.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.41,0:13:23.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-失陪  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Excuse me. - Got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:28.93,0:13:29.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.98,0:13:33.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想告诉你我和总统说了杰克的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just wanted you to know that I told the President about Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:34.74,0:13:35.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你说了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You did?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.40,0:13:37.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  如果杰克真的有他说的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. If Jack has what he says he has,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.74,0:13:39.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那么总统应该知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the President should know about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.74,0:13:41.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他作何反应\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How did he react?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:42.32,0:13:44.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他想让我们随时汇报进展\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He wants us to keep him apprised of the situation.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.34,0:13:48.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你做得对  托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You did the right thing, Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.77,0:13:51.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对不对等杰克拿来芯片就知道了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll find out when Jack gets here with that chip.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.31,0:13:53.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他说什么时候来  -再过20分钟左右\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- When did he say? - About 20 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.26,0:13:56.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等他来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, when he does get here,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.38,0:13:58.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要确定那东西是真的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you to make sure that thing is real.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.47,0:14:00.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我现在就去启动通道程序块软件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll pull up the CPB software right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.05,0:14:02.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.24,0:14:03.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:07.26,0:14:07.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.72,0:14:21.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,网络繁忙  请稍后再拨\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All circuits are busy. Please try your call again.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.57,0:14:24.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-还是没信号吗  -不  有信号\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Still no signal? - No, I have signal.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.53,0:14:26.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是无法接通  总是转到录音\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just can't get through. I keep getting a recording.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.02,0:14:28.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也许是反恐组那边的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Maybe it's from CTU's end.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.95,0:14:29.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们肯定很忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sure they're very busy
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.72,0:14:31.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,准备对我的国家开战\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}gearing up for the war against my country.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:32.49,0:14:35.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不会开战的  优素福  他们会拿到芯片\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There won't be a war, Yusuf. They'll get the chip.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.60,0:14:36.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们会知道真相\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're gonna know the truth.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.91,0:14:38.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,前提是他们想知道真相\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Assuming they want the truth.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.50,0:14:40.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们不想要战争\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They don't want war.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:42.17,0:14:43.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你确定吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You sure about that?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.76,0:14:51.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果是你的家人受到威胁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You might feel differently
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.50,0:14:53.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,或许你会有不同的体会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}if it was your family being threatened.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.85,0:15:01.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,葡萄园街和穆尔帕克街交汇处  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Vineland and Moorpark, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.67,0:15:02.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.99,0:15:19.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我去等杰克  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'll keep an eye out for Jack. - Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.04,0:15:24.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他在东北方位  -移动还是静止\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- He's in the northeast quadrant. - Moving or static?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.85,0:15:26.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-刚刚停下  -戴维斯  你在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Just stopped. - Davis, where are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:27.02,0:15:29.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,地下室  沿东墙向北搜查\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In the basement, sweeping north along the east wall.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.71,0:15:31.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他在东北角  堵住他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's inside the northeast corner. Pin him down.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.74,0:15:32.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们马上就来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're coming your way.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.76,0:15:33.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.49,0:15:35.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在我拿到芯片前不要杀他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do not kill him until I have that chip.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.56,0:15:37.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,明白\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Understood.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:11.67,0:16:13.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他把芯片上的追踪器取下来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He took the tracker off the chip.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.52,0:16:17.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,罗尼  他向北朝木兰街跑了  我们走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ronnie, he's running north toward Magnolia. Come on, let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.68,0:16:39.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了  带他进去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, let's get him back inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.39,0:16:59.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我开始怀疑总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm starting to question the president's
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.25,0:17:00.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对这项行动的决心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}dedication to this action.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.61,0:17:03.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,相信我  将军  他不是轻易做出的决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Believe me, General, this was not a decision he made lightly.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.70,0:17:05.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还没收到简报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I haven't been briefed on this.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.26,0:17:06.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统当然希望亲自向你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The president has every intention of
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.80,0:17:08.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,解释他的决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}explaining his decision to you personally.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.48,0:17:12.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但在那之前  你自己给下属准备简报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But until he does, you should brief your own staff.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.28,0:17:15.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好  我来处理  -谢谢你的耐心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- All right. I'll take care of it. - Thank you for your patience.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.80,0:17:19.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-又是不满  -远不止此\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- More blowback? - And then some.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.94,0:17:22.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,麦克  你听说了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen, Mike, have you heard anything
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.67,0:17:25.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,副总统要召集的会议吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}about this meeting that the vice president called?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:26.53,0:17:27.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会议\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A meeting?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.15,0:17:29.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,显然他要求内阁成员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Apparently he's asked Cabinet
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.31,0:17:31.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在一个半小时后待命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}members to be on hand an hour and a half from now.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.88,0:17:37.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么目的  -不知道  因为我没被邀请\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What's the agenda? - I don't know, because I wasn't invited.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.57,0:17:39.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谁告诉了你这个会议\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who told you about this meeting?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.15,0:17:40.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,詹德勒手下的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was someone on Gendler's staff.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.72,0:17:43.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但他只知道我告诉你的这些\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He doesn't know anything more than what I'm telling you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.88,0:17:46.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你认为与总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you thiking it has something to do with
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.40,0:17:48.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,取消军事打击有关吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the president calling off the military strikes?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.95,0:17:50.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,麦克  还能是什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mike, what else could it be?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.09,0:17:53.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你告诉总统了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did you tell the president about this?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.56,0:17:56.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不不不  要等我进一步了解\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, no no no, not yet, not until I find out more.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.00,0:17:57.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就我所知  这可能只是传言\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For all I know, it could just be a rumour.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.21,0:18:00.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可能只是这样  但...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's probably all it is.  But --
Dialogue: 0,0:18:01.60,0:18:02.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还是打听一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll ask around anyway.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:02.89,0:18:05.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有发现就告诉我  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. Keep me posted if you hear anything, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.54,0:18:38.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我是奥哈拉  -斯塔克在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- O'Hara. - Where's Stark?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.75,0:18:39.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就在这\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.53,0:18:44.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,扶他起来  是我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get him up. Yes?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.10,0:18:46.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,罗尼  你拿到芯片了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ronnie, you got the chip?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.99,0:18:49.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我正和从华莱士身上取出芯片的探员在一起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Actually, I'm with the agent who took it off Wallace.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.39,0:18:51.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-是杰克·鲍尔  对吧  -是的  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It was Jack Bauer, wasn't it? - Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.76,0:18:53.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们扫描了他的衣物\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We've scanned his belongings and his clothing
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.01,0:18:55.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,并且催吐检查了他的胃内容物\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and induced vomiting to check his stomach contents.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:55.84,0:18:56.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是浪费时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a waste of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.65,0:19:00.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他不会把芯片带在身上  让我和他谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's not gonna have it on him. Let me talk to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.59,0:19:06.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.89,0:19:12.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,换鲍尔接听\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're on with Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.16,0:19:17.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  你成了这里的英雄了  祝贺你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, you're a hero here. Congratulations.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.06,0:19:19.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉你我的打算\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me tell you what I wanna do.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.11,0:19:21.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这世界不是非得知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The world doesn't have to know
Dialogue: 0,0:19:21.28,0:19:24.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们的计划\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}anything about the arrangement we're about to make.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:24.18,0:19:27.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们保守这个秘密  -你是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- We'll keep it private. - Who am I talking to?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:27.64,0:19:32.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托  我需要那芯片\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Give me a break. Look, I need the chip.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.86,0:19:35.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别装傻了  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So let's not be pigs here, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.42,0:19:37.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉罗尼芯片在哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You tell Ronnie where it is,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.37,0:19:41.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我保证给你一大笔钱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I authorise a very large sum, large enough
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.06,0:19:44.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,足够补偿你的愧疚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to compensate you for any guilt you might feel about this.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.80,0:19:45.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,芯片不是拿来卖的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's not for sale.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.34,0:19:48.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有人想买就是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If someone wants to buy it, it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.45,0:19:49.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你怎能觉得挑起一场战争\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How can you justify starting a war
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.00,0:19:52.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只为从中渔利这种行为是正当的呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}just to profit from the outcome?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.16,0:19:55.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们只是在控制混乱局面  仅此而已\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're just controlling the chaos, that's all.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.75,0:19:57.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不对  你们是在制造混乱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, you're causing it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.71,0:20:00.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们不要为了消除分歧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's not waste each other's
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.73,0:20:03.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而浪费彼此的时间了  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}time trying to bridge our differences, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.03,0:20:06.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们只需在一件事上达成一致\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's only one thing we need to agree on:
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.63,0:20:08.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,价钱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}a price.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.87,0:20:10.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我已经跟你说了  免谈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I already gave you my answer.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.73,0:20:12.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等罗尼搞定你  你就不会这么说了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When Ronnie's finished working on you, you'll give me another.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.32,0:20:14.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不会的  我不会改变主意的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, my answer's final.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.06,0:20:18.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,罗尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ronnie!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.79,0:20:21.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想他要跟你说话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think he wants to talk to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.45,0:20:25.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听到了  我会帮你要到答案的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I heard what he said. I'll get you your answer.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.98,0:20:27.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个鲍尔  我看过他的档案\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This man Bauer, I've read his file.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.46,0:20:30.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我也看过  -你知道他不好对付的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- So have I. - You know he won't be easy to break.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.68,0:20:32.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我能搞定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He'll break.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.24,0:20:35.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我佩服你的自信  -我不是吃素的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I appreciate your confidence. - I've earned it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.20,0:20:39.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  你能  但是时间也是个问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, you have. There's also a time issue.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:39.59,0:20:41.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你更要让我开工了  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then you'd better let me get started, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:47.82,0:20:48.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,芯片  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The chip, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.53,0:21:30.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,芯片  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The chip, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.58,0:21:50.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你找我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You wanted to see me?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.02,0:21:54.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-杰克带着芯片来了  -那是托尼说的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Jack's bringing a chip in. - That's what Tony said.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.91,0:21:57.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他想让我来分析芯片\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He wants me to run point on the analysis.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.71,0:22:00.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我现在打不开通道程序块软件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm having trouble accessing the CPB software.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.33,0:22:03.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没问题  发到我电脑上  我来做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No problem, just send it to my screen. I'll do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.66,0:22:08.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只需要你帮忙解锁索引功能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just need you to... unlock the indexing function.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:08.38,0:22:10.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我说了我来做  -不用你做  凯莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I said I would do it. - I don't need you to do it, Carrie.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:10.87,0:22:13.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只要你解锁索引功能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need you to unlock the indexing function.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.30,0:22:14.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你什么毛病\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What is your problem?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:14.62,0:22:17.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你整天跟我对着干\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You've been gunning for me all day.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.05,0:22:18.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不也一样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I could say the same about you.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.66,0:22:20.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是在做我的本职工作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm just trying to do my job.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.04,0:22:24.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,德斯勒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Dessler.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.04,0:22:26.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你能不能上来一下  -好的  可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Can I see you up here a second? - Yeah, sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.26,0:22:31.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-按我说的做  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Just do what I asked. - Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.61,0:22:47.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那是干什么  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- So what was that about? - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.18,0:22:49.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你和凯莉  你们在吵什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You and Carrie, what were you arguing about?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:50.35,0:22:52.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没什么  我让她帮我打开个通道程序块软件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nothing. I asked her to open some CPB
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.38,0:22:55.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而她一直给我找茬\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}software and she's making me jump through hoops.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.80,0:22:56.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道你不想告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know you don't wanna tell me,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.89,0:22:59.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是不论你们之间有什么矛盾\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but whatever bad blood there is
Dialogue: 0,0:22:59.42,0:23:01.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得知道情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}between the two of you, I gotta know what it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.79,0:23:04.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那不重要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It doesn't matter,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.02,0:23:05.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尤其跟今天的事无关\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}especially with everything that's going on oday.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.87,0:23:07.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这就是关键所在  米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's exactly why it does matter, Michelle.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.12,0:23:09.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这都影响到你的工作了  到底什么事情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's interfering with your work. Now, what's the problem?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.26,0:23:18.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我以前在分局当凯莉的手下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When I worked for Carrie over at Division,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.84,0:23:20.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那时我们还是朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we were friends.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.19,0:23:23.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我把她介绍给了我哥\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I introduced her to my brother.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:23.27,0:23:24.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他已经结婚了  还有小孩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He was married. He had kids.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.83,0:23:27.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他为了她抛妻弃子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He left them for her.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.54,0:23:31.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,后来她玩腻了  把他甩了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And then she got bored. She dumped him.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.16,0:23:39.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,丹尼什么都没了  家没了  工作也丢了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Danny lost everything. His family, his job.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.96,0:23:44.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很惨  他还企图自杀\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It got so bad, he tried to kill himself.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.60,0:23:51.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.66,0:23:56.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很不幸你俩要一起工作  但是你没得选\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's unfortunate you two have to work together, but you do.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.45,0:23:59.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我今天还得管好这里  行吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I gotta keep this office running today, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.59,0:24:04.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我理解  -很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I understand. - Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.20,0:24:11.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿尔梅达\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Almeida.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.86,0:24:14.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼  打扰一下  我找米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony, sorry to bother you. Can I speak with Michelle?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:14.51,0:24:15.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just a second.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.12,0:24:16.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,找你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.94,0:24:21.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-戴斯勒  -你哥哥丹尼来找你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Dessler. - Your brother Danny's here to see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.38,0:24:24.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,带他去我办公桌  我这就下来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Show him to my station. I'll be right down.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.57,0:24:25.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right away.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.32,0:24:29.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们的事儿完了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are we OK here?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.84,0:24:31.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.70,0:24:47.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这太疯狂了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is nuts.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.18,0:24:53.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你好  妹妹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey. Hey, little sister.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.81,0:24:54.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你带他进来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thanks for bringing him in.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.83,0:24:59.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你好吗  你没事吧  -我没事  丹尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How are you? You OK? - I'm fine, Danny.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.25,0:25:00.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你来这里干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:00.68,0:25:01.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.20,0:25:02.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我本来想跟你谈谈的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just wanted to, you know, wanted to talk to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.63,0:25:04.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们正谈着呢  你就把我电话挂了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We were talking and then you hung up on me.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:04.47,0:25:05.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是的  我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.12,0:25:08.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想给你打回去的  但是电话打不通\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I tried to call you back, but the phones weren't working.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.29,0:25:10.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以你就凌晨两点半来这里找我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So you came here at 2:30 in the morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.51,0:25:11.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,丹尼  我现在很忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Denny, I don't have time for this right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.88,0:25:16.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听我说  我就是想当面跟你道歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen, I just, I wanted to apologise to you face to face.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.09,0:25:19.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很抱歉之前对你大喊大叫  对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry that I yelled at you before. I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.45,0:25:21.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我接受你的道歉  但是现在你得回去了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Apology accepted. But you have to go now.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.46,0:25:23.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就是炸弹这事儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's just this whole thing with the bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:23.63,0:25:24.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不光是我  很多人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's not just me. A lot of
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.96,0:25:27.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都害怕接下来会发生什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}people are afraid of what's gonna happen next.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.83,0:25:30.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没人知道怎么办  你懂吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nobody knows what to do, you know?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.91,0:25:35.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不会有事的  我们这里正在处理\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's gonna be OK. We're taking care of things here.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.02,0:25:36.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道你们在努力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know. I know you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:38.58,0:25:40.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你为什么不回家睡一觉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why don't you go home and get some sleep?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:40.08,0:25:41.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会尽快去找你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll come over as soon as I can.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.92,0:25:46.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-别管她  -你没跟我说过凯莉在这里上班\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Ignore her. - You didn't tell me Carrie works here.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.55,0:25:47.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是的  她不在这里上班\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, she's not working here.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.79,0:25:49.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们缺人手  她几个钟头前才来这帮忙的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We were short-handed. She came here a couple of hours ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:49.59,0:25:50.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托了  丹尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Danny, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.85,0:25:53.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你没给我回电话  我给你打了五个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't return my calls? I called you five times.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.47,0:25:55.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你是谁  -别担心  我妹妹在这里上班\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Who are you? - Don't worry aboout that. My sister works here.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.85,0:25:58.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你看  我一直在忙  丹尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I've been in the middle of things right now, Denny.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.07,0:25:59.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是吗  我就是很担心你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is that right? I was just worried about you.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.89,0:26:02.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,仅此而已  我希望也许你也能担心担心我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's all. I was hoping maybe you'd be worried about me too.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.39,0:26:03.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,丹尼  够了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Denny, stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.35,0:26:05.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么  你现在站凯莉那边吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why? You taking Carrie's side now?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.57,0:26:07.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当然没有  我没站她那边  到我办公桌去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course not. I'm not taking her side. Come to my station.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.53,0:26:10.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-喂  过来  我想跟你谈谈  -丹尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Hey, come here. I wanna talk to you. - Danny!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.43,0:26:15.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你为什么不回我电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why didn't you call me back?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:20.63,0:26:21.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉他们我是你哥哥  米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell them I'm your brother, Michelle!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.29,0:26:40.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,林恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lynne.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.20,0:26:50.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,关于那个会  你是对的  不是谣传\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You were right about the meeting. It's not a rumor.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.41,0:26:53.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,普莱斯考特亲自给内阁成员们打电话主持会议\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Prescott's calling Cabinet members personally to set it up.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.62,0:26:56.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会议是不是关于总统取消进攻的决定的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is it about the president's decision to call off the attack?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.22,0:26:57.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还不知道  我国防部的线人说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know yet. My source at Defence says
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.96,0:27:00.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他有消息  他答应见我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}he has information. He agreed to meet me.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:01.00,0:27:03.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他是谁  -他叫杰斯柏·伊斯伯格\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Who is it? -His name is Jesper Isberg.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.44,0:27:05.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,电话上他什么也不说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He won't tell me anything over the phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:07.07,0:27:08.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你什么时候见他  -现在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- When are you meeting him? - Now.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:10.26,0:27:10.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,地点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.63,0:27:15.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不要去为好  林恩  你可能会吓到他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't think you should be there, Lynne. You might spook him.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:15.19,0:27:16.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,麦克  是我带你进这个案子的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mike, I'm the one who brought you into this.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.74,0:27:17.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在我要得到一手消息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now I wanna hear what's going
Dialogue: 0,0:27:17.55,0:27:19.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后我们再汇报给总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}on first hand before we take this to the president.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:22.37,0:27:25.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,楼上有个房间  522房  是个储藏间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's a room upstairs, 522. It's used for storage.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:26.04,0:27:26.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们在那里见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll meet you there.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:46.43,0:27:47.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很快就回来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll be right back.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.98,0:27:55.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:58.84,0:27:59.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要去哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where are you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.21,0:28:02.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要去信息技术中心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was just going over to IT.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.55,0:28:05.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还在努力打开通道程序块软件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm still trying to access the CPB software.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.47,0:28:08.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,信息技术中心在另一边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}IT's the other way.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:11.68,0:28:14.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我就是  就是想静一静  托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just... I just need a minute, Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.51,0:28:20.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯莉会没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Carrie's gonna be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:24.76,0:28:27.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她会不会  会不会提起诉讼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is she gonna... Is she gonna press charges?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.15,0:28:29.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不会  我觉得不会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, I don't think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.24,0:28:35.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都怪我  我应该预见到的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's all my fault. I should've seen it coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.25,0:28:39.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,家里的事情  很正常  你无法预见的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's family. These things happen. You can't see it coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:42.16,0:28:45.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他是我哥哥  我是说  他的孩子们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's my brother. I mean, his kids...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.08,0:28:51.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也许我该事先告诉他炸弹的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Maybe I should have told him about the bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:53.95,0:28:56.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这太难选择了  但是你做得很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was a tough choice, but you made it.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.54,0:28:58.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而且  你做得对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And, by the way, you were right.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:00.18,0:29:00.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.18,0:29:03.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我今天做的没一件事是对的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nothing I've done today is right.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.47,0:29:06.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.70,0:29:08.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天这么多条生命没了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All these people today that are dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.05,0:29:14.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有这录音  我不知道我们到底做的对不对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And then this recording. I don't know if we're right about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.37,0:29:15.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't...
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.04,0:29:19.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不能再这么做了  托尼  我做不到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't do this any more, Tony. I can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.83,0:29:22.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔  没事  没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle. Come here, come here.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.65,0:29:26.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我好累  好害怕\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm so tired. I'm so scared.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.95,0:29:27.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's ok.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.77,0:29:32.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没关系的  没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's ok. It's all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.99,0:29:52.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对不起  对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.33,0:30:06.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.00,0:30:09.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,查普尔在找你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Chapelle's looking for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:10.58,0:30:11.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:39.61,0:30:40.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:57.75,0:30:58.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:01.52,0:32:02.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快点  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:10.14,0:32:13.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你这样会杀了他  你不能一直这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're gonna kill him. You can't keep doing this.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.18,0:32:16.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别再碰我一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't ever touch me again.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:48.60,0:32:51.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-是我  -有什么进展了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yes? - Have you made any progress?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.58,0:32:54.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们还在努力  -我说过我们时间不够了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- We're still working on him. - I told you, there's a time issue.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.04,0:32:56.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  您说过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir. You told me.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:57.08,0:32:59.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你可千万不要让我失望\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You do not wanna disappoint me on this.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.65,0:33:02.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一定要把芯片给我  斯塔克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get me that chip, Stark.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:04.46,0:33:05.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I will.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:25.43,0:33:28.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们要见的人呢  -马上就到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- So where's this person we're meeting? - He'll be here soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:30.15,0:33:30.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你还听说过其他什么风声吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Have you heard anything
Dialogue: 0,0:33:30.80,0:33:32.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么普莱斯考特要背着总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}else about why Prescott called this meeting?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:32.51,0:33:34.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,举行这次会面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Behind the president's back.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:34.19,0:33:36.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们都知道这是会有后果的  林恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We knew there'd be consequences, Lynne,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:36.70,0:33:39.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对当局有异议  但是从没有这样过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}dissent within the administration, but nothing like this.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:41.59,0:33:42.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么样  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Like what, Mike?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:43.65,0:33:47.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道第二十五号修正案第四条内容吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you know about Section 4 of the 25th Amendment?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:48.73,0:33:50.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当内阁大多数成员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It provides that if the majority
Dialogue: 0,0:33:50.82,0:33:54.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,认为总统无法履行职务时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}of his Cabinet feels he's unfit to fulfil his duties
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.03,0:33:56.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可以罢免总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that the president could be removed from office.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:56.83,0:33:59.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而副总统将成为代理总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And the vice president becomes acting president.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:02.57,0:34:04.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,普莱斯考特不能这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Prescott can't do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:06.54,0:34:09.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,麦克  这可是一场宫廷政变\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mike, we're talking about a palace coup.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:11.28,0:34:13.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-是杰斯柏·伊斯伯格吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Jesper Isberg? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:13.73,0:34:14.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,麻烦稍等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Give us a moment, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:19.92,0:34:21.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在我们跟他交流之前\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Before we talk to him, I need to
Dialogue: 0,0:34:21.46,0:34:24.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要问问你对于总统的决定持什么态度\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}know where you stand vis-a-vis the president's decision.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.85,0:34:27.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,麦克  你是在质疑我的忠诚吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mike, are you questioning my loyalty?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:27.41,0:34:29.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,国会内部最近会有很多暗中运作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's going to be a lot of lobbying
Dialogue: 0,0:34:30.08,0:34:33.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你需要知道你的立场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}among the Cabinet. I need to know where you stand.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:33.87,0:34:36.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  我或许不同意总统的决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I may not agree with the president's decision,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:36.33,0:34:38.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是做决定的人是他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but it was his decision to make.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:38.04,0:34:39.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,依我看来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As far as I'm concerned,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:39.62,0:34:42.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,普莱斯考特才是叛国的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it's Prescott who should be charged with treason.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:44.56,0:34:46.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你真是这么想的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you sure that's how you feel?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:46.98,0:34:48.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:50.51,0:34:51.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我就怕你会这么说  林恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was afraid you'd say that, Lynne.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:54.62,0:34:55.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,伊斯伯格先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Isberg.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:02.94,0:35:03.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:05.35,0:35:07.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要做什么  你去哪  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you doing? Where are you going? Mike?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:11.95,0:35:12.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:15.21,0:35:16.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你跟普莱斯考特是一伙的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're with Prescott?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.92,0:35:19.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为大卫不愿意听我们的理念\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Only because David wouldn't listen to reason.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:21.83,0:35:25.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你也这么说了  -麦克  你不能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You said so yourself. - Mike, you can't...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:26.18,0:35:29.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,自从他上任  我们就很担心他会优柔寡断\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We've been worried about his indecisiveness since he took office.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:29.82,0:35:33.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他的优柔寡断会害死两万个美国人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And now it's going to cost the lives of 20,000 Americans.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:33.05,0:35:34.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不能让这种事情发生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't let that happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:37.46,0:35:39.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我这么做是为了国家  林恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm doing this for the good of the country, Lynne.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.59,0:35:42.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,随你怎么说吧  别想骗我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lie to yourself all you want. Don't you dare lie to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:45.75,0:35:47.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-抱歉  -麦克  这不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'm sorry. - Mike, this is not...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:47.97,0:35:51.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要干什么  麦克  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you doing? Mike! Mike!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:54.43,0:35:55.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,开门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Open this door!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:57.12,0:35:58.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,开门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Open this door!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.08,0:36:03.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,除非收到我的命令  否则绝对不能让她离开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Until you hear from me - only me - do not let her out.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:04.01,0:36:04.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,明白\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Understood.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:07.02,0:36:08.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,开门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Open this door!
Dialogue: 0,0:36:24.36,0:36:25.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,开门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Open this door!
Dialogue: 0,0:36:26.21,0:36:28.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,白宫方面确认了核弹爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The White House has confirmed the nuclear explosion.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:28.54,0:36:30.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生不久后将发表演讲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The president will address the nation shortly.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:31.20,0:36:34.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,消息已经传到了南方地区  警方通报了一批\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The news has already reached the south land and Police have reported a number
Dialogue: 0,0:36:34.25,0:36:36.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,针对中东人的公司或宗教场地的仇恨活动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}of hate crimes against Middle Eastern businesses and places of worship.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:36.76,0:36:39.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有关部门提醒民众\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Authorities are urging people
Dialogue: 0,0:36:39.42,0:36:41.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尽量待在家中  减少外出\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to stay inside their homes and off the street.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:47.64,0:36:49.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克说我们应该不管他先走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack said we should leave without him.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:50.14,0:36:51.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再等等他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's give him another minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:51.30,0:36:53.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们已经给了他足够多的时间了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We've given him much longer than he asked for already.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:55.48,0:36:58.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要把芯片交到反恐组  他们还在等\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have to get this chip to CTU. They're expecting it.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:59.64,0:37:02.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果杰克需要我们的帮助呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about Jack? What if he needs our help?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:02.21,0:37:03.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把这个交给反恐组才是重中之重\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Getting this to CTU is the priority.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:14.42,0:37:16.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你还好吗  -没事  你呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You OK? - Yeah. You?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:16.77,0:37:17.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:21.94,0:37:23.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,臭中东佬\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's a damn towel head.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:23.57,0:37:25.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们想要用那颗炸弹炸死我们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your people tried killing us with that bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:25.14,0:37:27.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有第二次机会了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're not getting a second chance.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.12,0:37:35.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,后退  后退  把手举起来  趴下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get back. Get back, put your hands up, get down on the pavement.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:36.84,0:37:39.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把脸低下去  手放在我能看到的地方  快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Facedown! Hands where I can see 'em! Now!
Dialogue: 0,0:37:39.62,0:37:41.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-照他说的做  -该你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Do what he says. - Your turn.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:43.43,0:37:43.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,趴下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get down.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:47.73,0:37:48.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  回去车里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate, get back in the car.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:54.68,0:37:57.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,优素福  你后面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yusuf! Behind you!
Dialogue: 0,0:37:58.05,0:37:58.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:00.36,0:38:00.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:01.03,0:38:02.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,下次来之前好好想想\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Think twice next time you come here!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:02.71,0:38:05.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别这样  你不知道你在做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stop it! You don't know what you're doing!
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.71,0:38:20.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,查普尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Chapelle.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:20.65,0:38:24.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,莱恩  我是托尼·阿尔梅达  听说你找我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ryan, it's Tony Almeida. I was told you were trying to reach me.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:24.23,0:38:25.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你这么快回我电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thanks for getting back to me so soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:26.67,0:38:28.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,恭喜你升职\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Congratulations on the promotion.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.40,0:38:31.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也希望能在更合适的时候升职\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wish it could have been under better circumstances.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:32.34,0:38:36.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-梅森是个好人  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yeah, Mason was a good man. - Yeah, he was.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:36.65,0:38:38.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,莱恩  我们这里还挺忙的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, Ryan, we're pretty busy around here.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:38.58,0:38:40.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道  我只是想提醒你一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I just wanted to give you a heads-up.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:41.90,0:38:44.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么  -我带了些人从分局赶过来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- About what? - I'm on my way over with a couple of keys from Division.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.32,0:38:46.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:47.20,0:38:49.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,经历了这么多事情  我觉得你可能需要帮助\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I thought you could use some help, with all that's going on.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.36,0:38:53.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们还好  莱恩  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're doing pretty well here, Ryan. Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:53.83,0:38:56.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道你们还好  三十分钟后见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sure you are. I'll see you in 30 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.31,0:39:17.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-戴斯勒  -你好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Dessler. - Hey.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.75,0:39:20.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你收到关于你哥哥的消息了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Have you heard anything about your brother yet?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:20.36,0:39:22.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们给他打了镇静剂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. They sedated him.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:23.63,0:39:25.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们说等他醒来会叫我的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They said they'd call me when he wakes up.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:27.08,0:39:29.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你现在怎么样  -还可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How are you holding up? - OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:31.01,0:39:33.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你呢  -我没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You? - I'm OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:37.50,0:39:37.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:40.25,0:39:44.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对于刚才发生的事情   很抱歉  我不该\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}About what happened before. I'm sorry, I shouldn't have...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:44.14,0:39:46.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不用  你不用道歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, don't. Don't be sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.35,0:39:48.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没觉得抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:53.43,0:39:53.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Really?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:56.79,0:39:57.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Really.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:02.88,0:40:05.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-凯莉那边怎么样  -别担心凯莉了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What about Carrie? - Don't worry about Carrie.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:06.34,0:40:08.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我了解她  她不会轻易放手的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know her. She's not gonna let this go.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:08.61,0:40:12.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这跟她无关  没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's none of her business. It's gonna be OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:12.97,0:40:13.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:27.08,0:40:27.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把他叫醒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wake him up.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:31.49,0:40:34.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们应该让他休息一下  -叫醒他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- We should probably give him a minute. - Wake him up.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:44.71,0:40:46.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你也进行过逼供  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You've been on this side before, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:47.39,0:40:50.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道所有人都有忍耐的限度\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know everybody has a limit to how much they can take.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:50.56,0:40:53.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,每个人都有临界点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Everybody has a breaking point.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:54.11,0:40:54.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,即使是你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Even you.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:58.67,0:41:02.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道你有一个女儿  是金吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I understand you've got a daughter. Is it Kim?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:12.09,0:41:13.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你也不想让金成为孤儿吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You wouldn't want Kim to be an orphan, would you?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:24.95,0:41:25.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,电他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hit him.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:42.01,0:41:42.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Again.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:43.76,0:41:45.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他死了对我们就没意义了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's no good to us dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:59.72,0:42:00.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把他弄醒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wake him up.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:15.60,0:42:16.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,弄醒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wake him up.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:21.36,0:42:23.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么回事  -他没有回应\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What's the problem? - He's not responding.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:43.74,0:42:44.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他死了  -把他放下来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- He's dead. - Cut him down!
Dialogue: 0,0:42:51.36,0:42:51.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Outta the way!
Dialogue: 0,0:42:54.72,0:42:55.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去拿肾上腺素\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get some epinephrine!
Dialogue: 0,0:42:57.29,0:42:57.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把嘴打开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Clear his airway.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:01.30,0:43:03.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-肾上腺素呢  -这里没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where's that epinephrine? - There isn't any.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:03.54,0:43:04.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,赶紧去找\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go find some!

