[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,1,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.65,0:00:10.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(197.4,200.557)}{\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs25\b1\bord0\shad0\c&H78BDE7&\fad(0,808)}24小时\N\N{\fs15}第二季  第二十一集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.11,0:00:13.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(189.6,121.6,193.8,105.6,0,356)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad3\3c&H2F2F2F&\4c&H336D99&}{\fs10}{\t(0,356,\fs20)\fn方正正中黑简体}前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.91,0:00:16.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,吉姆  你我都清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jim, we both know that
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.34,0:00:18.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你一直是我取消这次袭击的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you've been one of the most outspoken opponents
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.78,0:00:16.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(96.6,217.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.83,0:00:16.87,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(121.8,201.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.87,0:00:16.91,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(147,184.553)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.91,0:00:16.95,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(171,168)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.95,0:00:16.99,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(194.4,149.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.99,0:00:17.03,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(220.8,132.553)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.03,0:00:19.08,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\fad(0,346)\pos(246,117.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.74,0:00:21.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,主要反对者之一\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to my decision to call off this attack.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.01,0:00:22.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要是有什么事要说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you have something to say,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.02,0:00:25.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我希望你先向我报告\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I would expect you to bring it to me first.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.57,0:00:28.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统知道情况吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Does the president have any idea what's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.41,0:00:30.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-应该不知道  -保持住\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I don't think so. - Let's keep it that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.21,0:00:33.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,感谢大家这么快就赶来开会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you for assembling at such short notice.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.05,0:00:33.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(298.2,223.753)}吉姆·普莱斯考特副总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.09,0:00:33.13,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(270,206.153)}吉姆·普莱斯考特副总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.13,0:00:33.18,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(240.6,188.553)}吉姆·普莱斯考特副总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.18,0:00:33.22,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(211.8,168.553)}吉姆·普莱斯考特副总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.22,0:00:33.26,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(183.6,152.553)}吉姆·普莱斯考特副总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.26,0:00:33.30,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(153,133.353)}吉姆·普莱斯考特副总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.30,0:00:35.30,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(125.4,114.953)\fad(0,347)}吉姆·普莱斯考特副总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.35,0:00:35.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想你们都想知道我为什么叫你们来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sure you're all wondering why I've invited you here.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.24,0:00:40.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我真诚地相信  基于他对于今日事件的回应\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It is my sincere belief, based on his response to today's events,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.58,0:00:42.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大卫·帕尔默不适合\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}David Palmer is unfit to continue
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.19,0:00:45.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,继续出任美国总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}as President of the United States.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.34,0:00:47.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看来你今天经历了不少\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Looks like you've had quite a day.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.16,0:00:50.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我没有杀人  -我知道你没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I didn't kill anyone. - I know you didn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.94,0:00:48.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(117,208.553)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.98,0:00:49.03,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(142.8,191.753)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.03,0:00:49.07,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(165.6,173.353)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.07,0:00:49.11,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(189.6,156.553)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.11,0:00:49.15,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(214.2,140.553)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.15,0:00:51.19,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(239.4,124.553)\fad(0,305)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.46,0:00:52.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们知道加里·马西森杀了他妻子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We know Gary Matheson killed his wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.63,0:00:53.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们正在找他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're looking for him now.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.56,0:00:56.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以今早发生的事情跟你无关了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So you're off the hook for everything that happened this morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.92,0:01:00.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不是说得很清楚吗  托尼  别再管鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I thought I made myself clear, Tony. We're past Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.33,0:00:59.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(126,230.153)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.37,0:00:59.41,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(146.4,212.553)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.41,0:00:59.46,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(168.6,194.153)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.46,0:00:59.50,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(189.6,176.553)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.50,0:00:59.54,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(211.8,158.153)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.54,0:00:59.58,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(234,141.353)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.58,0:01:01.58,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\fad(0,389)\pos(256.8,124.553)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.91,0:01:02.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  长官  你不管  我管\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, sir. You are. I'm not.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.45,0:01:04.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你不放心我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, if you're not comfortable
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.42,0:01:06.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,自己做决定的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}with me making my own decisions here,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.07,0:01:08.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我建议你立刻解除我的职务\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I suggest you relieve me of my duties now.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.49,0:01:09.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没这必要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That won't be necessary.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.99,0:01:12.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-谢谢你  长官  -不用谢我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Thank you, sir. - Don't thank me.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.95,0:01:15.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是我现在没有能取代你的人而已\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just don't have anyone to take your place right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.18,0:01:17.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不要  -快给我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- No! - Come on, give me that!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.56,0:01:19.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(126.6,226.153)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.61,0:01:19.65,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(149.4,207.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.65,0:01:19.69,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(172.2,191.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.69,0:01:19.73,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(193.8,174.153)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.73,0:01:19.77,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(214.8,158.153)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.77,0:01:19.81,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(237.6,141.353)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.81,0:01:21.85,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\fad(0,353)\pos(259.2,126.153)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.84,0:01:21.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  你没事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate, are you all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.17,0:01:22.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事  他们把芯片拿走了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. They've got the chip!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.88,0:01:26.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只想要芯片\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All I want is the chip!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.74,0:01:30.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你走进来  我就把芯片毁了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You come in here, I'm gonna smash this thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.80,0:01:32.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会踩烂它\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll put it right under my foot!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.78,0:01:39.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs15\t(696,6577,\fs16)\c&H4BAAAD&\fad(1697,1183)\pos(187.2,191.79)}以下故事情节发生在凌晨4点到凌晨5点之间
Dialogue: 0,0:01:40.98,0:01:42.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,至少告诉我你们是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}At least let me know who I'm speaking to.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.46,0:01:43.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们是谁并不重要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It doesn't matter who we are.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:43.96,0:01:45.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,重要的是我们有你们想要的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The only thing matters is we got something you want,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.39,0:01:47.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你女朋友愿意花大价钱得到它\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}something your girlfriend was about to pay us a lot of money for.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.61,0:01:48.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们两个  给我听清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen to me. Both of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:48.77,0:01:50.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大约五个小时前  有颗核弹爆炸了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}About five hours ago, a nuclear bomb went off.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.89,0:01:51.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想你们都听说了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sure you know about that.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:53.12,0:01:55.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们手里的芯片有对此事负责的人的信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The chip you have has the information about who's responsible.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.63,0:01:57.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这对我们的调查至关重要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's vital to our investigation.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.53,0:01:59.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们之前袭击的那个人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The man you assaulted was a foreign intelligence agent
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.71,0:02:01.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是来帮我取芯片的国际情报员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}who was bringing the chip to my office.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:04.21,0:02:06.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只给你们一次脱身的机会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna give you one chance to get out of this.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.28,0:02:08.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把芯片给我  我放你们走  绝不废话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Give me the chip back, and I'll let you walk, no questions.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.79,0:02:10.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别以为我们不知道你在骗我们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Think we don't know you're setting us up.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.12,0:02:10.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  别过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate, get back.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.78,0:02:12.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  你在干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack. What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.20,0:02:14.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们杀了优素福  还准备对我下手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They killed Yusuf. They are about to kill me.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.32,0:02:15.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们准备对三个本不该\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're about to call the war against three innocent countries
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.93,0:02:17.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为今天事发负责的无辜国家发动战争\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}who are not supposed to responseable for what happened today
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.88,0:02:20.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,唯一能阻止此事的就是把芯片交到总统手上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The only way I can stop it is when i give president that chip right now,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.85,0:02:22.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以我要竭尽所能拿到芯片\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so I'm gonna do everything I can to get it back.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.26,0:02:28.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托  凯特  帮帮我  联系反恐组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please, Kate, I need your help. Get in touch with CTU. Please!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.73,0:02:32.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,限你们半分钟内把门打开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll give you 30 seconds to open that door.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:32.90,0:02:34.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-给我  -你疯了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Give it to him. - Are you crazy?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:34.68,0:02:37.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只有这样他才不会像杀洛克斯一样杀了我们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is the only thing keeping him from killing us like he killed Rox.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.06,0:02:38.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有二十秒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You got 20 seconds!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:38.45,0:02:39.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是吗  我们得相信你吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes. We are just suppose to trust you?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.04,0:02:41.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们现在也别无选择\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right now you don't have a another choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:41.15,0:02:42.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-给他吧  -没门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Just give it to him. - No way
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.17,0:02:43.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他来真的  -我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- He's serious! - So am I.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.49,0:02:45.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我们不开门他会杀了我们的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's gonna kill us if we don't open the door.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:50.90,0:02:54.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,面靠墙  马上  芯片在哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Against the wall! Now! Where's the chip?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.46,0:02:55.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我丢掉了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I dropped it.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.09,0:02:58.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't move.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.98,0:03:01.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  凯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate! Kate!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.39,0:03:06.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,找绳子把他们绑起来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get some wires so I can tie these guys up.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.11,0:03:07.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-芯片怎样了  -我拿到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What about the chip? - I've got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.92,0:03:21.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,刚刚拿到国防部的简报声称\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just got this Pentagon briefing stating
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.58,0:03:23.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们的轰炸机不准备返回基地\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that our bombers aren't going back to their bases.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.95,0:03:28.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道这件事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you know anything about this?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.64,0:03:31.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道他们在待命航线上  等待燃料补给\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I understand they're holding pattern, awaiting refueling.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.32,0:03:34.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我下令让他们返回基地\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I ordered them back to their bases.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.41,0:03:36.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  先生  我知道  这是我来的目的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah sir. I know. That's why I'm here.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.72,0:03:38.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能跟我来一下吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Could I ask you come with me for a minute?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.73,0:03:41.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,跟你去哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come with you where?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.64,0:03:43.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去大厅那边的主会议室\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just down the hall to the main conference room.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:45.72,0:03:46.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么回事  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's going on, Mike?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.48,0:03:51.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托了  总统先生  跟我来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please, Mr President, come with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.82,0:03:55.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在命令我跟你去会议室吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're ordering me to the conference room?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.33,0:04:00.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  先生  当然不是  我很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, sir, of course not. I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.63,0:04:05.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在请求您  这非常重要  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm asking. It's very important, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.95,0:04:11.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,麦克  我是美国总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mike, I'm the President of the United States.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.98,0:04:14.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不告诉我发生了什么我哪儿也不去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not going anywhere until you tell me what this is about.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.79,0:04:18.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President...
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.00,0:04:23.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,似乎有部分内阁成员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it seems there are a number of people, cabinet members,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.82,0:04:27.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,质疑你是否有能力继续担任\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}who question whether you're fit to continue
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.08,0:04:29.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个国家的领导人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}as chief executive of this country.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:38.71,0:04:40.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些人现在在会议室里吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And these people are in my conference room?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.39,0:04:45.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,某种意义上讲  先生  是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In a manner of speaking, sir, they are.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.36,0:04:48.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我们去瞧瞧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then let's go see them.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.66,0:05:09.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:18.36,0:05:21.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我现在知道今天为何总是联系不到你  吉姆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So now I see why I had such a hard time reaching you today, Jim.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.02,0:05:25.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在忙着这些事情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You were busy.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.71,0:05:29.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,事发突然我很抱歉  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I apologize if this comes as a surprise, Mr President.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.49,0:05:33.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在我国历史上对于这种非常情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is a unique situation in the history of our country,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.88,0:05:35.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只能采取非常手段\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}calling for unique measures.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.27,0:05:38.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们还是废话少说  直入正题吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's skip the sound bites and cut to the chase.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.01,0:05:41.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有话直说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's going on here?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.86,0:05:43.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:43.61,0:05:45.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要行使第二十五修正案\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we are invoking the 25th Amendment.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.24,0:05:52.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"我们"是指谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who's "We"?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.26,0:05:55.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对于今天的决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's a general feeling
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.80,0:05:57.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大家总体上感觉...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that the some of decisions that be made today...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.12,0:06:00.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等  副总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hold on a minute, Mr. Vice President.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.57,0:06:05.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,恕我直言  先生  今天到场的大多数\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}With all due respect, sir, most of us here are scrambling
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.57,0:06:08.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只想弄清楚今天发生的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}just to understand today's events.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.10,0:06:09.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得现在提"总体感觉"\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think it's way way too early to
Dialogue: 0,0:06:09.97,0:06:13.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,恐怕还不太合适\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}be referring to a "general feeling" About anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.66,0:06:15.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说的没错  郑重声明\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fair enough. For the record,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.78,0:06:19.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我来重读一下二十五修正案的有关内容\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}let me review the relevant portions of the 25th Amendment.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.24,0:06:20.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,第四部分声明\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Section 4 states
Dialogue: 0,0:06:20.62,0:06:23.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果副总统和内阁主要成员一致决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}whenever the vice president and the majority of the cabinet determine
Dialogue: 0,0:06:23.82,0:06:26.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统没有能力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that the president is unable to discharge the powers
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.39,0:06:27.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,履行他的职责\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and duties of his office,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.06,0:06:31.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,应该由副总统代替接任\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the vice president shall immediately take office as acting president.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.94,0:06:32.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大家都听清了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is everyone clear on that?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.91,0:06:35.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,第二十五修正案针对的是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The 25th Amendment was designed for situations
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.79,0:06:38.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统身染疾病或丧失行动能力的情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}where the president is ill or incapacitated.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.13,0:06:41.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,表述已经很清楚了  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The language speak itself, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:41.08,0:06:43.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"未能履行其办公室的权利和职责"\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Unable to discharge the powers and duties of his office."
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.72,0:06:46.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不管是出于何种原因的无能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The reason for the disability isn't limited to any particular cause.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:47.47,0:06:49.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,司法部长同意这种解释\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The Attorney General agrees with this interpretation.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.26,0:06:53.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那究竟哪里显示出我的无能了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And just what exactly is my supposed disability?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.29,0:06:56.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得一目了然  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It seems clear to me, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.19,0:07:00.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天事发所带来的压力已超出你的承受能力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that the stress of today's events has overwhelmed you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.52,0:07:03.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天在美国境内有一枚核弹爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}An atomic device has been detonated on American soil today.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.00,0:07:08.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们很清楚哪些国家该为此负责\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have clear evidence which countries are responsible,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.32,0:07:12.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,以及他们支持的恐怖组织的详细情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}along with details of the terrorist group they sponsor.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.32,0:07:16.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,证据还未能确凿表明就是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The evidence implicating these countries
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.58,0:07:20.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些国家 普莱斯考特先生  远不够\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is not clear, Mr. Prescott. Far from it.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.47,0:07:23.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,塞浦路斯的录音已被我们多方情报机构\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The Cyprus audio has been independently verified
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.16,0:07:25.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,独立验证过了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}by every intelligence group we have.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.51,0:07:28.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我有理由相信这些人搞错了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have reason to believe that thoes agencies are mistaken.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.26,0:07:31.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就因为反恐组一个探员的话  杰克·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because of this lone CTU agent, Jack Bauer?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.69,0:07:37.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错  鲍尔先生认为塞浦路斯的录音是假的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes. Mr. Bauer believes that the Cyprus audio is a forgery.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.16,0:07:40.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他也相信很快他就能拿到证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He also believes that he will soon have proof.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.95,0:07:43.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他这话已经说了几小时了  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's been telling you that for hours, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.64,0:07:45.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你仍然没有拿到证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You still don't have the proof.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:49.22,0:07:51.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果还不采取军事行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If military strikes do not occur immediately,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.93,0:07:53.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,美军士兵的伤亡数\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}casualties to American soldiers
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.81,0:07:56.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会以万为单位增长\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}would increase by tens of thousands of lives.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:57.04,0:07:58.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这点毋庸置疑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That analysis is undisputed.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.94,0:08:02.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们不能冒险向无辜国家开火\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The risk of attacking innocent countries is unacceptable.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:02.34,0:08:03.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们必须有十足把握\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have to be sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.56,0:08:06.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大家都很笃定  总统先生  除了你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Everybody is sure, Mr. President. Everybody but you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.92,0:08:10.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,遇到这种情况  我说了算\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As it happens, I'm the only who counts.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.00,0:08:15.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会议到此为止\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This meeting is over.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:15.96,0:08:20.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  不管怎样  投票不可避免\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, one way or another, there will be a vote.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.77,0:08:23.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我认为在投票前应该让你知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think that you should be heard before that vote is taken.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.68,0:08:36.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不喜欢我其中一项决策\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't like one of my policy decisions.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.71,0:08:39.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,第二十五修正案就算在我身体不好的情况下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The 25th Amendment does not give you the right to reverse that policy
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.54,0:08:41.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也没有允许你修改我的决策\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}under the pretense saying I have a disability.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.26,0:08:44.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  我同意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, I agree.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.47,0:08:47.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想强调的是从这次危机开始\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What I intend to show is a pattern
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.89,0:08:50.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你所表现的不稳定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}of erratic and irrational behavior on your part
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.13,0:08:52.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,以及不理智行为\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}since the start of this crisis.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.24,0:08:55.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样想来  你拒绝授权军事行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Seen in that light, your refusal to authorize military action
Dialogue: 0,0:08:55.88,0:08:57.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这又是你无能的表现\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is simply another symptom of disability.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.25,0:09:01.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给我听着  在座的各位\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen to me. All of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.60,0:09:05.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道你们没有和我同处一室\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know you're not in the same room with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.63,0:09:10.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但你们能清晰地看到和听到我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But you can see and hear me plainly enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:11.48,0:09:12.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,瞧仔细了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Take a good look.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.06,0:09:16.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我表现出害怕了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do I seem scared?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.87,0:09:21.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我有紧张的汗流浃背吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Am I breaking into a nervous sweat?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.71,0:09:24.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我有胡言乱语  哑口无言吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Am I babbling? At a loss for words?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:24.64,0:09:26.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我声音有颤抖吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is my voice shaking?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.79,0:09:33.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们谁敢当着我的面说我是个无能的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can any one of you look me in the eye and tell me I'm disabled?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:38.25,0:09:39.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.36,0:09:43.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,问题并不在于你过去几分钟内的举止\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the issue is not your demeanor over the past few minutes,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.46,0:09:47.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而是过去二十个小时内你的行为\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but your actions over the past 20 hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.33,0:09:53.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  副总统提出的问题都很严重\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, the vice president has raised serious questions
Dialogue: 0,0:09:53.71,0:09:57.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在我看来  你不该对此置若罔闻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and, in my opinion, it would be a mistake to ignore them.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.70,0:10:00.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在我看来  只要你一如往常\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For my part, I'm confident that if you explain yourself
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.55,0:10:03.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,清晰明白的解释清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}with your usual candor and clarity,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.25,0:10:05.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所有问题将迎刃而解\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}all questions will be resolved
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.47,0:10:07.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能让在座的各位满意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to the satisfaction of everyone here.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.14,0:10:18.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,普莱斯考特先生  似乎各位确实\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Prescott, there seems to be a collective feeling
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.88,0:10:20.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都有一些疑惑需要讨论解决\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that a discussion is called for.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.19,0:10:24.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为了结束此事  我同意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In the interest of putting this behind us, I'll agree.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.32,0:10:32.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有个条件  等结束后  如果我得到拥戴\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}On one condition: when it's over, if I'm supported,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.19,0:10:35.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你递交辞呈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you tender your resignation
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.59,0:10:37.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,辞去副总统一职\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}as the vice president of this country.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.86,0:10:46.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好  总统先生  我同意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Very well, Mr. President. I agree.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:49.99,0:10:53.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我建议我们休息几分钟修整一下自己\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I suggest we all take a few minutes to compose ourselves
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.89,0:10:57.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,之后再继续这一议程\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and get on with the proceeding.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.37,0:11:00.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们别拐弯抹角  国务卿先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's not mince words, Mr. Secretary.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:01.26,0:11:03.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是指对大卫·帕尔默的审讯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You mean the trial of David Palmer.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.13,0:11:27.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在问题是他们对不上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, the problem is that they don't correspond.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.60,0:11:28.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要他们对得上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need them to.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:28.71,0:11:30.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,莱恩  我能和你谈谈吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ryan, could I have a word with you, please?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.75,0:11:32.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等我一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Give me a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.43,0:11:36.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我刚得到条消息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just got a message
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.41,0:11:39.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统一小时前取消了军事打击\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that the president called off the military offensive one hour ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.89,0:11:42.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-谁告诉你的  -司法部的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Who told you this? - Someone at DOJ.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.39,0:11:47.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-一个熟人  -没什么可担心的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Someone I trust. - I wouldn't worry about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.40,0:11:49.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is it true?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:50.54,0:11:52.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-是  -你早就知道了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yes. - And you knew about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:52.43,0:11:53.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没错  -你没想告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I did. - And you didn't tell me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.16,0:11:56.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么行动已经取消\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why you still keep my people processing intel
Dialogue: 0,0:11:56.91,0:11:58.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你还让人继续处理相关情报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}on a operation that's be scrapped?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.82,0:12:00.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为有很大可能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because there's a strong possibility
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.90,0:12:03.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,白宫会重启打击命令\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the White House will reinstate the attack.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:04.42,0:12:05.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这说不通\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It doesn't make sense.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.74,0:12:08.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统为什么会两次改变命令\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why would the president reverse his orders twice?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.71,0:12:11.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让你的人处于备战状态就行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just keep your people on a war footing.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.75,0:12:20.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼  有电话  杰克·鲍尔在二号线\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony, phones are up. I got Jack Bauer on line two.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.56,0:12:22.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他在哪儿  -他在凯特·华纳的家里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where is he? - He's in the Kate Warner's house.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.80,0:12:23.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他在那儿做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}what's he doing there?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.67,0:12:24.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道  但他拿到芯片了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know, but he has the chip.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.64,0:12:27.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-把电话接到我办公室  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Conference-call him to my office. - OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:42.61,0:12:43.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  我是托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, it's Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:43.89,0:12:45.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你怎么会在凯特·华纳的家里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}what are you doing at Kate Warner's house?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:45.23,0:12:47.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你一小时前就该把芯片带回来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You were supposed to bring that chip here over an hour ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:47.03,0:12:49.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们遇到些干扰  优素福·奥达死了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We ran into some interference. Yusuf Auda is dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.76,0:12:52.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么回事  -没时间解释了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What happened? - I don't have a time to explain.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.84,0:12:54.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们能拿到芯片多亏了他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's the only reason we still got this chip.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.01,0:12:56.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  我正在试着读取芯片内容\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look. I'm trying to read it now.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.67,0:12:59.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我把它放在闪存条适配器  但读不出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I put it on a flash card adapter, but something's not working.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.46,0:13:01.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  我是米歇尔  给我点时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, This is Michelle. Just give me a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.85,0:13:03.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你可能可以重启查阅功能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You may be able to override the reader function manually.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.89,0:13:04.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我来教你怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll talk you through it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.61,0:13:06.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  托尼  在她准备时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK. Good. Tony, while she's getting set up,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:07.06,0:13:08.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你帮我准备点东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need you to do a couple things for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.32,0:13:11.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,帮我查查彼得·金斯利这个人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you to run a background check on the name Peter Kingsley.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.28,0:13:12.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可能是个化名\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's probably an alias,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.56,0:13:13.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但也说不准\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but we might get lucky.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.46,0:13:14.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把他和石油工业有关的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you to cross-reference it
Dialogue: 0,0:13:14.82,0:13:16.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所有重要人物交叉对比\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}with every major player in the oil industry.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:16.49,0:13:19.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-彼得·金斯利  为什么  -我稍后解释\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Peter Kingsley. Why? - I'll explain to you later.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:19.19,0:13:21.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,首先告诉总统我们拿到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}First I need you touch with the president
Dialogue: 0,0:13:21.42,0:13:22.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他想要的证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}tell him we've got the evidence that he needs.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:22.64,0:13:26.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我告诉他了  我刚刚得知他取消了军事进攻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I already told him. I just found out he's called off the military strikes.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:26.31,0:13:27.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好  这给了我们多余时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good. Then we've got some time.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:27.80,0:13:31.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有  杰克  查普尔说命令可能会被重启\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not necessarily, Jack. Chappelle just told me the order may be reversed.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.42,0:13:32.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:32.69,0:13:36.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他没具体说  但白宫有事发生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He didn't get specific, but something's going on in Washington
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.53,0:13:38.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一些不该我们知道的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}something we're not supposed to know about.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.23,0:13:43.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-米歇尔  你准备好了吗  -好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Michelle, are you ready for me? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.42,0:13:47.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我邀请一个人加入我们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've asked someone to join us.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:00.38,0:14:02.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们很多人都认识罗恩·维兰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Most of you know Ron Wieland.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.75,0:14:06.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,罗恩是一名备受尊敬的国家事务记者\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ron is one of the most respected national affairs correspondent in our country.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.67,0:14:10.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今早在他身上发生了件有意思的事  罗恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He had a very interesting experience earlier today. Ron?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.64,0:14:15.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我当时去报道帕默尔总统的环境演讲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was sent to cover President Palmer's environmental speech
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.11,0:14:17.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉察出背后另有隐情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}when I began to sense a bigger story.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.64,0:14:20.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有传言称西海岸发生恐怖袭击\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There were rumors of a terrorist attack on the West Coast,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.21,0:14:22.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可能牵涉到核武器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}possibly involving a nuclear device.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.08,0:14:24.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我自然不停的追问\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Naturally i kept asking questions.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.04,0:14:27.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,接下来  我被叫去和总统见面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Next thing I know, I was called in to talk to the president.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:28.19,0:14:31.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他要我暂时把报道压下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He asked me to keep the story under wraps until later of the day,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.10,0:14:32.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,之后他会给我个独家新闻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}then he'd give me an exclusive.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:34.17,0:14:36.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你怎么回答的  -我说要想想\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What did you say? - I told he I'd think it over.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.10,0:14:38.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,正当我要离开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But as I was leaving the building,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.62,0:14:40.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一个特勤处探员抓住我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was suddenly grabbed by a secret service agent
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.52,0:14:41.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把我推到了一个房间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and hustled me into a room.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.91,0:14:43.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在里面被监禁了数小时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was kept there under guard for several hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:45.39,0:14:48.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你觉得作为一名记者和美国人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did you feel this was a violation of your First Amendment rights
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.41,0:14:51.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的第一修正案权利受到了侵犯吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}as a journalist as well as an American citizen?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.13,0:14:52.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.04,0:14:55.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,罗恩  你有没有受伤或受到威胁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ron, were you harmed anyway or threatened?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:55.67,0:14:57.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.68,0:15:01.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道自己被拘留的原因吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did you understand the reason for your being detained?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.70,0:15:02.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想是出于害怕\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I assume it was fear that
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.83,0:15:05.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果核威胁的消息传出  会造成民众恐慌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}if word got out of a nuclear threat, panic would strike.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.33,0:15:06.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,民众可能会受伤\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}People might get hurt.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:10.09,0:15:13.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你觉得数千生命比你几个小时的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you think the lives of thousands of citizens is less important
Dialogue: 0,0:15:13.97,0:15:16.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,第一修正案权利重要的多吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}than a couple of hours of your First Amendment rights?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.55,0:15:23.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  我不这么认为  但法案赋予的权利\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, I don't. But under the Bill of Rights,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.50,0:15:26.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,决定权在我手里  不在你  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that decision was mine, not yours, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.16,0:15:32.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你觉得帕尔默政府的行为\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did you get the feeling that things were a little out of control
Dialogue: 0,0:15:32.37,0:15:34.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有没有失控\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}in the Palmer administration?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:34.14,0:15:35.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在教他说话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're putting words in his mouth.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.19,0:15:40.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的确觉得帕尔默总统有些失控\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I did have a sense the president Palmer was not in control.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.72,0:15:42.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是在权衡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was trying to balance the need
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.46,0:15:45.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,民众安全和维兰德权利间的关系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}for public safety against Ron Wieland's rights.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.15,0:15:50.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我给罗恩提了个建议  他没同意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I offered Ron a deal, and he turned me down.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.52,0:15:53.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有所谓的失控\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nothing was out of control.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.63,0:15:58.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还要说一句  我的行为有法律先例\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I might add, I had legal precedent for my action.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.62,0:16:01.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你  维兰德先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you, Mr. Wieland.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.51,0:16:06.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还要传唤其他人作证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'd like to call someone else to testify.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.49,0:16:08.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他还需要几分钟时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He should be ready in a few moments.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.06,0:16:16.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,控制键加CX-5  按下回车键\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Control CX-5, then hit "Enter."
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.36,0:16:19.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-按完了  -什么情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Done. - Anything?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.31,0:16:20.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得在读取了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think it's reading it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.41,0:16:23.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  出现很多数字和符号\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, all I'm getting are numbers and symbols.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:23.91,0:16:26.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  把芯片拔下来  把导线露出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack. Take out the chip. Make sure the leads are exposed.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:34.91,0:16:36.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-该死  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Damm it! - What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.18,0:16:39.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-芯片损坏了  -多严重\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- The chip is damaged. - How badly?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:39.76,0:16:40.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不确定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.43,0:16:43.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一部分微处理器没了  连接的导线也没了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Part of the microprocessor is gone and the leads connected to it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:43.83,0:16:46.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  不管你手上有什么数据  发送给我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, Jack. Whatever the data you have, send it to my screen.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:46.62,0:16:47.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我用修复程序处理一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna run through retrieval program here.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:47.87,0:16:49.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能打开完整的音频文件吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}were you be able to access a complete audio file?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.22,0:16:52.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只要在里面  我就能找到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If it's on there, I'll find it.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:54.19,0:16:56.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-技术部  我是尔曼 -我是阿尔梅达\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- IT, this is Farmen. - This is Almeida.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.33,0:16:59.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,派两个技术人员过来  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen, send two your guys up here right away, would you?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.74,0:17:00.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们都在忙夏普尔的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're all doing MI for Chappelle.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.02,0:17:02.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不管他们在忙什么  派两个技术人员过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look. I don't care what they are doing. I need two IT people right away.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.88,0:17:05.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-查普尔明确...  -听我的  我挂了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Chappelle specifically... - Just do it. I gotta go. All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.82,0:17:07.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿尔梅达\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Almeida.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.12,0:17:09.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼  是我   金\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony, hi, it's Kim.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.21,0:17:12.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我一直没联系上我父亲  他现在有空吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I haven't been able to reach my dad. Is he available?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.92,0:17:15.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金  我们正在处理非常重要的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kim. We're in the middle of some really important right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.96,0:17:17.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能等他有空给你回电话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can i have he call back to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.40,0:17:19.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼  拜托了  就几分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony, please. It'll just take a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.32,0:17:22.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  稍等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK. OK, just hold on.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.58,0:17:30.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你拿到了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you getting it?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.84,0:17:33.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拿到了  杰克  但你说的没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I got it, Jack, but you were right
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.33,0:17:34.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,数据严重受损\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the data is pretty screwed.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.59,0:17:38.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我派了两个技术人员帮助米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, I've just assigned two IT people to help Michelle with this.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.54,0:17:40.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可能需要最多15到20分钟时间就能好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We should get through it in 15, 20 minutes tops.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.90,0:17:44.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好的  -对了  金打电话找你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- OK, good. - Also, I got Kim on the line for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.82,0:17:46.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你  托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you, Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.01,0:17:50.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金  你爸现在可以接电话了  你们聊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kim, I got your dad on the line. Go ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.78,0:17:52.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-爸  -亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Dad? - Sweetheart.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.04,0:17:56.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼告诉我你还活着  我一直在联系你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony told me you are alive. I've been trying to reach you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:56.37,0:17:57.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你到警局了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you at the sheriff's station?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.76,0:18:01.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们现在带我去马西森家去拿我的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're taking me to the Mathesons' house to pack up my things.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.00,0:18:04.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你没事真好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Glad you're OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:05.42,0:18:06.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你也是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Me too.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.61,0:18:09.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当我得知你去世的消息  我...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When I thought you were gone, I...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.86,0:18:15.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我好想你  爸  我真的好想你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just miss you, Dad. I miss you so much.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.63,0:18:17.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也想你  亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've missed you too, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.66,0:18:19.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只想回家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just wanna come home.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.07,0:18:24.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你很快就能回家了  我保证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You'll be home soon enough, I promise, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.37,0:18:28.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK. Hey, Dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.41,0:18:31.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么了  -我爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yeah? - I love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:35.68,0:18:37.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也爱你  宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I love you too, baby.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.12,0:18:40.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们很快就能见面了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll see you soon, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.11,0:18:42.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜拜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.37,0:19:13.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你早就知道这件事了  是吧  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You knew about this, didn't you, Mike?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.52,0:19:14.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道多久了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How long have you known?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.58,0:19:16.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这不重要  总统先生  -我觉得很重要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- That doesn't matter, Mr. President. - It matters to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.85,0:19:18.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,多久了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How long?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:20.79,0:19:22.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,几个小时前\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A couple of hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:34.20,0:19:35.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你也有份参与  是不是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You were part of it, weren't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:39.34,0:19:43.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说到底  你站在普莱斯考特那边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When all's said and done... you were on Prescott's side.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.48,0:19:49.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  先生  我永远都站在你这边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, sir. I'm on your side and always will be.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:52.54,0:19:54.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这或许是件好事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This could be a good thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.10,0:19:58.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一个纠正历史性错误的机会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A chance to correct a mistake of historic proportions.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:59.13,0:20:05.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大卫  我恳求你  重新考虑一下你的立场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}David, I'm begging you, reconsider your position on this.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.73,0:20:13.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是总统  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm the president, Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:15.82,0:20:17.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不能直呼我的名字\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't call me by my first name.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.18,0:20:22.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:42.57,0:20:43.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,已经在传输了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's transmitting.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:45.96,0:20:47.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,各位  抱歉让你们久等了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Gentlemen, I'm sorry for the delay.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.87,0:20:52.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们即将见到的这个人  身体状况不太好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The man you're about to see is not entirely well.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.74,0:20:54.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,事实上  他鼓起了极大的勇气\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In fact, it's taken a great deal of courage
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.71,0:20:55.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,才能来作证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}for him to join us at all.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.42,0:20:59.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,罗杰·斯坦顿  国家安全局局长\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roger Stanton, head of the National Security Agency.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.28,0:21:02.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,罗杰  谢谢你愿意来作证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roger, thank you for speaking with us.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.90,0:21:05.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,应该的  抱歉我可能看起来有点疲惫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, of course. Sorry if I seem a bit tired.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.08,0:21:11.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在行动中心被刑讯了好几个小时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was tortured for several hours at the operations complex,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:12.02,0:21:14.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是美国总统下的命令\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}by order of the President of the United States.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.06,0:21:15.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你为什么会被刑讯  罗杰\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And why were you tortured, Roger?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.30,0:21:18.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为你觉得在核弹位置的事情上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because you thought I knew more than I was saying
Dialogue: 0,0:21:18.67,0:21:21.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道的不止我告诉你的这些\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}about the location of the nuclear bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.80,0:21:23.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说得好像国安局局长\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As if the head of NSA would
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.47,0:21:25.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会对总统有所隐瞒一样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}withhold information from the president.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.93,0:21:28.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在撒谎  罗杰  这说辞可能暂时有用\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're lying, Roger. This may work for a while,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.77,0:21:30.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但真相终究会大白于天下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but eventually the truth will come out.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.61,0:21:32.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我毫不畏惧真相  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have nothing to fear from the truth, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:33.72,0:21:35.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,斯坦顿先生  请你尽可能简短地\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As briefly as possible, Mr. Stanton,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:35.54,0:21:37.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,向我们讲述一下你今天的经历\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}tell us what happened to you today.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.06,0:21:42.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我大约在中午到达行动中心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I arrived at the OC around noon
Dialogue: 0,0:21:42.30,0:21:44.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,却发现我的助理局长  艾瑞克·雷伯恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to find that my assistant director, Eric Rayburn,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.02,0:21:46.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,被总统免职了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}had been dismissed by the president.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:47.09,0:21:49.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,解雇雷伯恩先生的理由是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What was the reason given for Mr. Rayburn's firing?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:50.18,0:21:53.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,艾瑞克想让军方立即介入\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Eric wanted to bring the military into the equation right away,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.73,0:21:56.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但总统甚至都不愿意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and the president was reluctant
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.78,0:22:02.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,考虑一下采取军事行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to even contemplate the use of military action.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:02.30,0:22:03.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这不是真的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's not true.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.60,0:22:04.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,之后的几个小时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For the next few hours,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:04.66,0:22:06.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我都在尽力为总统工作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I worked for the president as best I could.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.36,0:22:12.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但他犹疑不决  行为无常  而且如我所言\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He was indecisive, erratic and, and as I said,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.89,0:22:17.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,连考虑都不敢考虑让军方介入\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}terrified to even think of military engagement.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:19.01,0:22:21.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后  大概晚上六点多\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then...a little after six this evening,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.30,0:22:23.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我被以叛国罪名逮捕\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was arrested on the charge of treason.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.63,0:22:27.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我被带到了一间没有窗户的小房间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was taken to a small windowless room.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:28.04,0:22:29.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统进来指控我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The president entered and accused me of
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.86,0:22:32.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说我对核弹知道的不止我告诉他的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}knowing more about the bomb than I was telling him.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.78,0:22:35.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这是真的吗  -不  当然不是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Was that true? - No, of course not.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.09,0:22:38.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为总统说句话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In fairness to the president,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.41,0:22:41.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得他真的相信那是真的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think he genuinely believed it to be true.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:41.94,0:22:43.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他为什么会那么觉得\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why would he hold such a belief?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.86,0:22:48.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大卫·帕尔默是个好人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}David Palmer is a decent man.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:48.95,0:22:51.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在现在这个时代  可能太"好"了一点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Maybe he's too decent for the times we live in.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.70,0:22:56.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他想不惜一切代价避免战争\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He wanted to avoid war at any cost.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.37,0:23:01.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果他能向自己证明核弹背后是美国人主使\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If he could prove to himself that Americans were behind the bomb,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.24,0:23:04.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那他就有足够的理由不对他国\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}then he'd have a good reason not to use military force
Dialogue: 0,0:23:04.66,0:23:06.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,使用军事力量\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}against any foreign country.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.45,0:23:16.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我听说你派了两个技术人员去搞什么数据恢复\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just heard you ordered two ITs onto some kind of retrieval project.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.15,0:23:17.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们本来在处理军方情报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They were working military intel.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.35,0:23:19.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克·鲍尔拿到了一块存储芯片\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack Bauer has a chip.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.43,0:23:22.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,里面有一个音频文件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It contains an audio file
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.02,0:23:25.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们认为它能证明塞浦路斯音频是伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that we expect will prove the Cyprus audio was indeed forged.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.58,0:23:27.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这芯片现在在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where is this chip?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:28.76,0:23:31.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-芯片损坏了  -损坏了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It's been damaged. - Damaged?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.37,0:23:33.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克把数据发给我们了  但数据损坏很严重\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack sent us the data but it's pretty messed up.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.64,0:23:35.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,音频文件需要进行数据恢复\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The audio file needs to be reconstituted,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:35.26,0:23:36.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这可能需要一点时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}which is gonna take a little time.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.75,0:23:39.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-要多久  -该要多久就多久\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How long? - However long it takes.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.45,0:23:42.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大约需要十五分钟  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It should take about 15 minutes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.85,0:23:52.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,分局  查普尔办公室\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Division, Mr. Chappelle's office.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.62,0:23:54.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我有消息需要告诉副总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need to get a message to the Vice President.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.65,0:23:55.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,马上  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right away, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.08,0:24:22.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,准备好告诉我一切了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ready to tell me everything I need to know?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.95,0:24:27.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,继续\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Continue.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.70,0:24:33.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们几周前就知道核弹的事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We knew about the bomb weeks ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.02,0:24:34.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,够了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Enough!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.55,0:24:39.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这句话足以让这次会议立即结束了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This should end this discussion here and now.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.71,0:24:44.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  我是对罗杰·斯坦顿用了刑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, I had Roger Stanton tortured.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.96,0:24:47.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这不是什么好事  天知道我多讨厌这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was a horrible thing to do and God knows I hated doing it.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.29,0:24:51.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但正如我所怀疑的  他早就知道核弹的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But just as I suspected, he knew about the bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.51,0:24:53.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们也都看到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You've just seen it for yourselves.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.49,0:24:55.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我被绑到一张椅子上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When I was strapped to a chair
Dialogue: 0,0:24:55.40,0:24:59.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,每隔几秒就有上千伏的电压\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and thousands of volts of electric current passed through my body
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.13,0:25:00.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,加到我身上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}every few seconds,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:01.80,0:25:05.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不为自己的行为感到自豪  但我敢说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not proud of it, but I dare say
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.09,0:25:07.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我做了你们大多数人都会做的事  我崩溃了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I did what most of you would've done - I cracked.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.70,0:25:10.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉了总统他想听到的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Told the president what he wanted to hear,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:11.01,0:25:12.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说我早就知道核弹的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that I knew about the bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.66,0:25:14.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你告诉我的可不止这些  罗杰\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You told me more than that, Roger.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.68,0:25:16.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你告诉我了珊瑚蛇小组的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You told me about the Coral Snake team.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:16.62,0:25:18.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你告诉我核弹在诺顿机场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You told me that the bomb was at Norton Airfield,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:19.28,0:25:22.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而我们很快就证实了这一信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}information that we corroborated very quickly.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.37,0:25:24.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道你在说什么  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know what you're talking about, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.46,0:25:26.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,普莱斯考特先生  把剩下的录像放完\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Prescott, play the rest of the tape.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.00,0:25:29.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有剩下的录像了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There is no rest of the tape.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:30.77,0:25:32.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么  -这就是全部了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What? - That's all I have.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.14,0:25:36.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不可能  我在那个房间里还待了十分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That can't be. I was in that room for another ten minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.82,0:25:39.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是行动中心传过来的全部视频  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is all that was transmitted by the OC, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.94,0:25:41.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们是要求的全部录像\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We did ask for everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.47,0:25:44.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那肯定哪里出错了  或是有人蓄意破坏\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There must be some kind of a mistake, or deliberate sabotage.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.88,0:25:46.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,斯坦顿先生说得比你们刚刚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Stanton had a whole lot more to say
Dialogue: 0,0:25:46.61,0:25:48.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在录像上看到的可多多了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}than what you just see on that tape.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:48.90,0:25:51.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  西蒙斯探员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, couldn't Agent Simmons
Dialogue: 0,0:25:51.33,0:25:53.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不能证明您刚刚跟我们说的话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}verify what you've been telling us?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.78,0:25:57.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不行  我让他出去了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. I sent him out of the room.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.78,0:25:59.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但事实仍在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But the fact remains
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.88,0:26:03.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是罗杰·斯坦顿告诉我珊瑚蛇小组的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that Roger Stanton told me about the Coral Snake team.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:03.56,0:26:05.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也是他告诉了我核弹的位置\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He told me about the location of the bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.87,0:26:07.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不然我们怎么得到这个情报的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where else could that information have come from?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:08.06,0:26:11.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们有很多情报机构  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have many intelligence agencies, Mr. President,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:11.48,0:26:14.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,上千位探员在全球各地搜集情报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}thousands of agents combing the planet.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.05,0:26:15.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,情报可能是从任何地方来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It could've come from anywhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.67,0:26:17.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只知道不是从我身上问来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just know it didn't come from me.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:17.52,0:26:19.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道这是谎言  告诉他们  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's a lie and you know it. Tell them, Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:25.32,0:26:27.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只知道总统跟我说的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I only know what the president told me.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.96,0:26:31.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我当时没在房间里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wasn't in the room.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.29,0:26:36.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,斯坦顿先生  再次感谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Stanton, thank you again.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:36.08,0:26:39.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,根据法律你会按帕尔默总统的命令继续被羁押\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Legally you will remain in custody as President Palmer has ordered
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.07,0:26:40.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,直到这件事结束\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}until this matter is resolved.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.82,0:26:41.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我明白\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:43.15,0:26:46.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  如果你还有其他证据想要出示的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, if you have any evidence you'd like to present,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.60,0:26:48.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请现在就出示\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}please do so now.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.26,0:26:50.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,目前我们听到的证词\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The testimony that's been presented here so far
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.88,0:26:53.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都是不准确和不完整的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is inaccurate and incomplete.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:54.08,0:26:56.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,罗杰·斯坦顿直接参与了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roger Stanton is directly responsible
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.27,0:26:58.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在美国国土上放置核弹的阴谋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}for placing a nuclear weapon on US soil.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.14,0:27:02.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我有证据  但你们没有给我足够的时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have evidence that proves it, but you've given me no time.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.40,0:27:07.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的行为可能看起来有些极端\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}While my behavior may have been extreme,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:07.95,0:27:11.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我只是在对今天的极端事件作出回应\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was just responding to the extremity of today's events.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.79,0:27:14.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不要弄错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Make no mistake.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.70,0:27:17.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我们对他国动用了军事力量\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If we unleash our military power on nations
Dialogue: 0,0:27:17.78,0:27:19.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,之后却发现他们是无辜的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that later prove innocent,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:19.25,0:27:20.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那将成为历史上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it will rank as one of
Dialogue: 0,0:27:20.29,0:27:22.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最无耻的偷袭行动之一\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the most despicable sneak attacks in history.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.49,0:27:26.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,中东将永远不可能再有和平\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Any chance for peace in the Middle East will vanish forever.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.14,0:27:29.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,即使这样做在未来会导致美国人牺牲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Even if it costs American lives in the future,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.49,0:27:34.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们还是必须推迟袭击  直到证据确凿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we must delay the attack until we are certain of our ground.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.34,0:27:35.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,打扰一下  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Excuse me, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.53,0:27:37.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我刚刚收到了反恐组分局局长\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just received an urgent message
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.03,0:27:39.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,莱恩·查普尔的紧急消息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}from CTU division chief Ryan Chappelle.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.37,0:27:42.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克·鲍尔声称他持有一份证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Apparently Jack Bauer has evidence
Dialogue: 0,0:27:42.02,0:27:46.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能证明塞浦路斯录音是伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}he claims will prove the Cyprus audio was forged.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:47.30,0:27:49.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托  各位  拜托  安静一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please, everyone, just please, settle down.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:50.41,0:27:53.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反恐组正在检查这份证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The evidence is being reviewed at CTU right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.09,0:27:54.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,查普尔先生说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Chappelle says that
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.13,0:27:56.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,几分钟之后应该就能分析完成\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the analysis shall be completed within the next few minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.64,0:27:59.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鉴于这份证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Considering the potential impact
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.57,0:28:02.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对当前议程可能的影响\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that this evidence will have on these proceedings,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:02.84,0:28:04.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得我们必须等待\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think it's incumbent upon us to wait.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.51,0:28:10.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  我现在正看着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I'm looking at it right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.98,0:28:13.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们也无法恢复\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, well we can't configure it, either.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.62,0:28:15.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  你试过用缺省模式运行吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. Did you try running it through the default mode?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.36,0:28:16.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,试过了  音频文件被损毁了  米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes. The audio files are gone, Michelle.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.96,0:28:19.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,上面只有重复的字符  没别的了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're just some markers that repeat. That's all.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.74,0:28:21.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好  谢谢  杰森  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- All right. Thanks, Jason. - All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.86,0:28:24.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他也没有发现\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He didn't find anything, either.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:27.07,0:28:28.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们有什么发现\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, what have you got?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.45,0:28:31.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,芯片的损坏程度比我们预期的要严重\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The chip was more compromised than we thought.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.22,0:28:33.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们恢复音频文件了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you have the audio file?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.47,0:28:36.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔恢复了一些数据  我们正在跟进\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle was able to recover some information we're following up on.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.90,0:28:37.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,重复的代码片段\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Reapeating code fragments,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:37.90,0:28:39.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,或许能让我们找出代码的编写者是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}may tell us who programmed the information.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.23,0:28:42.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有没有找到音频文件  我只需要知道这个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did you find the audio file or not? That's all I need to know.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:44.48,0:28:45.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有  没找到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, we didn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:48.27,0:28:50.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以鲍尔浪费了我们的时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So Bauer wasted our time.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:10.85,0:29:11.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:24.51,0:29:25.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:28.86,0:29:30.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate, are you all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.80,0:29:36.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天发生的一切\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Everything that's happened today,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:36.69,0:29:38.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在正在发生的一切\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}everything that's still happening...
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.32,0:29:42.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我止不住想这都是我的错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I keep thinking it's all my fault.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.44,0:29:44.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come here.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:45.93,0:29:49.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果没有你  我们绝不可能及时找到核弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We would never have found the bomb in time if it wasn't for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:49.83,0:29:52.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但核弹的幕后主使是我妹妹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But my sister was the one behind the bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:52.10,0:29:53.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她帮助了那些极端分子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She helped those fanatics.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:53.48,0:29:56.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  但你跟你妹妹不一样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes. But you're not your sister.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.94,0:30:00.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我应该在事态恶化之前就看出端倪的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I should've seen something was wrong before it got this bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:01.90,0:30:04.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她的所作所为可能会触发一场战争\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because of what she did, it could start a war.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.24,0:30:08.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我原本可以阻止的  我原本可以阻止的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I could've stopped it. I could've stopped it.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:08.34,0:30:10.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  凯特  你不能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, Kate, you couldn't have.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.10,0:30:14.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这世上总有一些事情不是我们能控制的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There are things in this world that are just out of our control.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.57,0:30:16.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有时候我们喜欢怪到自己头上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sometimes we're like to blame ourselves for them
Dialogue: 0,0:30:16.55,0:30:18.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来让自己心里好过一点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so that we can try and make sense out of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.26,0:30:24.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come here.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:32.05,0:30:33.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你无能为力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There was nothing you could have done.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:51.91,0:30:54.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  喂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry. Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:54.23,0:30:55.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  我是托尼  米歇尔也在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, it's Tony and Michelle.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:55.85,0:30:56.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,失陪一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:57.85,0:30:59.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你们恢复音频文件了吗  -没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You got the audio file? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.64,0:31:00.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么叫没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you mean? No?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:01.38,0:31:03.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们是说芯片上没有音频文件吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you telling me that there's no audio file on that chip?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:04.15,0:31:06.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,即使有  也在芯片被破坏的时候一起损坏了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If there were, they were destroyed when the chip was damaged.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:06.76,0:31:09.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  查普尔正在联系总统  你也要接通\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, Chappelle's phoning the president. He wants you on the call.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:09.20,0:31:10.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他当然想了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I bet he does.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:11.29,0:31:14.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有  米歇尔恢复的部分数据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Also, some of the information Michelle was able to recover
Dialogue: 0,0:31:14.47,0:31:15.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可能值得调查一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}may be worth looking into.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.64,0:31:17.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么数据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What kind of information?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.00,0:31:19.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有几串数据流末尾处有相同的代码片段\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Identical code fragments in the tailing of several data streams.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.98,0:31:21.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在说什么  什么代码片段\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you talking about? What kind of fragments?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:21.29,0:31:24.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-有什么功能  -没有功能  这就是重点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What are the fragments for? - Nothing. That's the point.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:24.33,0:31:25.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是垃圾代码\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's junk code.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:25.04,0:31:26.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,程序员和黑客有时候会在代码里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Programmers and hackers sometimes embed it
Dialogue: 0,0:31:26.98,0:31:29.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嵌入这些片段  作为他们的个人标志\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}into their programs as a marker, a signature.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:29.82,0:31:32.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔通过这段代码查到了一个黑客\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle was able to trace the sequence back to a hacker
Dialogue: 0,0:31:32.20,0:31:33.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,叫亚历克斯·休伊特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}named Alex Hewitt.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:33.74,0:31:35.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他在联调局有档案\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's got a file with the FBI.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.78,0:31:37.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们是说  你们觉得这就是伪造了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you telling me you think this is the technician
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.86,0:31:39.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,塞浦路斯音频的程序员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that created the Cyprus audio file?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:39.65,0:31:40.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.13,0:31:42.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,查普尔不让我们继续追查跟芯片有关的线索\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Chapelle's not gonna let us follow up any more leads on the chip,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:42.42,0:31:44.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以你得自己去找这家伙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so you're gonna have to talk to this guy on your own.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:44.36,0:31:46.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行  他现在的地址是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fine. What's his last known address?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:46.34,0:31:49.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,北好莱坞月桂谷大道210号\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}210 Laurel Canyon Boulevard, North Hollywood.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:51.27,0:31:53.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,知道了  我等下再打给你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, I got it. I'll get back to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:53.35,0:31:54.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:58.03,0:32:00.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-抱歉  我得走了  -去哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'm sorry. I've gotta go. - Where?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:00.43,0:32:01.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们从芯片上找到了些线索\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We got something off the chip,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:01.55,0:32:03.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是我们期望的  但也是条线索\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}not what we're looking for, but it's a lead.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:03.64,0:32:05.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得去跟进一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I have to follow it up.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:06.67,0:32:08.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你如果准备好离开了  会有警官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As soon as you're ready to leave here, one of the officers
Dialogue: 0,0:32:08.62,0:32:11.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,带你回反恐组  去见你父亲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}will take you back to CTU so you can be with your father.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:13.44,0:32:14.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:20.29,0:32:21.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ok.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:23.47,0:32:25.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-杰克  -什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Jack? - Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:29.82,0:32:31.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,小心点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Be careful.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.07,0:32:35.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢  我会的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thanks. I will be.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:44.03,0:32:46.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,自从帕尔默总统叫停突袭后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The airborne squadrons have been in a holding pattern
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.17,0:32:48.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,战斗机编队就一直在保持盘旋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}ever since President Palmer called off the attack.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:48.81,0:32:50.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们刚刚加了油\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They just refueled.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:50.77,0:32:52.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我们想继续行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If we want to resume the operation,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.44,0:32:55.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,必须现在就得出结论\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we need to come to a conclusion now.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.64,0:32:57.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再等几分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A few more minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:57.51,0:33:00.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,事关和平与战争  普莱斯考特先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is the difference between peace and war, Mr. Prescott.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.09,0:33:02.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这也是过去几个小时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's also a pattern
Dialogue: 0,0:33:02.17,0:33:04.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一直在重复发生的情景\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that's been recurring over the last few hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:05.54,0:33:08.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一旦鲍尔先生打电话来情况就会不同了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Everything will change once Mr. Bauer calls.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:08.97,0:33:10.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总是没进展\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It just never quite happens.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:16.48,0:33:17.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么事  -反恐组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yes, what is it? - CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.12,0:33:23.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克·鲍尔和莱恩·查普尔打电话来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack Bauer and Ryan Chappelle are on the line.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:25.50,0:33:26.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是帕尔默总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is President Palmer.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:26.59,0:33:28.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  我是莱恩·查普尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, this is Ryan Chappelle.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.74,0:33:31.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你好  莱恩  -杰克·鲍尔也在线\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Hello, Ryan. - I have Jack Bauer on the line as well.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:31.44,0:33:32.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他会向您汇报最新情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He'll give you an update.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:33.96,0:33:35.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  我找到了芯片\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, I found the chip.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:35.39,0:33:37.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但很不幸  芯片严重损坏了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But unfortunately, it's been very badly damaged.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.94,0:33:41.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,芯片目前的状况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is it in good enough shape to prove
Dialogue: 0,0:33:41.41,0:33:43.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能够证明塞浦路斯录音是伪造的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that the Cyprus recording was forged?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:43.02,0:33:44.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先生  以芯片目前的状况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, in its present condition,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:44.03,0:33:46.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,恐怕不能证明什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm afraid it doesn't prove much of anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:46.47,0:33:48.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-能修复吗  -不能  先生  我很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Can it be repaired? - No, sir. I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:48.41,0:33:50.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我们已经在追踪一条线索了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But we have been following up a lead.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:50.41,0:33:51.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大约一个小时前\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}About an hour ago,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:51.17,0:33:53.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想要拿到这个芯片的人抓住并拷打了我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was captured and tortured by men who wanted the chip.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:53.33,0:33:55.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们是为一个叫彼得·金斯利的人做事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They worked for a man named Peter Kingsley.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:55.43,0:33:57.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我相信他是核弹幕后策划集团的一员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I believe he's part of the group that was behind the bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:58.16,0:33:59.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得他们操纵了今天一整天发生的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think they've been manipulating today's events
Dialogue: 0,0:33:59.87,0:34:01.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是为了挑起一场战争  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to start this war, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:01.55,0:34:02.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:02.63,0:34:05.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为了提升他们在里海的石油生意的价值\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}To improve the value of their oil contracts in the Caspian Sea
Dialogue: 0,0:34:05.54,0:34:07.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,并且垄断从中东输出的石油\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and to control the oil coming out of the Middle East.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:10.12,0:34:12.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我需要确凿的证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I need something concrete. I need evidence.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:12.35,0:34:13.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  我明白\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, I understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:13.68,0:34:15.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我目前正在调查一处住所\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right now I'm checking up on an address of a man
Dialogue: 0,0:34:15.58,0:34:18.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们认为住户帮金斯利伪造了塞浦路斯录音\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}who we believe engineered the Cyprus recording for Kingsley.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:18.54,0:34:20.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  先生  但我们现在就只有这么多\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry, sir, but it's the best we've got.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:22.37,0:34:23.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就你看到的一切\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Everything you've seen,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:24.44,0:34:28.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你百分之百确信塞浦路斯录音是伪造的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}are you absolutely convinced that the Cyprus recording was forged?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:28.30,0:34:29.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  先生  百分之百确信\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir, absolutely.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:33.26,0:34:35.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  杰克  谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, Jack. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:41.79,0:34:44.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我期望看到的证据还没有出现\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The evidence I was hoping for is not yet available,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:45.08,0:34:47.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我相信不久之后就会有的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I believe it will be in the near future.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:47.48,0:34:51.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-多久之后  总统先生  -我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- When, Mr. President? - I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:51.85,0:34:55.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,与此同时  要想发动突袭所剩的时间不多了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Meanwhile, the window for a surprise attack is rapidly closing.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:57.85,0:34:59.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,该投票了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's time to vote.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:59.81,0:35:04.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,副总统先生  请给我一分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Vice President, if you could indulge me for one minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:05.08,0:35:05.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:09.24,0:35:12.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鲍尔的话只是你的幻想  是海市蜃楼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This Bauer thing is an illusion, a mirage.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:12.50,0:35:15.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你每次接近它  它就跑得更远\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Every time you get near it, it moves further away.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:15.48,0:35:20.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为你自己  也为国家着想  下令袭击吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For your sake, for the country's, authorize the attack.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:21.06,0:35:23.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这一切就都会烟消云散\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All this will just go away.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:23.96,0:35:25.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但很多人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And a lot of people,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:26.03,0:35:28.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,美国人和外国人  都会无辜死去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Americans and non-Americans, will die for no reason.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:28.78,0:35:30.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这我们可说不准  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We don't know that, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:34.92,0:35:36.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,投票吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's get on with the vote.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:38.86,0:35:42.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,内阁成员们  你们已经看到了证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Members of the cabinet, you've been presented with the evidence.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:43.91,0:35:45.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们也知道事关重大\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what's at stake.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:45.96,0:35:47.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们当中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Those of you who believe
Dialogue: 0,0:35:47.68,0:35:50.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,认为总统可以继续胜任的  投"赞成"\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the president is able to continue in office, vote yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:51.94,0:35:55.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,认为他不能继续胜任的  投"反对"\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Those of you who believe he isn't, vote no.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:56.80,0:35:58.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,诺维克先生会进行口头计票\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Novick will conduct a voice poll.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.08,0:36:01.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,票数会实时显示在屏幕上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The numbers will be reflected up on the screen.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:01.86,0:36:02.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,诺维克先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Novick?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:04.85,0:36:07.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,交通部长女士  您的选择是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ms. Secretary of Transportation, how do you vote?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.06,0:36:09.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,赞成\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:14.64,0:36:16.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,财政部长先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Secretary of Treasury?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:17.76,0:36:18.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:34.60,0:36:35.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,赞成\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:41.95,0:36:43.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-阿尔梅达  -托尼  我是杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Almeida. - Tony, it's Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:43.44,0:36:45.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我离休伊特的住所还有大约半个街区\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm about half a block from Hewitt's loft.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:46.16,0:36:48.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,联调局把他的档案传过来了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Has the FBI sent over his file yet?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:48.51,0:36:50.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们刚拿到  -有什么我需要知道的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yeah, we just got it. - What do I need to know?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:50.76,0:36:53.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,国务院在加州被攻击后就招募了他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The State Department recruited him right after the Cal attack.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.27,0:36:55.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他升级了他们整个监控项目\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He revamped their entire technical surveillance program.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:56.14,0:36:58.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,后来他就被发现在操纵\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then he got caught manipulating intelligence and files
Dialogue: 0,0:36:58.21,0:36:59.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他没有权限的情报和文件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that he didn't have clearance for.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:00.03,0:37:01.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拘押期间企图自杀\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tried to kill himself in custody,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.25,0:37:03.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在艾尔卡斯托的精神病监区待了一年\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}spent a year in psychiatric prison in El Casto,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:03.30,0:37:05.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去年九月被释放\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}before being released last September.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:05.33,0:37:08.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-和金斯利没有关联  -没有找到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- No connection to Kingsley? - No, not that we can find.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.04,0:37:12.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  我一找到休伊特就打给你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. As soon as I get Hewitt, I'll get back to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:12.69,0:37:13.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有  托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, and Tony,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:14.11,0:37:15.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,知道总统那边是怎么回事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}any word on what's happening with the president?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:15.75,0:37:18.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-还不知道  -好  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- No, not yet. - OK, thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:21.54,0:37:23.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,国防部长先生  您的选择是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Secretary of Defense, how do you vote?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:25.08,0:37:28.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,赞成  我认为总统应该继续任职\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, I believe the president should stay in office.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:36.96,0:37:39.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,农业部长先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Secretary of Agriculture.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:47.03,0:37:47.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:56.10,0:37:57.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,内务部长先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Secretary of the Interior.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:06.33,0:38:07.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:11.36,0:38:16.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,国务卿先生  目前是七票赞成七票反对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Secretary of State, the vote is seven for and seven against.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.24,0:38:20.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-您的票将决定结果  -我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yours is the deciding vote. - I'm aware of that.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:26.51,0:38:27.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我从未见过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've never met a man
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.76,0:38:33.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,比您更让我尊敬的人  总统先生  没有过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that I respected more than you, Mr. President. Never.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:39.74,0:38:45.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但事关上万美国人的性命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But we are talking about tens of thousands of American lives.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:50.04,0:38:51.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只能投反对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm compelled to vote no.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.87,0:39:20.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  您看到结果了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, can you see the results?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:22.53,0:39:24.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,您在四天内可以向国会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You will have an opportunity to appeal this
Dialogue: 0,0:39:24.88,0:39:26.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当面提起申诉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}in four days in front of Congress.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:27.67,0:39:30.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,与此同时  我必须要求您退出\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In the meantime, I must ask you to remove yourself
Dialogue: 0,0:39:30.84,0:39:32.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所有决策环节\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}from the decision-making process.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:35.56,0:39:37.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请带总统去拘留室\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please take the president to a holding room.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:50.61,0:39:52.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请跟我们来  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Will you please come with us, Mr. President?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:16.29,0:40:21.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  我不是律师\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, I'm not a lawyer, sir,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:21.43,0:40:25.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但就我所知  整个流程都遵从了宪法\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but as far as I can tell, the Constitution's been followed.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:25.36,0:40:27.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我别无选择  只能请您跟我们来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've got no choice but to ask you to come with us.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:30.34,0:40:31.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:57.72,0:42:00.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我谨庄严宣誓  我将忠诚履行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I do solemnly swear that I will faithfully execute
Dialogue: 0,0:42:00.38,0:42:02.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,合众国总统职务\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the office of the President of the United States
Dialogue: 0,0:42:03.09,0:42:05.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亦将竭尽所能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and will, to the best of my ability,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:05.27,0:42:06.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,恪守  维护  捍卫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}preserve, protect and defend
Dialogue: 0,0:42:06.91,0:42:09.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,合众国宪法\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the Constitution of the United States,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:09.67,0:42:10.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,上帝为证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so help me God.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:22.03,0:43:23.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚历克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alex?

