[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,1,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.65,0:00:10.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(197.4,200.557)}{\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs25\b1\bord0\shad0\c&H78BDE7&\fad(0,808)}24小时\N\N{\fs15}第二季  第二十集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.11,0:00:13.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(189.6,121.6,193.8,105.6,0,356)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad3\3c&H2F2F2F&\4c&H336D99&}{\fs10}{\t(0,356,\fs20)\fn方正正中黑简体}前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.20,0:00:16.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  杰克·鲍尔打电话说有新线索\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, Jack Bauer just called with some new information.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.03,0:00:14.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(316.2,223.753)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.08,0:00:14.12,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(295.8,210.153)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.12,0:00:14.16,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(274.8,197.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.16,0:00:14.20,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(254.4,184.8)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.20,0:00:14.24,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(234.6,170.953)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.24,0:00:14.28,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(214.8,158.953)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.28,0:00:14.32,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(193.8,145.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.32,0:00:14.37,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(174,132.553)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.37,0:00:14.41,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(152.4,120.553)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.41,0:00:16.33,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(133.2,106.953)\fad(0,355)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.88,0:00:20.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,声称他有证据证明塞浦路斯的录音是伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He claimed he has evidence the Cyprus recording is counterfeit.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.13,0:00:21.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要取消攻击\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm calling off the attack.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.23,0:00:23.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,停止再重启这次军事行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stopping and restarting military action
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.47,0:00:26.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可能会牺牲数万美国士兵的性命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}could cost tens of thousands of American lives.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.23,0:00:29.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,比起与三个无辜的国家开战\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}An acceptable risk if the alternative
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.46,0:00:32.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是可接受的风险\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is waging war against three innocent countries.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.95,0:00:36.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道第二十五号修正案第四条内容吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you know about Section 4 of the 25th Amendment?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.20,0:00:38.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当内阁大多数成员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If the majority of his cabinet
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.18,0:00:36.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(315,224.553)}麦克·诺维克
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.22,0:00:36.26,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(293.4,213.353)}麦克·诺维克
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.26,0:00:36.30,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(271.8,200.553)}麦克·诺维克
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.30,0:00:36.35,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(252,187.753)}麦克·诺维克
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.35,0:00:36.39,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(231,176.553)}麦克·诺维克
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.39,0:00:36.43,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(209.4,162.953)}麦克·诺维克
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.43,0:00:36.47,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(186.6,151.753)}麦克·诺维克
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.47,0:00:36.51,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(166.2,138.953)}麦克·诺维克
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.51,0:00:36.55,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(145.2,127.753)}麦克·诺维克
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.55,0:00:38.43,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(123.6,114.953)\fad(0,308)}麦克·诺维克
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.13,0:00:40.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,认为总统无法履行义务时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}feels he's unfit to fulfil his duties,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.21,0:00:42.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可以罢免总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the president could be removed from office.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:42.33,0:00:45.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而副总统将成为代理总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And the vice president becomes acting president.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.19,0:00:46.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,依我看来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As far as I'm concerned,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.39,0:00:49.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,普莱斯考特才是叛国的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it's Prescott who should be charged with treason.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.01,0:00:51.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我就怕你会这么说  林恩  -麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I was afraid you'd say that, Lynne. - Mike!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.05,0:00:55.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,除非收到我的命令  否则绝对不能让她离开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Until you hear from me, do not let her out.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.28,0:00:56.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我能把他们引开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think I can lure them away from here.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.99,0:00:56.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(62.4,230.153)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.03,0:00:56.08,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(82.2,217.353)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.08,0:00:56.12,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(102.6,204.553)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.12,0:00:56.16,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(121.8,193.353)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.16,0:00:56.20,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(142.8,178.953)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.20,0:00:56.24,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(162,167.753)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.24,0:00:56.28,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(181.2,154.953)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.28,0:00:56.32,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(200.4,142.153)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.32,0:00:56.37,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(219.6,129.353)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.37,0:00:58.20,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(240,114.953)\fad(0,308)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.63,0:00:58.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你和凯特把芯片带去反恐组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You and Kate get the chip over to CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.91,0:01:00.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,摩尔公园和葡萄园那里同我碰面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Meet me at Moorpark and Vineland.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.58,0:01:01.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要是我十五分钟内没到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If I'm not there in 15 minutes,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.96,0:01:03.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,带着芯片去找托尼·阿尔梅达\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}get it to Tony Almeida.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.45,0:01:05.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,优素福  你后面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yusuf! Behind you!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.54,0:01:07.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,臭中东佬\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's a damn towel head.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.24,0:01:09.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,住手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stop it!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.31,0:01:12.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼  我们拿到证明\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony, we got the evidence that proves
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.21,0:01:11.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(303.6,33.353)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.26,0:01:11.30,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(285.6,41.353)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.30,0:01:11.34,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(266.4,51.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.34,0:01:11.38,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(247.2,61.353)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.38,0:01:11.42,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(226.8,70.153)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.42,0:01:11.46,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(208.2,78.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.46,0:01:11.51,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(188.4,86.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.51,0:01:11.55,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(169.2,98.153)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.55,0:01:11.59,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(150,106.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.59,0:01:13.47,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(129.6,115.753)\fad(0,313)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.85,0:01:14.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,塞浦路斯录音是伪造的证据了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the Cyprus audio was forged.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.19,0:01:17.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是一个存有原始录音的芯片\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a CPB memory chip containing the original source recordings.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.60,0:01:20.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在我拿到芯片前不要杀他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do not kill him until he talks.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.59,0:01:24.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  我需要那个芯片\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, I need the chip.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.10,0:01:26.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那个不卖  这是我的最终回复\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's not for sale. My answer's final.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.04,0:01:29.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,罗尼干完活之后  你会给我另一个回答的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When Ronnie's finished, you'll give me another.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:30.84,0:01:31.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,芯片  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The chip, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.19,0:01:36.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他死了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.66,0:01:42.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs15\t(696,6577,\fs16)\c&H4BAAAD&\fad(1697,1183)\pos(187.2,191.79)}以下故事情节发生在凌晨3点到凌晨4点之间
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.79,0:01:44.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\frz22.15\move(141,44,137.4,60,22,1816)}{\fn方正兰亭粗黑_GBK\fax-0.6\fs25\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H74767D&}急救中心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.20,0:01:47.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果您刚收看我们的特别报道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you are just joining us special broadcast,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:47.20,0:01:50.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,白宫已经证实四小时之前\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the White House has confirmed the blast in the Mojave Desert
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.91,0:01:55.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,太平洋标准时间夜晚10点59分\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that occurred four hours ago at 10.59pm PST
Dialogue: 0,0:01:55.48,0:01:58.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,莫哈维沙漠发生的爆炸确实是核爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}was in fact a nuclear explosion.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:03.15,0:02:06.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们这就给你缝合  然后你就可以出院了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll stitch you up and get you out of here and on your way.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:07.83,0:02:10.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你在这做什么  -找肾上腺素\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What are you doing here? - Looking for epinephrine.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.85,0:02:12.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是处置室  我有患者\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is a treatment room. I have a patient...
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.44,0:02:19.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-肾上腺素在哪  -储藏室\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where's the epinephrine? - Storage room.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.60,0:02:20.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:24.09,0:02:25.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,离手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Clear.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:29.36,0:02:30.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没变化\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.83,0:02:32.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再来  把能量调高\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go again. Increase the joules.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.32,0:02:35.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不许死在我手上  你个混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You are not gonna die on me, you son of a bitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:37.42,0:02:39.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金斯利的电话  你跟他通话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's Kingsley. You talk to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.82,0:02:42.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么事  -让斯塔克接电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yes? - Let me talk to Stark.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.84,0:02:44.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他现在有点忙  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's a little busy right now, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:44.70,0:02:47.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-鲍尔给你们芯片了吗  -不  还没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Did Bauer give you the chip? - No, sir. Not yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:47.87,0:02:49.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么这么慢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's taking so long?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:49.60,0:02:51.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一切尽在掌控  金斯利先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's under control, Mr. Kingsley.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:51.78,0:02:53.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的话里有话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What am I hearing in your voice?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:54.32,0:02:55.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,回答我  雷蒙德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Answer me, Raymond.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.07,0:02:59.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,斯塔克对鲍尔下手太狠了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stark pushed Bauer too far.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.17,0:03:00.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他心跳停止了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's flat-lining.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.62,0:03:04.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不管他出了什么差错  他最好补救过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Whatever he broke, he'd better fix.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.33,0:03:07.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果罗尼搞不定  你就来动手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And if Ronnie can't handle it, do it yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.94,0:03:08.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alright.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.12,0:03:18.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-肾上腺素呢  -医生拿着呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where's the epinephrine? - The doctor's got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:18.90,0:03:20.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要是不把他救过来  你就死定了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you don't revive this man, you're dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.38,0:03:24.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你的人把他弄到轮床上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need your men to put him on the gurney.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.56,0:03:25.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把他抬到轮床上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Put him up on the gurney.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.96,0:03:28.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给他打最大剂量\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Give him as much as he can take.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.79,0:03:39.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快点  快点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's go! Let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.86,0:03:51.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你等什么呢  打\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you waiting for? Do it!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.03,0:03:57.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把电极板给他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Give him the paddles.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.28,0:04:03.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,离手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Clear.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.50,0:04:08.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还是室颤\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Still in v-fib.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.67,0:04:11.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再电一次\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hit him again!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.71,0:04:12.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,离手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Clear.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.46,0:04:21.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-太晚了  没用的  -再电一次\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It's too late. It's not gonna work. - Hit him again!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.65,0:04:26.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,离手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Clear.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:30.54,0:04:32.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,加油  加油\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.50,0:04:34.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有窦性心律了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got a sinus rhythm.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.12,0:04:39.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要一套急救包和一袋生理盐水\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need a Baxter set and a bag of normal saline.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.59,0:04:52.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金斯利说什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What did Kingsley say?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:54.34,0:04:56.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他说我升职了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He said I just got promoted.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.44,0:05:07.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.11,0:05:12.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你以为死就能解脱了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You thought death would save you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.63,0:05:16.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不亲手杀了你  你是不许死的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're not gonna die until I kill you myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.84,0:05:18.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,芯片在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, where is that chip?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.53,0:05:26.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们一小时内就召集内阁了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll be convening the Cabinet within the hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.99,0:05:29.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统知道情况吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Does the president have any idea what's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:30.02,0:05:32.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-应该不知道  -保持住\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I don't think so. - Let's keep it that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.93,0:05:34.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把他蒙在鼓里很重要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's critical he doesn't find out.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.95,0:05:36.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没那么容易的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's not going to be that easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.07,0:05:40.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,林恩·柯瑞斯基要提醒他  被我制止了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lynne Kresge was about to warn him, but I was able to intervene.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.81,0:05:41.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她现在在哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where is she now?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.88,0:05:44.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我把她关起来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I had to put her under guard.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:47.27,0:05:49.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道这很难  对我们都很难\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know it's difficult. It's difficult for all of us.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.21,0:05:53.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是希望我们做的是对的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just hope we're doing the right thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.28,0:05:55.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.90,0:05:57.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你以为我想在这种情况下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you think these are the circumstances
Dialogue: 0,0:05:57.72,0:06:00.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就任总统吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}under which I wish to assume the presidency?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:00.36,0:06:01.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你了解我的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know me better than that.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.71,0:06:06.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个国家被核武器袭击了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This country was attacked, with a nuclear weapon.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.85,0:06:10.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而总统却不做出军事回应\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And the president will not commit to a military response.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.28,0:06:12.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我希望你不是在动摇自己\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I hope you're not wavering yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.66,0:06:17.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  我没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. I'm not.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:17.74,0:06:18.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.73,0:06:21.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的任务就是确保\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, your responsibility is to make sure
Dialogue: 0,0:06:21.94,0:06:24.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,内阁投票罢免他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that the cabinet votes to remove him from office.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:24.63,0:06:27.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的责任是确保内阁投票\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have a responsibility to make sure the vote takes place,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.46,0:06:30.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而不是操纵结果\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}not to manipulate the outcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.59,0:06:31.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这话说得太不恰当了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Poor choice of words.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.75,0:06:34.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是我还是那个意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But my point is the same.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.60,0:06:37.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你做的是对的  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're doing the right thing, Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.06,0:06:38.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,历史会承认这一点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}History will recognise that.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.53,0:06:51.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克·鲍尔那边有消息吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Anything from Jack Bauer?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.04,0:06:54.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还没听说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not that I've heard.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.19,0:06:57.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mike...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:58.39,0:07:02.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道你认为拖延军事回应是错误的决策\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know you think delaying a military response is the wrong call.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.07,0:07:05.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为你只凭借单一的信息来源\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Only because you're relying on a single source.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.74,0:07:08.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克·鲍尔说他有证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack Bauer says he has evidence
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.52,0:07:10.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,证明我们是被操纵参与这场战争的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that we're being manipulated into this war.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.35,0:07:13.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得给他机会提交证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have to give him the opportunity to produce the proof.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.35,0:07:18.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果有什么我能说的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If there were anything I could say
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.64,0:07:20.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能让你改变主意的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to make you change your mind...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.67,0:07:22.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,并没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There isn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.91,0:07:26.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, Mike,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.44,0:07:28.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道这个决定并不受人支持\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know this is an unpopular decision.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.27,0:07:32.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就算连你也不认可\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And even though you don't agree either,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:32.15,0:07:34.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你对我的支持也还是很重要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}your standing by me means a great deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.62,0:07:42.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让林恩来我办公室  她在起草我的发言\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Send Lynne into my office. She's drafting my statement.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.06,0:07:43.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我找找看吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll see if I can find her.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.57,0:07:45.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.04,0:07:47.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她觉得不太舒服\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She wasn't feeling well.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.22,0:07:49.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我上次问的时候她休息了几分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She took a few minutes' downtime last I heard.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.44,0:07:52.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没关系  让她休息吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's fine. Let her rest.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.78,0:07:55.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我叫珍妮来做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll go over it with Jenny.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.93,0:08:05.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请打开门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please open this door.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.73,0:08:06.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不论你是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Whoever you are,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:06.45,0:08:09.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们都在共谋反对美国总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you are conspiring against the president of the United States of America
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.72,0:08:11.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道那意味着什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you have any idea what that means?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.53,0:08:13.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.17,0:08:18.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不知道后果有多严重  求你把门打开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You have no idea what's at stake here. Please open the door!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.62,0:08:54.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把他钱包拿走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, get his wallet.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.56,0:09:03.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-多少钱  -有几百块\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How much? - He's got a couple of hundred.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.52,0:09:04.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.08,0:09:06.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.00,0:09:08.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这是什么  -好了  快走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What's this? - Let's get out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.52,0:09:11.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-快点啊  -拿上  走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Come on! - Just take it. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.68,0:09:14.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-上车  我来开车  -芯片\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Get in the car. I'm driving. - The chip...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:15.73,0:09:20.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等  你多拿了一样东西  那是我的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wait. Wait! You took something from him. It's mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.50,0:09:22.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你跟他混在一起干什么  他很有钱吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why are you doing with him anyway? You think he's got money?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.86,0:09:25.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在这个国家比这些混蛋更差劲的就是你这种人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Only thing worse than these bastards in a country is people like you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:25.78,0:09:27.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  不  不是这样的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. No, no, it's not like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:27.96,0:09:30.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只需要你手上的那个塑料壳\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just need that plastic case you took from him.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:30.25,0:09:31.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这个吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- This? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:33.49,0:09:35.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就是这个  这是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This? What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.76,0:09:39.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,上面有重要的信息  对你来说没有什么价值\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's got information on it. It's not worth anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.25,0:09:42.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托  求求你了  给我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please, come on. Give it to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:42.32,0:09:43.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你怎么报答我们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What'll you give us for it?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.40,0:09:46.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我付你钱  我有钱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll pay you. I've got money.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:46.97,0:09:49.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-多少钱  -我身上没有  在家里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How much? - It's not here, it's at my house.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.70,0:09:51.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,算了吧  马库斯  我们走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Forget it, Marcus. Let's just go.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.72,0:09:55.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你家在哪儿  -汉考克公园\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where's your house? - Hancock Park.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.68,0:09:57.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,离这儿不远\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's not that far from here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.86,0:10:01.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.96,0:10:03.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.87,0:10:06.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行  就这么做  去你家取钱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, let's do it. Let's go get your money.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.33,0:10:11.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-但首先我得帮他了断  -别  别\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- First I'm gonna put him out of his misery. - No. No!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:14.18,0:10:16.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这就是和我们国家纠缠的后果  -求你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- This is for messin' with our country. - Oh, please!
Dialogue: 0,0:10:18.39,0:10:21.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-别  -马库斯  拜托  走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- No! - Marcus, man, come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.70,0:10:28.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了  我们走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.44,0:11:34.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  线路繁忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry. All circuits are busy.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:34.45,0:11:36.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请稍后再拨\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please try your call again later.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.73,0:11:43.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再推一点肾上腺素\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Give him more epinephrine.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:43.08,0:11:45.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,推的已经够多了  过量了他的心脏负担不起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's already had too much. You don't want to strain his heart.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.11,0:11:47.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他很强壮  能承受的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's strong. He can handle it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:58.18,0:12:00.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,准备一支贝洛格来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now prepare a syringe of beroglide.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.61,0:12:02.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,贝洛格来  那会损害他的肺的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Beroglide? It'll collapse his lungs...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.92,0:12:04.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,照我说的做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.37,0:12:20.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个贝洛格来  非常神奇\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, this beroglide stuff, it's amazing.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.31,0:12:22.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,它会让你的膈肌瘫痪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This will paralyse your diaphragm,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:23.36,0:12:25.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后你会逐渐窒息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and you'll slowly suffocate.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.51,0:12:27.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你会感到自己在慢慢淹死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You'll feel like you're drowning,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:28.59,0:12:30.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,直到你告诉我芯片在哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}until you tell me where the chip is.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:31.31,0:12:34.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我已经告诉你了  我不知道芯片在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I already told you, I don't know where the chip is.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.64,0:12:37.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金斯利想跟你通话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kingsley wants to talk to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.00,0:12:39.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我一会儿就回来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll be right back.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.09,0:12:51.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-帮我松一下绳子  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Help me loosen the rope. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.71,0:12:55.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-帮我把绳子解开  -我不能那样做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Help me undo the rope. - I can't do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.22,0:12:58.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他在打电话  其他人都离得很远\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's on the phone. The other guys are far enough away.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.90,0:13:00.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们只会以为你在给我注射药物\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They'll just think you're working on me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.70,0:13:03.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托了  机会仅此一次\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please. This is the only chance we've got.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.03,0:13:05.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他会杀了我的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He'll kill me.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.31,0:13:07.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他迟早都会杀掉你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's gonna kill you anyway.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:08.09,0:13:11.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些人打算在今晚谋杀几百万人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}These men were willing to kill millions of people earlier tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.99,0:13:14.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是你今晚活着走出这里的唯一希望\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I am the only chance you've got to get out of here alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.52,0:13:17.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们时间不多了  快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We don't have any time. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.01,0:13:19.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:23.66,0:13:27.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,从底下穿过去  快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Feed it through the bottom. Hurry.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.84,0:13:30.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hurry.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.42,0:13:34.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's coming.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.43,0:13:37.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.76,0:13:39.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得先把静脉通道关闭\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I had to disconnect his IV first.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.41,0:13:41.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-把贝洛格来拿来  -好的长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Get the beroglide. - Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.75,0:13:48.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先从两个单位开始\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Start him off with 2cc.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.49,0:14:21.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-查普尔先生  -嗨  米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Mr. Chappelle. - Hi, Michelle
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.17,0:14:22.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼在办公室吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is Tony in his office?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.41,0:14:24.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他去技术部门了  一会儿就回来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He went to IT. He'll be a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.39,0:14:26.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,通讯设备现在在监测中了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's the status on the phones?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.20,0:14:27.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,监测网络在全城都已经布好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Grid's down in most of the city.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.96,0:14:29.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,无线网络呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How about wireless?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.22,0:14:30.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,手机也已经差不多了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Cell service is pretty much out too.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.13,0:14:32.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你现在使用卫星通讯吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Are you using Satcom? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.30,0:14:35.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,保留高级别官员使用卫星通讯的权利\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Save Satcom for your highest priorities.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.52,0:14:37.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在我们还要和其他机构共享\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're sharing it with half a dozen other agencies.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.19,0:14:39.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ok.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.82,0:14:40.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:41.79,0:14:42.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嘿  莱恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Ryan.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.83,0:14:44.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,干得漂亮\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good work.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:46.55,0:14:47.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,关于什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good work on what?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.51,0:14:51.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道鲍尔想改变我们对塞浦路斯录音的立场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know Bauer's trying to change our position on the Cyprus audio.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.73,0:14:54.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,事实上并不是这样的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's not exactly true.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.32,0:14:56.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都没事了  你没必要解释\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Whatever. You don't have to explain.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:56.18,0:14:59.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很高兴你没有本末倒置\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm just glad you're not letting the tail wag the dog.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:00.00,0:15:00.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,莱恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ryan,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:02.54,0:15:04.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克说的可能没错  他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack may not be wrong about this. He's...
Dialogue: 0,0:15:04.86,0:15:07.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等  我不想听这些\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wait. Wait. I don't wanna hear that.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.29,0:15:12.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们下周三就要对中东发起进攻了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're about to bomb the Middle East into next Wednesday.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:12.64,0:15:15.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们应该处理好情报维护这次行动顺利进行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're supposed to be processing intel to support that operation.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.80,0:15:17.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我已经派出了手下的大部分人手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've got most of my people on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.13,0:15:19.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我希望你能派出所有人手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want all your people on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.04,0:15:23.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,莱恩  难道你不觉得我们应该\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ryan, don't you think we need to eliminate doubt
Dialogue: 0,0:15:23.11,0:15:24.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再考虑一下这份录音的真实性吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}about the authenticity of this recording?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:25.35,0:15:28.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的部门已经证实了这份录音的真实性\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your department has already authenticated that recording.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:29.97,0:15:32.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别把我当成坏人  托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't make me the bad guy here, Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.77,0:15:36.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治·梅森也许推荐了你来领导反恐局\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George Mason may have recommended you to direct CTU,
Dialogue: 0,0:15:36.89,0:15:38.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但你要在这个位置上坐稳的话还需要我的支持\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but you'll need my blessing to stay on.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:38.99,0:15:40.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我相信这觉得是你想要的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I assume that's what you want.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.34,0:15:45.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只想在这样的情况下做出正确的决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What I want is to do what's right in this situation.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:46.80,0:15:49.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,正确的决定就是服从命令\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's right is to follow the chain of command.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.33,0:15:52.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让所有人待命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Put everyone on domestic response.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.94,0:16:57.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.15,0:16:59.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-该死  -冷静下来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- God damn it! - Calm down.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.95,0:17:16.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你什么意思  联系不到他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you mean, you can't get through to him?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.79,0:17:22.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,无法联系  我现在就要和他通话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Unreachable? I want him now.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.72,0:17:23.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我再试一次  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll try again, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.06,0:17:33.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚伦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Aaron?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.63,0:17:39.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-叫我吗  总统先生  -关上门  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yes, Mr President? - Close the door, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.42,0:17:52.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你为多少届政府服务过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How many administrations have you worked for?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.85,0:17:54.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,从里根第二届任期开始\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I came in on Reagan's second term.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.98,0:18:00.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在过去的半小时内\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I haven't been able to establish contact
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.99,0:18:03.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我都联系不到我的副总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}with my vice president in the last half-hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.72,0:18:05.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你觉得这是为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you make of that?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.64,0:18:10.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道怎么回答这个问题  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wouldn't know how to respond to that, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.06,0:18:15.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我刚刚不顾所有人的反对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just pulled our bombers out of the air,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:15.24,0:18:17.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,下令轰炸机返回\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}against everyone's recommendations.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.29,0:18:20.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在我的副总统联系不上了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now my vice president suddenly is unreachable.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.00,0:18:23.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是否可以得出某些结论\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Should I draw any conclusions?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.12,0:18:26.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,长官  我没有资格在这方面给您意见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, I'm not qualified to give an opinion...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:26.59,0:18:29.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚伦  过去的二十年你都在做这件事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Aaron, you've been doing this nearly 20 years.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.49,0:18:32.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道这个系统是如何运转的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know how the system works.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:33.65,0:18:36.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,普莱斯考特是否有在背着我筹谋什么事情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is Prescott planning something behind my back?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.82,0:18:42.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在和总统密谈  控制好三号位置\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm going 20-10, please cover position three.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:42.55,0:18:43.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,收到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roger that.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.55,0:18:48.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说句公道话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For what it's worth,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.83,0:18:51.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,您今天做的决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think the choices you've made today
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.78,0:18:53.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是正确的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}have been the right ones.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.00,0:18:54.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我问的不是这个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's not what I asked.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.76,0:18:57.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我相信在某一个政府中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sure there are always those inside the administration
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.85,0:19:00.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总会有人认为做事不宜拖延\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}who feel that delay is a weakness.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:00.90,0:19:03.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果有足够的人都这么觉得  那么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If enough individuals share this point of view, then...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:03.08,0:19:04.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亚伦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Aaron.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.78,0:19:06.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,普莱斯考特会报复我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is Prescott coming after me?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.80,0:19:09.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不确定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.04,0:19:13.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但您的直觉应该很准  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But you have good instincts, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.27,0:19:15.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我是你的话  我会听从直觉的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'd listen to 'em if I were you.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:18.27,0:19:20.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-谢谢你  亚伦  -没事  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Thank you, Aaron. - Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.51,0:19:43.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,马克斯很不高兴\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Max is very unhappy.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:44.68,0:19:47.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,马克斯可以不高兴  我们都有权不高兴\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Max can be unhappy. We're all entitled to our feelings.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:47.73,0:19:51.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,彼得  别用你平时的那些哲学观察唬我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Peter, spare me your usual metaphysical observations.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.64,0:19:54.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们的整个计划都决定于\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Our entire project depends on military action
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.69,0:19:57.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统刚刚取消的军事行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the president just suspended.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.18,0:20:00.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-只是暂时的  -但这就已经足够了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- For now. - Now is all that matters.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.60,0:20:02.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你这话可太有哲理了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now you're being metaphysical.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.56,0:20:04.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,彼得\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Peter...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.48,0:20:06.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,帕尔默将难以承受\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Palmer won't be able to stand
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.61,0:20:09.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来自内部官员的政治施压\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the political pressure from his own administration,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.77,0:20:11.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,更不要说人民群众给的压力了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}let alone the will of the people.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.41,0:20:13.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他别无选择\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's not gonna have any choice
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.64,0:20:15.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,必须对核武器作出回应\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but to respond to the nuclear weapon.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.29,0:20:18.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你这是在假设鲍尔这家伙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're assuming of course that this man Bauer
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.46,0:20:22.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还没有向他的人证明\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}hasn't already delivered proof to his people
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.74,0:20:25.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,塞浦路斯录音是伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that the Cyprus audio was false.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.52,0:20:29.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鲍尔不是问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bauer won't be a problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.40,0:20:43.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我芯片在哪里  我就放过你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell me where the chip is, I'll make it stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.79,0:20:44.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你会弄死他的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You gonna kill him.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.99,0:20:47.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  但他会宁愿死掉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. But he'll wish he'd stayed dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:49.05,0:20:51.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我跟你玩够了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm all done playing games with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:52.61,0:20:55.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快把我想知道的告诉我  告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now tell me what I wanna know! Tell me!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:55.06,0:20:57.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他们在楼上会听到  -那就闭嘴  关门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- They'll hear you upstairs. - Then shut up and close the door!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.32,0:21:02.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,用双倍剂量加满注射器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fill the syringe and double the dosage.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.40,0:21:22.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会告诉你芯片在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll tell you where the chip is.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.53,0:21:26.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.16,0:21:30.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再说一遍\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Again.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.57,0:21:32.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,它在...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's in...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.55,0:21:35.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,它在一个...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's in a p...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:36.38,0:21:37.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What did you say?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:38.56,0:21:40.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们要把芯片送去...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're taking the chip to...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.00,0:21:42.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们要把它送去哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're taking it where?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.17,0:22:17.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stay down.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.80,0:22:24.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他还能活多久\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How much longer does he got before he's dead?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:24.64,0:22:26.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只有15分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As long as 15 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.00,0:22:49.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你告诉我电话那头是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You tell me who was on the other end of that phone,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.77,0:22:50.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我就让你早点解脱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and I'll make it quick.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.85,0:23:01.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,彼得·金斯利\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Peter... Kingsley.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:36.47,0:23:39.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-您找我吗  总统先生  -对  请关门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You wanted to see me, sir? - Yes. Close the door, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.75,0:23:42.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请坐  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Have a seat, Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.25,0:23:47.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在过去的一个小时里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've been feeling a little
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.01,0:23:49.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,感觉与我的人失去了联系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}disconnected from my people in the last hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:50.13,0:23:52.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  我一直在努力应付\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, I've been trying to manage
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.39,0:23:54.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,参谋长们和国土安全部\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the Joint chiefs and Homeland Security.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.49,0:23:55.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但您要是想让我更...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But if you want me closer...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.44,0:23:58.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是说你  麦克  是在华盛顿的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not you, Mike. Back in Washington.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.85,0:24:00.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-谁  -普莱斯考特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Who? - Prescott.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.42,0:24:03.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我认为他在回避我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think he's avoiding me.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.36,0:24:09.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们在过去的18小时里经历了那么多\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}With what we've gone through in the last 18 hours,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:10.84,0:24:13.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我相信他只是有点迷失方向\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm certain he's just being pulled in ten different directions.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.91,0:24:16.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们曾处于  在某种意义上仍正处于\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We were, and in some ways still are,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:16.24,0:24:17.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,战争的边缘\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}on the brink of war.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:18.66,0:24:20.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是总司令\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm the commander in chief.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:20.36,0:24:23.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当我下命令时  只有一个方向\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When I call, there's only one direction.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:24.31,0:24:27.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当然  我马上打电话给他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Absolutely. I'll get him on the phone right away.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.63,0:24:29.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去吧  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do that. Oh, and Mike?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.60,0:24:33.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,珍妮拟的这份声明不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This statement that Jenny made a pass on, it's not working.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:34.23,0:24:37.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-有什么问题吗  -内容没有更新\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What's the problem? - The facts aren't updated.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:37.28,0:24:39.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她没有获悉所有情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I don't think Jenny's been apprised of everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.85,0:24:41.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想让林恩检查一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want Lynne to go over it.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.68,0:24:44.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给我吧  我会转交给她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why don't you give it to me? I'll get it to her.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.39,0:24:46.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:21.55,0:25:22.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是普莱斯考特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Prescott.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.58,0:25:24.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是麦克·诺维克  你方便说话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's Mike Novick. Can you talk?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.76,0:25:29.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你还要继续吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you going forward or not?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.37,0:25:31.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当然  一切不变\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course. Nothing's changed.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.38,0:25:33.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你越快开始越好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The sooner you can execute, the better.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:33.89,0:25:35.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们在尽快推进\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Going as fast as we can here.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:35.73,0:25:40.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大卫·帕尔默不愚蠢  他知道有不对劲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}David Palmer is not a stupid man. He knows something is going on.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:40.52,0:25:43.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,过不了多久他就会弄清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It won't take him long to figure out what it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.78,0:25:44.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他怎么知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How does he know?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.90,0:25:47.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,首先  你没有给他回电\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For one thing, you haven't returned his calls.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:47.44,0:25:50.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我现在就打给他  -好主意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'll call him now. - I think that's a good idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.77,0:25:52.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,麦克  我就指望你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mike, I'm counting on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.03,0:25:55.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要在我准备好之前  让他别闲着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You gotta keep him busy until I can get everyone together.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.76,0:26:00.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-还要多久  -半个小时  最多45分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How much longer? - A half-hour. 45 minutes tops.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:00.14,0:26:03.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,越快越好  我现在孤立无援\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The sooner the better. I'm all alone out here on this.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.09,0:26:06.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他开始找林恩·柯瑞斯基了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He started to ask about Lynne Kresge.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:06.03,0:26:07.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我撑不了多久了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't keep up the act much longer.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.61,0:26:08.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不用撑很久\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You won't have to.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.58,0:26:10.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,坚持住  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just hold your mud, Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:27.51,0:26:28.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反恐组  我是戴斯勒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}CTU. Dessler.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.31,0:26:30.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔  我是杰克  我要跟托尼说话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle, it's Jack. I need to speak to Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:30.63,0:26:32.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰...杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}J... Jack?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:32.98,0:26:36.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔  我不知道你是否能听见我说话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle, I don't know if you can still hear me.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:37.29,0:26:38.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,芯片在凯特和优素福手上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate and Yusuf have got the chip.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.69,0:26:41.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要去葡萄园街和穆尔帕克街的见面地点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm going to meeting at Vineland and Moorpark,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.55,0:26:44.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看看他们是否还在那里等我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}just in case they're still waiting for me there.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.75,0:26:46.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.20,0:26:49.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Damn it.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:49.86,0:26:50.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.21,0:27:03.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.50,0:27:05.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么事  -刚刚杰克打电话来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What's up? - Call just came through I think it's Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:06.03,0:27:07.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他说了什么  -我们失去了信号\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What'd he say? - We lost the signal.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:07.93,0:27:08.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有打回给他吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You try him back?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.92,0:27:10.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我给那个号码加上了自动追踪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. I put an auto-trace on the number
Dialogue: 0,0:27:10.29,0:27:11.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,以防他再打来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}in case he gets through again.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.64,0:27:13.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去看看调度站是否记录在日志里了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right, go to, see if Dispatch picked it up in the log.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:13.67,0:27:15.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,查查是手机还是固定电话打来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Find out if it was a cell or land line.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:17.71,0:27:18.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.72,0:27:22.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's that all about?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.81,0:27:26.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克·鲍尔刚刚联系了我们  但信号断了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack Bauer just tried to contact us. We lost connection.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:26.96,0:27:27.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我告诉过你  我不想\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I told you I don't want
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.77,0:27:30.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让你和你的手下因为他分心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bauer distracting you or your resources.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.24,0:27:32.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不管他在干什么  都与我们无关\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Whatever he's doing out there is irrelevant.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.78,0:27:34.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道这对不对  莱恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not so sure it is right, Ryan.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.62,0:27:37.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克说他有证据证明塞浦路斯录音是伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack says he's got proof that the Cyprus audio was fabricated.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.49,0:27:38.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他会在一个小时之内把证据带来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Says he's bringing it here within the hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:39.22,0:27:41.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他要是有证据  就让他拿出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If he's got proof, let him produce it.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.81,0:27:44.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我要你专注重要的事  托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I want you to keep your eye on the ball, Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.30,0:27:56.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,吉姆  你一直是我取消这次袭击的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jim, we both know you've been one of the most outspoken opponents
Dialogue: 0,0:27:56.99,0:27:59.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,主要反对者之一\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to my decision to call off this attack.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:59.03,0:28:00.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我可能有过的任何批判\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Any criticisms I may have
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.51,0:28:03.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都是关起门来表达的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}had have been expressed behind closed doors,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.01,0:28:04.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不受公众监督\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}out of reach of any public scrutiny.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:05.43,0:28:06.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,自从这一切发生  我们一直没有机会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know we haven't had a chance
Dialogue: 0,0:28:06.95,0:28:08.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一对一交流\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to talk one-on-one since all this began.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.92,0:28:13.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以你要是有什么事要告诉我  就说吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So if you have something to tell me, go ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.96,0:28:17.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's nothing, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.64,0:28:20.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的大门一直为你敞开  吉姆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My door is always open, Jim.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:21.17,0:28:22.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要是有什么事要说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you have something to say,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.52,0:28:25.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我希望你先向我报告\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I would expect you to bring it to me first.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.84,0:28:27.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当然  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:27.93,0:28:29.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你的回电\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thanks for getting back to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.97,0:28:35.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还是不信任他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I still don't trust him.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:37.19,0:28:38.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想让我怎么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you want me to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.24,0:28:41.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-抱歉打断您了  总统先生  -什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Sorry to interrupt, sir. - What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:42.41,0:28:45.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,林恩·柯瑞斯基受伤了  她从楼上摔下来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lynne Kresge is injured. She fell down some stairs.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.84,0:28:48.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:48.02,0:28:50.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们不确定  她当时可能在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're not sure. It appears she may have been
Dialogue: 0,0:28:50.06,0:28:52.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,逃离楼上一间着火的房间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}running from a fire in an upstairs room.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:52.28,0:28:55.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-她还好吗  -现场医生说她情况危急\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Is she OK? - On-site physician says she's critical.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:55.05,0:28:56.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,带我过去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Show me where.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.38,0:29:29.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在调度站发现了什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, what'd you find out from Dispatch?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.25,0:29:31.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克是用手机打给我的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, Jack called me from a cell.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.19,0:29:36.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来自恩西诺和影视城之间的某个地方\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Came from somewhere between Encino and Studio City.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.47,0:29:39.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以两个小时之前\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, so he was in an urgent care centre
Dialogue: 0,0:29:39.49,0:29:41.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他在这里的一个急救中心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}right around here about two hours ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:41.71,0:29:44.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他要是来反恐组  可能会走101道或5道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If he was coming to CTU he probably would take the 101 or the 5.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:44.97,0:29:46.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想让我启动卫星吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you want me to pull up the satellite?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.42,0:29:48.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  那将会引起查普尔的警惕\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, that would just raise a red flag with Chappelle,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:49.04,0:29:50.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是我现在最不想要的情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}which is the last thing I need right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.43,0:29:51.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,用警用频道怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about police channels?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.94,0:29:53.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他就算联系不上我们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean even if he couldn't contact us,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:53.42,0:29:54.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可能会找自己人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}maybe he tried someone local.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:55.86,0:29:58.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能在不被发现的情况下进行监控吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can you monitor those without being detected?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.94,0:30:00.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:02.98,0:30:05.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  专注在市中心区域\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. Focus on the downtown precincts.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.81,0:30:57.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,优素福\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yusuf!
Dialogue: 0,0:30:58.76,0:31:00.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  他们拿走了芯片\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, they took the chip.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:00.63,0:31:02.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在说什么  他们是谁  凯特在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you talking about? Who's "they"? Where's Kate?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:03.08,0:31:06.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们把她带去她家了  在汉考克公园\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They took her to her house. Hancock Park.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:07.53,0:31:09.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她提出用钱换芯片\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She offered to exchange money for the chip.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:10.38,0:31:11.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来  我带你走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, let's get you out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:11.65,0:31:13.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  我活不成了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, I'm not gonna make it.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:14.07,0:31:15.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快去拿芯片  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go and get the chip, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.82,0:31:17.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,优素福  坚持住  坚持住\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yusuf, just hang on. Just hang on.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.39,0:31:21.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,优素福  别这样  优素福  坚持住\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yusuf, come on. Yusuf, hang on!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:23.43,0:31:24.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,优素福\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yusuf!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:36.70,0:31:37.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,优素福  对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yusuf, I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.61,0:31:41.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:59.53,0:32:00.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.02,0:32:03.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大家小声点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Everybody, be cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.77,0:32:09.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你住在这里吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You live here? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.54,0:32:10.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-一个人吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- By yourself? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:11.59,0:32:12.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真壕\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Damn.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:19.43,0:32:20.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没有钥匙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't have my keys.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:21.30,0:32:23.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这真是你家吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Is this really your house? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:25.91,0:32:28.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,花盆下面有后备钥匙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's a spare key under the pot.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:36.41,0:32:38.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快进去  她在骗我们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get inside. She's setting us up, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.05,0:32:39.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快进来  快进来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get in here! Get in here!
Dialogue: 0,0:32:39.18,0:32:40.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,关掉报警器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shut it off.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:40.40,0:32:42.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我说关掉报警器  快关掉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I said, shut it off. Shut it off!
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.88,0:32:44.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,密码是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's the code?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:44.64,0:32:46.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-快关掉  -51224\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Shut it off. - 51224.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.05,0:32:48.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,51224\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}51224.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.91,0:32:55.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,带我们去拿钱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Show us where the money's at.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:03.73,0:33:05.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,医生  她的伤情如何\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Doc, what's her status?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:05.79,0:33:08.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她的神经好像受到了损伤\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She sustained some sort of neurological damage.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:08.58,0:33:10.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在把她送到医院之前  我们不清楚受损程度\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We won't know the extent till we get her to the hospital.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:10.53,0:33:12.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-她能活下来吗  -现在言之尚早\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Will she live? - It's too early to say.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:13.07,0:33:14.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我能和她说话吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can I talk to her?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.01,0:33:16.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  这样可能不好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, that may not be a good idea.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:16.12,0:33:18.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我问医生问题  -可以试试\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I asked the doctor a question. - You can try.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.30,0:33:21.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是她现在处于时醒时昏迷的状态\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But she's slipping in and out of consciousness.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.98,0:33:23.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,林恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lynne.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.96,0:33:24.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,林恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lynne.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:27.36,0:33:28.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,林恩  是我  大卫·帕尔默\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lynne, it's me. David Palmer.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:34.55,0:33:35.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很抱歉你伤成这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm so sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:41.28,0:33:42.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们现在送你去医院\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're getting you to the hospital,
Dialogue: 0,0:33:43.08,0:33:45.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是我要你把事发经过告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I need you to tell me how this happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:46.57,0:33:49.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  她的脑部受到了重击\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, she took a severe blow to the head.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:49.45,0:33:52.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她有脑震荡  说话含糊不清\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She has a concussion and she's not coherent.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:53.25,0:33:56.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-她想说些什么  -他...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- She's trying to say something. - D... D... D...
Dialogue: 0,0:33:56.78,0:33:59.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事  我在这  我在听你说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's OK. I'm here. I'm listening.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:00.69,0:34:01.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想说什么  林恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What is it, Lynne?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:05.00,0:34:06.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:22.50,0:34:23.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事  林恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's all right, Lynne.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:25.94,0:34:27.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,医生会治好你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're going to take good care of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:31.13,0:34:33.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们要送她去医院  -去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- We need to get her to the hospital. - Go.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:50.79,0:34:52.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快点  托尼  快接电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, Tony. Pick up the phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.69,0:34:55.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-抱歉  线路全忙  -该死的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'm sorry. All services are busy. - Damn it!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:14.19,0:35:15.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,夏普尔会发现的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Chappelle's going to find out.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:17.42,0:35:18.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:18.75,0:35:21.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他说过不要浪费时间去找杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He said not to waste time looking for Jack,
Dialogue: 0,0:35:21.39,0:35:24.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但你和米歇尔全心在找他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but that's all you and Michelle are doing.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:24.95,0:35:26.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你为什么不去看看任务情报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why aren't you working on the field intel?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:27.11,0:35:28.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别把我撂在一边  托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't shine me on, Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:28.21,0:35:30.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是想帮你保住你的工作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm just trying to help you keep your job.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:30.98,0:35:33.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是吗  怎么保\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Really? By doing what?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:34.32,0:35:37.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-守口如瓶  -那好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Not saying anything. - OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:37.88,0:35:39.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那就守口如瓶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then don't say anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:41.31,0:35:42.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我有交换条件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want something in return.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:46.40,0:35:47.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么交换条件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And what would that be?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:48.09,0:35:49.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔以前在局里是我下属\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle worked for me at District.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:50.58,0:35:52.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那样工作更顺手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Things worked much better that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:53.18,0:35:55.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她的能力不足以出任我上司\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's not qualified to be my boss.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:56.13,0:35:58.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以今晚这里才搞得一团乱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's why things have been so messed up here tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.61,0:36:00.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:02.04,0:36:05.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想要米歇尔的职位  这才是重点对吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you want Michelle's job. Is that what this is about?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:05.99,0:36:07.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:08.76,0:36:10.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我猜你也想保住你自己的职位吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I assume you wanna keep yours.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.16,0:36:14.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:16.68,0:36:20.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,夏普尔先生  你能过来一会吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Chappelle, could you come over here a second?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:20.39,0:36:21.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有事吗  阿尔梅达\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you need, Almeida?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:22.27,0:36:23.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯莉有事想和你说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Carrie's got something she wants to tell you.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:24.67,0:36:25.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这两份\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, here these two...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:32.45,0:36:33.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么事  凯莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What is it, Carrie?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:39.55,0:36:40.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:42.82,0:36:45.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯莉想敲诈我  逼我给她升职\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Carrie was trying to extort a promotion out of me
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.32,0:36:47.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她才会保证守口如瓶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}by promising to keep her mouth shut.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:47.56,0:36:48.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是这样吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That about right?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:50.15,0:36:51.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,守口如瓶什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mouth shut about what?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:53.68,0:36:56.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他和米歇尔还在想办法找寻杰克·鲍尔的下落\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He and Michelle are still trying to find Jack Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:56.49,0:36:59.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是出于礼貌想提醒托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was trying to give Tony the courtesy of a warning.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:00.85,0:37:02.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我本来打算告诉你的  查普尔先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was gonna tell you, Mr. Chappelle...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:02.25,0:37:04.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,够了  凯莉  回去工作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's enough, Carrie. Get back to work.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:05.89,0:37:06.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:09.50,0:37:12.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不是说得很清楚吗  托尼  别再管鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thought I made myself clear, Tony. We're past Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.21,0:37:15.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  长官  你不管  我管\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, sir. You are. I'm not.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:15.67,0:37:17.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我现在还是反恐组的主管\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm still director of CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:17.03,0:37:18.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在合理分配资源\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm allocating reasonable resources
Dialogue: 0,0:37:18.81,0:37:20.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,确保我们能掌握所有的事实\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to ensure we have all the facts.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:20.22,0:37:22.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你不放心我自己做决定的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you're not comfortable with me making my own decisions,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.45,0:37:24.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我建议你立刻解除我的职务\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I suggest you relieve me of my duties right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:28.40,0:37:29.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没这必要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That won't be necessary.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.89,0:37:33.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-谢谢你  长官  -别谢我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Thank you, sir. - Don't thank me.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:33.77,0:37:36.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是我现在没有能取代你的人而已\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just don't have anyone to take your place right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:38.73,0:37:41.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不喜欢下属违抗命令\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't like insubordination.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:55.02,0:37:55.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:58.72,0:37:59.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,动作最好快点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You better hurry up.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:01.16,0:38:02.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,钱在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's there.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:05.60,0:38:06.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是什么东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What the hell is this?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:06.87,0:38:08.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那里至少应该有两万欧元\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That should be at least 20,000 euros.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.81,0:38:10.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-欧元  -欧洲货币\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Euros? - It's European money.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.98,0:38:13.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你觉得我看着像欧洲人吗  现金在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I look European to you? Where's the cash?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:13.27,0:38:15.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这就是现金  和美元一样好用\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That is cash. It's as good as dollars.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:15.41,0:38:17.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要的是能用的现金  明白吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We want cash money. You understand me?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:18.13,0:38:19.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,马库斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Marcus?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:26.36,0:38:27.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们觉得这是真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You think this is real?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.68,0:38:29.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是  有钱人喜欢把假货锁起来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, they keep the fake ones locked up
Dialogue: 0,0:38:30.35,0:38:31.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,1500块\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}1500.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:32.18,0:38:34.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-就这点吗  -就这点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- That's it? - That's it.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:35.64,0:38:36.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now what do we do?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.58,0:38:49.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,全都拿走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, just take it all.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.06,0:38:50.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只要留下芯片就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just gimme the chip.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:52.57,0:38:53.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她看到我们的脸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She knows what we look like.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:54.82,0:38:56.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也知道我们的名字\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She knows our names too.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:57.42,0:38:58.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们说好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We had a deal.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:58.71,0:39:00.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他说得对  我们不能把你留在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's right. We can't just leave you here.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:00.74,0:39:03.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,全部拿走  我不会告诉任何人的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Take everything! I won't tell anyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:03.49,0:39:05.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不会报警的  我保证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I won't tell the police, I promise.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:05.53,0:39:07.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快把芯片给我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just give me the chip!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:08.67,0:39:10.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,马库斯  算了  我们拿东西走人吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Marcus, don't do this. Let's take the stuff and go.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:10.64,0:39:12.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们一离开这里  她马上就会报警\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The second we walk out of here, she's calling the cops.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:13.40,0:39:14.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不能再坐牢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't get locked up again man.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:14.94,0:39:15.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别开枪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:33.28,0:39:34.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不要  -快给我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- No! - Gimme that!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:40.70,0:39:41.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  你没事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate, are you all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:42.01,0:39:43.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事  他们把芯片拿走了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. They've got the chip.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:45.06,0:39:46.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,走廊里有几间房\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How many rooms at the end of the hall?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:46.40,0:39:48.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,两间  是卧室和浴室\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Two. That's bedroom and bathroom.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.59,0:39:49.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,蹲着别起来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stay down.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:06.46,0:40:07.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只想要芯片\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All I want is the chip!
Dialogue: 0,0:40:24.14,0:40:25.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我叫杰克·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My name is Jack Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:26.39,0:40:27.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是联邦探员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm a federal agent.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:28.08,0:40:30.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只想要芯片  然后会放你走的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All I want is the chip, and then I'll let you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:34.12,0:40:36.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你开枪打了我朋友  你指望我相信你吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You shot my friend, man. You expect me to believe you?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:37.38,0:40:39.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在你也没得选\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right now you don't have a choice.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:41.26,0:40:43.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你走进来  我就把芯片毁了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You come in here and I'm gonna smash this thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:43.15,0:40:44.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会踩烂它\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll put it right under my foot.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:50.97,0:40:52.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要找杰克·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're looking for Jack Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:52.38,0:40:53.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,上次和他联系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Last time we heard from him,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:53.57,0:40:56.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他的电话信号是在恩西诺和影视城交界处\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}he was on a cellphone between Encino and Studio City.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:57.05,0:40:58.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要尽快找到他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We need to find him as soon as possible.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:59.30,0:41:01.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要大家把这列为首要目标\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need everyone to make this priority one.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:15.22,0:41:17.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,各位  我们可以开始了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ladies and gentlemen, we can begin.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:20.97,0:41:23.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想感谢大家这么快就赶来开会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'd like to thank you for assembling at such short notice.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:24.37,0:41:27.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想你们都想知道我为什么叫你们来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sure you're all wondering why I've asked you here,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:28.31,0:41:29.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我为什么让你们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}why I've asked you
Dialogue: 0,0:41:29.27,0:41:31.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,保密这次开会的消息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to keep the news of this meeting to yourselves.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:32.12,0:41:34.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  副总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Excuse me, Mr. Vice President.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:34.06,0:41:35.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是我们难道不该等总统来再开始吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But shouldn't we wait for the president?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:35.89,0:41:37.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,帕尔默总统晚一点会出席的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}President Palmer will be joining us later.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:39.56,0:41:41.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不是很明白你的意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not sure I understand you.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:42.28,0:41:44.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,此次会议的第一部分将不对外公开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The first part of this meeting will be a closed session.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:45.51,0:41:47.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对总统也不公开吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Closed to the president?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:47.41,0:41:50.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我恐怕那就是此次会议的重点  亚历克斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm afraid that's the point of the meeting, Alex.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:55.54,0:41:58.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对你们一些人来说  这将令你们很诧异\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}To some of you this will come as a surprise.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:58.91,0:42:00.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但对大多数人来说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For most of you, though,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:00.09,0:42:02.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我希望会让你们如释重负\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I hope it comes as a relief.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:03.49,0:42:05.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是我真诚地相信\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But it is my sincere belief that,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:05.45,0:42:08.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,基于他对于今日事件的回应\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}based on his response to today's events,
Dialogue: 0,0:42:09.11,0:42:12.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大卫·帕尔默不适合\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}David Palmer is unfit to
Dialogue: 0,0:42:12.10,0:42:14.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,继续出任美国总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}continue as President of the United States.

