[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,1,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.69,0:00:10.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(197.4,200.557)}{\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs25\b1\bord0\shad0\c&H78BDE7&\fad(0,808)}24小时\N\N{\fs15}第二季  第七集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.49,0:00:13.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(189.6,121.6,193.8,105.6,0,356)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad3\3c&H2F2F2F&\4c&H336D99&}{\fs10}{\t(0,356,\fs20)\fn方正正中黑简体}前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.45,0:00:17.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-雷扎的父母来了  -雷扎在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Reza's parents are here. - Where is Reza?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.70,0:00:15.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs9\c&H449BA1&\pos(169.2,160.553)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.74,0:00:15.79,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(155.4,139.753)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.79,0:00:15.83,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(139.8,118.953)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.83,0:00:17.87,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(127.8,98.153)\fad(0,268)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.64,0:00:19.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有几个政府的人来找他谈话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Men from the government are here talking to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.73,0:00:22.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是谁把钱转到赛伊德·阿里的账户的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who wired that money into Syed Ali's accounts?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.61,0:00:25.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鲍勃·华纳  玛丽的父亲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bob Warner, Marie's father.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.29,0:00:27.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请跟我走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come with me, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.51,0:00:31.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你和他们说了什么  -实话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What did you tell them? - The truth.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.13,0:00:33.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有我的授权你是怎么进来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How did you get in here without my authorization?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.18,0:00:33.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H437B80&\pos(153,231.753)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.23,0:00:33.27,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(167.4,218.153)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.27,0:00:33.31,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(182.4,202.953)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.31,0:00:33.35,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(196.2,187.2)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.35,0:00:33.39,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(210.6,170.953)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.39,0:00:33.43,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(224.4,157.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.43,0:00:33.47,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(238.2,141.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.47,0:00:35.47,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs17\c&H449BA1&\pos(253.8,126.153)\fad(0,267)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.85,0:00:36.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我需要和你谈谈  -你不再是我妻子了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I need to talk to you. - You're not my wife anymore.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:36.93,0:00:39.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不是我们的事  -那是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It's not about us. - Then what?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:39.72,0:00:43.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的政府内部有人联合起来反对你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There are members of your own administration allying against you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.64,0:00:45.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这就是我今天来的原因\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's why I came here today.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:45.75,0:00:47.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅根  我要带你离开这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Megan, I need to get you out of here,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.61,0:00:46.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(214.8,212.553)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.65,0:00:46.70,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(189,192.553)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.70,0:00:46.74,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(164.4,170.953)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.74,0:00:46.78,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs15\c&H449BA1&\pos(139.8,149.353)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.78,0:00:48.82,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(116.4,130.153)\fad(0,220)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.67,0:00:49.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我希望你安全\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}because I want you to be safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.11,0:00:50.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好的  -来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Okay. - Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.67,0:00:53.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们给科室都打了电话  都没有看到你女儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I called all the departments. Your daughter is not with them.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.24,0:00:54.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那她还会在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then where the hell is she?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.74,0:00:56.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把她交给我  金\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Give her to me, Kim.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.69,0:01:01.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们得赶快离开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We need to get out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.92,0:01:06.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-去拿他的车钥匙  -尼娜杀了你妻子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Get his car keys. - Nina killed your wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.11,0:01:07.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不希望你靠近她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't want you anywhere near her.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.04,0:01:07.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(231.6,209.353)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.09,0:01:07.13,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(209.4,191.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.13,0:01:07.17,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(188.4,171.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.17,0:01:07.21,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs15\c&H449BA1&\pos(167.4,153.353)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.21,0:01:07.25,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(146.4,133.353)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.25,0:01:09.30,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(126,114.153)\fad(0,313)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.44,0:01:10.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的目的和你一样  阻止炸弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My goal is the same as yours, to stop this bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:10.59,0:01:12.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在维萨利亚的那个人是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who is the man at Visalia?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.53,0:01:14.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在维萨利亚的是马穆·法海因\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The man at Visalia is Mamud Faheen.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.67,0:01:16.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只有他知道炸弹在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's the only one who knows where the bomb is.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.10,0:01:18.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,小队在维萨利亚集结\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The team's assembled in Visalia.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.62,0:01:20.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会有实战和外勤部队\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll have tactical and field units.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.58,0:01:23.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-杰克  -没事的  艾德  放松点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Jack-- - It's all right, Ed. It's all right. Just take it easy.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:28.73,0:01:34.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs15\t(696,6577,\fs16)\c&H4BAAAD&\fad(1697,1183)\pos(187.2,191.79)}以下故事情节发生在下午2点到3点之间
Dialogue: 0,0:01:36.57,0:01:39.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\fad(359,0)\pos(193.8,224.553)}洛杉矶沃登空军基地
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.18,0:02:01.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,下来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Move.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.16,0:02:09.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克给米勒下药好跟我独处  告诉梅森\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack drugged Miller to get me alone. Tell Mason.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.80,0:02:12.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他在车里吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Is he in the van? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:12.80,0:02:14.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他大约二十分钟左右会醒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's going to come to in about 20 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.73,0:02:16.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会有点头疼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He'll have a bit of a headache.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.19,0:02:17.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是授权文件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here's the command authority.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.74,0:02:20.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我欠你人情  道格  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I owe you, Doug. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:20.32,0:02:21.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不客气\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.23,0:02:26.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,上飞机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get in the plane.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.63,0:02:51.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鲍尔特工  我是里克·菲利普斯  联调局\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Agent Bauer. Rick Phillips, F.B.I.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.50,0:02:55.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,哈里斯特工和我会送你们去维萨利亚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Agent Harris and myself will be your transits into Visalia.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.13,0:02:57.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,着陆后我们就是你的后援\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll act as reinforcements once we're on the ground.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:58.91,0:03:00.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把话说开  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So we're clear here, Jack--
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.07,0:03:01.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道你对艾德·米勒做了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know what you did to Ed Miller.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.14,0:03:04.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,里克  是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Rick, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:04.50,0:03:07.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,帮你自己个忙  少管闲事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do yourself a favor. Stay out of this.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.34,0:03:09.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,做你该做的事  送我们到维萨利亚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do your job. Get us to Visalia.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:10.15,0:03:12.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的工作是保证一切顺利\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My job is to make sure this runs smoothly.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:13.13,0:03:14.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就是说要保证她的安全\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That means keeping her safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:17.13,0:03:18.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当我是你的新陪护好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Consider me your new chaperone.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.04,0:03:25.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要两条和反恐组的通话线\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need two lines of communication set up through C.T.U.--
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.55,0:03:27.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一条手机  一条解码器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}one for mobile, one for the translator.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.10,0:03:28.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会有难度\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's gonna be tricky right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.09,0:03:31.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他们的线路还很糟糕  -已经设置好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Cause their phone lines are still sketchy. - It's already done.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.27,0:03:34.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.96,0:03:59.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,干得好  凯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Way to go, Kate.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.13,0:04:02.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你把他父母的心也伤了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You broke his parents' hearts too.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.58,0:04:04.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很抱歉  玛丽  但是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm so sorry, Marie, but I
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.22,0:04:06.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道这些政府人员发现了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}don't know what these government people found.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.00,0:04:09.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,相信我  我希望他们什么都没有发现\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And believe me, I wish they hadn't have found anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:10.11,0:04:13.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不好奇吗  为什么他们又开始问爸爸问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But aren't you curious? Why are they asking Dad questions now?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.28,0:04:16.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为你在我们家里挑起了一场政治迫害\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because you started a witch hunt in our family.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.75,0:04:20.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  玛丽  因为雷扎和一些坏人有联系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, Marie. It's because Reza is connected to some bad people.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.77,0:04:24.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-甚至可能是恐怖分子  -你疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Maybe even terrorists. - You're out of your mind.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.36,0:04:26.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们不能就这么不闻不问  玛丽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're not going to put our heads in the sand, Marie,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:27.12,0:04:28.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不然这可能会伤害到爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}or this could end up hurting Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.30,0:04:30.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们不能让那种事发生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're not gonna let that happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.13,0:04:33.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,跟我来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.79,0:04:36.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你跟他们说了什么  雷扎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What did you tell them, Reza?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.74,0:04:37.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你指控我父亲什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What did you accuse my father of?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.86,0:04:39.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没有指控他任何事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I didn't accuse him of anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.35,0:04:40.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是他的公司  不是我的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's his company, not mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.83,0:04:42.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's that supposed to mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:42.01,0:04:44.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你指控他好为自己脱罪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're pointing your finger at him to cover yourself
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.29,0:04:46.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  -你少管  玛丽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate - Stay out of this, Marie!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.28,0:04:47.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不准和她那样讲话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't talk to her like that.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:47.53,0:04:48.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你听着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, you listen to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.06,0:04:52.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我为你父亲付出的多出你的想象\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have done more for your father than you will ever know,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.25,0:04:55.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然而我从你那里得到的从来只有猜疑和憎恨\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and all I've ever gotten from you is suspicion and resentment.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.48,0:04:57.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我已经受够了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And you know what? I'm sick of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.02,0:04:59.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我并不是把你和恐怖分子联系起来的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, I'm not the one that connected you to a terrorist.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.60,0:05:00.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是吗  那是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No? Then who did?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:00.78,0:05:02.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我可不认识什么恐怖分子  凯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because I don't know any terrorists, Kate!
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.55,0:05:05.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只知道你花钱请人去挖掘我的丑事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All I know is that you paid for someone to dig up dirt on me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.45,0:05:06.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很显然  他办到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, apparently, he did.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.87,0:05:08.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  他没有  因为他唯一发现的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, he didn't, because all he found out
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.48,0:05:10.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是关于鲍勃  不是我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}was stuff about Bob, not me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.59,0:05:13.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以即使谁有罪  也是你的父亲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, if anybody's guilty of anything, it is your father.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:13.30,0:05:15.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你敢把这事情往我父亲身上扯  -住口\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Don't you make this about my father. - Just stop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.39,0:05:18.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你敢  -住口  凯特  你们都住口\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Don't you dare! - Stop, Kate! Both of you, stop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:27.47,0:05:28.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你干的好事  凯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nice work, Kate.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:35.16,0:05:36.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你收到消息了就给我打电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, why don't you just call me when you get that?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.97,0:05:38.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会帮你搞到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll have it for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.12,0:05:40.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-四点会不会太晚  -不  没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Is 4:00 too late? - No, that's good for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:40.23,0:05:43.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-到时联系  -很好  再见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'll talk to you then. - Yeah, good, all right. Bye-bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.72,0:05:49.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这不是幕僚长吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, if it isn't the chief of staff himself.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:49.09,0:05:51.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-麦克  -雪莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Mike. - Sherry.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.38,0:05:55.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你还是一如既往的美丽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You look beautiful, as always.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:56.20,0:05:59.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在这里做什么  大卫请你来的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you doing here? Did David ask you to come here?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.96,0:06:03.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  我自己来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Uh, no. I just showed up on my own.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.53,0:06:07.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,近来还还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So... how have you been?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:07.72,0:06:10.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-还好  麦克  -是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Fine, Mike. Just fine. - Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.43,0:06:14.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  这一年是不太顺\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. Well, you know, it's been a challenging year.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.17,0:06:15.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是那话怎么说的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But what is it they say?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.81,0:06:19.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们  要从自己的错误中学习\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We, uh, learn from our mistakes...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.39,0:06:22.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在不幸中成长\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and grow from our misfortunes.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.68,0:06:25.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些你跟大卫说了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Have you, uh, told that to David?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.35,0:06:26.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:28.08,0:06:30.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他还没有准备好听这些\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't think he's ready to hear that yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:30.18,0:06:31.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,至少不是现在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not now.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.85,0:06:34.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是他正在等你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But he is waiting for you,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.94,0:06:36.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以你进去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so why don't you just go on in?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.56,0:06:39.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等下再见  我确信\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll see you later, I'm sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.41,0:06:43.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,您的  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here you go, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.73,0:06:49.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不要推断  什么都不要说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't speculate, don't say anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.18,0:06:50.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们单纯不知道他在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We simply don't know where he is.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:50.94,0:06:53.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那就是我们的态度  - 好的  我明白\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- That is our position. - Yes, Madam, I understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.50,0:06:55.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-很好  谢谢  -不客气\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- All right, all right, good. Thank you. - You're welcome.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.75,0:07:00.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  我们得谈谈罗恩·维兰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, we have to talk about Ron Wieland.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.65,0:07:04.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他怎么了  还有人知道我们将他扣押了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about him? Does anybody know we have him sequestered?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.01,0:07:06.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有  但是珍妮刚刚接到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, no, but Jenny just got a call
Dialogue: 0,0:07:06.09,0:07:07.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,维兰德团队成员的电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}from Wieland's production crew.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:07.35,0:07:09.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们已经有四个小时没有见过他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They haven't seen him in the last four hours,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:09.36,0:07:10.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,用不了多久他们就会发现\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and pretty soon they're gonna figure out
Dialogue: 0,0:07:10.69,0:07:12.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他最后一个见过的人是你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the last person they did see him with was you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.68,0:07:14.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那么就放个消息出去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then leak a story.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:14.90,0:07:17.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,麦克  很高兴见到你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mike. Good to see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.34,0:07:19.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我尽快赶来了  总统先生  你好  林恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got here as soon as I could, Mr. President. Hi, Lynne.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:19.86,0:07:20.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.91,0:07:25.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我和阿莫斯谈过了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I spoke to Armus.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.10,0:07:27.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他给我介绍了维兰德的情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He brought me up to speed on the Wieland situation.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.48,0:07:28.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我做了些调查\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I did some research.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:29.03,0:07:31.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,发现有行政部门在国家危机的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Found out there is precedent for the executive branch...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:31.68,0:07:36.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,采取行动控制媒体的先例\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}taking action against the press at times of national crisis.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.81,0:07:41.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你刚才说放消息出去  是指什么消息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, when you say leak a story, what kind of a story? What--
Dialogue: 0,0:07:41.08,0:07:43.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让它看起来像维兰德去了波特兰\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Make it appear as though Wieland went to Portland...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.13,0:07:45.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,处理一些私人事务\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}for the rest of the day on a personal matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:45.93,0:07:47.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿莫斯能安排\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Armus can arrange that.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.45,0:07:49.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只是个权宜之计  但是会让我们撑过今天\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a Band-Aid, but it'll get us through the day.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:53.49,0:07:55.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-让阿莫斯处理  -是的  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Talk to Armus. Put it in motion. - Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:01.75,0:08:04.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我进来的时候看到雪莉了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I saw Sherry on my way in.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:04.92,0:08:06.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有什么我需要留意的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Should I attach any significance to that?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:07.00,0:08:10.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-是她自己要来的  -她也是那么说的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It was her decision to come here. - That's what she said.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:11.32,0:08:12.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我想说的是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I have to tell you,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.44,0:08:15.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很惊讶你竟然让她留下了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm surprised you're allowing her to stay.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:16.30,0:08:19.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,特殊时期  麦克  特殊处理\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For the time being, Mike. Just for the time being.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.12,0:08:22.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去指挥中心吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's go to the O.C.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.64,0:08:24.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得让你跟上进度  有太多事情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll bring you up to speed. There's a lot to cover.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.59,0:08:30.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-把那个发给分局  -好的 先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You want to send that on to Division? - Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.58,0:08:35.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-梅森先生  -什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Mr. Mason. - Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.10,0:08:37.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我刚刚和艾德·米勒通完话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just got off the phone with Ed Miller.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.11,0:08:39.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克和尼娜怎么样了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How's it going between Jack and Nina?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.44,0:08:40.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He doesn't know. Jack
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.76,0:08:42.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克迷晕了他  独自上了飞机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}drugged him and got on the plane without him.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:43.94,0:08:45.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请告诉我你在开玩笑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please tell me you're kidding.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.10,0:08:49.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,斯隆现在送艾德回来  你想让我做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sloan's bringing Ed back now. What do you want me to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.04,0:08:51.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们在去维萨利亚的飞机上  我们无能为力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're on a plane to Visalia. There's nothing anybody can do--
Dialogue: 0,0:08:52.42,0:08:53.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,除了希望他复仇的冲动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Except hope that his impulse
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.75,0:08:56.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不要影响他的判断力就行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}for revenge doesn't cloud his judgment.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.20,0:08:58.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"影响他的判断力"  比如给自己人下药\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Cloud his judgment"? You mean like drugging one of our agents?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.83,0:09:01.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我能说什么  他本来就是疯子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What can I say? The guy's a little crazy.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.22,0:09:02.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以我一开始才不希望他来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's why I didn't want him here in the first place.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.79,0:09:05.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是他能拿到结果\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But he gets results,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.18,0:09:08.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们现在需要一个好的结果\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and we need some pretty big results here.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:08.24,0:09:09.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以  随他了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So--
Dialogue: 0,0:09:29.81,0:09:31.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,仅凭雪莉告诉你政府内部\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just because Sherry tells you that
Dialogue: 0,0:09:31.38,0:09:34.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有人阴谋反对你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}there's a conspiracy in the government arraying against you,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:34.11,0:09:35.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,并不代表是真的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that doesn't make it true.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.48,0:09:41.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但如果是真的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But if it is true,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.75,0:09:45.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就会影响到我们处理炸弹的一切行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it will affect every aspect of our response to this bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.02,0:09:48.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雪莉在洛杉矶军队撤离一事上是对的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sherry was right about the military evacuation of Los Angeles.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.17,0:09:50.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是特殊消息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's specific information.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.81,0:09:54.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她还是有不少耳目  但是阴谋论\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She still has well-routed sources. But a conspiracy?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.57,0:09:57.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别忘了她是什么人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't forget where she's coming from.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.44,0:09:59.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她可能有自己的企图  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She may have her own agenda, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.43,0:10:00.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我非常清楚这点  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm well aware of that, Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.08,0:10:04.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她在控制之下  我要找出她的耳目\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's on a tight leash. I want to find her source.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:06.13,0:10:09.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我找出这所谓的阴谋集团\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me look into this so-called cabal against you.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:10.16,0:10:12.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果真的有这种事  我会查清楚的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If there's any substance to it, I'll uncover it.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.77,0:10:15.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在  国家需要你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right now, the country needs your attention
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.05,0:10:16.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,集中注意力在洛杉矶的情况上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}on the situation in L.A.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.48,0:10:25.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-从斯坦顿开始  -斯坦顿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Start with Stanton. - Stanton?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.22,0:10:28.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,国家安全局的首脑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The head of N.S.A.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:28.73,0:10:31.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阴谋反对美国总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Conspiring against the president of the United States?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:32.22,0:10:35.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抛开如果那是真的会带来的巨大影响不谈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Aside from the enormous implications if that were true,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.42,0:10:38.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他难道不是一直都是你的同盟吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- hasn't he always been an ally to you? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.98,0:10:41.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是他也是艾瑞克·雷伯恩的老板\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But he's also Eric Rayburn's boss.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.34,0:10:42.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雷伯恩会帮斯坦顿做事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's not inconceivable
Dialogue: 0,0:10:42.32,0:10:44.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,并不奇怪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that Rayburn could be doing Stanton's bidding.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:45.65,0:10:48.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们两人总是统一步调  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Those two have always been on the same page, Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:48.40,0:10:51.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那并不足以指控罗杰  -我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- That's not enough to indict Roger. - I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.47,0:10:53.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以我才希望你调查他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's why I want you to check him out.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:53.67,0:10:55.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我希望你可以证明我错了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm hoping you can prove me wrong.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.74,0:11:03.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我一安顿好就去跟罗杰谈话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll talk to Roger as soon as I settle in,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:03.30,0:11:04.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看看能不能发现什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}see if I can get a read on him.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:06.14,0:11:07.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thanks, Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:19.42,0:11:20.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有多久降落\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How long till we land?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.57,0:11:21.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大约十分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}About 10 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.80,0:11:31.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,法海因离机场还有多远\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How far is Faheen from the airport?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:31.95,0:11:34.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,降落后我会告诉你  我要喝水\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll tell you when we land. Can I have some water?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.26,0:11:36.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们时间紧迫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're fighting the clock here,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.37,0:11:37.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尼娜  所以你最好开始交代\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nina, so you better start talking to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:37.93,0:11:40.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,法海因离机场还有多远\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How far is Faheen from the airport?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:40.53,0:11:42.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们需要她合作  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We need her to cooperate, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:42.64,0:11:44.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,威胁她帮不上什么忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Threatening her isn't gonna help.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:48.93,0:11:52.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  给她换衣服\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fine. Get her changed.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:53.28,0:11:55.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要她看起来像个普通人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need her to look like a civilian.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:00.40,0:12:01.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.31,0:12:04.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.12,0:12:08.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在这换  她不能离开我的视线\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here. She doesn't leave my sight.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:55.55,0:12:56.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但起作用了  不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But it's  out, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.08,0:12:59.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不如自己过来看看  我们...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, why don't you come by and see? We're--
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.23,0:13:01.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,虽然不如丽思卡尔顿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's not the Ritz Carlton,
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.23,0:13:01.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}美国高级连锁酒店
Dialogue: 0,0:13:01.12,0:13:03.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-但对我们来说足够了  -好的  我下来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but it's working for us. Okay. I'll come on down.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:03.42,0:13:04.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得挂了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I gotta go.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.06,0:13:04.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.89,0:13:09.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-喂  -杰克马上就要在维萨利亚降落了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yeah? - Jack's about to land in Visalia.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:10.29,0:13:12.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们从她口中问出法海因的位置了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Have they got a location for Faheen out of her yet?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.41,0:13:13.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还没有  要到落地之后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, not until they land.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.90,0:13:16.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-继续跟进  我马上下来  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Stay on it. I'll be down in a minute. - Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:29.18,0:13:31.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这位女士的双份意式浓缩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Double espresso for the lady...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.38,0:13:33.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,小心烫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and it's hot.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:36.48,0:13:40.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,收三块  找你五分\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Out of three, and five cents is your change.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.44,0:13:44.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-喂  -约翰  是我  爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Hello? - John, it's your father.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.56,0:13:51.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-喂  你还在吗  -在  我在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Hello? You there? - Uh, yeah, yeah. I'm here.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.28,0:13:55.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道我们有段时间没联系了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I, uh... I know it's been a while.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:55.83,0:13:58.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-两年  -这么久了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Two years. - That long?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.29,0:14:00.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-是的  -是我的错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yep. - Well, that's my fault.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.57,0:14:06.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,约翰  我今天很想见见你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, John, I'd really like to see you today.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:06.79,0:14:09.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我来不了  -这很重要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I can't. - It's important.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.05,0:14:13.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸  你不能无缘无故地打电话给我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Dad, listen, uh-- You can't just call me out of the blue...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:13.21,0:14:14.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还指望我立马过来  因为首先\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and expect me to jump, because first off,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.81,0:14:15.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不是很想见你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't really want to see you.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.91,0:14:17.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,即使我想  我也来不了  我很忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Even if I did, I can't. I'm busy.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.86,0:14:19.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道是我搞砸了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I know I screwed up.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.08,0:14:20.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也能理解\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I understand if I'm not
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.08,0:14:21.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你现在很讨厌我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}your favorite person in the world right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:21.51,0:14:22.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但你能不能暂时放下成见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But can you just set that aside and
Dialogue: 0,0:14:22.77,0:14:25.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就为我做这一件事  我需要你来反恐组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}do this one thing for me? I need you to come to C.T.U.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.47,0:14:27.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你知道在哪儿的吧  -今天不行  爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You know where that is, right? - I can't do it today, dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.42,0:14:28.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我跟你说过了  我在忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I told you. I'm in the middle of something.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:29.81,0:14:31.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,到底什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just tell me what's goin' on.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:31.62,0:14:33.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要见你  约翰  就是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need to see you, John. That's what's going on.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.69,0:14:35.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,算了  你根本没在听我说话  爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what? You're not listening to me, Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:35.19,0:14:36.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我现在正在忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm in the middle of something right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:36.13,0:14:37.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得等有空再打给你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna have to call you when I have a chance.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.45,0:14:54.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\fad(359,265)\pos(194.4,196.553)}达文波特机场\N加州  维萨利亚
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.76,0:15:02.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,起来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get up.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.44,0:15:12.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,开过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bring it in now.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.83,0:15:31.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:41.47,0:15:42.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是多克蒂探员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm Agent Dockerty.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.41,0:15:44.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克·鲍尔  这是菲利普斯和哈里斯探员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack Bauer. Agents Phillips and Harris.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:44.78,0:15:47.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们都准备好了  现在只需要一个地址\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're all set up. All we need now is a location.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:48.04,0:15:51.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们该去哪儿  尼娜  地址是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where we going, Nina? What's the location?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.05,0:15:54.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-北科林斯一家二手商店  -叫什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It's a thrift store on North Collins. - What's the name?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.97,0:15:57.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-新月回收品店  -我们车辆配置怎样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Crescent Collectibles. - What's our transportation?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:57.93,0:16:00.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,三个小队  三辆车  都在等你的命令\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Three teams, three vehicles. They're waiting for your orders.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.49,0:16:04.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,新月回收品店在迪安萨区\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Crescent Collectibles is in the De Anza district.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.22,0:16:05.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,离这儿不远\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's not too far from here.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.42,0:16:07.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们可以把大本营就设在机场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We can set up base camp here at the airport.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.93,0:16:09.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行  带上她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do it. Take her.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.97,0:16:13.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你打算拿她怎么办  -她跟我走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What do you want to do with her? - She stays with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.73,0:16:16.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么  把她留在这  我的人会看着她的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why? Keep her here. My guys will watch her.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.04,0:16:17.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她不会妨碍任何人的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She'll be out of the way.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:17.20,0:16:19.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我要利用她  -怎么利用\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'm gonna use her. - Use her how?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.62,0:16:20.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,到时候你就知道了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You'll see.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.74,0:16:27.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好了各位  谢谢  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- All right, everyone. Thank you. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.84,0:16:30.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-罗杰  -麦克  我听说你来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Roger. - Mike. I heard you were here.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.35,0:16:33.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我听说总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I understand the president
Dialogue: 0,0:16:33.53,0:16:36.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,解雇了艾瑞克·雷伯恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}handed Eric Rayburn his walking papers.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.75,0:16:38.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,艾瑞克搞砸了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, Eric messed up.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:38.86,0:16:40.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统将他解职是对的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The president was right to dismiss him.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.95,0:16:43.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  但他毕竟炒了一个你任命的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Still, he fired someone you appointed.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.09,0:16:46.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是所有人都能支持这样的决定的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It takes character to support that.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:49.54,0:16:53.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我今天任务艰巨  抱歉得失陪了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've got a nasty workload today. You'll have to excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:53.45,0:16:55.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,事实上  总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Actually... the president
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.34,0:16:57.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,需要我今天叨扰你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}wants me to insert myself into your day.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.84,0:17:01.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这可能有点困难  我这儿的情况瞬息万变\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, that might be difficult. I'm moving a mile a minute here.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.50,0:17:03.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道  我想看看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I understand. I'd like to have a look
Dialogue: 0,0:17:03.76,0:17:06.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有关最新线索的所有文件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}at any paper you have on the most active leads.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:06.45,0:17:07.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我来赶你的进度就好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me play catch-up.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:09.25,0:17:10.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.34,0:17:13.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在民众反应方面你确实可以帮我一把\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I could use a little help in the civil response area.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.05,0:17:17.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好  我在这儿的四号站  把资料发给我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Great. I'll be working up here in four. Get me what you got.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.08,0:17:33.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,汇报进展\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Update me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.07,0:17:36.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,洛杉矶反恐组正在跟进最有希望的线索\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, CTU Los Angeles is yielding the most promising leads.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.52,0:17:38.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们今早突袭了市区的一个仓库\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They raided a warehouse this morning within city limits,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.96,0:17:42.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,发现了武器级别的核材料\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and they found weapons-grade nuclear material.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:42.07,0:17:44.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,中情局正在回放卫星图像\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Langley is using satellite playback
Dialogue: 0,0:17:44.13,0:17:46.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,以确定去过那里的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}as we speak to determine who was there.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.11,0:17:48.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-有一名疑犯被击毙  -发生了交火\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- A suspect was killed? - There was a shoot-out.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.62,0:17:50.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,分局还没有确认死者身份\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Division's having a hard time I.D.ing the body.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.22,0:17:53.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's this?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:53.33,0:17:55.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很显然杰克·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, apparently Jack Bauer is still
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.34,0:17:56.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还在参与调查\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}involved in the investigation.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.00,0:17:58.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还以为他在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I thought he was dismissed
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.38,0:18:00.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,完成了今早的任务之后就退出了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}after he completed this morning's assignment.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.23,0:18:03.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有  追踪马穆·法海因的小队就是他领头\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. He's heading the team that's tracking Mamud Faheen.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.26,0:18:06.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有尼娜·迈尔斯  您今早豁免的那个女人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And Nina Myers, the woman you granted immunity to this morning?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.23,0:18:07.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她在协助他们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's helping them.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:10.77,0:18:13.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克·鲍尔和尼娜·迈尔斯在一起合作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack Bauer and Nina Myers are working together?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.26,0:18:14.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:14.77,0:18:16.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他应该是主动要求去的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I believe he volunteered.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.34,0:18:21.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们有多少时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's the time divisibility?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.62,0:18:22.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,从我们破门进去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}From the time we break in
Dialogue: 0,0:18:22.57,0:18:24.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,到逮捕他  预计有三十秒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}until we get him secured we estimate 30 seconds.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.89,0:18:25.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果从屋顶进去呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about going through the roof?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.93,0:18:28.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们在看建筑平面图  看可不可行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're looking at the building plans to see if it's viable.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:28.14,0:18:31.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不可行  他在墙上和地基上都会装传感器的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's not. He'll have sensors on the walls and foundations.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.38,0:18:32.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你们从正门进去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you guys go in through the front door,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.63,0:18:34.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就会给法海因足够的时间自杀\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that'll give Faheen enough time to commit suicide.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:34.61,0:18:37.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果他这么不怕死  为什么还要离开洛杉矶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If he's so willing to die, why'd he leave Los Angeles?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.23,0:18:38.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他不想成为附带损伤\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He doesn't want to be collateral damage,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.52,0:18:39.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但这不代表\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but that doesn't mean
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.04,0:18:41.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他不会为了保护计划而献出自己的生命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}he won't give up his life to protect the plan.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:41.22,0:18:43.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们不能冒险  我们需要活捉这个人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We can't afford to take a chance. We need this guy alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.79,0:18:45.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-催泪弹呢  -没用的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Gas canister? - It won't work.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:45.97,0:18:47.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他知道我们所有的规程  他早有准备\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He knows all our protocols and he's prepared.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:47.83,0:18:50.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他怎么会知道我们的规程  -她给他的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How does he know your protocols? - She gave them to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:51.70,0:18:54.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这不重要  尼娜  你进去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Doesn't matter. Nina, you're going in.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:54.35,0:18:56.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么  -他认识你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What? - He knows you.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.23,0:18:57.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他也知道我进监狱了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He also thinks I'm in prison.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:57.80,0:18:59.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你最好让他相信你出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You better make him believe you got out.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:59.97,0:19:01.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,恰好在他的炸弹要爆炸的那天\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The day his bomb's supposed to go off?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:01.73,0:19:02.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他会发现我在说谎的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He'll know I'm lying.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.95,0:19:04.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你最擅长说谎了  尼娜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're a good liar, Nina.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:04.00,0:19:06.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,除非你想让他知道  否则他不会发现的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The only way he's gonna know is if you let him.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.26,0:19:09.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们需要三十秒  -他会在我打招呼之前\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- We need 30 seconds. - He is going to put a bullet in my head...
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.15,0:19:10.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就一枪崩了我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}before I can say "Hello,"
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.11,0:19:12.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后一枪崩了自己的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and then he's gonna turn the gun on himself.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.58,0:19:16.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们会保证他不崩了自己的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll make sure he doesn't turn the gun on himself.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.96,0:19:35.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么样了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How's it looking?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.07,0:19:36.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好  所有频道都开了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good. We've got all the channels open.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.36,0:19:37.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只需要等信号传过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're just waiting for the feeds.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:37.68,0:19:40.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们知道法海因讲的是哪里的阿拉伯语吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do we know what dialect of Arabic Faheen speaks?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:40.12,0:19:42.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-知道  尼娜告诉我们了  -梅森先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yeah. Nina gave us the information. - Mr. Mason.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.94,0:19:44.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼·阿尔梅达找你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony Almeida's on the line.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.44,0:19:54.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-托尼  -纳耶尔开口了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yeah, Tony. - Naiyeer's starting to talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:54.78,0:19:56.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他说是鲍勃·华纳\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He says that Bob Warner's the one
Dialogue: 0,0:19:56.05,0:19:57.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在跟赛伊德·阿里做交易\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that had dealings with Syed Ali.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.21,0:20:00.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当然了  华纳宣称他对此毫不知情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course, Warner claims he doesn't know anything about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.82,0:20:03.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把他们都带回来  分开审讯  给他们施压\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bring 'em both in. We'll separate 'em and turn up the heat.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.38,0:20:06.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是批准我逮捕他们了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you giving me the okay to arrest these people?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:06.74,0:20:07.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果他们不自愿过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If they don't come willingly,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:07.81,0:20:10.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那就是批准了  -用什么罪名\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- that's exactly what I'm doing. - On what charge?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:11.16,0:20:12.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,用乱穿马路都行啊  把他们带回来就行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't care if it's jaywalking. Just bring 'em in.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:18.14,0:20:20.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  收到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. You got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.69,0:20:27.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我父亲怎么了  -请等一下  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What's going on with my father? - Give me a minute, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:31.94,0:20:33.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你去把鲍勃·华纳带过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need you to get Bob Warner.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:33.37,0:20:35.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们去反恐组继续  知道了吗  -收到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- We'll finish this up at CTU, okay? - Got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.97,0:20:39.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雷扎  我需要你跟我们走一趟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Reza, I'm gonna need you to come with us.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:40.53,0:20:43.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-跟你们去哪里  -回反恐组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Come with you where? - Back to C.T.U.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:43.97,0:20:46.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-去干什么  -进一步讯问\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- For what? - Further questioning.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:46.09,0:20:47.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我哪都不会跟你去的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not going with you anywhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:48.97,0:20:51.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我暂时还没有打算逮捕任何人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I'm not arresting anybody...
Dialogue: 0,0:20:51.94,0:20:54.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但如果你逼我的话  我会的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}yet-- but I will if you force me to.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:54.89,0:20:56.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,无论如何你都得跟我们走一趟的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, you're coming with us either way.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:56.48,0:20:58.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,具体怎么去就完全取决于你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How we do this is entirely up to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:59.35,0:21:02.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,按他说的做  雷扎  不要跟他理论\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just do what the man says, Reza. Don't argue with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:02.03,0:21:03.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鲍勃  我没做错什么  他不能逮捕我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bob, I haven't done anything wrong. He can't arrest me.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.83,0:21:06.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雷扎  雷扎  拜托了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Reza. Reza, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:06.42,0:21:07.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就当是为了我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do this for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:10.90,0:21:11.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.66,0:21:17.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我要跟你们一起去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then I'm coming with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:17.83,0:21:19.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  我们不能带你一起去  女士\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, we can't take you with us, ma'am.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.97,0:21:23.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我就跟着  反正你们已经毁了我的婚礼了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then I'll follow you. You've ruined my wedding day.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:23.30,0:21:25.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不会让你们把我和我未婚夫分开的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not going to let you separate me from my fiance.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:30.34,0:21:31.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right this way.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.85,0:21:40.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.32,0:21:43.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,通知所有人婚礼推迟了  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Call everyone. Explain the wedding's been postponed, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:43.93,0:21:44.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.34,0:21:48.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,打电话给拉里  告诉他我的情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you to call Larry, and tell him where I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.09,0:21:50.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-爸  拉里只是个税务律师  -没关系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Dad, Larry's a tax attorney. - Doesn't matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.19,0:21:52.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没关系  他知道该怎么做的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Doesn't matter. He'll know what to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.98,0:21:54.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:55.34,0:21:56.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.67,0:22:16.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,下午好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good afternoon.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.00,0:22:18.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们俩还没正式认识过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ah, you two haven't been formally introduced.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.94,0:22:21.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,林恩·柯瑞斯基  雪莉·帕尔默\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lynne Kresge, Sherry Palmer.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:22.05,0:22:25.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,林恩  很高兴认识你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lynne. It's lovely to meet you.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.35,0:22:26.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,帕尔默女士\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mrs. Palmer.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.70,0:22:30.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  斯坦顿局长...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Um, Mr. President, there were a few guidelines...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.11,0:22:31.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,写了几份准则\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}from Director Stanton that
Dialogue: 0,0:22:31.28,0:22:33.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想和您在这次会议中讨论一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wanted to go over with you in this meeting.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.20,0:22:37.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  我来简单介绍一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. Let me just break the ice here.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:37.63,0:22:40.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,林恩  我已经行使行政特权\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lynne, I have invoked executive privilege...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.16,0:22:43.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给予雪莉临时安全权限\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and have granted Sherry a provisional security clearance.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:43.75,0:22:44.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我明白了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I see.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:45.57,0:22:47.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这次会议是关于可能存在的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This meeting's about the possibility of
Dialogue: 0,0:22:47.60,0:22:49.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,本届政府内部\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}people inside this administration...
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.00,0:22:50.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,正阴谋反对我的成员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}who may be organizing against me.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:51.88,0:22:53.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反对你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A-Against you?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.00,0:22:56.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大卫  或许你应该...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}David, um, maybe you should, uh,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:56.09,0:22:58.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,跟林恩讲一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}bring Lynne up to speed
Dialogue: 0,0:22:58.22,0:23:00.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,关于罗杰·斯坦顿的最新情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}on where we are with Roger Stanton.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:10.79,0:23:12.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-总统先生  -林恩  我很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Mr. President? - Lynne, I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:12.50,0:23:14.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天一切都进展得太快了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Things have been happening too fast today.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:14.57,0:23:16.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们面临的问题又多了一个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Our problems are compounded
Dialogue: 0,0:23:16.08,0:23:18.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可能存在一个持异见的小集团\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}by the possibility of a dissenting faction.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.74,0:23:20.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而您觉得罗杰可能参与其中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And you think that Roger might be a part of that?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.98,0:23:25.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-可能  -如果您不介意我问的话  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It's possible. - If you don't mind my asking, sir,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:25.59,0:23:27.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是什么让您作出了这样的假设\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}what led you to this hypothesis?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:27.78,0:23:30.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很不想说那么直白  林恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It troubles me to articulate this, Lynne,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.14,0:23:33.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但大使直升机的事故\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but the ambassador's helicopter accident
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.73,0:23:35.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,的确解决了罗杰·斯坦顿的很多问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}solved a lot of Roger Stanton's issues.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.01,0:23:38.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先生  很多人都有这些问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, those issues were shared by many others--
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.98,0:23:43.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,非常抱歉  我要打断一下  大卫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm so sorry to interrupt, uh, David,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.01,0:23:45.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但还有一件事情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but there's something else
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.60,0:23:48.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你可能不知道  林恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that you probably don't know, Lynne,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.02,0:23:52.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就是罗杰·斯坦顿一直在秘密会见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and that is that Roger Stanton has been having secret meetings...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.47,0:23:54.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,参议院少数党领袖\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}with the minority leader in the Senate,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.02,0:23:57.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,艾瑞克·雷伯恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and Eric Rayburn...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:57.60,0:23:59.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也都出席了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}has been in attendance.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.54,0:24:03.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,事实上  雪莉  我知道这些会面的存在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, actually, Sherry, I am aware of those meetings.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:04.00,0:24:07.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们在争取形成两党合作以阻止\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They were trying to forge a bipartisan base in order to stop
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.56,0:24:09.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,由军事委员会下达的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}questionable allocations that
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.21,0:24:11.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一些有问题的分配\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}were being made by the Armed Services Committee.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.99,0:24:15.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先生  我之所以没和你汇报...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And, sir, the only reason I did not brief you on this earlier...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.99,0:24:18.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是因为接下来两个月不会进行投票\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is because the vote is not for another two months.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.04,0:24:23.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是如果你想看的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I have very detailed records
Dialogue: 0,0:24:23.02,0:24:24.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我这里有详细记录\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}if you would like to take a look at them.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:28.43,0:24:30.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这不能解决我们今天的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This doesn't solve any of our problems today.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.22,0:24:32.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要阻止一场灾难发生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We've got to avert a disaster,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:32.83,0:24:36.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们自己窝里反可没办法成功\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and we can't do that if our own people are working against us.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:36.76,0:24:39.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在  我想知道罗杰·斯坦顿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, I need to know that Roger Stanton...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:39.99,0:24:41.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会不会支持我们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is supporting this administration.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.78,0:24:45.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我和罗杰已经在一起工作了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm already working alongside Roger.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:45.47,0:24:47.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,林恩  我希望你能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lynne, I'd like you to keep
Dialogue: 0,0:24:47.20,0:24:49.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,和他保持密切联系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}track of your conversations with him as well.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.98,0:24:53.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在  我整理了一份国会山上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, I've put together a list of people on the Hill...
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.99,0:24:56.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能帮上忙的人的名单\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}who might be able to help in this matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.37,0:24:57.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you, Mike.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.33,0:25:25.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\frz3.414\fax0.05\move(196.8,113.6,210,108.8,0,404)}{\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs8\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H000000&}结束睡眠模式
Dialogue: 0,0:25:25.75,0:25:26.96,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an8\frz3.414\fax0.05\move(210,108.8,186.6,94.2,0,1193)}{\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs8\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H000000&}结束睡眠模式
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.30,0:25:37.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(220.2,118.4,226.8,107,0,820)}{\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs7\b1\bord0\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}输入该账号密码
Dialogue: 0,0:25:37.14,0:25:37.80,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(226.8,107,205.4,115,0,647)}{\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs7\b1\bord0\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}输入该账号密码
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.29,0:25:52.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,洛杉矶调查局  我是保罗·柯普林\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}L.A. Investigations. Paul Koplin speaking.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.72,0:25:55.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你好  保罗  我是凯特·华纳\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hi, Paul. This is Kate Warner.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.05,0:25:56.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拉尔夫·波顿在吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is Ralph Burton there?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.31,0:25:58.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不好意思  凯特  拉尔夫不在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, I'm sorry, Kate. Ralph's not here.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.65,0:26:02.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-有什么我能帮你的吗  -我找拉尔夫有事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Can I help you with something? - I need to talk to Ralph.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:02.45,0:26:05.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他今天下班了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, he left for the day. You know,
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.20,0:26:07.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他是我手下  他的案子我都清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}he works for me. I'm familiar with the case.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.02,0:26:08.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有什么我能做的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is there something I can do for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:11.83,0:26:13.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要帮助\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need some help.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.35,0:26:17.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想知道我父亲的个人档案\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have to get into my father's private records.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.98,0:26:26.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-林恩  林恩  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Lynne? Lynne. - Yes?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:26.92,0:26:28.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-能和你谈谈吗  -可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Can I have a sec? - Sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:38.59,0:26:40.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道你不喜欢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I, uh, know that you're uncomfortable
Dialogue: 0,0:26:40.85,0:26:43.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我抢了你的工作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}with me taking some of these tasks from you.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:43.46,0:26:46.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,毕竟  名义上我不属于大卫团队了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}After all, I'm not officially on David's staff.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.71,0:26:48.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,帕尔默女士  我舒不舒服\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mrs. Palmer, my discomfort
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.65,0:26:51.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,和你是不是他的手下没任何关系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}has nothing to do with you being on his staff.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:51.45,0:26:54.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只在乎保护和效忠总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My only concern is to protect and to serve the president.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:54.22,0:26:56.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得知道他身边的人是否有真才实干\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need to know the people around him are competent.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.14,0:26:57.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是不了解你罢了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I simply don't know you.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:57.97,0:27:00.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你看上去就很聪明  林恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, you seem like a pretty smart woman, Lynne.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:00.10,0:27:03.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以我把有些话挑明了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So let me explain something to you clearly.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.98,0:27:07.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大卫能走到今天可不是凭借一己之力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}David did not get here by himself.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.19,0:27:11.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他身边一直不乏精明能干之辈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's had competent people around him his entire life.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.40,0:27:14.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很明显  你也是其中之一\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Obviously, you're one of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.29,0:27:17.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是最厉害的  只是最近的一个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not necessarily the best, just the most recent.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:19.46,0:27:23.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以给那些把他扶到今天位置的人一点尊重\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So have some respect for those of us who put him into office.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.97,0:27:26.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们也许就用得上我们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We just might be able to help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:34.98,0:27:36.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你说得对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fair enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:44.11,0:27:45.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,小心点  雪莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Be careful, Sherry.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:47.27,0:27:51.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要林恩  别把这变成一场比赛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need Lynne. Don't turn this into a competition.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:51.45,0:27:53.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:53.94,0:27:57.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是...让她知道...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just... need her to know...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.63,0:28:00.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在这里可不是充当摆设的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that I'm not just around here as window dressing.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:01.31,0:28:03.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想她已经知道了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sure she got the message.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.89,0:28:06.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我保证不会乱来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll behave. Promise.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.91,0:28:08.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雪莉...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sherry...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.44,0:28:14.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你现在在这没多少朋友\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you don't have a lot of friends here today.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.61,0:28:19.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,事实上  身边总有人告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In fact... it seems like every time I turn around,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:19.57,0:28:21.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不该把你留在身边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}somebody's advising me to send you away.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:24.65,0:28:26.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你怎么不照做呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then why don't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:27.40,0:28:30.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为你可能有别人得不到的情报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because you may be able to get information that nobody else can.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.97,0:28:51.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,开慢点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. Slow down.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:52.59,0:28:54.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等我们通过监视器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As soon as we get a positive I.D.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:54.05,0:28:56.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,确认对方身份后  我们30秒内就冲进去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Through your camera, we'll be in within 30 seconds.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.98,0:29:01.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就这里  下去吧  快点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is it. Get out. Get out!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.03,0:29:10.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,各单位注意  尼娜出现  尼娜出现\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All teams on alert. Nina is in play. Nina is in play.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.02,0:29:13.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,第二小队收到  我们看到她了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is Team Two. We've got her.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.30,0:29:15.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,收到  第二小队\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Roger that, Team Two.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.32,0:29:21.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,保持在一号频道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stay on frequency one.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.02,0:29:44.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔  你能听到吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle, can you read me?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:44.22,0:29:46.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-能听到  杰克  -好  她进去了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Copy, Jack. - Okay, she's in.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.76,0:29:48.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们马上就位\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're moving into position now.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:55.40,0:29:57.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有什么需要帮忙的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is there something I can help you find?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:00.80,0:30:04.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我要见马穆  -抱歉  这没有什么马穆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I need to see Mamud. - I'm sorry. I don't know any Mamud.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:04.39,0:30:06.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉他尼娜要见他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell him Nina is here to see him.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:07.79,0:30:08.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尼娜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nina?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:14.36,0:30:15.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请在这里稍等\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wait here, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:50.12,0:30:51.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,跟我来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:03.04,0:31:05.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔  都是静电干扰\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle, all I've got is static.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.26,0:31:07.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,监视器上什么也看不到  怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's nothing on my monitor. What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:07.64,0:31:10.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她把她带进走廊了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's leading her through a door into a hallway.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:13.72,0:31:14.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,靠着墙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Against the wall.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.60,0:31:18.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,举起手来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hands in the air.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:22.60,0:31:24.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们好像在检查她是否携带武器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now it looks like they're checking her for weapons.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:29.61,0:31:30.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are they saying?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.69,0:31:33.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她说他们以为她进了监狱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She said they thought she was in prison.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:32.16,0:31:32.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\move(91.8,120.8,129.2,123,0,565)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs11\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H000000&}我们以为你进了监狱\N\N我逃出来了  我需要马穆带我出境
Dialogue: 0,0:31:32.74,0:31:33.28,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an4\move(129.2,123,151.8,150.8,0,527)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs11\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H000000&}我们以为你进了监狱\N\N我逃出来了  我需要马穆带我出境
Dialogue: 0,0:31:33.28,0:31:34.33,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an4\move(152,149.4,150.2,128.6,0,1030)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs11\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H000000&}我们以为你进了监狱\N\N我逃出来了  我需要马穆带我出境
Dialogue: 0,0:31:33.06,0:31:34.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尼娜说她逃出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nina said she escaped.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:44.95,0:31:46.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在他们把她带到另一间屋子了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now they're taking her into another room.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:46.97,0:31:50.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好像是东边出口那间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It looks like the one off the east exit.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.20,0:32:39.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她在和谁说话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who is she talking to?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:39.66,0:32:41.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道  目标还在阴影里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't tell. The target's still in shadow.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:41.99,0:32:45.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他们在说什么  -她说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Well, what are they saying? - She said
Dialogue: 0,0:32:45.73,0:32:48.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她解释她是怎么买通关系逃出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's explaining who she had to pay to escape from prison.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:48.91,0:32:50.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  要行动吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, should we go?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.12,0:32:53.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不要  等我确认那人是法海因再说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, not until I have confirmation that it's Faheen.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:02.80,0:33:05.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我什么也看不见了  -我也是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- My audio just went dead. - Yeah, I lost mine too.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:05.20,0:33:07.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-就现在  行动吧  -快行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Okay, that's it. Everybody, go. - Okay. Let's go.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:32.73,0:33:35.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,危险已消除  各就各位\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have it clear! Stand in position!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:41.69,0:33:43.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快  快行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on! Sweep! Let's go!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:45.11,0:33:46.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,各就各位\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stand in position!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.58,0:33:54.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快  快  快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go, now! Go, go! Go!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:58.41,0:34:01.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,菲利普斯  法海因昏倒了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Phillips! Faheen's unconscious.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:01.73,0:34:04.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她不见了  尼娜不见了  搜索大楼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's gone. Nina's gone. Secure the building.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:04.78,0:34:07.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是菲利普斯  东门需要医护人员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is Phillips. We need medics at the east entrance.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:39.02,0:34:40.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,放下枪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Drop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:53.55,0:35:55.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们刚从洛杉矶出发  卡罗尔姑姑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're just leaving L.A. Right now, Aunt Carol.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:55.63,0:35:57.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们可能还得四到五个小时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll probably be another four or five hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.49,0:36:01.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  没事  再见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, we will. Bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.08,0:36:12.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-该死  -这是在逗我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Damn it. - Oh, you gotta be kidding.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:14.12,0:36:15.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,冷静点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just play it cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:15.39,0:36:17.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么冷静  车都是偷来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Cool? We're in a stolen car.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.28,0:36:47.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请出示驾照和车主信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your license and registration, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:47.46,0:36:49.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-有什么问题吗  -你刚刚超速了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Did I do something wrong? - You were speeding.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:55.68,0:36:58.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-车主信息  -这是我老板的车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Registration too. - Um, this is my boss's car.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:58.61,0:37:00.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道他放哪儿了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not sure where he keeps it.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.61,0:37:03.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,肯定就在车里的什么地方\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sure it's in here somewhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:05.34,0:37:06.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,应该是这个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think this is it.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:07.99,0:37:08.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:16.17,0:37:17.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,稍等  我马上回来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay. I'll be right back.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:30.93,0:37:31.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你这是要干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What the hell are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.97,0:37:33.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有什么事吗  乔治\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Anything else I can do for you, George?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:33.47,0:37:35.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没事了  肯  这里交给我  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- No, Ken. I got it from here. - Got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:36.41,0:37:37.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  约翰\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry, John.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:39.30,0:37:41.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我跟你说过我得见见你  对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, I told you I needed to see you, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:44.45,0:37:45.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里发生了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What happened here?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:47.01,0:37:49.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你从来都不看新闻的  是吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Never could get you to watch the news, could I?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:49.63,0:37:50.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你想一叙父子情  爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you're looking to bond here, Dad,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:50.91,0:37:53.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把你儿子抓来可不是怎么好主意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}having your son arrested probably isn't the best way to do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:58.24,0:38:01.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我时间不多  约翰  发生了一些事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't have much time, John. Things are happening here.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:01.68,0:38:04.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我就不详细解释了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I, uh... I can't go into it fully.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:04.62,0:38:06.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你总是含糊其辞  不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You could never go fully into much of anything, could you?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:06.52,0:38:07.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我工作性质就是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's my line of work.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:07.50,0:38:08.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要是想重新组建家庭\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's just something you should look into
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.54,0:38:09.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就应该这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}if you decide to start a second family.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:09.97,0:38:11.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不可能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's not gonna happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.73,0:38:16.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  我知道你很生气\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I understand if you're angry.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:16.37,0:38:19.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没生气  爸  我不在乎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not angry, Dad. I don't care.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:21.16,0:38:23.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是不明白  你到底想干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I really just don't understand. What are you trying to do here?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:31.25,0:38:33.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我有个没人知道的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got this bank account that's
Dialogue: 0,0:38:34.45,0:38:36.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,银行账户\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}nobody knows about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:36.53,0:38:38.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,里面有几十万美元\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's got a couple hundred thousand dollars in it.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:38.04,0:38:38.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都是你的了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you to have it.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:38.97,0:38:42.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是我会计的电话号\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's the... number for my bookkeeper,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:42.89,0:38:44.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我和他打过招呼了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}who I've already spoken to.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:44.31,0:38:46.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他会把钱转到你的账户\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's gonna be transferring money to your account.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.11,0:38:46.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看我说的对不对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me get this right then.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.91,0:38:49.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你让我来这里只是要给我钱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You bring me here to tell me you're giving me money?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.21,0:38:50.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想让我怎样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What'd you expect me to do?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.17,0:38:53.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给你个大大的拥抱  爸  我不要你的钱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did you expect me to give you a hug? Dad. don't want your money.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:53.89,0:38:56.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那就给你妈吧  她肯定会要的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, then, give it your mom. I'm sure she does.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:58.76,0:39:00.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,事实是  这笔钱我用不上了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The thing is, I'm not gonna be needing it, so
Dialogue: 0,0:39:00.89,0:39:01.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, why is that?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:09.62,0:39:10.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么  爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why is that, Dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.21,0:39:13.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  你不能把我带到这\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen, you don't bring me here,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:13.72,0:39:16.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给我一笔钱还不告诉我原因\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}offer me a small fortune then not tell me what's going on.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.19,0:39:23.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我要死了  约翰  -你个...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'm dying, John. - You son of a bitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:49.28,0:39:52.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是癌症...还是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is it cancer... or something?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:53.88,0:39:55.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,差不多吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Something like that, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:59.48,0:40:00.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  约翰\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, John.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:02.52,0:40:05.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天洛杉矶会发生惊天灾难\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Something bad is gonna happen in Los Angeles today,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:07.08,0:40:10.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你得离开这里  -现在吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- and I need you to leave town. - Leave now?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:10.37,0:40:11.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想你去凤凰城\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you to go to Phoenix.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:11.26,0:40:13.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,和你母亲住段时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stay with your mom for a little while, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:13.61,0:40:16.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是认真的  约翰  这里太危险了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean it, John.It's dangerous to be here.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:18.16,0:40:19.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没法给你解释原因\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't explain it to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:19.35,0:40:22.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你就听我的吧  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But you just have to go, okay? Just go.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:22.40,0:40:25.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸  听着  我不  没关系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Dad, listen. I don't-- This doesn't--
Dialogue: 0,0:40:26.13,0:40:27.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Damn it.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:33.30,0:40:36.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是个好孩子  希望我没把你毁得太过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're a good kid. I hope I didn't mess you up too bad.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:36.97,0:40:37.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:39.22,0:40:40.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-走吧  好吗  -你就不能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Get out of here, all right? - Can you just--
Dialogue: 0,0:40:40.81,0:40:42.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听话  快走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just get out of here, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:54.37,0:40:55.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天呐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, God.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:03.32,0:41:06.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们不能让他带我们回洛杉矶  -我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- We can't let him take us back to L.A. - I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:08.01,0:41:09.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么这么长时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why is it taking so long?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:25.18,0:41:27.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你说这是你老板的车  -没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You say this is your boss's car? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:30.50,0:41:33.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这个小女孩是谁  -我是她家的保姆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Who's the little girl? - Oh, I'm her au pair.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:34.14,0:41:36.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么  -她是她的保姆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Her what? - She baby-sits her.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:37.36,0:41:38.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我又没问你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wasn't talking to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:45.01,0:41:45.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll tell you what.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:48.10,0:41:50.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我这次就给你个口头警告\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna let you get off with just a warning this time.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:50.37,0:41:53.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但记得别超速  听见了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But you slow down. All right?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:54.02,0:41:55.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  长官  谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, Officer. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:55.63,0:41:56.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:08.04,0:42:08.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hold up.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:18.66,0:42:21.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,下车把后备箱打开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You want to step out of the car and open up the trunk?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:23.06,0:42:25.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,下车把后备箱打开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Step out of the car and open up the trunk.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:57.58,0:43:00.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-天呐  -双手放头顶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Oh, my God. - Put your hands on your head.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:00.25,0:43:01.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-趴在地上  -这不是我干的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Lay on your stomach. - I don't know anything--
Dialogue: 0,0:43:01.61,0:43:03.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,趴下  趴下  趴下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get down, get down! Get down!
Dialogue: 0,0:43:03.82,0:43:05.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,下车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get out of the car!
Dialogue: 0,0:43:05.35,0:43:06.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-双手放头顶  -不是我干的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Keep your hands on your head. - I don't know anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:06.90,0:43:07.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请下车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get out of the car, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:07.73,0:43:09.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-趴下地上  -怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Lay down on the ground. - What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:09.74,0:43:11.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-给我趴在地上  -卡拉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I said, get down on the ground! - Carla!
Dialogue: 0,0:43:11.42,0:43:14.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-天呐  他杀了她  -怎么回事  金\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Oh, my God! He killed her! - What's happening, Kim?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:14.30,0:43:16.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-听着  趴下地上  -梅根  回到车里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Come on. On the ground. - Megan, get back in the car.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:16.71,0:43:18.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把双手放头顶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Put your hands behind your head.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:20.81,0:43:23.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,待着别动  双腿交叉  别动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stay there. Cross your legs. Stay there. Stay still.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:23.09,0:43:24.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请求支援\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Officer in need of assistance.

