[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,1,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.70,0:00:10.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(197.4,200.557)}{\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs25\b1\bord0\shad0\c&H78BDE7&\fad(0,808)}24小时\N\N{\fs15}第二季  第八集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.49,0:00:13.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(189.6,121.6,193.8,105.6,0,356)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad3\3c&H2F2F2F&\4c&H336D99&}{\fs10}{\t(0,356,\fs20)\fn方正正中黑简体}前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.95,0:00:15.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们为什么问爸爸问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why are they asking Dad questions?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.82,0:00:14.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(223.8,235.753)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.86,0:00:14.91,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(214.2,221.353)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.91,0:00:14.95,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(202.2,206.153)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.95,0:00:14.99,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(193.2,193.353)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.99,0:00:15.03,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(184.2,178.153)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.03,0:00:15.07,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(172.2,164.553)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.07,0:00:15.11,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(162,149.353)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.11,0:00:15.15,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(151.8,132.553)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.15,0:00:17.03,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(142.2,121.353)\fad(0,304)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.33,0:00:17.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为你在我们家里挑起了一场政治迫害\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Cause you started a witch hunt in our family.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.56,0:00:20.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你指控我父亲什么  -什么也没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What did you accuse my father of? - I didn't accuse of him anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.36,0:00:22.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你指控他是为了给你自己脱罪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're pointing your finger at him to cover yourself!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.66,0:00:25.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他说是鲍勃·华纳在跟赛伊德·阿里做交易\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He says that Bob Warner's the one that had dealings with Syed Ali.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.39,0:00:27.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把他们都带回来  分开审讯  给他们施压\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bring them both in. We'll separate them and turn up the heat.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.96,0:00:31.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要帮助  我要看看我父亲的个人记录\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need some help. I have to get into my father's private records.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.50,0:00:29.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(215.4,98.4,221.8,86.6,0,822)}{\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs8\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H000000&}密码保护账户
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.34,0:00:29.88,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(221.8,86.6,202.2,88.8,0,524)}{\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs8\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H000000&}密码保护账户
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.47,0:00:33.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在维萨利亚的那个人是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who is the man in Visalia?!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.55,0:00:33.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(51.6,245.353)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.60,0:00:33.64,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(72.6,229.353)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.64,0:00:33.68,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(94.2,214.153)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.68,0:00:33.72,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(115.8,198.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.72,0:00:33.76,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(136.2,182.153)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.76,0:00:33.80,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(159,166.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.80,0:00:33.84,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(178.8,152.553)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.84,0:00:33.88,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(200.4,134.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.88,0:00:35.68,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(220.2,118.153)\fad(0,269)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.42,0:00:35.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在维萨利亚的那个人是马穆·法海因\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The man in Visalia is Mamud Faheen.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.99,0:00:37.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他也以为我在监狱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He also thinks I'm in prison.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.13,0:00:40.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你最好让他相信你出来了  -我要见马穆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You better make him believe you got out.. - I need to see Mamud.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.09,0:00:41.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  要行动吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, Should we go?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.49,0:00:43.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  等我确认那人是法海因再说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, not until I have confirmation it's Faheen.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.53,0:00:45.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就现在  行动吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Okay, that's it. Everybody, go.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.95,0:00:50.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  我们得聊聊罗恩·维兰德的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, we have to talk about Ron Wieland.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.90,0:00:48.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(103.8,209.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.95,0:00:48.99,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(122.4,196.553)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.99,0:00:49.03,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(142.2,184.553)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.03,0:00:49.07,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(161.4,171.2)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.07,0:00:49.11,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(181.2,159.753)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.11,0:00:49.15,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(201.6,146.153)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.15,0:00:49.19,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(221.4,133.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.19,0:00:51.11,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(239.4,122.153)\fad(0,308)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.40,0:00:52.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有人知道我们扣押他了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Does anybody know we have him sequestered?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.19,0:00:53.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有  但是很快他们会意识到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, but pretty soon they gonna figure out
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.74,0:00:56.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们最后看到和他在一起的人是你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the last person they did see him with was you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.17,0:00:58.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我已经行使行政特权\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have invoked executive privilege
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.08,0:01:00.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给予雪莉临时安全权限\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and have granted Sherry provisional security clearance.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.87,0:01:02.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,身边总有人告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Seems every time I turn around,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.77,0:01:04.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不该把你留在身边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}somebody advises me to send you away.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:04.93,0:01:06.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你怎么不照做呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why don't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:06.01,0:01:08.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为你可能有别人得不到的情报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because you may be able to get information that nobody else can.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.46,0:01:11.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,该死  冷静点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Damm it! Just play it cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.18,0:01:13.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么冷静  车都是偷来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Cool? We're in a stolen car.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.92,0:01:11.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(285.6,55.753)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.96,0:01:12.01,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(264.6,68.553)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.01,0:01:12.05,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(243.6,78.153)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.05,0:01:12.09,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(221.4,90.953)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.09,0:01:12.13,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(201.6,100.553)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.13,0:01:12.17,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(180,110.153)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.17,0:01:12.21,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(157.8,121.353)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:12.21,0:01:14.13,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(138,131.753)\fad(0,305)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.29,0:01:16.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,下车  把后备箱打开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Step out of the car, please. And open the trunk.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.09,0:01:18.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-天呐  -卡拉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Oh, my God! - Carla!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.26,0:01:22.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-天呐  他杀了她  -把双手放头顶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Oh, my God! He killed her! - Put your hands behind your head.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:23.10,0:01:29.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs15\t(696,6577,\fs16)\c&H4BAAAD&\fad(1697,1183)\pos(187.2,191.79)}以下故事情节发生在下午3点到4点之间
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.50,0:01:36.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-车是谁的  -她父亲的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- So whose car is it? - It's her father's.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:37.28,0:01:41.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他把车给你了  -不算是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Did he give it to you? - Not exactly.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:41.57,0:01:46.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那到底是什么  -我们未经允许开走了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Then what, exactly? - We took it without permission.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:46.63,0:01:50.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你偷了这辆车  -无法相信他杀了她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You stole this car? - I can't believe he killed her.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:50.50,0:01:54.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  警官  加里·马西森  金的雇主\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, officer, Gary Matheson, the man Kim works for,
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.39,0:01:56.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一直打他的妻子  并且开始伤害他的女儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}had beat his wife and was starting to hurt his daughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:56.91,0:01:59.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金找我帮她带梅根远离这个男人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kim called me to help her get Megan away from this guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.60,0:02:02.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果是真的  你们为什么不去找警察\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If that's true, why didn't you go to the police?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.14,0:02:04.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么我在离洛杉矶32千米的地方找到你们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why do I find you 20 miles outside of LA?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:08.54,0:02:11.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我就知道  你有权保持沉默\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's what I thought. You have the right to remain silent.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.45,0:02:14.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你所说的每句话都将可能作为呈堂证供\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Anything you say can and will be used against you in a court of law.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:14.68,0:02:15.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有权请律师\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You have the right to an attorney.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.87,0:02:16.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你请不起律师\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you can't afford an attorney,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.92,0:02:19.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,法庭会为你指定一名律师\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}one will be appointed for you by the court.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.28,0:02:21.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你明白这些权利吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you understand these rights?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:30.65,0:02:32.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里安全吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is it safe in here?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:33.04,0:02:35.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只要远离隔离区  就没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just stay away from cordoned areas, you'll be all right.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:35.68,0:02:38.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这是今早发生爆炸的那栋楼  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- This was the building that bombed this morning. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:40.07,0:02:42.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,房间准备好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You got the rooms ready?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:42.26,0:02:43.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  还是有点乱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah. They're a little messed up,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:43.71,0:02:45.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是用来审讯没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but thay're good enough for interrogation.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:46.58,0:02:48.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,情况怎样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How we doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.29,0:02:52.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最终统计  三十人死亡  十七人受伤\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Final tally... 30 dead, 17 wounded.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.34,0:02:54.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大卫多夫和林道尔伤重\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Davidorff and Lindauer are critical.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.34,0:02:56.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,宝拉呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about Paula?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.06,0:03:05.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能不能帮我把他们带回房间去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Could you do me a favour and take them back to the rooms?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:06.03,0:03:07.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请跟我来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Follow me, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:11.16,0:03:14.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能和你单独聊聊吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen, can I talk to you alone?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.09,0:03:15.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,跟着他们  我一会就去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stay with them. I'll be there in a minute.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:20.48,0:03:22.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有新发现吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Find anything new?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.15,0:03:25.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有  就是我电话里和你说的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, just what I told you on the phone.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.47,0:03:27.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这两个人的话自相矛盾\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The two men are contradicting each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.85,0:03:29.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,绝对和赛伊德·阿里有关联\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's definitely a tie to Syed Ali.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:30.10,0:03:32.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,越来越觉得阿里是这次事件的核心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Looks more and more like Ali is at the centre of this thing.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.64,0:03:35.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只希望这一切能让我们快点找到核弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just hope all this brings us closer to finding the nuke.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:35.45,0:03:38.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我能对他施加多大的压力  -随便你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Just tell me how hard I can push him. - Hard as you have to.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.44,0:03:40.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,指甲里插竹签\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stick bamboo shoots under their fingernails.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.31,0:03:42.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,得到他们所知道的  时间不多了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get what they got. Time's running out.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.45,0:03:48.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\fad(359,265)\pos(196.2,194.953)}西北战区行动中心
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.89,0:03:50.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,打给联调局的亨德森\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Call Henderson at FBI.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:50.25,0:03:53.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,安排一次他和司法部长的电话会议\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Set up a conference call with him and the Attorney General.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.33,0:03:59.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-林恩  有空吗  -当然  罗杰\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Lynne. You have a sec? - Sure, Roger.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.88,0:04:07.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道雪莉·帕尔默\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I understand that Sherry Palmer
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.09,0:04:09.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,得到了临时安全权限\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}has been given provisional security clearance.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.96,0:04:14.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  没错  总统行使了行政特权\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, that's right. The president has invoked executive privilege.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:14.11,0:04:15.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你没意见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You OK with that?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.13,0:04:21.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-今时不同往日了  -是  没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It's different. - Yes, it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:22.01,0:04:24.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我已经考虑过了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, you know I've weighed in about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:24.18,0:04:25.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我觉得她成为一个问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And if I feel that she's becoming a problem,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.79,0:04:27.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我会告诉总统的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll let the president know.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.78,0:04:32.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她是他的前妻  这本身就是个问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's his ex-wife. That's a problem all by itself.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.40,0:04:35.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  桑德拉  谢谢  我再打给你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. Sandra, thank you. I'll get back with you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:35.52,0:04:36.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好的  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- All right. - OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.99,0:04:51.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-和我说说罗恩·维兰德  -说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Tell me about Ron Wieland. - What about him?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.18,0:04:56.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我刚和广播公司的桑德拉·伊万尼通过电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just got off the phone with Sandra Ivany at the network.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.79,0:04:58.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她说自从他今早见过你后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She said no one's heard from him
Dialogue: 0,0:04:58.20,0:05:00.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就再没他的消息了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}since he met with you this morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.18,0:05:08.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大卫  你没有拘留他吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}David? You didn't detain him, did you?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.61,0:05:12.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你今天是来帮我的  不是来质疑我的判断\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You are here today to help me, not question my judgment.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.21,0:05:14.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在尽力帮忙呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I am trying to help.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.06,0:05:17.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,维兰德出什么事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's going on with Wieland?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.94,0:05:21.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他本来要公开散布谣言  -关于炸弹的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- He was going to go public with a rumour. - About the bomb?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.97,0:05:24.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不能允许公众恐慌发生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I cannot afford a panic.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:25.96,0:05:29.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你也不能无限期地关押他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You... you can't keep him locked up indefinitely.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.65,0:05:32.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,人们已经开始起疑了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}People are already starting to ask questions.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:32.18,0:05:34.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们把他关在指挥中心了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're holding him at the OC.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.29,0:05:36.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,危机结束后  我会放他走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When the crisis passes, I'll let him go.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:36.41,0:05:39.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,与此同时  你就有麻烦了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, meanwhile you've got a problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:39.25,0:05:42.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他的失踪会引出你不想回答的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}His disappearance could raise questions you don't want to answer.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.74,0:05:46.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我让阿莫斯来解决  -显然并没有帮助\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I put Armus on it. - Apparently it hasn't helped.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.42,0:05:50.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-现在流言四起  -你有什么建议\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- The word is getting out. - What do you suggest?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.60,0:05:55.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,事情结束后让他做单独采访\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Give him an on-air exclusive when this is over.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.64,0:05:58.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我和他提过  他不接收\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I offered that to him. He didn't want it.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.60,0:06:01.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那让我和他说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then let me talk to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.44,0:06:06.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大卫  你知道我的特长就是和媒体打交道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}David, one talent you know I have is dealing with the media.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.40,0:06:09.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而且我了解罗恩  他喜欢我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I know Ron. He likes me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:13.07,0:06:15.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  你是来这里收集信息的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. You're here to gather information.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.41,0:06:18.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是为了帮忙  你自己也这么说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And to help. You said so yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.33,0:06:20.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如今你不能再忽略这一点了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And today you can't afford to ignore that.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.42,0:06:24.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我试着和罗恩谈谈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me try talking to Ron.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.17,0:06:30.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你会和他说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What would you say to him?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.84,0:06:36.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会确保他什么都不说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll make it worth his while not to say anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.93,0:06:42.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-金  我很害怕  -没事的  梅根\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Kim, I'm scared! - It's OK, Megan.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.10,0:06:45.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你会没事的  会没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're gonna be OK. It's gonna be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.94,0:06:49.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要带她去哪里  她不能回洛杉矶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where are you taking her? She can't go back to LA.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.34,0:06:52.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-为什么不能  -不安全\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Why not? - It's not safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.24,0:06:59.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么不告诉他  -爸爸说不能告诉任何人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Why didn't you tell him? - My dad said not to tell anyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.87,0:07:02.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他不知道你会被指控谋杀\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He didn't know you'd be charged with murder.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.50,0:07:04.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我要告诉他  金  -不行  别说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'm gonna tell him, Kim. - No. You can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.76,0:07:08.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听我说  米格尔  我爸说不能让别人知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm telling you, Miguel, my dad said no one can know about this.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.81,0:07:10.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得你该告诉他你爸爸是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think you should tell him who your dad is.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.71,0:07:12.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让他们打电话给他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let them call him.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.96,0:07:15.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让你爸爸解释我们想要离开城市的原因\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let your dad explain why we're trying to get out of town.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:17.39,0:07:19.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,过来  走吧  过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, let's go. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:38.20,0:07:40.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  我爸在反恐组工作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen, my father works at CTU,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.50,0:07:42.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天早上发生爆炸的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the place that got bombed this morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:42.30,0:07:44.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他的名字是杰克·鲍尔  给他打电话吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}His name is Jack Bauer. Please call him.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:44.58,0:07:47.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他会解释为什么今天留在洛杉矶不安全\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He'll explain why it's not safe to be in LA today.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:48.35,0:07:50.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等你被处理后可以给你爸爸打电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You can call your father after you've been processed.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:50.31,0:07:51.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,明白吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.12,0:07:56.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\fad(359,265)\pos(195,239.753)}加利福尼亚  维塞利亚
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.47,0:08:03.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"你在洛杉矶和谁合作"\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Who are you working with in LA?"
Dialogue: 0,0:08:09.65,0:08:13.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"我不会告诉你任何信息的"\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"I'm not going to give you any information."
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.21,0:08:27.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"法海因说  太晚了  别浪费时间了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"It's too late. Don't waste your time.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:27.95,0:08:29.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行动势在必得"\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The operation will be done."
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.53,0:08:32.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这行不通  -行得通\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- This is not working. - It will work.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:32.01,0:08:34.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我只是需要一点时间  -不  到此为止\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I just need a little more time. - No, you're done.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:34.96,0:08:37.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-杰克  别这样  -站起来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Jack, don't do this! - On your feet.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:37.91,0:08:40.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-玩得愉快  我们要回去了  -他说了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Happy playing, we're going back. - Did he talk?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:40.17,0:08:42.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没有  他不和她谈  -我们要怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- No, he wouldn't talk to her. - What we gonna do?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.71,0:08:45.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让分局准备一间审讯室  我们在洛杉矶处理\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Have Division set up a white room. We'll handle it in LA.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.99,0:08:47.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  错误的决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, wrong move.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:47.16,0:08:48.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你越是带他深入系统内部\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The deeper you bring him into the system,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:48.32,0:08:50.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他就会越封闭自己\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the more he's gonna shut down.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:50.00,0:08:53.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-到时就知道了  -里克  再给我点时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- We'll see. - Rick, give me more time with him!
Dialogue: 0,0:08:53.07,0:08:56.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给你时间够多了  确保把法海因弄到机场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You've had enough time. Make sure Faheen gets to the airport.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:56.20,0:08:58.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你呢  -我随后就到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- And you? - I'll be right behind you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:58.57,0:09:00.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等  你明白他要做什么  他不需要我了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wait. You see what he's doing? He doesn't need me any more.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:00.75,0:09:02.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克你不能带她走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, you can't take her.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:02.16,0:09:05.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我有总统签署的文件  他不能这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have a document signed by the president! He can't do this!
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.34,0:09:06.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  我不能这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, I can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:06.22,0:09:07.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的任务是守着你和她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My order is to stay with you and her.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:07.19,0:09:09.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别管你的任务了  他们只要法海因\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Forget your orders. All they need is Faheen.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:09.83,0:09:12.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别任性  杰克  我不能让你单独和她一起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't push this, Jack. I can't leave you alone with her.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:12.58,0:09:14.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这事跟你没关系  里克  别插手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's got nothing to do with you, Rick. Back off.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:14.86,0:09:16.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,离开车子  鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Step away from the car, Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:40.99,0:09:43.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,保罗·柯普林  幸会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Paul Koplin. Nice to meet you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.13,0:09:44.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你能来  请进\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hi. Thanks for coming. Come in.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.66,0:09:47.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别客气  我跟拉尔夫谈过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No problem. I spoke to Ralph,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.39,0:09:49.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他跟我说要查阅一些什么文件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}he told me what files we're going to have to get into.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:49.71,0:09:51.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把雷扎和恐怖分子关联起来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The ones that linked Reza to this terrorist?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.96,0:09:53.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  就是赛伊德·阿里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes. That's Syed Ali.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:54.38,0:09:57.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,公司的电脑跟这房子里的网络相连\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The company computer is networked into this house.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:57.55,0:09:59.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要黑几个密码\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll have to hack some passwords.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.55,0:10:01.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,希望能得到你的允许\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I assume you're authorising me to do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:02.18,0:10:05.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好的  当然  -是这个吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yeah. Yeah, of course. - Is this it?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.93,0:10:08.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道他们为什么在我妹妹结婚这天\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know why they dragged my family in
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.58,0:10:11.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把我们一家搅进来盘问\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}for questioning on my sister's wedding day.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.11,0:10:12.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这一点我也有点吃惊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm a little surprised about that, too,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:12.78,0:10:15.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是现在的世界完全不一样了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but it's a whole new world out there now.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.47,0:10:22.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对于所出的事情我很遗憾\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry about what happened,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:22.76,0:10:26.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是作为私人调查员  法律要求我们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but as private investigators we're required by law
Dialogue: 0,0:10:26.12,0:10:29.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要立刻向国安局汇报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to report any terrorist-related information
Dialogue: 0,0:10:29.33,0:10:31.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所有与恐怖分子相关的信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to Homeland Security right off.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:34.21,0:10:38.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是这样的  我能进入月结账单\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here it is. I was able to accessed the monthly statements
Dialogue: 0,0:10:38.20,0:10:40.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是没法查看具体账目\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I couldn't get into any detailed records.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:40.28,0:10:43.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  看看我们能做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. Let's see what we can do.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:55.52,0:10:58.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿莫斯  你要去哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Armus? Where are you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:58.69,0:11:01.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要带帕尔默夫人去会议室\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm taking Mrs. Palmer to one of the conference rooms.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.32,0:11:04.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-她有权限吗  -不好意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Does she have clearance? - Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.79,0:11:07.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们谈论我的时候\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But you don't need to speak about me
Dialogue: 0,0:11:07.36,0:11:08.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不用把我当空气  斯坦顿先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}as if I weren't here, Mr. Stanton.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.74,0:11:11.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  帕尔默夫人  我是罗杰·斯坦顿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry, Mrs. Palmer. Roger Stanton.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.09,0:11:13.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我认识你  罗杰\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know who you are, Roger.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:13.88,0:11:16.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只不过这是高级禁区\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's just a highly restricted area.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:16.92,0:11:20.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道  不过  我得到许可了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, I know. However, I have been granted access.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:21.26,0:11:22.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,您为何要到这里来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why do you need to be here?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:23.08,0:11:25.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你就该问总统了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That you'll have to ask the president.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:25.68,0:11:27.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-阿莫斯  -失陪了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Armus. - Excuse me.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:29.06,0:11:30.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  帕尔默夫人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My apologies, Mrs. Palmer.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.56,0:11:36.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们对今天的信息流非常谨慎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's just we're very careful about the flow of information today.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:36.20,0:11:38.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不用道歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's no need to apologise.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:38.26,0:11:39.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在我看来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I would assume that you're careful
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.79,0:11:43.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们对每天的信息流都很谨慎\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}about the flow of information every day.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:45.41,0:11:46.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.46,0:11:59.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-雪莉·帕尔默  -你好  罗恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Sherry Palmer. - Hello, Ron.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.46,0:12:02.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还以为今天的意外也不过如此了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just when I thought this day couldn't get any stranger.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:03.51,0:12:06.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我能想象你对此事并不满意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can imagine you're not happy about all of this.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.71,0:12:08.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想知道你说的"此事"是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'd like to know what "This" Is.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.54,0:12:11.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我自己也不太清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't exactly know myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.77,0:12:14.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不信你  雪莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't believe you, Sherry.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:15.69,0:12:19.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,除非他们杀了我  不然我会成为年度头条的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But unless they kill me I'm gonna have the story of the year.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:20.07,0:12:22.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我竟然被自由世界的领袖绑架了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was kidnapped by the leader of the free world.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.77,0:12:25.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,事实并非如此  罗恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's not necessarily true, Ron.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.70,0:12:27.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这种动用特权的行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There actually has been precedent
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.02,0:12:29.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,以前也是有先例的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}for this kind of executive action.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:30.24,0:12:33.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你是来让我闭嘴的  恐怕你白费时间了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you're here to try to shut me up, you're wasting your time.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.83,0:12:34.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道自己查到了一些事情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I sensed I was onto something.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:34.99,0:12:37.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而他们把我关起的事实恰恰证实了这点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The fact that they locked me in here only confirms it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:39.25,0:12:42.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我从这走出去的时候会有新闻的  接招吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm coming out of here with a story. Deal with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.72,0:12:51.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-介意我坐下吗  -当然不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Mind if I sit down? - Of course not.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.69,0:13:01.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们愿意释放你  罗恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'd like to release you, Ron.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.23,0:13:03.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们也会这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And we will.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.49,0:13:05.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是我们需要你保证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But we need assurances you won't go public
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.83,0:13:09.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不会将你此前威胁着要散播的谣言公布出去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}with the rumour you threatened to broadcast.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.66,0:13:11.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拿什么交换呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In return for what?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.68,0:13:15.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我能拿到总统毫无干货的独家报道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I get an exclusive with the president on some watered-down story?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.25,0:13:19.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是毫无干货的  而是别的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not a watered-down story. Something else.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.58,0:13:25.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你站出来  让所有人知道你并没有失踪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You go out there, let everyone know that you are not missing.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:25.80,0:13:28.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,绝口不提今早发生的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't say anything about this morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:30.89,0:13:35.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统会让你进入指挥中心报道第一手消息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The president will let you inside of the OC to report first-hand.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.98,0:13:38.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,从来没有记者进去过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No journalist has ever been inside there.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.32,0:13:46.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么他派你来谈这个交易  雪莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why did he send you down here to make this offer, Sherry?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.54,0:13:47.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,事实上  你回到大卫·帕尔默\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In fact, what are you even doing
Dialogue: 0,0:13:47.78,0:13:50.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,小圈子里做什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}back inside David Palmer's circle?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:51.82,0:13:53.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,接受这个交易吧  罗恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Take the deal, Ron.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.33,0:13:58.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,几小时之后  他们会把情况告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In a couple of hours they'll brief you
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.13,0:14:01.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,到时候你知道的就比我多了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and then you'll know more than I do.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.83,0:14:19.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an2\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs15\bord0\shad2\b1\pos(190.8,239.2)}大家都准备好了
Dialogue: 0,0:14:19.33,0:14:22.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an2\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs15\bord0\shad2\b1\pos(192.6,212.8)}他们就等着我们送炸弹了
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.38,0:15:04.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an2\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs15\bord0\shad2\b1\pos(190.2,237.6)}把手在哪儿
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.05,0:15:06.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an2\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs15\bord0\shad2\b1\pos(190.8,239.2)}没有把手
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.44,0:15:12.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,伙计们  需要帮忙吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey! Guys, you need some help?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.91,0:15:16.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,需要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:35.09,0:15:38.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"逃脱的唯一方法就是跟他们合作"\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"The only way out of this is to cooperate with them."
Dialogue: 0,0:15:43.59,0:15:47.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"马穆  死在这对你的行动没有任何好处"\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Mamud, it does your case no good if you end up dead."
Dialogue: 0,0:15:51.57,0:15:54.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"想想吧  马穆  我们正在赶往洛杉矶"\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"Think about it, Mamud. We're on our way to Los Angeles."
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.04,0:16:03.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"我不怕死"\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"I'm not afraid to die."
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.74,0:16:43.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"这个炸弹的规模有多大"\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"How big is the bomb?"
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.38,0:16:50.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"准备什么时间引爆"\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"What time is it supposed to go off?"
Dialogue: 0,0:16:59.55,0:17:04.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,"你背叛了我  背叛了我们  叛徒"\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"You betrayed me. You betrayed us all. Traitor."
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.10,0:17:06.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把她带过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bring her back here now.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:13.28,0:17:14.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:20.16,0:17:21.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尼娜  我们没时间了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nina. We are out of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.74,0:17:24.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要是想活命  就得跟我说实话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you want to live through this, you gonna be straight with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.67,0:17:28.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这事什么时候策划的  -我被捕前六个月\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- When was this planned? - Six months before I was arrested.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:28.48,0:17:31.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-法海因找你的  -是的  通过中间人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- And Faheen approached you? - Yes, but through an intermediary.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.34,0:17:34.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他没跟你说核武器  -不  我跟你说了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- He didn't tell you about the nuke? - No. I told you.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.22,0:17:36.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道结局是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I didn't know what the endgame was.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.04,0:17:38.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只知道有大事情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just knew it was something big.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.51,0:17:42.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-突破法海因还有别的办法吗  -没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Is there another way around Faheen? - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.06,0:17:48.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他真的愿意送死吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is he really willing to die?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:51.10,0:17:52.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.58,0:18:08.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  我们怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, what are we gonna do?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.76,0:18:20.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,带她回去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Take her back.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.46,0:18:50.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别用那个备胎开太远的路\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wouldn't drive too long on that spare.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:50.95,0:18:52.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,上面没有多少胎纹了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's not a lot of tread left.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:53.13,0:18:55.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  非常感谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes. Thank you very much, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.35,0:18:58.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,跟我一起去文图拉大道吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why not follow me to Ventura Boulevard?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:58.98,0:19:02.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那有个轮胎店  -不用  没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- There's a tire store there. - No, no, no. We'll be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.44,0:19:04.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  都修好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. You're all set.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:06.17,0:19:08.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-请收下  -不用客气\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Here. Please. - Don't worry about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.74,0:19:11.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要是有人需要泳池服务的话  把我名片给他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know anybody who needs pool service, give 'em my card.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.85,0:19:12.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我服务整个谷地\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I work the whole valley, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.84,0:19:14.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course, of course.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:14.76,0:19:16.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-谢谢  谢谢先生  -再见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Thank you. Thank you, sir. - See ya!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:26.33,0:19:28.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个孩子说什么有危险\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The kid said something about danger
Dialogue: 0,0:19:28.23,0:19:30.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要离洛杉矶远一点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and need to stay out of Los Angeles.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.14,0:19:33.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个也说了类似的  但没说细节\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This one told me a similar story. Didn't go any detail, though.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.51,0:19:36.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你觉得是真的吗  -不  我不认为\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Do you think it's true? - No. I don't think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.63,0:19:38.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那是什么  -他们就是编故事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What, then? - They're telling stories.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.66,0:19:41.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-需要我汇报吗  -等我们回去再说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Want me to call it in? - Listen. Wait until we get back, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:41.43,0:19:43.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-回头见  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'll see you there. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.97,0:19:50.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你朋友还挺有想象力的  -他说什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Your friend's got quite an imagination. - What did he say?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:50.67,0:19:51.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们今天逃跑的原因\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The reason that you were leaving town
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.94,0:19:55.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是因为洛杉矶有炸弹要爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}because some bomb's supposed to go off in LA today.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.15,0:20:00.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你说不安全的时候是说这件事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So what you were talking back there when you said it wasn't safe?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:00.91,0:20:04.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托  请给反恐组打电话  跟我爸联系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please, just call CTU and try and reach my dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:04.36,0:20:05.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们得带着梅根\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You need to get Megan,
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.31,0:20:08.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,跟我们一起的那个小姑娘  让她远离城市\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the girl that was with us. Keep her out of the city.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:19.71,0:20:21.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,洛杉矶分局  我是621\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}LA Dispatch, this is 621.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:21.60,0:20:24.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请帮我接通当地联调局的弗兰克·里德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Put me through to Frank Reed over at FBI Local.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:24.24,0:20:26.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,621  我已经有45分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}621. I've been unable to reach anyone
Dialogue: 0,0:20:26.59,0:20:28.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,无法联系上联调局的人了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}at the FBI for the last 45 minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:28.97,0:20:30.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,无法联系  为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Unable to reach them? Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:30.89,0:20:33.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,由于某些原因他们线路繁忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lot of traffic on their lines for some reason.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:34.82,0:20:37.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,继续联络  接通之后给我打个电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. Just keep trying. Give me a call when you get through.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:37.73,0:20:38.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,收到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Copy that.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.37,0:20:43.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What the hell is going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.22,0:21:00.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-维兰德那边什么情况  -他不肯配合\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How did it go with Wieland? - He's not gonna play ball.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:00.46,0:21:02.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他觉得自己占了上风\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He thinks he's got the upper hand.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.23,0:21:05.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他知道我们最终还是得放他走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He knows we have to let him go eventually.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:05.80,0:21:07.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不论这事是否有合法先例\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Whether there's a legal precedent for this or not,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:07.53,0:21:09.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他已经手握重大新闻了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}he has got one hell of a story.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.93,0:21:12.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很抱歉  大卫  我以为我能说服他的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm so sorry, David. I thought I could charm him.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:15.10,0:21:17.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了  雪莉  就这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, Sherry. That'll be all.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.11,0:21:25.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大卫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}David?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:27.41,0:21:29.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你为什么要这样对我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why are you treating me like this?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.87,0:21:31.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是你的原因  雪莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's not about you, Sherry.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:32.36,0:21:34.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我现在有更重要的事情办\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just have more important things to deal with right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:39.71,0:21:40.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:41.29,0:21:43.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你总是能原谅别人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you've always been able to forgive.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.77,0:21:49.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总是能给别人第二次机会  但对我不是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Always given everyone a second chance, but not me.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.23,0:22:01.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我今天来是为了告诉你  你是对的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I came here today to tell you that you were right.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:03.19,0:22:05.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把我赶出竞选团队是对的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right to kick me off the campaign,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:07.32,0:22:09.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,提出离婚也是对的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}right to file for divorce.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:11.70,0:22:13.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where's all this coming from?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.45,0:22:21.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在其他地方感受到了诚信和个人价值\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A place of honesty, of realisation.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.25,0:22:25.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我以前太受困于权力了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was too caught up in the power.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.59,0:22:29.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-现在不是吗  -当然  你知道我爱权力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- And you're not now? - Of course. You know I love it.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:30.43,0:22:34.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但现在我明白哪些我能胜任  哪些不能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But now I am aware of what I can and can't handle.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.56,0:22:37.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以你还要什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So what are you asking for?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.27,0:22:44.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我帮你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.86,0:22:49.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我给你的信息有用\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If what I bring to you can be useful,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.57,0:22:53.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你就能再次开始培养对我的信心了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}then you can consider it the start of a new confidence.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.24,0:22:59.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行  但我保证不会给你任何回报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. But I promise you absolutely nothing in return.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:01.67,0:23:02.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.77,0:23:42.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an2\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs15\bord0\shad2\b1\pos(190.8,239.2)}我不想这么做
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.73,0:23:45.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an2\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs15\bord0\shad2\b1\pos(190.8,239.2)}我不想杀人
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.86,0:23:47.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an2\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs15\bord0\shad2\b1\pos(190.8,239.2)}做好你的工作
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.78,0:23:49.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an2\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs15\bord0\shad2\b1\pos(188.4,238.4)}不
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.19,0:24:54.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些是交易记录\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, there are the transaction records.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.97,0:24:56.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,23号那一周\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}On the week of the 23rd,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.65,0:24:58.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雷扎从公司的委托账户中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Reza made four withdrawals
Dialogue: 0,0:24:58.56,0:25:01.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,取了四次钱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}from the company's discretionary account.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:02.41,0:25:06.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,17.5万  15万  5万  又是5万\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}$175,000, $150,000, $50,000, another $50,000...
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.87,0:25:09.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-总共接近五十万美元了  -是啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- That's almost a half a million dollars. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:09.92,0:25:12.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他把钱用在哪里了  -看吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What did he do with the money? - Let's see.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:14.55,0:25:15.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他给赛伊德·阿里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He wrote a check to Syed Ali
Dialogue: 0,0:25:15.72,0:25:17.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,开了一张47.5万美元的支票\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}for $475,000
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.77,0:25:20.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,作为"咨询服务"的回报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}in return for "Consulting services."
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.72,0:25:23.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后呢  也许他们是在做生意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So what? Maybe they were doing business.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.27,0:25:27.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,赛伊德·阿里专门给恐怖分子提供资金\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Syed Ali's only business is bankrolling terrorists.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.74,0:25:31.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我的父亲呢  他跟这件事有什么关系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about my father? What's his connection to all this?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:32.54,0:25:36.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雷扎让反恐局相信这些交易是你父亲授权的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Reza convinced CTU that your father authorised these transactions,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.15,0:25:39.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,或者确实是他自己做的  我推测\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}or maybe he just did them on his own. I'm speculating.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.04,0:25:41.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我父亲和恐怖主义无关\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My father is not involved in terrorism.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.92,0:25:43.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是政府弄错了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The government made a mistake.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.16,0:25:46.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们得想办法证明他的清白\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have to find it and clear him.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:48.92,0:25:53.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我试一下看能不能黑进他的个人日历\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. Let's try and get into his personal calendar.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:53.25,0:25:56.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看看他那几天做了些什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's see what he did the days the checks were written.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:56.30,0:25:57.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.18,0:25:59.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:59.30,0:26:01.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是你父亲那周的行程表\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here's your father's schedule for that week.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:06.56,0:26:09.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么都没有  -当然没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Nothing here, either. - Of course not.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.77,0:26:12.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我父亲和这些事没关系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My father has nothing to do with any of this.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:12.36,0:26:14.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对不起  保罗  我不该找你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry, Paul, I shouldn't have called you.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:14.63,0:26:15.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这就是浪费时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is a waste of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:15.61,0:26:17.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-等等  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Wait a minute. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:19.20,0:26:21.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他的通讯录里有个文件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's a file here in his personal directory
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.77,0:26:23.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,几乎每天都访问\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that's accessed almost daily.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:23.52,0:26:27.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,上面有个资源表  这说明这是政府文件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It has a resource tab on it, which means it's a government file.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:28.37,0:26:30.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我父亲有些政府的客户  -哇噢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- My dad has government clients. - Whoa!
Dialogue: 0,0:26:31.88,0:26:34.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么  -这是个自动删除的程序\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What? - It's an auto-delete program.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:34.16,0:26:36.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你有什么办法吗  -我正在尝试\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Can't you do something? - Yeah, I'm trying.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.51,0:26:42.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这不可能是真的  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- This can't be right. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:42.13,0:26:45.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些数据都连了卫星网\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The data on this volume has a comsat grid.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:45.81,0:26:48.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些都是地址  CSG14877\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You see, these are addresses. CSG14877.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:48.52,0:26:50.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是一个编了码的坐标\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's an encoded coordinate.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.98,0:26:52.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不明白是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know what you're getting at.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.11,0:26:55.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只有拥有政府的安全权限的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The only people who have files like these
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.23,0:26:57.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,才有可能掌控这些文件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}have government security clearance.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.57,0:27:03.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-为什么我父亲会有  -我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Why would my dad have that? - I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.89,0:27:12.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么我得一直在这里等\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why have I been kept waiting here like this?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:12.92,0:27:14.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请坐下  华纳先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sit down, please, Mr. Warner.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:14.46,0:27:17.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我有一些信息  -坐下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I have some information. - Sit down!
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.11,0:27:36.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有些什么信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What information do you have?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:38.32,0:27:41.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我本不能向任何人提起的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not supposed to talk to anybody about this,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:41.36,0:27:43.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但在这种情况下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but under the circumstances...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:44.57,0:27:52.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是中央情报局的情报员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I am a consultant for the CIA.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:55.29,0:27:57.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里有我的联络编码\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's the contact code for my liaison.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.66,0:27:59.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,打给中情局  他们会证实的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Call Langley, they'll verify.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.22,0:28:09.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在家里怎么不告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why didn't you tell me this at the house?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:09.10,0:28:12.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,少来了  你知道的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on. You know the drill.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:13.06,0:28:16.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,未经允许我不能和任何人提起这件事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not supposed to talk to anyone about this without clearance.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.11,0:28:19.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的I-3协议是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's your I-3 protocol?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:21.04,0:28:24.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为我在全球范围内的投资\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was approached about five years ago
Dialogue: 0,0:28:24.34,0:28:26.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们五年前找到了我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}because of my international investment work.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.37,0:28:33.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,问我是否愿意帮助国家  我说没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They asked me if I'd like to help my country and I said OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.54,0:28:37.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你做些什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you do?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:38.54,0:28:42.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,利用我的公司\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My corporation is used as a conduit
Dialogue: 0,0:28:43.26,0:28:45.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来前后传递消息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to pass information back and forth.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:46.34,0:28:49.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-给谁  -我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- To whom? - I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:53.81,0:28:55.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这就是事实\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That is the truth.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.23,0:28:58.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你给我听好  阿尔梅达先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now you listen to me, Mr. Almeida.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:59.44,0:29:02.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不是这个国家的敌人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I am not an enemy of this country.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.11,0:29:05.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是爱国者  我爱我的国家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I am a patriot. I love my country.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.86,0:29:08.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不认识什么赛伊德·阿里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know any Syed Ali,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.93,0:29:12.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也不知道为什么有我和他做生意的记录\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}nor why there is a record of me doing business with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:13.68,0:29:14.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.37,0:29:18.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果是真的你就没有什么好担心的  不是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}if that's true then you have nothing to worry about, do you?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:19.00,0:29:22.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但你的公司的确和赛伊德·阿里有关联\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But there is a connection between your company and Syed Ali.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:22.84,0:29:24.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会找出到底是什么的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I'm gonna find out what it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.18,0:29:32.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在请你坐好了  我去核实一下这个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So in the meantime, sit tight. I'm gonna check this out.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.68,0:29:44.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-金柏莉·鲍尔  -我们找杰克·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Kimberly Bauer? - Yes. We need to speak with his father Jack Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:44.49,0:29:46.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他现在不在这里  有什么事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's not here right now. What's this about?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.75,0:29:47.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她女儿被拘留了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have his daughter in custody.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.81,0:29:50.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们需要立刻联系他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's important that we speak to him immediately.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.64,0:29:53.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别挂  劳丽  我需要你给楼下打电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hold on. OK. Laurie, I need you to call downstairs...
Dialogue: 0,0:29:53.71,0:29:56.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治  鲍勃·华纳刚刚告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George, Bob Warner just told me
Dialogue: 0,0:29:56.77,0:29:58.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他是中情局的情报员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}he does deliveries for the CIA.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.32,0:30:01.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,中情局  你核实了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}CIA? Did you check it out?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:01.79,0:30:03.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有  我准备去核实\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. I was about to call his liaison,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:03.18,0:30:06.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但看起来他的联络编码是真的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but it looks like he's got a legitimate contact code.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:12.51,0:30:15.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果是真的  那就是雷扎在骗我们了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If that is the case, then Reza's lying to us.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:15.70,0:30:17.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道  我给了雷扎不少压力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know. I pushed Reza pretty hard.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:18.35,0:30:19.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得他说的是真的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think he's telling the truth.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:20.73,0:30:23.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们今天要再多给点压力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have to push harder than usual today.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.03,0:30:26.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,继续调查  看看能发现什么  记得告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So dig in and see what you can find out. Let me know.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:26.11,0:30:28.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅森先生  是纽霍尔的警长\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Mason? It's the sheriff in Newhall.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:28.77,0:30:30.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们拘留了金·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're holding Kim Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.02,0:30:32.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-为什么  -她被指控谋杀\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Why? - She's been charged with murder.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:32.33,0:30:33.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,打给杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Call Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.58,0:30:37.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是乔治·梅森  你是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is George Mason. Who am I speaking to?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:45.90,0:30:46.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:46.44,0:30:48.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-杰克  我是米歇尔  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Jack, it's Michelle. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:49.01,0:30:51.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道怎么跟你说  但是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen, I don't know how to tell you this but,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:51.50,0:30:53.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们和纽霍尔的警长通过话了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we're on the line with the sheriff in Newhall.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:53.32,0:30:55.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他们拘留了你女儿金  -为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- They're holding your daughter Kim. - Holding her for what?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:55.81,0:30:58.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她被指控犯罪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's being held on some criminal charges.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:59.22,0:31:00.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you talking about?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:00.89,0:31:02.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她在线上  需要我给你接通吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have her on the second line. Should I patch her through?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:02.78,0:31:04.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  叫梅森也接电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes. Get Mason on this now.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:04.50,0:31:07.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们正在处理这件事  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm on with the precinct Jack. We're working on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:07.09,0:31:08.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治  真的  绝对是弄错了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George, honestly, there's some kind of mistake.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:08.52,0:31:11.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你帮我摆平这件事  让金离开洛杉矶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need you to straighten it out and get Kim out of LA.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:11.79,0:31:13.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我会处理好的  -爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'll take care of it. - Daddy?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:13.93,0:31:15.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金  怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kim, what happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.45,0:31:17.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我正准备离开这座城市的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was leaving the city, like you said.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.26,0:31:19.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我跟梅根和我男朋友米格尔一起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was with Megan and my boyfriend, Miguel.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:19.65,0:31:21.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,加州高速警察以超速逮捕了我们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And the CHP pulled us over for speeding.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:24.13,0:31:27.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们在车里发现了一具尸体  卡拉的尸体\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They found a body in the trunk. Carla's body.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:28.45,0:31:30.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-卡拉  你的老板吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Carla? The woman you work for? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:31.52,0:31:33.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们开的她丈夫的车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We took her husband's car.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:33.57,0:31:36.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一定是他干的  然后把尸体丢在了车里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He must've done it this morning and put the body in the trunk.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:36.59,0:31:38.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天啊  帮帮我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, my God, help me.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:38.28,0:31:40.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事的  我们会救你出来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just relax, we're gonna straighten this out.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:40.87,0:31:43.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他打她  所以我才带梅根走的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He beat her up. That's why I needed to take Megan.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:43.57,0:31:44.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他也打了梅根\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He was hurting her, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:45.24,0:31:48.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反恐局会派人来的  他们会马上救你出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}CTU will send someone. They'll get you out of there now.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:49.49,0:31:51.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不要他们派别人来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't want them to send someone else.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:52.74,0:31:55.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要你帮我  这都不行吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you to help me. Can't you do that?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:56.51,0:31:59.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们认为我杀了卡拉  爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They think I killed Carla, Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:03.63,0:32:07.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸  我现在需要你来这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Dad, I need you here now.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.02,0:32:08.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亲爱的  等一会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sweetheart, hold on for one second.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:08.14,0:32:09.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔  你还在吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle, are you on the line?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.27,0:32:11.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-在  -法海因现在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yeah. - What is Faheen saying now?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:11.84,0:32:15.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尼娜告诉他美国军队已经被派去他的村子了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nina told him that US forces have been sent to his village,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.67,0:32:18.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们正在找他的家人和表亲们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that they're rounding up his family, his cousins.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:18.71,0:32:20.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-法海因不相信她  说她是骗子  -爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Faheen didn't believe her and called her a liar. - Dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:20.97,0:32:21.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金  等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kim, hold on.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:29.70,0:32:32.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她刚和法海因说她有能力救他们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She just told Faheen that she has the power to save them.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.99,0:32:37.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-爸  -金  等等  他们现在在说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Dad? - Kim, hold on. What are they saying now?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:43.14,0:32:44.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们接收不到  音频太小声\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We can't pick it up. The audio's too low.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:45.28,0:32:47.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-爸  你在听吗  -亲爱的  我还在听\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Dad, are you there? - Yeah. Sweet heart, I'm still here.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.67,0:32:49.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治  我需要你现在去帮金\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George, I need you to help Kim now.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:49.58,0:32:51.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你要越过地方当局  就去做吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you have to supersede local authority, do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.34,0:32:53.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-只要把她带离洛杉矶就行了  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Just get her out of LA. - Done.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.26,0:32:57.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尼娜  他和你说了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nina, what did he tell you?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.34,0:33:02.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所有的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:02.85,0:33:06.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不  她划破了他的喉咙  -喂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- No! She just slit his throat! - Hello?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:07.31,0:33:08.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我抓住她了  让他躺在地上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got her! Get him on the floor!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:08.81,0:33:09.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,出什么事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:09.67,0:33:11.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让他躺在地上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get him on the floor!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.29,0:33:12.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,发生了什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's happening?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.79,0:33:16.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,止不了血\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can't stop this.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:17.99,0:33:19.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Dad!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:20.17,0:33:21.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你救得了他吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You got him?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:22.41,0:33:23.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,救不了了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're losing him.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.71,0:33:25.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-混蛋  -爸  到底出了什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Son of a bitch! - Dad, what's happening?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:27.30,0:33:30.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-杰克  -把她抓起来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Jack... - Secure her!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:30.26,0:33:31.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道炸弹在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know where the bomb is.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:32.57,0:33:34.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把飞机开去圣地亚哥\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Take the plane to San Diego.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:34.72,0:33:37.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,准备民用飞机等着送我去圣保罗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want civilian transport waiting for me to take me to Sao Paolo.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:37.91,0:33:39.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,着陆后  我会把所有的事都告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll tell you everything when we're on the ground.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.72,0:33:42.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-乔治  这些你都听到了吗  -听到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- George, are you getting this? - Yeah, I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:42.47,0:33:44.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他不行了  -现在由你决定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- He's gone! - This is your call.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:44.48,0:33:47.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们没时间了  我不喜欢被人指手画脚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We run out of time. I don't like being dicked around.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:47.61,0:33:50.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们可以把她带去反恐组严刑拷问\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We can bring her into CTU and press her there.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:50.45,0:33:52.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  那样太久了  带她去圣地亚哥吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. It'll take too long. Take her to San Diego.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:52.62,0:33:53.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:54.83,0:33:57.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-叫飞行员开去圣地亚哥  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Tell the pilot to go to San Diego. - You got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:59.75,0:34:01.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,事情现在是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is how this is gonna work.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:01.11,0:34:03.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们一着陆  你告诉我炸弹的下落\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna land, you're gonna tell me where the bomb is.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:03.22,0:34:05.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在有结果之前  我们会扣押你  明白吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna hold you until we get a result, you got that?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:06.59,0:34:07.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,明白\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:25.98,0:34:29.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,长官  我也许在法海因的录音上有所发现\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir? I think I may have found something in the Faheen recordings.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:29.68,0:34:31.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-录音上说什么  -一个名字\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What'd it say? - A name.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:31.95,0:34:34.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,马尔科·哈塔米  你听听\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Marko Khatami. Listen.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.28,0:34:38.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,马尔科·哈塔米\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}...Marko Khatami.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:39.75,0:34:40.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你试过交叉对比吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did you try cross-referencing?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:40.78,0:34:43.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,试过  他和赛伊德·阿里有联系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, he's connected to Syed Ali.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:56.39,0:34:58.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-纳耶尔先生  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Mr. Naiyeer? - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:59.72,0:35:01.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-马尔科·哈塔米是谁  -我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Who's Marko Khatami?! - I have no idea!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:01.99,0:35:02.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who is he?!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:02.50,0:35:03.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,放开他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get off!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:08.48,0:35:11.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-谁来帮帮忙  -你疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Somebody help me. - You're crazy!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:13.70,0:35:17.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你是疯子  -冷静点  冷静点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You're mad! - Just cool it! Cool down!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:19.79,0:35:20.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,放开我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me go.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:28.88,0:35:32.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-要释放我们了吗  -不是  要转移你们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Are we being released? - No. You're being transferred.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:32.92,0:35:34.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-转移去哪  -我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- To where? - I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:34.89,0:35:36.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反恐组的人打来电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Someone from CTU called.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:37.54,0:35:40.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说他们过来接你们  接手这件案子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Said they were coming to pick you up and take over the case.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:40.09,0:35:42.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那梅根呢  你把她带回来这里了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about Megan? You brought her back here, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:43.93,0:35:47.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-她会怎么样  -和你无关\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What's gonna happen to her? - It's none of your business.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:47.90,0:35:50.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不能把她带回洛杉矶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You can't take her back to LA!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:56.57,0:35:57.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You listen to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.95,0:36:02.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我查过你  你父亲的确是在反恐组工作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I checked you out. Your father does work for CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:02.52,0:36:06.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你告诉我  他和你说洛杉矶今天会出什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now you tell me, what did he tell you would happen today in LA?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:06.78,0:36:11.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我什么也不能说  但是你不能带梅根回去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't say anything, but you can't take Megan back.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:11.16,0:36:13.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我到底是怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just tell me what's going on.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:22.26,0:36:23.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是核弹爆炸事件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a nuclear bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:28.56,0:36:29.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们之所以什么也没说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The reason why they didn't say anything
Dialogue: 0,0:36:29.65,0:36:31.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是因为他们不想引起恐慌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}because they don't want to start a panic.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:41.49,0:36:42.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:00.09,0:37:01.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在法海因的录音里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Were you be able to get anything else
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.11,0:37:02.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还听到别的信息吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}off the recording of Faheen?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:02.84,0:37:04.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,99%都是噪音\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's 99% noise.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:07.81,0:37:11.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你没事吧  -只是饿着肚子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You OK? - Just running on empty.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.75,0:37:17.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不如你先去吃点东西吧  -我没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Then why don't you get something to eat? - No, I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:18.67,0:37:20.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的脖子在流血\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your neck's bleeding here.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:23.49,0:37:25.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是别人的血\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's somebody else's blood.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:33.17,0:37:35.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔  不如你先休息一会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle, why don't you take a few minutes,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:35.79,0:37:38.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去清洗一下  换身衣服  那样你会舒服点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}get cleaned up and changed. You'll feel better.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:46.60,0:37:48.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们会熬过今天的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna survive this day.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:50.19,0:37:51.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:53.94,0:37:57.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去吧  换身衣服  去吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, get changed. Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:07.24,0:38:08.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.37,0:38:13.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些是斯坦顿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}These are the updated guidelines
Dialogue: 0,0:38:13.50,0:38:16.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,发给当地执法机关和联调局最新的指导方针\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stanton sent to local law enforcement and the FBI.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.01,0:38:23.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我知道雪莉遇到了斯坦顿  -这我没听说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I understand Sherry ran into Stanton. - I didn't hear that.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:24.26,0:38:26.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他有和你说起她在这里吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Has he said anything to you about her being here?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.64,0:38:31.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得他对此不太高兴\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't think he's very happy about it.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:32.10,0:38:33.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你对她有意见吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you have a problem with her?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:34.31,0:38:35.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道你认为她对你来说用处很大\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know you think she's useful to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:35.91,0:38:37.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我问的不是这个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's not what I asked.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:38.98,0:38:41.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说实话我接受任何我们能得到的帮忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I honestly welcome help wherever we can get it.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:41.96,0:38:44.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你觉得她在这里能起到作用的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you feel she performs a function here, then...
Dialogue: 0,0:38:44.39,0:38:45.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  你最好出来一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, you better come out here.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.70,0:38:46.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么事  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What is it, Mike?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:52.62,0:38:55.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我已经确认国家安全和公众安全\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've confirmed that there is an imminent threat
Dialogue: 0,0:38:55.46,0:38:57.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有一个迫在眉睫的威胁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to national security and public safety.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:58.17,0:39:01.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在我无法确认目标或是袭击的性质\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}While I cannot confirm the target or nature of the attack,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:01.76,0:39:04.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那也许是来自中东的恐怖分子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it may come from Middle Eastern terrorists,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:04.05,0:39:07.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但同时也表明美国大规模的恐怖分子集团\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but it's also indicated that mass terrorists group
Dialogue: 0,0:39:07.23,0:39:09.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-可能也有份参与  -他怎么出去的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- in the US may also be involved. - How did he get out?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:09.93,0:39:12.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,此事件令我感到最不安的是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What I find most troubling about this story
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.57,0:39:15.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们的总统知道此威胁的存在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is that our president knows about this threat
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.19,0:39:17.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,却对公众只字未提\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and isn't saying anything to the public.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:18.15,0:39:21.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-掌控那个房间的人是谁  -阿莫斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Who was controlling that room? - Armus.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:21.69,0:39:23.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我现在就要见他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want to see him now.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:29.20,0:39:31.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样解释不通啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It doesn't make sense.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:31.06,0:39:33.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我父亲真是为政府工作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If my father really does work for the government,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:33.58,0:39:36.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这一点都难以置信\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}which is impossible to believe,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:36.05,0:39:39.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,难道他会不知道雷扎做了犯法的事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}wouldn't he know if Reza did something illegal?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:39.06,0:39:42.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也会这么认为  尤其是涉及到恐怖分子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I would think so, especially if terrorism was involved.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:42.05,0:39:44.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果他真知道雷扎所做的事  那意味着什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And if he did know about Reza, what does that mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:44.84,0:39:47.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我猜如果你父亲知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, my guess is that your father was aware
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.77,0:39:50.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雷扎涉及某些非法活动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that Reza was involved in some kind of illegal activity.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:50.71,0:39:52.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而出于某种原因  他在监视他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And he was monitoring him for some reason.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:52.88,0:39:54.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是这样也解释不通啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But that doesn't make sense either.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:55.44,0:39:58.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我父亲绝对不会让玛丽嫁给他正在调查的人的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My father would not let someone he was investigating marry Marie.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:58.81,0:40:03.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果任何人批评雷扎  他都会不开心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, he got upset if anyone made any critical remark about Reza.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:03.80,0:40:05.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他待他如己出\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He treated him like a son.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:05.96,0:40:09.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我和反恐组的阿尔梅达特工很熟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know Agent Almeida at CTU pretty well.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:09.24,0:40:11.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我给他打个电话  看看我们能否查出...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll give him a call and see if we could find out...
Dialogue: 0,0:40:33.14,0:40:34.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快走  快走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go! Go!
Dialogue: 0,0:40:50.53,0:40:53.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你杀死我妻子的前一个星期\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The Sunday before you killed my wife,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:54.45,0:40:57.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我和特里去了威尼斯海滨路\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Teri and I went down to the boardwalk in Venice.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:58.87,0:41:01.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,观赏那些轮滑爱好者和音乐家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just watching all the rollerbladers and musicians,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:02.64,0:41:04.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嘲笑那些疯狂的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}laughing at the crazy people...
Dialogue: 0,0:41:09.05,0:41:10.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,享受在一起的时光\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just spending time together.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:13.85,0:41:16.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后特里看到一个甜筒摊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And Teri sees this snow-cone stand.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:19.56,0:41:21.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她傻笑得像个小孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She giggles like a kid,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:21.86,0:41:23.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她跑过去想要排队\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}she takes off running and she wants to get in line,
Dialogue: 0,0:41:23.59,0:41:24.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她想吃一个甜筒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}she wants one.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:26.44,0:41:28.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我记得我当时看着她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I remember I was watching her, just...
Dialogue: 0,0:41:31.07,0:41:32.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我无法自拔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I couldn't help myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:34.54,0:41:37.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她当时在和排在她后面的一位老太太聊天\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She was talking with an old lady in line behind her.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:37.50,0:41:39.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她们俩都在笑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The two of them were laughing.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:40.08,0:41:42.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我记得我心想  她是怎么做到的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I remember thinking to myself "How the hell does she do that?"
Dialogue: 0,0:41:44.96,0:41:46.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她是怎么和一个完全陌生的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}"How does she strike up a conversation
Dialogue: 0,0:41:46.50,0:41:48.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,聊起来的  然后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}with an absolute stranger?" And...
Dialogue: 0,0:41:49.01,0:41:50.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她们开始大笑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and they just started laughing
Dialogue: 0,0:41:52.34,0:41:53.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好像她们一直都是好朋友一样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}like they'd been friends forever.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:57.56,0:41:58.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是一种天赋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's a gift.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:01.27,0:42:03.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我记得我在想  天呐  但愿我也能做到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I remember thinking "God, I wish I could do that."
Dialogue: 0,0:42:04.71,0:42:05.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是我做不到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:08.65,0:42:09.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那就是特里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That was Teri.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:13.03,0:42:14.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的妻子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:17.33,0:42:19.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而你把她从这世上夺走了  尼娜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's what you took from this world, Nina.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:23.21,0:42:26.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把她从我和我女儿身边夺走了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's what you took from me and my daughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:33.34,0:42:35.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是想你知道这一点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just wanted you to know that.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:49.15,0:42:51.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里有人员伤亡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We got a man down!

