[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,1,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.65,0:00:10.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(197.4,200.557)}{\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs25\b1\bord0\shad0\c&H78BDE7&\fad(0,808)}24小时\N\N{\fs15}第二季  第十八集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.07,0:00:13.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(189.6,121.6,193.8,105.6,0,356)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad3\3c&H2F2F2F&\4c&H336D99&}{\fs10}{\t(0,356,\fs20)\fn方正正中黑简体}前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.56,0:00:15.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,副总统来电\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Vice president's on the line.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.53,0:00:19.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我有理由相信塞浦路斯录音有可能是伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jim, I have reason to believe the Cyprus audio was fabricated.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.16,0:00:18.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(102,62.953)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.21,0:00:18.25,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(129.6,74.153)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.25,0:00:18.29,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(156.6,82.153)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.29,0:00:18.33,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(186,90.4)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.33,0:00:18.37,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(211.8,99.753)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.37,0:00:18.41,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(237.6,108.553)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.41,0:00:20.45,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(269.4,118.953)\fad(0,346)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.17,0:00:21.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们不是已经分析并证明它是真的了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I thought the analysis had proved it was real.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:21.24,0:00:23.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,洛杉矶反恐组正在搜集\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}CTU LA is in the process of
Dialogue: 0,0:00:23.63,0:00:25.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可能证明录音是伪造的证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}obtaining intelligence that may show otherwise.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.85,0:00:26.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,恕我直言\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}With all due respect,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:26.83,0:00:28.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你授权了这次军事行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you authorized this military action,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:28.72,0:00:30.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在再犹豫太晚了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}it's too late for second thoughts.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.78,0:00:34.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-把双手放在头顶走出来  -我杀了人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Come out with your hands on top of your head. - I killed a man!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.31,0:00:35.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是个意外\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was an accident.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.01,0:00:35.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(310.8,228.553)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.05,0:00:35.10,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(292.8,214.953)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.10,0:00:35.14,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(274.2,199.753)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.14,0:00:35.18,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(257.4,185.353)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.18,0:00:35.22,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(237.6,169.353)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.22,0:00:35.26,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(219.6,158.153)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.26,0:00:35.30,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(201,142.153)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.30,0:00:35.34,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(184.2,128.553)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.34,0:00:37.26,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(165,115.753)\fad(0,347)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.14,0:00:37.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你现在自首  他们会考虑这一点的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you turn yourself in, they'll consider that.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.24,0:00:41.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,若我看到你们进来  我会杀了她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If I see you coming in, I will kill her!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.81,0:00:43.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行动  行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go, go, go!
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.52,0:00:46.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我觉得他不是单独行动  -什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I don't think Jack was working alone. - What do you mean?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.31,0:00:46.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(323.4,41.353)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.36,0:00:46.40,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(302.4,48.553)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.40,0:00:46.44,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(280.8,57.353)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.44,0:00:46.48,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(259.8,65.353)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.48,0:00:46.52,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(240,73.353)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.52,0:00:46.56,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(219,81.353)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.56,0:00:46.61,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(198.6,87.753)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.61,0:00:46.65,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(178.2,98.153)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.65,0:00:46.69,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(156,103.753)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.69,0:00:48.61,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(135,112.553)\fad(0,352)}托尼·阿尔梅达
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.95,0:00:48.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,原本是贝克看着凯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Baker was keeping an eye on Kate.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:48.58,0:00:49.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔把他支开了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle distracted him.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.92,0:00:52.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你帮助杰克带走了凯特·华纳吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did you help Jack take Kate Warner out of here?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:52.37,0:00:53.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当然没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Of course not.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.09,0:00:55.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你对米歇尔所有通讯活动进行监视筛选\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need you to put a filter on all of Michelle's communications.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.94,0:00:58.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克试图联络她的时候你就告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And you let me know when Jack tries to contact her.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.29,0:00:59.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(64.2,218.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.34,0:00:59.38,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(84,207.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.38,0:00:59.42,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(102,198.153)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.42,0:00:59.46,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(123,184.553)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.46,0:00:59.50,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(141.6,173.353)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.50,0:00:59.54,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(160.2,162.153)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.54,0:00:59.58,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(178.2,150.153)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.58,0:00:59.62,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(197.4,138.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.62,0:00:59.66,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(218.4,126.153)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.66,0:01:01.62,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(238.2,114.153)\fad(0,349)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:58.14,0:00:59.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.04,0:01:01.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,十分钟前有个人打电话给我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ten minutes ago a man called me.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.10,0:01:02.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我他能证明\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Told me he had proof that the evidence
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.81,0:01:05.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统做出决策所基于的证据是伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the president was using to base his decisions on was forged.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.83,0:01:07.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他不愿再告诉我别的信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He won't give me any other information
Dialogue: 0,0:01:07.28,0:01:08.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,除非我带你去见他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}unless I brought you to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.16,0:01:09.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还拿着你要的证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I still got what you need.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:09.41,0:01:11.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你不给我凯特·华纳  我是不会给你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I won't give it to you until you give me Kate Warner.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.59,0:01:14.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我那个证据怎么证明录音是伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell me more about the evidence how it proves the Cyprus recording was forged?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:14.58,0:01:16.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我有源录音\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have the source recordings.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.05,0:01:18.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么从反恐组跟踪我  优素福\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yusuf, why did you follow me from CTU?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.06,0:01:20.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你逃出去时  就孤立了自己\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When you broke out, you isolated yourself.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.05,0:01:21.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不管你在做什么  你都需要帮助\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Whatever you do, you'll need help.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.44,0:01:33.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs15\t(696,6577,\fs16)\c&H4BAAAD&\fad(1697,1183)\pos(187.2,191.79)}以下故事情节发生在凌晨1点到凌晨2点之间
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.58,0:01:41.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们从巷子两边同时向我们发起进攻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're coming at us from both sides of the alley!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:42.98,0:01:44.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,房顶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The roof!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.96,0:01:47.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,太平梯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fire escape!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:00.22,0:02:01.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给我钥匙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Give me the keys!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:02.36,0:02:05.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-给  -优素福  掩护我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Here! - Yusuf, give me cover!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.44,0:02:12.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  从后备箱出来  压低身体\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate, get out of the trunk and stay down!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.14,0:02:20.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,左边  在左边  现在往门那里冲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Left! On the left! Go for the door now!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.44,0:02:50.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  跟我来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate, come with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.45,0:02:54.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,躲好  别起来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get down. Stay down!
Dialogue: 0,0:02:55.84,0:02:59.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那些人是谁  -我的雇主派来的后续队伍\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Who are these guys?! - Follow-up team sent by my employers.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:59.07,0:03:01.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们肯定是意识到他们上次没干掉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They must finally figured out they didn't get me in the first time.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:01.23,0:03:02.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们怎么知道你在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How'd they know you were here?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:02.99,0:03:04.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鬼才知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Beats the hell out of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.13,0:03:24.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-杰克  你在吗  -优素福  你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Jack, you there? - Yusuf, are you OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.41,0:03:25.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-还好  -你在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yeah. - Where are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:25.98,0:03:28.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我又设法回车这里拿到了武器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've managed to get back to the vehicle and rearm.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:28.62,0:03:31.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-外面情况如何  -我知道有三个人死了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What's out there? - Three down that I know of.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.37,0:03:34.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,起码还有三个  我不知道他们在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's at least three more out here. I don't have their positions.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:34.52,0:03:36.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要找个更有利的地形\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll find a better vantage point.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.04,0:03:38.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  我们马上决定一下策略\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, good. We'll figure out what we're gonna do in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:38.05,0:03:40.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会再联络你  你等着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll get back to you. Stand by.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:40.05,0:03:42.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让他掩护我们  夺回你的车然后离开这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Have him cover us. Let's get your car and get out of here!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.37,0:03:44.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们都不知道外面有多少人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We don't know how many man are out there!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.29,0:03:46.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会联系反恐组里的我的人  她能帮忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me call my person at CTU. She can help us.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:46.33,0:03:48.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,否决  你谁都不能联系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Negative. You're not calling anybody.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.88,0:03:51.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要拿到帕尔默需要的证据就得照我说的做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The only way you get the proof Palmer needs is if we do this my way.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.59,0:03:53.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们现在离开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We go now!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:55.55,0:03:57.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,外面有人要杀我们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's men out there trying to kill us.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:57.34,0:03:58.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这难道不能说明问题吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Doesn't that prove something?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.81,0:04:01.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不足以说服华盛顿联合部门的长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not to the Joint Chiefs of Staff in DC.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:01.24,0:04:04.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给优素福打电话  我们定一个逃脱策略\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Call Yusuf, let's shape an exit strategy!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:04.33,0:04:05.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:07.67,0:04:08.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,优素福  说吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yusuf, go ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.53,0:04:11.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我听到了声音  好像是另一辆悍马开来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm hearing something sounds like another Humvee just arrived.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:11.43,0:04:13.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,混蛋  你待命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Son of a bitch. Stand by.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.63,0:04:15.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们被包围了  我们要没时间了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're surrounded. We're running out of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.21,0:04:16.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你得让我打这个电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You've gotta let me make this call.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:16.39,0:04:19.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在内部有人  能提供红外卫星支援\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've got someone on the inside that can give us infrared satellite.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.27,0:04:23.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我向你保证不会泄露你的身份\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I guarantee you, I will not jeopardise your identity.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:25.05,0:04:27.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-离线的  -对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Off line? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:28.46,0:04:29.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,做吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:33.92,0:04:34.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,戴斯勒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Dessler.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:34.44,0:04:36.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔  我是杰克  现在通话安全吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle. It's Jack. Are we secure?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:36.78,0:04:39.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的电话通信加了密  但别拨我的工作号码\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My cell's scrambled, but don't call me on any agency numbers.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:39.19,0:04:40.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我被监控了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm being monitored.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.85,0:04:43.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是对的  赛伊德·阿里的录音是伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You were right, Syed Ali's recording was fake.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.14,0:04:44.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统基于伪造的证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The president's about to invade the Middle East
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.61,0:04:46.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,马上要进攻中东了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}based on falsified evidence.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.21,0:04:49.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有证据吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you have proof?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:49.52,0:04:50.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没  现在没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, not yet,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:50.14,0:04:51.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我能拿到  我需要你的帮忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I can get it. I need your help.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:51.70,0:04:52.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很难\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It is gonna be difficult.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:52.75,0:04:55.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,自从我帮你逃出去后托尼就一直密切注意我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony's been breathing down my neck since I helped you get out of here.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.77,0:04:57.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你得设法办到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You gonna have to work around it.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.09,0:04:59.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要我目前所在地的红外卫星图像\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need infrared satellite my poisition now.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.07,0:04:59.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:59.74,0:05:02.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你利用手机通讯定位  然后再联系我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You get the coordinates of cell off our connection and get back to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.05,0:05:03.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要找什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you looking for?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:03.53,0:05:05.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们被包围了  我们在一间仓库里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're surrounded. We're in a warehouse.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.37,0:05:06.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们有三个人在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's three of us inside.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:06.42,0:05:08.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得知道我们外面有多少人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need to know how many men are outside where the position we are.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:08.89,0:05:12.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,巷子北边有个我的朋友  在垃圾桶后面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got a friend at the north end of the alley, behind the dumpster.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.75,0:05:15.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我看看我能做点什么  -谢谢  米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Ok, I'll see what I can do. - Thanks, Michelle.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.09,0:05:17.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-优素福  -我在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yusuf? - I'm here.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.27,0:05:19.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,得等几分钟  我们在等卫星图像\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna be a few minutes. We're waiting on satellite.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:19.43,0:05:20.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会再联系你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll get back to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.56,0:05:23.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,得等一阵子  我们得找个安全的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's gonna take a while. We should secure our position.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.03,0:05:25.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.48,0:05:31.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-加西亚先生会平安吗  -死不了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Is Mr. Garcia gonna be all right? - He'll live.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:33.43,0:05:34.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.79,0:05:37.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会记下来  你声称枪击是一起意外\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna put down that you claim the shooting was an accident.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:37.68,0:05:38.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,它就是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:38.55,0:05:41.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他还是得和检察官解释\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, well. He'll still have to explain to the DA
Dialogue: 0,0:05:41.12,0:05:43.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他带着枪进商店干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}what he was doing going into the store with a gun.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.87,0:05:57.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那不是他的  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It wasn't his. - What's that?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.65,0:06:01.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,枪  那是我的枪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The gun, it was mine.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.75,0:06:04.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你拿枪干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you doing with a gun?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.66,0:06:09.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今晚早些时候有个人给我的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Someone gave it to me earlier tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.57,0:06:15.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我叫金·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, my name's Kim Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:18.82,0:06:22.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天下午  我从看守所逃出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This afternoon, I escaped from police custody.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.54,0:06:24.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是一起谋杀案的嫌犯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And I'm a suspect in a murder.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:26.82,0:06:29.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\fad(319,0)\pos(190.2,222.953)}洛杉矶  总部
Dialogue: 0,0:06:27.83,0:06:31.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尽管大多数美国人现在都在睡觉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}While most Americans are asleep and haven't heard the news
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.05,0:06:33.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,并且对加州的核爆事件一无所知\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}about the nuclear detonation in California,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.49,0:06:32.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(253.8,113.6,247.2,149.6,0,945)}{\fn方正小标宋_GBK\fs18\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&}福克斯新闻警报\N\N\N\N\N{\fs10\fn方正兰亭粗黑_GBK}乔治亚州  玛丽埃塔爆发暴力事件
Dialogue: 0,0:06:32.53,0:06:34.83,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(248.4,149.6,238.2,160.8,30,2282)}{\fn方正小标宋_GBK\fs18\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&}福克斯新闻警报\N\N\N\N\N{\fs10\fn方正兰亭粗黑_GBK}乔治亚州  玛丽埃塔爆发暴力事件
Dialogue: 0,0:06:33.37,0:06:35.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很多人起床了并且做出了回应\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}many are up and are starting to react.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.97,0:06:37.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,人们的反应多种多样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That reaction is taking many forms,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.52,0:06:40.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有些人采取了暴力行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and in some cases violence is erupting.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.53,0:06:42.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们仍在等待白宫发表声明\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're still awaiting a statement from the White House
Dialogue: 0,0:06:42.94,0:06:45.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那也许会指出加州袭击背后的真凶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that might shed some light on who is behind the attack in California.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:45.57,0:06:47.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-够了  -我们希望\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- That's enough. - We hope...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.05,0:06:49.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,警卫队警戒状态如何\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's the alert status of the National Guard?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:49.93,0:06:52.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大城市内的警卫队都在随时待命状态\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're ready to be deployed in all major metropolitan areas.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:52.89,0:06:54.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大城市之外呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about outside the big cities?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.83,0:06:57.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,事态一旦失控  我们将求助军方\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If things get out of control, we may have to get help from the military.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.89,0:07:00.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,地方执法部门也许应对不来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Local law enforcement might not be able to do the job.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:01.48,0:07:05.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,联系鲍登将军  让他令部队待命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Call General Bowden, tell him to put troops on standby.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:05.41,0:07:07.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,部队  我们不能这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The army? We can't do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.47,0:07:11.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你担心民兵部队  -正是如此\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You're worried about posse comitatus. - Exactly.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:11.09,0:07:13.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们不能在本土动用陆军或空军\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We can't use army or air force on American soil.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:13.58,0:07:15.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只能动用海军和海军陆战队\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Only navy and marines.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.11,0:07:16.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  海军帮不上忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, the navy can't help us.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:16.96,0:07:19.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而且没有那么多待命中的海军陆战队\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And there are not enough marines on standby.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:21.55,0:07:24.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我来处理后果  打给鲍登  -是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'll deal with the consequences. Call Bowden. - Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:24.74,0:07:25.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们的轰炸机情况如何\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The status of our bombers?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:25.95,0:07:27.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们正按计划前往他们的目标\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're proceeding as schedule to their targets.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:27.92,0:07:30.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他们现在在哪里  -格陵兰岛南部\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where are they now? - At the South of Greenland.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.94,0:07:34.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,四五个小时内他们应该就进入中东领空了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They should be entering Middle Eastern airspace in four or five hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.16,0:07:35.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.98,0:07:45.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你用卫星地图干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you doing on the satellite?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:47.58,0:07:51.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,检查一下  准备好换班的文件了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just checking on something. Prepped the files for the next shift?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:51.48,0:07:53.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,差不多了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I'm almost done.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:55.64,0:07:57.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我去看看托尼是否需要帮助\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna go see if Tony needs some help.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.85,0:08:18.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么了  -你不是让我留意米歇尔吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Hey... what's up? - You asked me to keep an eye on Michelle?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.64,0:08:22.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-是  -她刚才在看工作站的模拟卫星影像\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yeah. - She was just accessing a mod-sat screen at the workstation.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.70,0:08:25.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这没什么啊  我们整晚都开着模拟卫星\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's not unusual. We've been on mod-sat all night.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:25.65,0:08:28.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在那之前  她刚接了一个无法监听的电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just before that she received a call that wouldn't lock onto our log.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:28.80,0:08:30.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-是开放信号吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It was open? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:31.30,0:08:34.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-应该是分局吧  -应该是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It might have been Division. - It might have been.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:38.37,0:08:43.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  再看看她在找什么  告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right... find out what she was looking at. Let me know.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:13.25,0:09:15.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,优素福  外面什么情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yusuf, what's happening out there?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:20.03,0:09:21.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得他们在调整位置\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think they're repositioning.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.26,0:09:25.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们还在等卫星定位  还要几分钟再打给你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're still waiting on satellite. It's gonna be a few minutes. I'll get back to you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:35.90,0:09:38.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有反恐组的帮助我们会出去的  我保证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}With CTU's help, we're gonna get out of here, I promise.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.78,0:09:41.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,华莱士想要我做什么呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What does Wallace want with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.62,0:09:44.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他需要你帮他逃出国\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He needs you to help him get out of the country.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:44.01,0:09:45.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,需要我  怎么帮\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Needs me? How?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.81,0:09:47.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,用你父亲在中情局的关系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}With your father's CIA connections,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:47.25,0:09:50.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他的公司有一种特殊的旅游豁免权\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}his company has a special travel dispensation.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.58,0:09:56.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们不会让他登记  除非...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They wouldn't let him on board as a passenger unless...
Dialogue: 0,0:09:56.99,0:09:58.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我和他一起上飞机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was on the plane with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:59.36,0:10:00.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:01.65,0:10:03.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.09,0:10:07.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不会让你上那架飞机的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I will not let you get on that plane.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.31,0:11:05.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我怎么样才能知道我男朋友的状况呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is there any way I can find out how my boyfriend is doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:05.56,0:11:08.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道  等我们到警察局再说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know anything about that. Wait till we get to the station.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:08.82,0:11:11.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有一位警官  他的名字叫布朗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There was also another officer. I thing his name was Brown.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:12.18,0:11:15.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他也遭遇了事故  -我也不认识他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- He was in the accident as well. - I don't know him either.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:15.36,0:11:20.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  女士  你被逮捕了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, miss, you're under arrest.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:20.25,0:11:24.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听我句劝  别再说话了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So, take my advice, don't say any more.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.27,0:11:26.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反正也无所谓了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It doesn't matter anyway.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.73,0:11:30.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,到警察局后你可打个电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You can make a phone call until we get to the station.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:30.39,0:11:32.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,打给谁呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who am I gonna call?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:33.42,0:11:35.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我爸爸就驾驶着那架飞机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My dad was the one who was flying the plane,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:35.22,0:11:36.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,装着炸弹的那架飞机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the one with the bomb in it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:39.19,0:11:41.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没有可以联系的人了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't have anyone any more.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.85,0:11:55.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\frz5.461\move(125.4,46.4,96.6,78.4,3115,4075)}{\fn方正黑体_GBK\fax0.2\fs15\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H000000&}分析
Dialogue: 0,0:11:55.40,0:11:55.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(296.4,95.2)\frz6.083}{\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs14\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H000000&}卫星遥测和图像
Dialogue: 0,0:12:06.58,0:12:09.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-阿尔梅达  -她在看红外线影像\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Almeida. - She's looking at infrareds.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.10,0:12:11.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她在持续收集数据  大约已有十分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's been collecting data now for almost ten minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:11.46,0:12:14.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  提取她看的位置的坐标\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. Pull coordinates off what she's looking at.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:14.49,0:12:16.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果她是在帮杰克  我们就能找到他了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If she is doing it for Jack, that's where we'll find him.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:16.75,0:12:19.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我试过了  -有什么问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I tried that. - What's the problem?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.63,0:12:22.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她藏得很深  混入了100个位置\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's covered her tracks. She's pulled 100 quadrants.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.63,0:12:24.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道她真正在看的是哪个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have no idea which one she's really interested in.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:25.23,0:12:26.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我来处理吧  凯莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll tell you what, I'll deal with this, Carrie.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:26.67,0:12:28.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  多谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right? Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.20,0:12:51.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么样  -时间紧急  准备好了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yeah? - I don't have a lot of time. Are you ready?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.63,0:12:53.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,稍等\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Give me one sec.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:56.08,0:12:57.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  准备好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, I'm ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.61,0:12:59.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,包括你们在内有十一个人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I count 11, including your friendly.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.45,0:13:02.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我把他们在红外线地图上的位置发给你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sending you their positions on an infrared map.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:02.31,0:13:04.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们都站定了  只有一个人例外\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're all stationary except for one.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:04.91,0:13:06.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  他在移动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, he's roving.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:06.59,0:13:08.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好  发吧  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- OK, send it. - OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.89,0:13:13.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\frz336.4\move(210,139.2,213,109.6,0,694)}{\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs11\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H9D8A7E&}下载数据
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.56,0:13:15.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-收到了  -收到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You got it? - Yeah, I got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.44,0:13:18.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  你还要藏匿多久\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, how much longer do you need to stay anonymous?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:18.37,0:13:20.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不知道  怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know, why?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.53,0:13:22.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼在监视我  挂了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony's watching me. Gotta go.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:33.69,0:13:36.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你去卫生间总是带着手机吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You always take a phone with you to the bathroom?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:37.35,0:13:39.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-杰克在哪  -不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where's Jack? - I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:41.14,0:13:43.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔  你知道我们整天\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, Michelle, you know we've been monitoring
Dialogue: 0,0:13:43.19,0:13:45.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都在监控着所有的通讯活动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}all communication coming in and out all day.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:45.25,0:13:47.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-如果你违反了制度...  -我没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- If you're breaking protocol... - I'm not.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.72,0:13:52.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  那我再问你一遍\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, then I'll ask you again.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.90,0:13:56.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-杰克在哪  -我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where's Jack? - I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:57.74,0:13:59.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不过你得打给帕尔默总统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But you have to call President Palmer.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:59.92,0:14:01.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你得告诉他在杰克结束他的调查前\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You have to tell him not to act on the recording
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.65,0:14:04.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不要基于录音有任何行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}until Jack finishes his investigation.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:05.39,0:14:09.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你和杰克联系过  -我可没说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- So you have talked to Jack? - I didn't say that.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:10.24,0:14:12.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听清楚了  米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen carefully, Michelle.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.10,0:14:14.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不是为杰克工作  你是为我工作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't work for Jack, you work for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:14.04,0:14:15.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能不能不那么自负\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Would you get past your ego...
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.06,0:14:16.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,自负  我在尽职责\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ego? I got a job to do.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:16.54,0:14:18.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不喜欢我的工作方式  那是你的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't like the way I'm doing it, that's your problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:18.95,0:14:20.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是如果你知道杰克·鲍尔的任何情报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But if you know anything about Jack Bauer,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.55,0:14:22.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最好立刻告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you'd better tell me about it right now!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:25.06,0:14:29.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没有任何情报  我没有帮助杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have no information. I'm not helping Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:37.92,0:14:39.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,希望你没骗我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I hope you're not lying to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:48.87,0:14:51.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有九个人  其中一人在移动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She counted nine, plus one roving.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.22,0:14:52.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,从上次交火来看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Based on the last exchange of fire,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:52.85,0:14:54.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我是狙击手  我会从这里俯瞰全楼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}if I was a sniper, I'd cover the building from here.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:54.78,0:14:58.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-看着没错  -我们得搭一条廊道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yeah, looks right. - We'll have to build a corridor.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:58.14,0:15:00.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-通向哪个出口  -这里这个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Which exit? - This one right here.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:01.40,0:15:03.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,从这两组人中间冲过去  让他们互相开火\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go between these two groups, let 'em fire at each other.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.95,0:15:06.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大约能给我们十秒钟时间去车上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It'll give us about ten seconds to get to the car.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:06.11,0:15:07.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就我们开枪吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}With just us firing?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.33,0:15:11.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没别的办法了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We don't have another way.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:21.75,0:15:24.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  我知道怎么开枪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, I know how to shoot a gun.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:30.71,0:15:34.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拿着这个  你跟在我后面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Take this. You stay right behind me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.59,0:15:40.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-优素福  是杰克  能收到吗  -可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yusuf, this is Jack, do you copy? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.25,0:15:42.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们准备好开路出去了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're getting ready to make our exit.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.81,0:15:45.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我和你说说枪手的位置  -说吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Let me give you positions of the shooters. - Go ahead.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:45.12,0:15:47.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,发现九个  一个在移动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We've counted nine, plus one roving.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:47.54,0:15:50.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在我上方的阳台上有两个狙击手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We got two shooters on the balcony right above me.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:50.71,0:15:53.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,相邻的大楼里有三个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We got three in the building adjacent.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.23,0:15:56.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统  我刚和国防部长谈过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, I just got off with the secretary of defence.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:56.10,0:15:58.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他想知道你还要给杰克·鲍尔多久\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He wants to know how much longer you'll give Jack Bauer
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.99,0:16:01.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来证明录音是假的  之后才能确定命令\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to disprove that tape before we fail-safe the orders.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:01.93,0:16:04.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要把投弹前的所有时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As far as I'm concerned Jack Bauer will have up until
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.13,0:16:06.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都留给杰克·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the time the planes start releasing bombs.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.59,0:16:10.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,部长认为这会限制国防部的行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}From the secretary's point of view, that's tying the DOD's hands.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.48,0:16:12.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他说你做决定需要的时间越久\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He claims the longer it takes for your decision,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.82,0:16:14.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他掌握的灵活性就越小\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the less flexibility he has,
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.37,0:16:16.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他非常想要先发制人...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and he may very well want to launch a prestrike...
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.41,0:16:19.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这次任务不允许先发制人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There will be no prestrikes on this mission.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:20.15,0:16:23.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要利用一切时间做到面面俱到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna utilise every moment we have to be thorough.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.04,0:16:26.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他会很生气  先生  -那是他的问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- He is not gonna like that, sir. - That's his problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.63,0:16:27.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,明白了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:27.51,0:16:31.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统  有个情况需要您立即处理\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, there's a situation that requires your immediate attention.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.61,0:16:32.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么  麦克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What, Mike?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:32.83,0:16:36.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,国内动乱开始在东海岸活跃起来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Civil unrest is starting to tip up and down the East Coast.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:36.40,0:16:40.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我最担心的是亚特兰大外的地区\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The area I'm most concerned about is outside of Atlanta.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.05,0:16:41.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's going on there?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:41.59,0:16:44.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一些临时民兵加入了军队\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Some ad hoc militias have joined forces
Dialogue: 0,0:16:44.02,0:16:47.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们在某个郊区变得非常激进\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and they're getting very aggressive in one of the suburbs.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:48.26,0:16:50.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-是由种族歧视所激化的吗  -当然了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Is this racially motivated?  - Absolutely.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.68,0:16:54.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这片区域主要居民是中东人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The demographics of the area are predominantly Middle Eastern.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:55.19,0:16:57.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你来这儿的目的是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you hope to accomplish here?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:57.57,0:17:01.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,希望华盛顿知道我们已经进入作战状态了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We want Washington to know we consider ourselves at war situation.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:01.15,0:17:02.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们希望这些人能被拘留起来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We want these people interned.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.95,0:17:04.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,否则的话  我们会自己动手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And if they won't do it, we will.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.46,0:17:08.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord0\shad0\fs14\fn方正小标宋_GBK\b1\move(148.2,144,150,135.2)}福克斯紧急新闻\N\N\N\N\N\N{\an8\bord0\shad0\b1\fs10\fn方正黑体_GBK}民事骚乱\N{\an8}玛丽埃塔  乔治亚州
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.50,0:17:05.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么你希望他们被拘留\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who do you want interned?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:05.54,0:17:08.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我被告知本地的大多数居民都是美国公民\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm told the majority in this neighbourhood consists of US citizens.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:08.36,0:17:11.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是被归化的  他们不是土生土长的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Naturalized. They weren't born here.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.03,0:17:12.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有些人甚至不会说英语\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Some of them don't know how to speak English.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.51,0:17:14.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们背了五十个问题的答案\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They memorise answers to 50 questions,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:14.43,0:17:16.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后参加测试  接着我们就允许他们投票了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}take the test, then we let them vote.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:16.31,0:17:19.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先生  你如何回应州长宣称这些人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, how do you respond to the governors that claim that these people
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.23,0:17:22.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对加州的炸弹了解的并不比你或我多\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}have no more to do with the bomb in California than you or I?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.01,0:17:23.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我们二十年前就封锁边境\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If we'd locked down our borders 20 years ago
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.39,0:17:24.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就像我们该做的那样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}like it should,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:24.22,0:17:26.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就不会发生这种事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}none of this would have happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:27.77,0:17:29.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,令人奇怪的是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's eerie about the scene is,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.45,0:17:32.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,虽然人群已经在此聚集超过了半小时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}even though the crowd has been here for over half an hour,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.20,0:17:34.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现场却只有寥寥数量警车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}there are only a few police cars on site.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:34.36,0:17:38.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么  我以为我们已经派出国民警卫队了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why? I thought we ordered the National Guard.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.48,0:17:41.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一部分在路上  还有一些被派到其他现场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Some are on their way, some are dispatched at other flash points.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:41.56,0:17:43.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要我联系联调局和军队吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you want me to call the FBI and the army?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.76,0:17:45.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后告诉他们什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And tell them what?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:46.65,0:17:48.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们已经收到各自的命令了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They've already received their orders.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.62,0:17:49.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,问题在于人力资源\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The problem is resources.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:49.81,0:17:52.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们没有足够的人手来照顾一切\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We just don't have enough bodies to cover everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.98,0:17:54.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,媒体现在在去哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where's the media heading right now?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:55.00,0:17:58.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很显然  全部都朝东海岸去了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Apparently, it's happening all up and down the East Coast.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:58.22,0:18:00.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但这个城市  亚特兰大的玛丽埃塔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But this city, Marietta in Atlanta,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.90,0:18:03.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,似乎是最吸引媒体的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}seems to have the most traction with the press.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.00,0:18:08.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了  那我们就这样做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right. This is what we're gonna do.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:09.31,0:18:11.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们也许人手不够\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We may be short on manpower,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.49,0:18:13.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但不一定要表现出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but it doesn't have to appear that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:13.49,0:18:16.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把乔治亚州东部国民警卫队的所有人手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Send all the Eastern Georgia National Guard
Dialogue: 0,0:18:16.11,0:18:17.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,都派去玛丽埃塔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to Marietta.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:17.18,0:18:18.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉媒体\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And tell the media that
Dialogue: 0,0:18:18.83,0:18:20.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里有事情要发生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}this is where something's going to happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:21.33,0:18:23.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么事要发生  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's going to happen, sir?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:24.83,0:18:27.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果这里就是人们所关注的地方\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If this is what the people are going to be watching,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.44,0:18:29.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就让我们告诉他们我们要怎么回应\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}let's show them how we're going to respond.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:30.21,0:18:32.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要让他们看看我们会怎么保护我们的公民\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want them to see how we protect our citizens.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:32.76,0:18:36.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们绝不忍受种族歧视或仇外心理\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We will not put up with racism or xenophobia.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:36.51,0:18:40.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果事起于此  就让事终于此\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If this is where it's gonna start, this is where it's gonna stop!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.73,0:19:11.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好了  我准备好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, I'm all set up here.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.28,0:19:13.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,收到  开始放烟雾弹  我们准备好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Copy that. Start laying down the smoke. We're ready to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:13.94,0:19:16.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,收到  我投烟雾弹了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Copy that. Go in on the smoke.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:32.36,0:19:33.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你解决左手边的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You take the men on the left,
Dialogue: 0,0:19:33.62,0:19:35.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我负责上方的  准备好了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got the ones right above us. You ready?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:36.22,0:19:39.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,烟雾弹就位了  我来吸引火力  去开车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Smoke's in place. I'll draw fire and go pick up the vehicle.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:45.15,0:19:46.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:10.00,0:20:12.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-凯特  -爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Kate!  - Dad!
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.50,0:20:14.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  趴下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate, get down!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.03,0:21:14.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  快  我们得走了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate. Come on, we gotta keep going.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.95,0:21:22.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别停下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Keep moving!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:25.55,0:21:27.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,到前排  趴低一点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get in the front seat and stay down!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:28.56,0:21:30.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,趴下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get down!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:54.14,0:21:57.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,趴下去  快  快  走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stay down! Go, go, go!
Dialogue: 0,0:22:09.15,0:22:10.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我看看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me look at it.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:16.09,0:22:18.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有出口伤  我们得把你送到医院去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's no exit wound. We gotta get you to a hospital.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.84,0:22:21.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  洛杉矶国际机场  货运港\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. LAX, cargo departures.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:21.82,0:22:23.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你撑不到那儿的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You will not make it.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.15,0:22:25.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我能撑到的  帮我止血就行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll make it. Just stop the bleeding.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:25.51,0:22:27.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  在手套箱里  有急救包\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate, in the glove box, there's a first-aid kit.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:27.33,0:22:29.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给我拿一些纱布还有包扎带\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get me all the gauze, pads and wraps.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.01,0:22:34.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,坚持住  坚持住\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hold on, hold on.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:36.49,0:22:38.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,用力压住止血\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Put pressure on it now.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:39.01,0:22:40.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽埃塔现在是一幅难以置信的场景\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a surreal scene in Marietta.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:40.90,0:22:44.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在早晨四点半  通常人们都还在睡梦中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's 4.30 am and normally people would be at home, asleep.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.17,0:22:46.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是今天却有大戏即将上演\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yet today a showdown is in the making.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.63,0:22:49.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\bord0\shad0\b1\fs14\fn方正小标宋_GBK\frz0\move(202.2,144,202.2,140)}福克斯紧急新闻\N\N\N\N\N{\an8\bord0\shad0\b1\fs10\fn方正黑体_GBK}暴乱加剧\N{\an8}玛丽埃塔  乔治亚州
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.75,0:22:49.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,整座城市的暴乱都在加剧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The riots have escalated all over the city.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:49.17,0:22:52.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,到处都是火灾与抢劫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fires and looting are reported to be widespread.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.02,0:22:54.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,国民警卫队在不断增援\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The National Guard continue to roll in,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:54.19,0:22:55.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但愤怒的群众也在增加\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}as do the angry citizens,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:55.99,0:22:57.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们将自己的愤恨\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}who are taking out their frustration
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.71,0:23:01.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,发泄到了这个平时一贯平和的中东社区\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}on this normally peaceful Middle Eastern community.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.00,0:23:03.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,您的要求我们已经办到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You got what you asked for.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:03.53,0:23:05.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先生  现在所有新闻都在播这个\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, it's on all the news channels.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:05.42,0:23:07.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,长官  国民警卫队的肯特·曼斯基\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, Kent Manski of the National Guard
Dialogue: 0,0:23:07.93,0:23:09.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想知道你的行动原则是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}wants to know what tactical rule-set you wanna follow.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:09.98,0:23:11.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他们现在是怎么做的  -只是在控制人群\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What are they on now? - Containment only.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.66,0:23:13.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不镇压小规模的暴行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Allowing minor misdemeanors to go unchallenged.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:13.64,0:23:15.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不行  必须按法律处置\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Unacceptable. I want the law enforced.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:15.97,0:23:18.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉他可以对人群进行逮捕了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell him to start making arrests and taking people in.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:18.78,0:23:20.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,长官  如果你宣布实行宵禁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, if you declare a curfew
Dialogue: 0,0:23:20.99,0:23:22.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就可以在事情失控之前\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you can start pulling every one of them in
Dialogue: 0,0:23:22.94,0:23:24.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把所有人都一一逮捕了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}before this thing gets out of control.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:24.95,0:23:26.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是个好主意  就这样做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That a good idea, do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.38,0:23:29.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉曼斯基我们不怕采取行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell Manski we're not afraid to start taking actions.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.04,0:23:30.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:30.26,0:23:33.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最能奏效的是您的发声  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What will help more than anything, sir, is your voice.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:33.88,0:23:36.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,您得跟大家面对面地谈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You need to talk directly to the people.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.93,0:23:40.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我明白\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:41.94,0:23:44.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉詹妮我一会儿就下去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell Jenny I'll be down in a few minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.40,0:23:46.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an4\fs10\bord0\shad0\b1\fn方正黑体_GBK\move(78.6,162.4,64.8,152.8,0,1401)}国民警卫队介入\N{\an8}玛丽埃塔  乔治亚州
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.78,0:23:47.65,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an4\fs10\bord0\shad0\b1\fn方正黑体_GBK\move(64.2,154.4,28.8,137.6,21,856)}国民警卫队介入\N{\an8}玛丽埃塔  乔治亚州
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.59,0:23:47.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是墨菲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Murphy speaking.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:47.88,0:23:50.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是诺维克  詹妮·道奇在吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is Novick. I need Jenny Dodge.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.26,0:23:54.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-凯里  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Carrie. - Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:54.65,0:23:58.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,洛杉矶警局说刚刚影视城发生了枪击事件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}LAPD just called, there was automatic-weapon fire in Studio City.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.20,0:24:01.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,警察到后发现了尸体  还有军队专用的武器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Police are arriving and finding bodies and military-spec weapons.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:01.05,0:24:02.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,情报机构有地址\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Communication's got the address.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.40,0:24:03.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,核对一下与米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Check it against the accordance of the images
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.36,0:24:05.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,从卫星上下载的图片之间的一致程度\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle pulled off the satellite.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.29,0:24:06.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,马上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right away.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:08.37,0:24:11.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是那儿吗  米歇尔  是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is that the location, Michelle? Huh, is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:12.34,0:24:13.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,警察刚刚到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The police just got there,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.33,0:24:15.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们已经发现了四具尸体  快说吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}they already got four bodies. So let's talk!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:21.35,0:24:22.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是那里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, that's it.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:22.49,0:24:25.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们得联系他  他可能需要我们的帮助\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We gotta call him. He may need our help.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:25.41,0:24:26.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克说得很清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack made it clear that
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.66,0:24:27.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想要证实这份录音真假\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the only way to get proof on this tape is
Dialogue: 0,0:24:27.97,0:24:29.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只有反恐局不参与才可以办到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}if CTU stays out of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:29.39,0:24:31.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们都不知道他现在是死是活\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We don't even know if he's still alive!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.54,0:24:42.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他在一条公用线上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's on an open channel.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:42.16,0:24:44.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你没办法追踪  但可以跟他说话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You won't be able to trace it, but you can talk to him.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:48.48,0:24:50.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-米歇尔  -不是  杰克  是托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Michelle! - No, Jack, it's Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:50.86,0:24:53.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼  相信我  别管这件事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony, trust me, stay out of this!
Dialogue: 0,0:24:53.20,0:24:54.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,发生什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:54.57,0:24:56.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统想要得到证明那份录音\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The president asked me for proof
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.85,0:24:59.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是假的的证据  我现在正在努力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that the Cyprus recording was fake. I'm trying to do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:59.87,0:25:03.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那个能提供证据的人只愿意见我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The man who can provide proof will only deal with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.42,0:25:05.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他不接受与反恐局合作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He won't cooperate with CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:05.31,0:25:07.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以我才那样走掉的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's why I left in that way.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:07.28,0:25:08.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要怎么知道他不是在利用你  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How do we know he's not using you, Jack?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.85,0:25:10.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为有十个突击队员想杀他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Cause ten commandos tried to kill him
Dialogue: 0,0:25:10.64,0:25:12.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阻止他与我交易\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to stop him from making a deal with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:12.71,0:25:15.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他目的何在  -他想消失\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What's he want? - He wants to disappear.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:15.78,0:25:17.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把他带过来  杰克  我们在这儿跟他谈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bring him here, Jack, we'll deal with him here.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.44,0:25:18.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼  我刚刚说了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony, I just told you he will not cooperate with us
Dialogue: 0,0:25:18.99,0:25:20.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在那种情况下他是不会合作的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}under those circumstances.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:20.83,0:25:22.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我明白  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I understand what you're saying, Jack,
Dialogue: 0,0:25:22.05,0:25:24.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但整个国家的安危都在这件事上  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but this country's about to go to war over this, alright?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:24.49,0:25:27.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这事靠一个人是处理不好的  即便是你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is way too big for one person to handle. Even you.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.27,0:25:28.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,保持直行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Keep going straight!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:29.60,0:25:32.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  我不能这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry, I can't do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:43.75,0:25:45.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他还在大量出血\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's still bleeding bad!
Dialogue: 0,0:25:50.54,0:25:52.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,波比\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Bobby.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:52.78,0:25:54.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是金·鲍尔吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is this Kim Bauer?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.24,0:25:58.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-交给我吧  -程序怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'll take her. - What about processing?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.50,0:26:01.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没关系  去填报告吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's OK. Go fill out the report.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:07.11,0:26:08.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,跟我来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:10.14,0:26:11.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,进去这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll go in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:21.47,0:26:22.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请坐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Have a seat.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.73,0:26:41.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看来你今天经历了不少\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Looks like you've had quite a day.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:41.97,0:26:43.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.08,0:26:46.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你把梅根·马西森从她父母家带走了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You took Megan Matheson from her parents' home.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:46.01,0:26:49.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-她遭受了虐待  -你和她父亲起了争执\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- She was being abused. - Got into a fight with her father.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.05,0:26:53.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这一次  你又从医院把梅根带走了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then, you took Megan again, this time from the hospital.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:53.93,0:26:55.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你偷了加里·马西森的车  逃到城里去了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You stole Gary Matheson's car and fled the city.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:55.91,0:26:58.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我必须这么做  我知道炸弹的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I had to. I knew about the bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:58.24,0:26:59.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,明白\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Understood.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:00.85,0:27:03.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但你后来被加州高速巡警雷蒙德·布朗拦下了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But then you were stopped by CHP Officer Raymond Brown,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:03.52,0:27:05.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他在车尾箱发现了卡拉·马西森的尸体\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}who discovered the dead body of Carla Matheson in the trunk.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:05.84,0:27:08.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我没有杀人  -我知道你没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I didn't kill anyone. - I know you didn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:08.73,0:27:10.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们知道加里·马西森杀了他妻子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We know Gary Matheson killed his wife.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:10.98,0:27:11.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们正在找他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're looking for him now.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:11.96,0:27:13.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们有目击证人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There was a witness,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:13.27,0:27:15.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,并且我们在凶器上发现了加里的指纹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and we found Gary's prints on the murder weapon.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:15.36,0:27:17.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-真的吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You did? - Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:17.41,0:27:20.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以今早发生的事情跟你无关了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So you're off the hook for everything that happened this morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.03,0:27:21.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢天谢地\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank God.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:21.94,0:27:23.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但还有个问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But there's still the matter of
Dialogue: 0,0:27:23.18,0:27:25.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你和你的男朋友试图逃脱拘留\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you and your boyfriend's attempted escape from custody.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:26.69,0:27:29.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,布朗警官在车祸中受了重伤\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Officer Brown was badly injured in the accident.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.03,0:27:32.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但他会没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But he's gonna make it.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.95,0:27:33.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而现在我们知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And we now know that
Dialogue: 0,0:27:33.82,0:27:35.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你跟他说的炸弹事件是真的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you were telling him the truth about the bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:37.05,0:27:38.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以我没事了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So I'm free?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:38.96,0:27:40.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你应该让反恐组的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You should probably have somebody from CTU
Dialogue: 0,0:27:40.72,0:27:42.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,替你给地检署打个电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}call the DA's office on your behalf.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:43.25,0:27:45.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错  你可以走了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But yes, you'll be free to go.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:49.66,0:27:52.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道我父亲经常这么做  但我有权限\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I know my father usually does this, but I have clearance.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:52.20,0:27:53.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你可以查查记录\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You can check your book.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:54.51,0:27:57.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,必须要有一位公司官员在飞机上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}An officer of the company has to be on the flight.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.12,0:28:00.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我会一起去  你能稍等吗  -当然可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'll be on it. Can you hold on? - Certainly.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.36,0:28:03.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你要去哪里  -雅加达\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where are you going? - Jakarta.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:04.94,0:28:07.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要放弃我的目的地  你很惊讶吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're surprised I'm giving up my destination?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:07.33,0:28:10.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  一起飞你就会改变主意\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. You'll just change it once you're in the air.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:12.45,0:28:15.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,准备一架去印度雅加达的货机\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Prep a cargo transport to Jakarta, Indonesia.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:15.56,0:28:18.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再给我们优先许可  好让我们今晚就能出发\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And give us priority clearance so we can leave tonight.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.20,0:28:20.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有谁会跟你一起飞\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who else will be flying with you?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:21.21,0:28:23.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我应该跟他们说什么名字\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What name should I give them?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:23.24,0:28:26.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-护照在我口袋里  -我来拿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Passport, in my pocket. - I got it.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.08,0:28:36.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-威廉姆·帕特森  -请稍等\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- William Patterson. - One moment, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:41.14,0:28:44.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,坚持住  他正在失去意识\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, stay with me. He's losing consciousness!
Dialogue: 0,0:28:45.19,0:28:47.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,华莱士  我们不能冒这个险\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wallace, we can't take this chance.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.20,0:28:49.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我证据在哪里  我向你保证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell me where the evidence is, and I give you my word,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.30,0:28:51.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会把你送出国\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I will get you out of this country.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:51.75,0:28:53.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道吗  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what, Jack?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:53.81,0:28:57.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在仓库的时候  你真是太厉害了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You were a real badass back there at the warehouse.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:57.08,0:28:58.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,混蛋\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Son of a bitch.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:00.55,0:29:02.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:02.77,0:29:07.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他快不行了  该死  -你在干吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'm losing him! Damn it! - What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:07.13,0:29:08.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要看看这附近\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wanna see if there's an urgent care centre
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.66,0:29:10.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有没有急救中心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}in the neighbourhood.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:07.14,0:29:08.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(132.6,159.2,142.8,137.6)}{\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs14\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H000000&}医疗中心
Dialogue: 0,0:29:08.92,0:29:11.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(198,79.2)}{\fn方正兰亭粗黑_GBK\fs15\b0\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H000000&}地图加载中
Dialogue: 0,0:29:10.93,0:29:12.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快点吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:12.43,0:29:15.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(219,36.8,196.2,45.6)}{\fn方正兰亭粗黑_GBK\fs15\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&}医疗中心
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.64,0:29:17.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,离这里四个街区  四个街区  右转  快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Four blocks. Four blocks, make a right. Go!
Dialogue: 0,0:29:21.54,0:29:23.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要所有死者的身份\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want IDs on all the bodies.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.34,0:29:25.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看看能在凶器上找到什么线索\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}See what traces we can find on the weapons.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:25.13,0:29:26.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,鲍尔的行动是反恐组的责任\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bauer's actions are CTU's responsibility.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.92,0:29:27.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道那是反恐组的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know it was CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:27.93,0:29:29.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,相信我  我们不会推诿责任\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And believe me we're not gonna run away from this.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.53,0:29:30.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,查出这些人是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So let's just find out who these people are.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:30.97,0:29:32.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,带上法医队去吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Send in forensic teams?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.25,0:29:33.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有美国国家安全局和外勤部队吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}NSA and field units?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.90,0:29:35.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, that's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:37.64,0:29:40.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿尔梅达先生  金·鲍尔在四号线找您\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr Almeida, Kim Bauer on line four.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.03,0:29:43.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金  你在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kim, where are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.94,0:29:46.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在圣克拉里塔的一个警察局\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}At a sheriffs station in Santa Clarita.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.90,0:29:47.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,发生什么事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:47.59,0:29:48.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Doesn't matter.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:48.26,0:29:50.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们不会以谋杀罪或绑架罪控告我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're not gonna charge me for murder or kidnapping,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:50.07,0:29:51.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but...
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.23,0:29:53.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也许还需要帮忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I still might need some help.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:53.14,0:29:55.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没问题  你需要什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sure, what do you need?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:55.34,0:29:57.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们本来要把我们带回洛杉矶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They were taking us back to Los Angeles,
Dialogue: 0,0:29:57.42,0:29:59.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而我和我的男朋友试图逃跑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and my boyfriend and I tried to escape.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:59.55,0:30:03.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,然后发生了车祸  有个警官受伤了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And we got into a car accident. A police officer was injured.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:03.73,0:30:06.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会打给地检署  看看能帮什么忙\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alright look, I'll call the DA's office, see what I can do.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.60,0:30:07.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:07.81,0:30:11.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金  我相信你更想跟你父亲聊聊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kim, I'm sure you'd rather be talking to your dad about this,
Dialogue: 0,0:30:11.20,0:30:13.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但他们应该告诉过你  他现在没空\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I know they probably told you he's not available right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:15.85,0:30:19.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你在说什么  -他在出外勤\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What are you talking about? - He's in the field.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:20.89,0:30:23.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,出外勤吗  他还活着吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In the field? You mean, he's alive?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:23.40,0:30:26.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天呐  金  你还以为他死在飞机上了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, my God, Kim. You still think he died in the plane.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:27.17,0:30:27.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他没死吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He didn't?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:27.99,0:30:30.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  没有  乔治·梅森接手了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, no, no. George Mason took over.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.28,0:30:32.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他及时出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He was able to get out in time.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:33.06,0:30:35.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天呐  我什么时候能跟他说话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, my God. When can I talk to him?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:36.75,0:30:38.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还需要一段时间  金\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not for a while, Kim.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:38.48,0:30:39.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\frz19.91\move(157.2,69.6,156,57.6)}{\fn方正兰亭粗黑_GBK\fax-0.3\fs25\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H74767D&}急救中心
Dialogue: 0,0:30:49.34,0:30:50.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快  快  扶他下来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on, come on, get him!
Dialogue: 0,0:30:58.87,0:31:01.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我需要医生  -先生  你不能这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I need to see the doctor now! - Sir you can't do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:01.23,0:31:03.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-开门  -先生  我要报警了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Open the door! - Sir, I will call the police!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:03.48,0:31:05.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,女士  我就是警察  快开门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Lady, I am the police. Now, open the door!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.26,0:31:07.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让他进去  让他进去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let him in. Let him in!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:10.09,0:31:11.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-医生  我们现在需要你  -发生什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Doctor we need you now! - What the hell happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:11.98,0:31:14.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这位男士背部中弹了  我是联邦探员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This man has been shot in the back. I'm a Federal Agent.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:14.76,0:31:17.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他握有对国家安全很重要的信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This man has information vital to national security.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:17.15,0:31:20.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你帮他止血  让他活着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need you to stop the bleeding and keep him alive.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:22.04,0:31:24.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里只是个诊所  他需要去医院\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is just a clinic. This man needs a hospital.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:24.03,0:31:24.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们没有时间了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We don't have time.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:24.85,0:31:29.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你现在得尽你所能  拜托了  医生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You've got to do what you can now. Doctor, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:29.15,0:31:31.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  克莱拉  给我准备好缝合包\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Alright, alright. Clara, get me suture kits,
Dialogue: 0,0:31:31.23,0:31:33.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,利多卡因  肾上腺素  和急救车  快去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}lidocaine with epi, and a crash cart. Now, now!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:35.41,0:31:38.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,伤口就在这里  他的背部中了一颗子弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The wound's right here. He's got a bullet lodged in his back.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:06.07,0:32:08.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你好  -米格尔  是我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Hello. - Miguel, it's me.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.82,0:32:13.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-金  你还好吗  -我很好  你怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Kim. Are you OK? - I'm fine. How are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.76,0:32:17.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我没事  -是吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'm OK. - Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:20.31,0:32:25.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这很奇怪  但警察知道加里杀了卡拉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, it's so weird, but the police know Gary killed Carla.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:26.54,0:32:28.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们不会受到任何控告\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And we're not gonna be charged with anything,
Dialogue: 0,0:32:28.08,0:32:29.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,逃跑有可能会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}except maybe the escape.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:29.46,0:32:31.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我觉得那件事也没关系了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I think we're OK there, too.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:32.73,0:32:35.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那就好  -好吗  简直太棒了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- That's good. - Good? It's great.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:39.06,0:32:41.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你呢  -我没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How about you? - I'm fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:42.52,0:32:44.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你确定吗  你听起来不...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you sure? I mean, you don't sound...
Dialogue: 0,0:32:44.70,0:32:47.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我听起来怎么样  不激动吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't sound what? Excited?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.46,0:32:49.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天呐  金  我真的很抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Gee, Kim, I'm really sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:49.84,0:32:52.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米格尔  怎么了  你为什么这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Miguel, what's wrong? Why are you acting like this?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.39,0:32:59.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不该让你说服我参与这一切\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I shouldn't have let you talk me into all that stuff.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:59.13,0:33:00.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但这的确有效\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, but it worked out.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:00.58,0:33:03.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对你来说有效  而进医院的是我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For you. I'm the one that's here in the hospital.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:05.33,0:33:09.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你说你没事  -我会没事的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You just said you were fine. - I am going to be fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:11.45,0:33:14.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没有你我就没事了  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'm just gonna be fine without you. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:16.57,0:33:19.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我不想再见到你  -为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I don't wanna see you anymore. - Why not?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:20.63,0:33:23.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没有为什么  就是不想  -不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- There's no "why not", it just is. - No.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:23.65,0:33:26.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米格尔  出了什么事  你没事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Miguel, what is going on? Are you OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:29.29,0:33:30.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我现在马上去见你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm coming to see you right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:30.62,0:33:32.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金  我说了不要  我们结束了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kim, I said no. It's over.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:34.94,0:33:36.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你说认真的吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You mean that?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:39.63,0:33:42.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  我说认真的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah... I mean it.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:33.24,0:34:36.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道规定  我知道我是你的手下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know the rules. I know that I work for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:36.69,0:34:39.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你将我革职  我也不会怪你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And if you fire me, I wouldn't blame you.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:39.92,0:34:42.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,重点不是在于革职你  米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This isn't about me firing you, Michelle.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:42.24,0:34:43.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个机构\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This agency is supposed to
Dialogue: 0,0:34:43.46,0:34:46.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,应该要支持总统和本国\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}be supporting the president and this country.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:46.05,0:34:48.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我无法解释特工的行为\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If I can't account for agent's actions,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:48.30,0:34:49.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们只会陷入混乱当中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and all we've got is chaos.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.21,0:34:50.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克现在陷入了艰难的局面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack is in an impossible situation.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:50.97,0:34:52.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是在帮他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All I was trying to do was helping him
Dialogue: 0,0:34:52.57,0:34:54.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,证明塞浦路斯录音是伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}get the proof that the Cyprus audio was forgery.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:54.48,0:34:59.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是吗  那证据呢  我们没有任何证据\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah? Well, where's the proof? We don't have any proof.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:59.25,0:35:01.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克也不在我们手上  他不想被发现\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We don't have Jack, he doesn't want to be found.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:04.86,0:35:06.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想我怎么样  米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you want from me, Michelle?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:13.27,0:35:15.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是想说对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just wanted to say I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:18.09,0:35:21.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你已经说了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, well, you've said it.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:21.82,0:35:24.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不好意思  我还有工作要做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, if you don't mind, I got work to do, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:52.49,0:35:54.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,目前我们的飞机已经抵达大西洋上空\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Our planes are currently over the Atlantic.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:54.78,0:35:56.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先头机群将在三个小时之内\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The first of them will be reaching their targets
Dialogue: 0,0:35:56.64,0:35:57.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,首先到达目标位置\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}just under three hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:57.88,0:35:59.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,飞行员的通信情况如何\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Pilots' communication posture?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:59.55,0:36:01.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,通讯器已开放\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Comm is open to them.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:01.09,0:36:03.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,随时可以下令让飞机返回\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The planes can be ordered back at any time.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:03.64,0:36:05.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:05.26,0:36:07.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  我不知道是否有人跟你说过\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, I don't know if anyone's told you,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:08.04,0:36:09.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是我们越早锁定该任务\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but the sooner we can lock this mission down,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:09.77,0:36:12.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,参谋长们就会对此越放心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the more comfortable the Joint Chiefs' gonna be with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.23,0:36:16.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的工作不是为了让参谋长们放心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My job's not to make the Joint Chiefs comfortable.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:16.90,0:36:19.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢  暂时就这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you. That'll be all.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:19.58,0:36:21.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:30.03,0:36:35.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  玛丽埃塔有变化\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President. There's been a development in Marietta.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:35.30,0:36:38.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,国民警卫队在我们的要求下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The National Guard took on a more aggressive posture
Dialogue: 0,0:36:38.45,0:36:40.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,采取了更强硬的姿态\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}at our request.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:40.11,0:36:43.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是骚乱已经超出了他们的控制范围\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But the disturbance got to be more than they could handle.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.57,0:36:46.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,发生了什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What happened?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:48.39,0:36:50.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,两人身亡  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Two people were killed, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:50.92,0:36:54.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,国民警卫队开始向人群发射橡皮子弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The National Guard started shooting rubber bullets into the crowd,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:54.10,0:36:56.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,两人遭到致命一击\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and there were two fatal hits.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:56.95,0:37:00.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,其中一名死者是抗议人群的领导  而...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}One of the victims was a leader of the dissent, and...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:08.61,0:37:09.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:10.37,0:37:12.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而另一名是个小男孩  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And the other was a young boy, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:13.59,0:37:15.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他是中东人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He was Middle Eastern, and...
Dialogue: 0,0:37:15.75,0:37:18.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们想要保护的家属当中就有他的家人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}he was from one of the families that we were trying to protect.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:30.06,0:37:31.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在的情况如何\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's going on now?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.69,0:37:35.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们逮捕了一些人  但是人群还是难以控制\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They've made some arrests, but the crowd is still unruly.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:36.37,0:37:40.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也许我们可以考虑退一步\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, we might want to think about... taking a step back.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:40.95,0:37:45.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也许国民护卫队的出现加剧了事态的严重性\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Maybe the presence of the National Guard is making matters worse.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:45.38,0:37:46.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我们现在退一步\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If we step back now,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:46.71,0:37:49.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那些家属就会完全失去保护\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}those families are left completely unprotected.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:49.61,0:37:50.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.84,0:37:53.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,年轻人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A young boy.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:56.84,0:37:58.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他叫什么名字\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What was his name?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:00.26,0:38:01.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那个孩子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The boy?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:04.98,0:38:06.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:06.25,0:38:08.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他肯定有名字的  去查\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The boy had a name. Find out.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.79,0:38:10.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Indeed I will, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:22.91,0:38:25.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那是一个悲剧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was a tragic accident.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:34.07,0:38:36.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉国民护卫队坚守其阵地\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell the National Guard to hold their ground.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.45,0:38:40.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要保护那个社区  我要秩序得以恢复\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want that neighbourhood protected. I want order restored.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:41.76,0:38:43.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,遵命  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:57.36,0:38:58.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,子弹在这个位置\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's the bullet.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:58.38,0:39:01.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没打中颈静脉  但还是造成了很大伤害\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It missed the jugular, but still caused a lot of damage.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:01.26,0:39:02.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有办法吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What can you do?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:02.57,0:39:04.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也许可以帮他止住血  但是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I might be able to tie off the bleeders, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:39:04.66,0:39:06.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不做手术是取不出子弹的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you can't get the bullet out unless it goes with the surgery.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:06.96,0:39:08.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没时间做手术\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We don't have time for that.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:08.74,0:39:11.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得说一句  我不愿意这样抢救他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got tell you, I don't feel comfortable with this.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:11.59,0:39:12.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们会查封我这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They can shut me down.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:12.67,0:39:15.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没有资格做这种手术\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not authorised perform procedure like this.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.03,0:39:16.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,医生  我向你保证不会的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Doctor, I guarantee that won't happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:16.83,0:39:18.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你立刻去做手术\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need you to do this now.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:18.34,0:39:20.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你起码告诉我这到底是怎么回事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}At least tell me what this is all about.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:20.19,0:39:23.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,和爆炸的炸弹有关\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It has to do with the bomb that went off.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:23.11,0:39:25.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对不起  我只能告诉你这么多\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry, I can't tell you more than that.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:27.96,0:39:31.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-那好  我尽力而为吧  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- All right, I'll see what I can do. - Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:31.11,0:39:33.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,给他注射一点安眠药  我好开始做手术\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Give him some Versed, so I can work on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:33.01,0:39:34.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不要给他注射镇静剂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, don't sedate him.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:34.13,0:39:35.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要他能开口说话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need him to be able to talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:35.75,0:39:37.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只要麻痹伤口周围的区域就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just numb the area around the wound.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:41.47,0:39:45.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别担心  美女  我受过比这更严重的伤\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't worry, beautiful. I've been worse than this.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:46.46,0:39:48.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请给他打一点非尼布特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please give him some Phenibut.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:46.46,0:39:48.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体_GBK\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}中枢神经系统阻滞剂  用于止痛
Dialogue: 0,0:39:48.19,0:39:49.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我去拿  -他会死的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'll get it. - He's gonna die.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:50.32,0:39:51.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们最好希望他不会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We better hope he doesn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:51.64,0:39:56.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,3点25分起飞吗  太好了  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, so we'll depart at 3:25? That'd be great. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:57.45,0:40:00.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-准备好了吗  -他们说3点45分起飞\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Is he on? - They gave us a departure time for 3:45.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:00.85,0:40:02.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:02.26,0:40:04.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,起飞前  他是不会把情报告诉你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He is not gonna give you information till we're off the ground.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:05.34,0:40:07.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我和你说了  凯特  我不会让你上飞机的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I already told you, Kate, I'm not letting you get on that plane.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:08.23,0:40:10.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他只想离开这个国家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All he wants to do is get out of the country.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:11.07,0:40:12.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只要我们把他带到机场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Soon as we get him to the airport,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:12.15,0:40:14.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他就会把我们需要的情报告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}he'll give us the information we need.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:14.31,0:40:16.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,规则已经变了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The rules have changed.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:17.49,0:40:19.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别动  就快好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hold still, almost there.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:23.86,0:40:26.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,停  我不行了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stop. It's done.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:26.28,0:40:27.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还没做完  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's not done. Now, sir,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:27.38,0:40:30.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请趟好别动  不然我要给你注射镇静剂了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}please lie still or I'll have to sedate you.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:30.59,0:40:32.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我说我不行了  给我走开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I said, I'm done! Get the hell of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:32.75,0:40:34.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-立刻注射安眠药  -等等\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Push the Versed now. - Wait!
Dialogue: 0,0:40:35.71,0:40:36.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:36.99,0:40:37.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:37.53,0:40:41.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  我不行了  我能感觉到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, I'm not gonna make it. I can feel it.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:42.01,0:40:44.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,赶紧告诉我证据在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just tell me where the evidence is now.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:45.28,0:40:48.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在一个存储芯片上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's on a memory chip.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:49.67,0:40:51.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,两个自动化情报资料文件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Two AIF files.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:54.75,0:40:59.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,原始记录证明了塞浦路斯录音是伪造的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The source recordings prove the Cyprus audio is a fake.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:00.43,0:41:02.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,存储芯片在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where is the memory chip?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:03.51,0:41:06.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's in... inside...
Dialogue: 0,0:41:07.38,0:41:09.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-在什么  -在...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Inside what? - Inside...
Dialogue: 0,0:41:10.19,0:41:13.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在哪里  快说  华莱士\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Inside where? Come on, Wallace.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:13.11,0:41:14.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Inside where?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:16.41,0:41:16.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,医生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Doctor!
Dialogue: 0,0:41:16.93,0:41:17.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他出现心室纤颤了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's in V-fib!
Dialogue: 0,0:41:17.75,0:41:19.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让一下  我们要采取救治\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Excuse us. We need to get in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:20.48,0:41:22.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没有脉搏  -已充电至200焦耳\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- No pulse. - We're at 200 joules.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:22.60,0:41:24.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可以开始了  医生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here you go, Doctor.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:26.20,0:41:30.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-充电  123  松手  -松手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Charging. 1-2-3, clear. - Clear.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:32.27,0:41:33.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,心室纤颤仍未减退\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Still in V-fib.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:34.11,0:41:37.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-充电  123   松手  -松手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Charging, 1-2-3, clear. - Clear.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:40.23,0:41:41.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,心室纤颤仍未减退\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Still in V-fib.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:42.21,0:41:45.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-充电  123   松手  -松手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Charging, 1-2-3, clear. - Clear.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:55.33,0:41:56.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,病人宣布死亡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:06.58,0:42:07.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  我们要怎么办\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, what are we gonna do?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:09.30,0:42:09.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:13.79,0:42:14.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我真不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:01.16,0:43:02.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:03.13,0:43:04.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you doing?!
Dialogue: 0,0:43:21.45,0:43:22.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拿到芯片了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We got it.

