[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,1,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.65,0:00:10.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(197.4,200.557)}{\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs25\b1\bord0\shad0\c&H78BDE7&\fad(0,808)}24小时\N\N{\fs15}第二季  第十四集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.45,0:00:13.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(189.6,121.6,193.8,105.6,0,356)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad3\3c&H2F2F2F&\4c&H336D99&}{\fs10}{\t(0,356,\fs20)\fn方正正中黑简体}前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:13.91,0:00:17.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有一个特别行动小组跟着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's no chance that this bomb is ever gonna go off
Dialogue: 0,0:00:17.10,0:00:19.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这颗核弹永远都不可能爆炸的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}with a Special Ops team following it every step of the way.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.53,0:00:16.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(267.6,18.953)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.58,0:00:16.62,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(253.8,27.753)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.62,0:00:16.66,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(240.6,36.553)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.66,0:00:16.70,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(226.8,47.2)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.70,0:00:16.74,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(215.4,55.753)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.74,0:00:16.78,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(197.4,63.753)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.78,0:00:16.82,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(184.8,72.553)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.82,0:00:16.87,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(172.2,82.153)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.87,0:00:16.91,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(158.4,89.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.91,0:00:16.95,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(145.2,98.953)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.95,0:00:18.83,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(135.6,103.753)\fad(0,352)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:19.78,0:00:22.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克·鲍尔找到了珊瑚蛇特种兵\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack Bauer found the Coral Snake commandos.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.30,0:00:24.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,六名队员悉数被杀\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All six members of the team had been killed.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:24.47,0:00:26.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你有什么话还没说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If there's something that you haven't told me...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.60,0:00:30.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去问雪莉  她才是你要找的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ask Sherry. She's the one you wanna talk to.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:30.95,0:00:32.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我父亲为政府做事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My father works for the government.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.17,0:00:31.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(311.4,238.153)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.21,0:00:31.26,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(290.4,223.753)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.26,0:00:31.30,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(271.2,210.953)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.30,0:00:31.34,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(251.4,196.553)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.34,0:00:31.38,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(231,183.753)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.38,0:00:31.42,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(213,170.153)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.42,0:00:31.47,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(193.2,156.553)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.47,0:00:31.51,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(175.2,143.753)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.51,0:00:31.55,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(153.6,130.153)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:31.55,0:00:33.47,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(135.6,116.553)\fad(0,353)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.37,0:00:33.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他说今天有人要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He said that someone's gonna
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.30,0:00:35.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在洛杉矶引爆一枚炸弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}detonate a nuclear bomb in Los Angeles today.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:35.83,0:00:37.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我给你看个东西  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'm gonna show you something. - What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:37.55,0:00:38.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这是个防弹掩体\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's a bomb shelter.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.64,0:00:40.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-引爆了  -炸弹引爆了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It happened. - The bomb went off?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:41.00,0:00:44.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有辐射  我们得待到地下  趁还来得及\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The radiation. We gotta get down below, before it's too late.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.12,0:00:49.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你好  -玛丽  计划有变\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Hello? - Marie. There has been a change of plans.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.61,0:00:47.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(89.4,37.353)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.65,0:00:47.70,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(109.2,46.153)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.70,0:00:47.74,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(128.4,57.353)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.74,0:00:47.78,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(147.6,66.153)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.78,0:00:47.82,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(165.6,76.553)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.82,0:00:47.86,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(184.8,86.953)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.86,0:00:47.90,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(204,94.953)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.90,0:00:47.94,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(221.4,106.953)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:47.94,0:00:49.86,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(240.6,116.553)\fad(0,309)}玛丽·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.57,0:00:51.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么  怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why? What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.29,0:00:54.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽  我们的计划就靠你了  我相信你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Marie, our mission depends on you now. I'm counting on you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.16,0:00:56.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an2\fs16\bord0\shad2\b1\\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\pos(190.8,235.2)}谁来驾驶飞机
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.91,0:00:57.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an2\fs16\bord0\shad2\b1\\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\pos(190.8,235.2)}我来
Dialogue: 0,0:00:57.84,0:00:58.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,真主至上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Allahu Akbar.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:00.90,0:01:03.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们是一支不受控制的队伍  自主行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're a rogue unit, acting on their own authority.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.12,0:01:02.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(68.4,126.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.17,0:01:02.21,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(90.6,126.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.21,0:01:02.25,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs10\c&H449BA1&\pos(113.4,123.753)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.25,0:01:02.29,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(136.2,124.553)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.29,0:01:02.33,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs14\c&H449BA1&\pos(156,122.153)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.33,0:01:02.37,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(178.2,120.553)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.37,0:01:02.41,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs16\c&H449BA1&\pos(199.8,118.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.41,0:01:02.45,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(223.2,116.553)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:02.45,0:01:04.37,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(240,115.753)\fad(0,305)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.33,0:01:05.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我怎么找到他们  -在机场的某处\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How do I find them? - Somewhere at the airport.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.92,0:01:08.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们最好的办法还是由你绕过他们找到炸弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Our best bet is still you getting past them to the bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.57,0:01:11.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那个地方的某处有个核弹头\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There is a nuclear warhead somewhere on-site.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:11.88,0:01:13.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就是它  快跟上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There it is! Go, go!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.10,0:01:16.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把手举过头顶  保持不动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Put your hands above your head! Keep 'em there!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:16.59,0:01:18.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这不是炸弹  这是个假的炸弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This isn't a bomb. It's been rigged to look like one.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:18.55,0:01:20.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这不是炸弹  我们被骗了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is not the bomb. This is a decoy.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:20.45,0:01:23.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,重复  我们仍在寻找核弹装置\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I repeat, we are still looking for the nuclear device.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.06,0:01:29.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs15\t(696,6577,\fs16)\c&H4BAAAD&\fad(1697,1183)\pos(187.2,191.79)}以下故事情节发生在晚上9点到10点之间
Dialogue: 0,0:01:34.80,0:01:36.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  我们轻点拿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, let's go easy with this.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:39.30,0:01:40.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:57.65,0:01:59.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们要在这里处理所有的指纹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're gonna have to process all of the prints here.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:59.22,0:02:01.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,带上你的移动设备  没时间把东西传回去了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Bring in your mobile equipment. We don't have time to send anything back.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.87,0:02:05.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你  真的炸弹在哪里  到底在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You! Where's the real bomb? Where's the real bomb?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.49,0:02:09.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能听懂我说话吗  你会说英语吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you understand me? Do you speak any English?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.35,0:02:12.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你会说英语吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you speak any English?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.20,0:02:15.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抓住他搜身  我去找个翻译\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Secure the man, search him. I'll get us a translator.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.29,0:02:16.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:16.59,0:02:19.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克·鲍尔在21号机棚  需要一名翻译员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is Jack Bauer requesting a translator in hangar 21.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:19.22,0:02:22.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在21号飞机棚  需要一名翻译人员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I am requesting a translator in hangar 21.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:48.66,0:02:52.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅森先生  杰克·鲍尔在二号线\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Mason, Jack Bauer is on line two.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:52.03,0:02:53.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:53.47,0:02:54.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:56.19,0:02:57.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,搜查情况如何  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How's the search going over there, Jack?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:57.76,0:02:59.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还是没有新线索指向炸弹的位置\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Still no new leads on where the bomb is.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:00.98,0:03:03.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,发现诱饵的那架飞机呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about that plane you found the decoy in?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:03.13,0:03:05.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有  我需要你用逆时卫星\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's clean. I need you to use reverse-time satellite to
Dialogue: 0,0:03:05.54,0:03:07.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,追踪下这架飞机最初的位置\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}trace the plane to its original location.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:07.87,0:03:09.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们可能就是在那里装置诱饵炸弹的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's where they would've loaded the decoy bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:09.97,0:03:12.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看看能否从那里找到是谁在背后捣鬼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}See if we can find out who the players are from there.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:12.10,0:03:13.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里和这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Here and here.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:14.59,0:03:16.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治  听着呢吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George? You with me?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.10,0:03:22.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治  你能听到吗  你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George, can you hear me? Are you all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:22.44,0:03:23.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-是的  -乔治\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yeah. - George!
Dialogue: 0,0:03:23.27,0:03:26.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  我就去  逆时卫星\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I'm on it! Reverse-time satellite. Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:27.70,0:03:31.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治  对你今天的遭遇我深感抱歉  真的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George, I'm really sorry about everything that's happened to you today. I am.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:31.82,0:03:33.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是如果你思维混乱  就得退下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But if you can't think clearly, you need to step aside
Dialogue: 0,0:03:33.78,0:03:36.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让其他人接手掌控  我们需要人掌控全局\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and let someone else take over command. We need someone to command now.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.90,0:03:39.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没有其他人了  杰克  -托尼呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- There isn't anybody else, Jack. - What about Tony?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:42.45,0:03:45.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我清醒着呢  我没问题的  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got it together. I can handle it. All right?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:47.65,0:03:48.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:48.98,0:03:51.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们还真有个问题  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- We do have another problem. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.91,0:03:53.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你发现死亡的六名成员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The six dead commandos you found,
Dialogue: 0,0:03:53.50,0:03:56.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,发现可能还有一个逃跑了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}turns out there was a seventh may have escaped.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:56.93,0:03:59.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不可能  我检查了所有的枪伤\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That wouldn't make sense,I examined all the gunshot wounds.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:59.42,0:04:01.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,成员中的三个人绝对认识开枪者\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Three of the commandos definitely knew who the shooter was-
Dialogue: 0,0:04:02.08,0:04:03.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们的伤口射击距离很近\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}their wounds were at close range.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:03.91,0:04:05.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,其余三人有挣扎的痕迹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The other three showed signs of a struggle,
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.44,0:04:07.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这表明他们有时间做出反应\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}which indicates they had time to react.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.24,0:04:09.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以第七个人没逃跑\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So the seventh didn't escape.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:09.79,0:04:11.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没错  他就是开枪者\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right. He was a shooter.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:13.52,0:04:15.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治  我得走了  尽快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George, I gotta go. Get me an ID
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.43,0:04:18.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-帮我查到第七个人的身份好吗  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- on the seventh commando as soon as you can. OK? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:18.01,0:04:19.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这就查  -很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'm working on it. - Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:19.68,0:04:20.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,搜到什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you got?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:20.65,0:04:23.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,钱包  有现金  没身份证或信用卡\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A wallet, some cash, no ID, no credit cards.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.15,0:04:31.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他要说话  翻译人员到底在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He wants to talk. Where the hell is my translator?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:37.85,0:04:39.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,华纳先生  您女儿凯特的电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Warner, it's your daughter Kate.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:40.32,0:04:41.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-凯特  -爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Kate? - Dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:41.58,0:04:43.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  你在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate, where are you?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:43.57,0:04:45.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没事  我在一个机场\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm fine. I'm at an airport.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:45.74,0:04:48.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,机场  你要出城吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}An airport? Are you leaving the city?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:48.80,0:04:52.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  还不走  我在帮助一个探员调查\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, Not yet. I'm helping one of the agents on an investigation.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:53.31,0:04:56.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸爸  他们告诉你雷扎的事了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Dad... did they tell you about Reza?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:56.64,0:05:01.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  我无法相信他们说的  玛丽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I... I can't believe what they're saying about Marie,
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.09,0:05:05.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,与恐怖分子为伍  她杀了雷扎  我...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that she's with these terrorists, that she killed Reza. I...
Dialogue: 0,0:05:05.60,0:05:06.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我明白  爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know, Dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.24,0:05:09.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-凯特  -爸爸  等一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Kate... - Dad, hold on a second.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:09.08,0:05:10.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是炸弹  我们逮捕了飞行员\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It wasn't the bomb. We arrested the pilot.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:10.81,0:05:12.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你帮忙翻译  走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need your help as a translator.Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:12.89,0:05:14.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸爸  我等会再打给你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Dad, I'm gonna have to call you back.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:15.02,0:05:16.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你没事吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:16.09,0:05:20.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  我很好  爸爸  我爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, I'm fine. Dad, I love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:21.16,0:05:22.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也爱你  宝贝\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I love you, too, sweetheart.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:24.64,0:05:27.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,罗杰·斯坦顿到底和你说了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What exactly did Roger Stanton tell you?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:28.03,0:05:29.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雪莉也参与了这些\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sherry was somehow involved in this.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:31.21,0:05:34.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-核弹威胁  -他没细说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- The nuclear threat? - He didn't elaborate.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:34.70,0:05:35.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他就说了这些\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's all he said.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:42.78,0:05:45.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亲爱的  他们说这很紧急\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Baby, they said it was urgent.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:45.20,0:05:46.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是炸弹吗  他们找到了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is it about the bomb? Have they found it?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:46.95,0:05:48.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还没呢  坐下吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not yet. Sit down.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:51.49,0:05:53.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我刚和罗杰·斯坦顿聊了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just spoke with Roger Stanton.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:53.06,0:05:55.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他承认炸弹的事他已经知道好几周了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He confesses that he's known about the bomb for weeks.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:55.91,0:05:57.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,几周\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For weeks?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:58.11,0:05:59.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他为什么要隐瞒你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why would he withhold that from you?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.97,0:06:02.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他说他想等炸弹到美国领土上时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He said  he wanted to wait until the bomb was on US soil
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.08,0:06:03.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,再拦截它\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}before he intercepted it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:04.09,0:06:05.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那么他知道炸弹在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So he knows where the bomb is.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:05.71,0:06:07.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他追踪的人知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The men he had tracking it did.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.70,0:06:10.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不过他们全死了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But they're all dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:11.28,0:06:13.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,炸弹还在  而且我们不知道在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The bomb's still out there, and we don't know where it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.30,0:06:18.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天呐  天呐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:22.09,0:06:24.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我说的这些你已经知道了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Am I telling you something you already know?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:25.83,0:06:27.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么  -和我说实话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What? - Tell me now.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:29.89,0:06:31.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有没有不可理喻到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Have you done the unthinkable
Dialogue: 0,0:06:31.93,0:06:34.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,与罗杰·斯坦顿为伍吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and put yourself in league with Roger Stanton?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:34.61,0:06:37.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,太过分了  当然没有  他说什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's outrageous! Of course not! What did he say?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.99,0:06:39.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,坐下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sit down.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:39.36,0:06:41.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-大卫  -坐下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- David... - Sit down!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:43.58,0:06:46.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他说和我作对你也有份\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He said you were involved, working against me.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.54,0:06:48.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他在说谎  大卫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's lying, David!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.07,0:06:51.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天下午之前我都没见过罗杰·斯坦顿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I never even met Roger Stanton not until this afternoon!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.20,0:06:53.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我知道这不是真的  -他在戏弄你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I know that's not true. - He's playing you!
Dialogue: 0,0:06:53.41,0:06:56.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不论他做什么  都是为了让你不信任我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Whatever he's doing, he's doing it so that you won't believe I...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:56.42,0:06:57.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别说了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just stop it!
Dialogue: 0,0:07:02.86,0:07:08.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雪莉  我们现在即将面临一场战争\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sherry... right now we are teetering on the brink of a war
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.86,0:07:11.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可能会使数百万人丧命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that will lead to the deaths of millions of people.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:12.04,0:07:15.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们今天必须阻止这场灾难\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have to stop this disaster today,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:15.42,0:07:17.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在  在它开始前\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}right now, before it begins.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:18.62,0:07:20.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你对我有所隐瞒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If there is something you're not telling me,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:20.70,0:07:23.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,任何可能对找到炸弹有帮助的信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}anything that could help us find this bomb,
Dialogue: 0,0:07:23.84,0:07:26.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,作为美国总统  我要求你...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}as President of the United States, I order you...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.87,0:07:31.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  作为你口中的爱人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, as someone that you claim you love...
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.43,0:07:38.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我请求你  帮助我  雪莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm asking: help me, Sherry.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.93,0:07:51.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,几个月前的半夜  我接到一个朋友的电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got a phone call... A few months ago in the middle of the night
Dialogue: 0,0:07:52.40,0:07:56.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他是国安局的高层\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}from a friend of mine who's high up in NSA.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.75,0:08:00.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他告诉我罗杰·斯坦顿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He told me that Roger Stanton
Dialogue: 0,0:08:00.47,0:08:03.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,第二天早上想先和我聊聊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}wanted to speak to me first thing in the morning,
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.64,0:08:09.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以我们在弗吉尼亚州的一个公园见面了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and so we met at a park in Virginia.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:12.53,0:08:13.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他想怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What did he want?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:14.76,0:08:17.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他想招募我  -做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- He wanted to recruit me. - To do what?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:20.93,0:08:25.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他想知道谁对你忠诚  谁会出卖你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He wanted to know who was loyal to you and who could be turned.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.27,0:08:31.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他想  他想知道你的弱点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He wanted... He wanted to know where you were weak.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.30,0:08:36.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你告诉他了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And you told him?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.49,0:08:40.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:45.44,0:08:48.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我那么做是为了获取他的信任\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I only did it to gain his confidence.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.22,0:08:54.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我和他不是一伙儿的  我这么做是为了你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was not aligning myself with him. I was doing it for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:57.29,0:09:01.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大卫  我知道你不相信我  给我三十分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}David, I know you don't believe me, but just give me 30 minutes
Dialogue: 0,0:09:01.58,0:09:03.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大卫  就三十分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}David, just 30 minutes
Dialogue: 0,0:09:03.60,0:09:05.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我证明我说的是事实\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to prove to you that I'm telling the truth,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:05.86,0:09:10.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,证明我所做的都是为了保护你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that I did all of this to protect you,
Dialogue: 0,0:09:10.92,0:09:12.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,绝非想伤害你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}not to hurt you.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:18.65,0:09:21.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想他是说他这么做是为了他的家人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think he's saying he did it for his family.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:21.14,0:09:22.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们保证给他钱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They promised him money.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:22.99,0:09:24.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,问问"他们"是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ask him who "They" is.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:37.89,0:09:39.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,赛伊德·阿里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Syed Ali.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.89,0:09:44.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,问问他是否知道有第二个炸弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ask him if he knows about a second bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:50.45,0:09:51.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Eh?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:51.51,0:09:55.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我觉得不太对  我想我们的方言表述不同\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't think that was right. I think we have different dialects.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.09,0:09:56.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没关系  再试试\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It doesn't matter. Just keep trying.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:05.46,0:10:07.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  翻译官来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack, the translator's here.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.30,0:10:09.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是杰克·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:09.97,0:10:12.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,犯人在那  凯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The subject's there. Kate?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:15.78,0:10:19.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-真抱歉  杰克  -你做得很好  很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'm really sorry, Jack. - You did great. You did great.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:19.37,0:10:21.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,贝克探员会带你回控制区\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Agent Baker is gonna take you back to the controlled area.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.30,0:10:23.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我尽快过去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll be there as soon as I can.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.72,0:10:30.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,问他是否知道有第二个炸弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ask him if he knows about a second bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.14,0:10:36.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他说他什么都不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He said he doesn't know anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:46.49,0:10:49.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请出示证件  给我看下你的证件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}ID, please. Can I see your ID?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.09,0:11:01.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那边那些是什么人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who are those people over there?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:02.02,0:11:04.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们要封锁机场  检查所有人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're locking down the airport, checking everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:04.39,0:11:05.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,稍等我一会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Excuse me for one second.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:32.45,0:11:35.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,问问他的学校和他的金主的名字\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ask him where he went to school and the name of his sponsor.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:41.86,0:11:43.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,简直不敢相信炸弹爆炸了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't believe the bomb went off.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:44.71,0:11:46.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你听到什么了  多少人受伤\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What did you hear? How many people?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:46.91,0:11:50.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不知道  传送器坏了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know. The transmission just went dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.96,0:11:53.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你还好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:11:54.50,0:11:56.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我爸爸  我要和他联系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My dad, I need to get in touch with my dad.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:57.12,0:11:59.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会的  不过现在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We will. But for right now,
Dialogue: 0,0:11:59.66,0:12:02.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们必须待在这里  这里是安全的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we have to stay down here, where it's safe.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:02.55,0:12:06.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们不清楚辐射云会向哪里蔓延\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have no idea which way that radiation cloud is gonna travel.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:08.67,0:12:12.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我看看短波收音机上能找到什么  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll see if I can pick something up on the short-wave radio, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:32.89,0:12:37.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,洛杉矶最爱的全天候广播  全年无休\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}...LA's favourite all-talk radio all the time, 24-7.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.26,0:12:38.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,关于学校代金券的争论\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The school voucher debate
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.99,0:12:42.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,又开始升温了...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is really beginning to heat up again here...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:46.81,0:12:48.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说什么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What did they say?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:48.56,0:12:50.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么都没收到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I couldn't get anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.18,0:12:52.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,辐射在干扰无线电\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The radiation is interfering with the antenna.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:52.49,0:12:55.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,可能得几个小时才能收到信号\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It could be hours before we're able to pick up anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:00.00,0:13:01.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们会怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's gonna happen to us?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:13.53,0:13:16.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-没事的  -我很害怕\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Shh, it's OK. - I'm scared.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:17.65,0:13:19.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别害怕  没什么可怕的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't be scared. You got nothing to be scared of.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:20.79,0:13:23.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我保证我们在这里很安全\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're safe down here. I promise.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:38.27,0:13:40.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你就是分局派来的新助理吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You must be the new assistant Division sent.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:40.83,0:13:43.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我叫凯莉·特纳  您就是乔治·梅森吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Carrie Turner. You must be George Mason.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:46.51,0:13:47.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Excuse me...
Dialogue: 0,0:13:49.97,0:13:51.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你看起来比我预期得还差\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You look worse than I expected.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:52.91,0:13:56.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-有什么能帮你的吗  -没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Is there something I can help you with? - No, I'm set.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:56.38,0:13:58.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我一直遵从分局的指示\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've been following everything from Division.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:58.86,0:14:01.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会接替宝拉的工作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll be taking over from Paula,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:01.08,0:14:03.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你需要用服务器做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so if there's anything you need the server to do,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:03.52,0:14:04.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我来搞定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll make it happen.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:04.80,0:14:08.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好  过去一小时情况有变\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good. The situation reports have changed in the past hour,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:08.38,0:14:11.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以你得刷新所有电脑屏幕\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so you have to refresh all the computer monitors.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:11.50,0:14:12.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:12.87,0:14:15.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,确保没有人碰我的系统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just make sure everyone keeps their hands off my system.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:15.71,0:14:16.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ok.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:17.77,0:14:22.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅森先生  我应该直接向谁汇报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Mason... who do I report to... directly?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:24.78,0:14:26.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,向我汇报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You report to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:27.40,0:14:29.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没有恶意  梅森先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No offense, Mr. Mason, but
Dialogue: 0,0:14:30.25,0:14:32.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但听人说你不会在这里待很久\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}rumour has it you're not gonna be around much longer.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:33.45,0:14:37.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以我应该向谁汇报\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So... who do I report to?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:38.46,0:14:40.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,终于有我喜欢的人在这里了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I finally get someone around here who I like,
Dialogue: 0,0:14:40.03,0:14:42.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会在这里享受这段时光的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and I'm not gonna be around to enjoy it.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:43.72,0:14:45.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼·阿尔梅达\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony Almeida.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:47.08,0:14:49.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有米歇尔·戴斯勒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And Michelle D-Dessler.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:50.28,0:14:53.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你说米歇尔·戴斯勒吗  -是  怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Did you say Michelle Dessler? - Yes, I did. Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:53.93,0:14:58.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们在分局共过事  那时我是她的主管\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We worked together at District. I was her boss then.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:59.82,0:15:01.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你告诉我这个是什么意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And you're telling me this why?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:03.00,0:15:06.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事  这不重要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It'll be fine. It's not important.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:09.03,0:15:10.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅森先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Mason?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:11.64,0:15:14.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,天哪  梅森先生  梅森先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My God. Mr. Mason? Mr. Mason!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:15.37,0:15:17.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你还好吗  -还好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Are you all right? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:18.14,0:15:20.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(168.6,61.6,105.6,35.2,779,2447)}{\fn方正大标宋_GBK\fs13\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H1D2235&}麦克纳布航空服务
Dialogue: 0,0:15:20.63,0:15:24.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-有照证件  -谢谢你们的合作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Picture ID? - Thank you for your cooperation.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:24.18,0:15:27.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们会尽快帮你们离开这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We will try to get you out of here as quickly as we can.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:33.53,0:15:37.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,手臂伸直放在外面  站着不要动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Arms straight out. Just stand perfectly still.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:37.64,0:15:40.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,提前准备把你兜里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Prepare to give the scanners
Dialogue: 0,0:15:40.03,0:15:42.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,任何金属物品送进扫描仪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}any metal objects in your pockets beforehand.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.83,0:15:45.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这会加快队伍前进的速度\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It will speed the process through the line.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:49.23,0:15:51.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-玛丽  -不用担心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Marie! - No need to be concerned.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:52.12,0:15:55.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请配合  感谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please just cooperate. We appreciate it.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:55.69,0:15:58.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不好意思  你不能去那里  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Whoa, excuse me. You can't go there. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:15:58.47,0:16:00.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,每个人离开前都要搜身\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Everyone is searched before they're let go.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.57,0:16:03.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-是我妹妹  很重要  -抱歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It's my sister. It's important. - Sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:05.18,0:16:06.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等  给你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wait, here.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:06.37,0:16:08.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反恐组的杰克·鲍尔让我来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm with Jack Bauer, CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.22,0:16:12.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好  进去吧  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- OK. Go on. - Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:12.71,0:16:14.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你能联系杰克·鲍尔吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Could you get in touch with Jack Bauer?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:14.56,0:16:16.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉他玛丽·华纳来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell him Marie Warner is here.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.54,0:16:17.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他会懂的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He'll understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:18.46,0:16:21.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,巡警  我们找反恐组的杰克·鲍尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Dispatch, we need to locate a Jack Bauer with CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:22.11,0:16:23.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,收到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Copy that.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:58.06,0:17:00.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-玛丽  -我需要你的证件  凯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Marie. - I need your badge, Kate.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:00.47,0:17:02.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你去哪了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where've you been?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:02.53,0:17:04.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-给我你的证件  -玛丽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Give me your badge. - Marie...
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.26,0:17:07.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,闭嘴  你个蠢货\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shut up. You stupid idiot.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:07.11,0:17:09.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么你要开始问东问西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why did you have to start snooping around?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:10.17,0:17:11.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:11.46,0:17:12.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你总是把我当成\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You have always treated me
Dialogue: 0,0:17:12.66,0:17:15.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,无助的受伤动物一样照顾我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}like I was some helpless injured animal.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.83,0:17:18.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好像我没有你的照顾就没法活一样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Like I couldn't get by without you looking over me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:19.09,0:17:20.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What happened to you?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:22.06,0:17:24.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我睁开了眼  就是这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I opened my eyes. That's what happened to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.45,0:17:29.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我曾很可悲  像你一样  直到见到赛伊德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was pathetic, just like you. Until I met Syed.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.95,0:17:33.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,直到我看到人生中和这个国家中的谎言和伪善\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Until I saw the lies and hypocrisy of my life, of this country,
Dialogue: 0,0:17:33.94,0:17:36.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,像爸爸这样的人  帮政府做事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}of people like Dad, who help the government.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:36.55,0:17:38.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他为中情局工作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He works for the CIA.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:38.02,0:17:39.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道  所以呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know. So what?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:39.30,0:17:40.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So what?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:40.40,0:17:43.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道他们在世界上造成的痛苦吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you have any idea the suffering they cause around the world?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:43.76,0:17:47.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行了吧  你才六岁吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, please. What are you, six years old?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:47.46,0:17:49.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你现在觉得爸爸是敌人了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You think Dad is the enemy now?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.10,0:17:52.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不敢相信你有这么不知感恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't believe how ungrateful you are.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:52.91,0:17:54.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我应该感恩吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I should be grateful?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:54.34,0:17:57.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当然  妈妈死后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, absolutely. Dad and I
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.30,0:18:00.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸爸和我为了你完全改变了生活\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}turned our lives upside down for you after Mom died.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:00.67,0:18:02.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,难道为了你今天变成这样吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is what we did it for?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:03.01,0:18:05.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让你被什么疯子洗脑吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So you could be brainwashed by some lunatic?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.18,0:18:07.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,醒醒吧  你要变成\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wake up! You're about to
Dialogue: 0,0:18:07.83,0:18:10.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,美国历史上杀戮最多的杀人犯了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}become the biggest murderer in American history!
Dialogue: 0,0:18:20.84,0:18:24.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你要干什么  -给我你的证件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What are you gonna do? - Give me your badge.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:25.39,0:18:26.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:27.66,0:18:28.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.30,0:18:35.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽  听我说  城里有个核弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Marie, listen to me. There's a nuclear bomb in the city.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:37.09,0:18:38.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不管你信仰什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No matter what you believe,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.50,0:18:41.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不会想让无辜的人丧命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you don't want all those innocent people to die.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.96,0:18:45.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把证件给我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Give me the badge.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:46.41,0:18:49.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  我不信你会开枪打我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. I don't believe you'd shoot me.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:49.67,0:18:50.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I will...
Dialogue: 0,0:18:52.04,0:18:54.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为这比你的生命更重要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}because this is more important than your life.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:56.32,0:18:57.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,或是我的生命\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Or my life.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:05.41,0:19:06.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  趴下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate, stay down!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:08.63,0:19:10.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-趴下  -我的手臂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Stay down! - My arm!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:10.85,0:19:12.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,收走她的武器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Secure the weapon!
Dialogue: 0,0:19:12.05,0:19:13.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你没事吧  -没事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You all right? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:17.85,0:19:19.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想这是你妹妹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I take it that's your sister.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:46.97,0:19:48.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你怎么不治好她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What don't you treat her?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:48.21,0:19:49.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,至少给她点减轻痛苦的东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}At least give her something for the pain.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:49.61,0:19:51.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等她告诉我她知道什么我就给她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I will when she tells us what she knows.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:51.74,0:19:53.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不能让她受苦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You can't let her suffer.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:53.34,0:19:57.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要让我用我的方法  你要相信我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're gonna have to let me do this my way. You have to trust me.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:57.12,0:19:58.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道她是你妹妹  你爱她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know she is your sister and that you love her.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:58.20,0:20:02.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我要为百万人的性命着想\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I have to worry about the millions of lives at stake.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:02.70,0:20:05.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她是唯一知道炸弹在哪的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She is the only person who knows where this bomb is.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.83,0:20:09.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要利用能找到的一切优势来阻止它\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need to use every advantage I've got to find it and stop it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:09.49,0:20:11.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你肯定也懂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Surely you understand that.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.38,0:20:14.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just let me do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:25.70,0:20:26.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,手臂给我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Give me your arm.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:50.13,0:20:52.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽  炸弹在哪  真正的炸弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where's the bomb, Marie? The real bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.34,0:20:56.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你去死吧  混蛋  我什么也不会说的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You can go to hell, you bastard. I'm not telling you anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.70,0:21:10.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想知道为什么这么痛吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You wanna know why the pain's so severe?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.89,0:21:15.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,子弹还在你手臂里  顶着这里骨头\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The bullet's still in your arm, lodged right up against the bone in here.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:19.42,0:21:21.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我炸弹在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell me where the bomb is,
Dialogue: 0,0:21:21.01,0:21:23.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会给你止痛并且治好你的手臂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and I'll get you something for the pain and treat your arm.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:26.65,0:21:28.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托了  玛丽  说吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please, Marie, just talk to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.63,0:21:31.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说吧  告诉我炸弹在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just talk to me. Tell me where the bomb is.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.64,0:21:32.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No!
Dialogue: 0,0:21:45.54,0:21:48.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道你觉得你现在的行为会光大你的信仰\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know you think what you're doing now will further your cause.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:49.02,0:21:52.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但打心底里我觉得你不会真正去完成\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Deep down, I don't think you wanna go through with it.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:52.24,0:21:53.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不觉得你能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't think you can
Dialogue: 0,0:21:53.03,0:21:55.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为杀害百万无辜民众找到正当理由\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}justify killing millions of innocent civilians.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:56.35,0:21:58.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个国家没有人是无辜的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nobody's innocent in this country.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:01.83,0:22:03.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不怕死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not afraid to die.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:13.61,0:22:17.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不信  我见过赴死之人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't believe you. I've seen people who are willing to die.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:17.76,0:22:20.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我曾直视他们的眼睛  就像现在这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've looked them straight in the eye, just like right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:23.18,0:22:24.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不是那种人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're not one of them.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.43,0:22:29.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想给你止痛剂  但你必须先帮我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wanna give you a painkiller, but you must help me first.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.73,0:22:31.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请告诉我炸弹在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please tell me where the bomb is.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:32.10,0:22:33.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,炸弹在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where's the bomb?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:53.94,0:22:55.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要检查无线电\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna check the radio.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:00.86,0:23:02.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有糖吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you have any sugar?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.66,0:23:06.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有  在后面角落的架子上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, yeah, it's in the back corner, on the shelf there.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:11.85,0:23:13.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}糖
Dialogue: 0,0:23:17.36,0:23:19.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,电视连着同一个天线吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is the TV hooked up to the same antenna?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.26,0:23:27.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(118.2,142.4)}{\fn方正粗黑简体\fs12\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&}周末天气
Dialogue: 0,0:23:26.45,0:23:28.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,每个人都可以拿出高尔夫球杆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Everyone can take out their golf clubs...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:29.38,0:23:31.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这球...  挥杆吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}...delivery is... Swung on.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:31.99,0:23:34.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,著名民事领导和好莱坞明星\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}...prominent civic leaders and Hollywood stars...
Dialogue: 0,0:23:32.14,0:23:33.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(112.2,161.6)}{\fn方正粗黑简体\fs12\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&}蒂娜·兰瑟
Dialogue: 0,0:23:34.68,0:23:38.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,创纪录的民众今天聚集在海滩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}...record numbers today gathered at beaches
Dialogue: 0,0:23:38.60,0:23:42.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,庆祝南加州美妙的天气\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to celebrate the beautiful weather of southern California,
Dialogue: 0,0:23:42.22,0:23:45.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,同样的天气会持续整个周末\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}which will continue throughout the weekend.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:58.19,0:23:59.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没有信号\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Still nothing.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.08,0:24:05.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\frz357.7\pos(241.8,87.2)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs12\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H56665F&}乔纳森·华莱士
Dialogue: 0,0:24:03.26,0:24:05.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-就是他吗  -是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- This is our man? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:05.62,0:24:06.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,第七小队\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Seventh commando.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:07.36,0:24:09.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔纳森·华莱士队长\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Captain Jonathan Wallace.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:09.12,0:24:11.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在海湾战争中带领一个狙击小队\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Led a sniper unit in the Gulf War,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:11.35,0:24:13.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在马来西亚领导过暗杀任务\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}led an assassination detail in Malaysia.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:13.73,0:24:15.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你告诉杰克了吗  -现在就办\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Have you got this to Jack? - I'm on it.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:15.83,0:24:18.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,和指挥中心建立一个关于他的情报共享分局\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Start up a shared volume with OC on this guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:26.43,0:24:27.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你好  米歇尔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hello, Michelle.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:30.23,0:24:31.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯莉  你在这里做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Carrie, what are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:31.80,0:24:33.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,分局派我来代替宝拉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Division sent me over to replace Paula.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:35.56,0:24:38.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  需要我帮你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right. Do you need help
Dialogue: 0,0:24:38.18,0:24:40.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,进入网络里任何锁住的分局吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}getting into any of the locked volumes on the network?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:40.07,0:24:44.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不用  我都弄好了  你看起来真不错\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, actually. I'm all up and running. You look great, by the way.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:44.87,0:24:46.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-算了吧  凯莉  -什么算了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Stop it, Carrie. - Stop what?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:49.19,0:24:50.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你今天不是我的领导  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're not my boss today, all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:24:51.77,0:24:52.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你是来代替宝拉的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you're here to replace Paula,
Dialogue: 0,0:24:52.93,0:24:55.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,严格来讲你就是我的下属\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}then technically you work for me.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:56.10,0:24:59.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行  给我下命令吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fine. Give me an order.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:03.77,0:25:06.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,洛杉矶有个核弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's a nuclear bomb in Los Angeles.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:06.78,0:25:08.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们奉命找到它\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We've been charged with finding it.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:08.91,0:25:12.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不如你开始分析这些吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So why don't you start by analyzing these?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:17.58,0:25:18.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.10,0:25:34.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-托尼  有时间吗  -没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Tony, do you have a second? - Sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:36.60,0:25:37.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What is it?
Dialogue: 0,0:25:39.82,0:25:43.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想我该退下了  我感觉不太好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think it's time I step down. I'm not feeling so hot here.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.84,0:25:47.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-有什么我能做的吗  -有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Is there anything I can do? - Actually, yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:48.72,0:25:53.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等明天一切都结束了  替我向大家道别\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tomorrow, when this is all over, say goodbye to everybody for me
Dialogue: 0,0:25:54.76,0:25:57.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉他们和他们一起共事很荣幸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and let them know what an honour it was working with them
Dialogue: 0,0:25:58.02,0:26:00.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,以及我认为他们都十分出色  所有人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and what a great job I think they all did, everybody.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:01.45,0:26:02.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:04.65,0:26:05.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,早晨我对你说的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This morning when I told you
Dialogue: 0,0:26:05.67,0:26:07.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我等不及要离开这里的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I couldn't wait to get out of here...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:09.15,0:26:10.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在我不这么觉得了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't feel that way any more.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:13.10,0:26:15.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-给你  -这是什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Here you go. - What's this?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:16.49,0:26:19.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,反恐组和分局的登入密码\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Access codes for the CTU and Division.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:20.59,0:26:22.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不能收下这个  乔治\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't take this, George.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:22.59,0:26:25.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只有反恐组主管才可以有这种权限\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Only the CTU director is allowed that kind of access.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:25.92,0:26:28.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你就是新的反恐组主管  托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're the new CTU director, Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:29.20,0:26:32.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不能给我升职  乔治  只有夏普尔可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You can't promote me, George. Chappelle is the only one who can do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:33.13,0:26:36.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我刚刚和夏普尔说过了  你就是新任主管\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just talked to Chappelle. You're the new guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:39.71,0:26:41.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听我说  乔治\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen, George...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:43.98,0:26:44.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry, I...
Dialogue: 0,0:26:44.50,0:26:46.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不要这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:26:50.78,0:26:51.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,祝你好运\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good luck.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:28.12,0:27:29.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会在上面指挥\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll be operating from up here,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:29.79,0:27:32.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以我需要把登入密码录入系统\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so I'll need my access codes piped into the system.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:32.94,0:27:35.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,收到  所有人已就绪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Got it. Everyone's ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:35.18,0:27:36.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good. Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:52.97,0:27:54.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你们还没听说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In case you haven't heard,
Dialogue: 0,0:27:55.55,0:27:57.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治·梅森今早遭到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George Mason was exposed to
Dialogue: 0,0:27:57.04,0:27:59.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,致死剂量的钚辐射\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}a lethal dose of Plutonium this morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:00.38,0:28:02.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,恐怕他撑不了多久了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm afraid he hasn't got much time.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:03.38,0:28:05.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他刚刚离开了办公区  也不会回来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He just left the office and won't be coming back,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:05.83,0:28:09.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果没有其他命令  我就是主管\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}which means that I'll be in charge until further notice.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:10.43,0:28:13.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果是平时  我们会为乔治默哀\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, on a normal day, we'd be mourning George,
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.17,0:28:16.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,正如我们会哀悼艾弗斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}just like we would've mourned Ivers
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.68,0:28:19.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,克拉克  宝拉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and Clark and Paula
Dialogue: 0,0:28:20.16,0:28:22.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,以及今天在这里丧生的其余同事们一样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and the rest of our co-workers who were killed here today.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.48,0:28:24.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,遗憾的是  我们得先把对哀悼情绪放在一边\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Unfortunately, we have to hold our thoughts of them
Dialogue: 0,0:28:25.79,0:28:28.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,直到我们解除了这场危机为止\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}until we can get through this present crisis.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.89,0:28:33.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大家继续工作吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So... let's get back to work.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:36.64,0:28:37.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:39.62,0:28:41.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你刚刚说的那番话很感人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It was a nice thing you just did.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:43.90,0:28:45.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,机场那边怎么样了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's going on at the airfield?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:45.10,0:28:47.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克还在审问玛丽·华纳\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack's still interrogating Marie Warner.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.27,0:28:49.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,目前我们没有任何新线索\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So far we don't have anything new.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:49.23,0:28:51.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好吧  有消息通知我  当然\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- All right. Keep me posted. - Sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:58.30,0:29:00.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别昏过去  玛丽  别昏过去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stay with me, Marie. Stay with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:01.14,0:29:02.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,史蒂夫  跟我来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Steve, walk with me.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:03.09,0:29:04.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你给她拿点止痛药\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need you get her some Demerol for the pain.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:04.61,0:29:06.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她要开始休克了  我需要她神志清醒\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's starting to go under shock. I need her lucid.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:06.89,0:29:08.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-需要多久  -五分钟应该就行了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- For how long? - Five minutes should do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:10.26,0:29:10.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我过去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Clear.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:11.02,0:29:12.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-凯特  -嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Kate. - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:14.41,0:29:16.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-她说了什么  -她什么都还没说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What did she say? - She hasn't said anything yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:17.35,0:29:20.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我需要你的帮忙  -帮忙  怎么帮\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'm gonna need your help. - Help? How?
Dialogue: 0,0:29:20.47,0:29:21.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是她姐姐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're her sister.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:21.70,0:29:23.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要你试着把她带回现实当中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need you to try bring her back to some kind of reality.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.82,0:29:25.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不像你这样了解她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know her like that. I don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.70,0:29:28.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我以为我了解她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I thought I did.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.19,0:29:31.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她已经不是我今早认识的那个玛丽了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's a different person from the Marie I knew this morning.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:31.76,0:29:32.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  凯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, Kate.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:32.66,0:29:34.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她还是那个和你一起长大的女孩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's the same girl you've grew up with your whole life.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:34.74,0:29:36.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在她只是在照搬\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right now she's just regurgitating everything
Dialogue: 0,0:29:36.80,0:29:38.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,赛伊德·阿里所教给她的一切\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that Syed Ali ever taught her.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:38.95,0:29:41.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我需要你提醒她  她曾经所爱的事物\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need you to remind her of the things she used to love.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:42.30,0:29:44.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你可以做到的  凯特  你可以打动她的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You can do this, Kate. You can get to her.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:51.01,0:29:52.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:55.60,0:29:58.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为吃了止痛药  她会有点昏昏沉沉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's going to be a little groggy because of the painkiller, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:06.94,0:30:07.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你还好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You all right?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:09.88,0:30:10.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:21.35,0:30:23.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Marie.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:25.77,0:30:27.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hi, Kate.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:30.59,0:30:32.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,走开  我不需要你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get away. I don't need you.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:34.97,0:30:38.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你为什么不帮我们  -我正在帮你们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Why won't you help us? - I am gonna help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:40.66,0:30:44.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会帮你们  不让你们成为问题的一部分\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna help you stop being a part of the problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:30:48.78,0:30:53.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以如果今天我和爸爸死了  你也没关系吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So it's OK with you if Dad and I died today?
Dialogue: 0,0:30:56.58,0:31:00.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我杀了雷扎  我爱过他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I killed Reza. And I loved him.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:01.28,0:31:03.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那我为什么会在乎你和爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why would I care about you and Dad?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:05.95,0:31:08.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为我们在乎你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because we care for you.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:09.42,0:31:10.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为我们爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because we love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:15.59,0:31:17.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你为什么要这么做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why are you doing this?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:18.96,0:31:21.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽  你本可以拯救所有的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Marie, you could save everyone.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:22.84,0:31:25.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你本可以阻止这件可怕的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You could stop this terrible thing from happening.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:27.35,0:31:32.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不想  我做不到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't want to. I can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:32.29,0:31:36.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽  我求求你了  别这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Marie, I'm begging you. Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:37.60,0:31:38.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:50.46,0:31:53.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的手臂  天呐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My arm... God!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:55.80,0:31:57.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特  我需要你退后\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate, I need you to step back.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:02.21,0:32:03.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽  止痛药的效力开始减退了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Marie, that's the Demerol wearing off.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:03.72,0:32:06.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我炸弹的下落  我会多给你一点止痛药\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell me where the bomb is, and I'll get you more.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:07.44,0:32:09.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请你告诉我炸弹的下落  我可以帮你止痛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please tell me where the bomb is, I can make the pain go away.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:09.78,0:32:11.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽  告诉他吧  求你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Marie, just tell him, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:12.05,0:32:13.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,炸弹在哪  玛丽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where is the bomb, Marie?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:13.80,0:32:15.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  给她止痛药吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jake, give her something for the pain.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:15.22,0:32:16.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:17.87,0:32:19.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽  求你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Marie, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:20.24,0:32:21.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我炸弹的下落\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell me where the bomb is.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:21.77,0:32:22.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,炸弹在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where is the bomb?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:22.60,0:32:25.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-凯特  让他住手  -不  玛丽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Katie, make him stop! - No, Marie.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:25.92,0:32:27.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你让他住手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You make him stop.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:31.67,0:32:33.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,疼痛只会越来越严重\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The pain's only gonna get worse.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:33.26,0:32:34.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请告诉我炸弹在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please just tell me where the bomb is.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:36.45,0:32:39.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没事  告诉我炸弹在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's all right. Just tell me where the bomb is.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:45.22,0:32:47.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在手提箱里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In the suitcase.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:47.50,0:32:48.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,手提箱在哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where's the suitcase?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:52.19,0:32:55.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-在车里  -什么车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- In the van. - What van?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:55.82,0:32:57.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,车开往什么地方\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where was the van headed?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:59.18,0:33:01.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-市中心  -市中心哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Downtown. - Where downtown?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:01.81,0:33:03.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿尔科塔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}At the Arco Towers.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:03.97,0:33:06.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是什么样的车  颜色和产地呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What kind of van was it? What colour? What make?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:07.94,0:33:10.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,绿色的  我不知道产地\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Uh... green. I don't know what make.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:10.66,0:33:12.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们要找一辆绿色车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're looking for a green van.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:12.42,0:33:14.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,核弹也许在车里的手提箱里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The nuke may be inside the suitcase in the van.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:14.33,0:33:15.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,派一支小队去阿尔科\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Send a team down to the Arco.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:15.84,0:33:17.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,炸弹什么时候会引爆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When is the bomb set to go off?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:18.84,0:33:21.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-三小时后  -你怎么知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Three hours. - How do you know that?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:21.60,0:33:24.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我看到了定时器  -形容一下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I saw the timer. - Describe it.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:25.23,0:33:27.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么  -形容一下那个定时器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What? - The timer. Describe it.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:28.42,0:33:29.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't...
Dialogue: 0,0:33:31.88,0:33:33.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在骗我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're lying to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:33.97,0:33:36.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那种体积的炸弹不会有直观的定时器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}A bomb that size wouldn't have a visual timer.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:37.52,0:33:40.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没有骗你  炸弹就在阿尔科塔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not lying. It's at the Arco Towers.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:40.81,0:33:42.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在就派人去市中心\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Send them all downtown now.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:43.34,0:33:44.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么现在  着急什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why now? What's the hurry?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:44.92,0:33:45.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是有三个小时的时间吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I thought I had three hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:46.13,0:33:47.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你和我说有三个小时对吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You told me I had three hours, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:47.41,0:33:49.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-是有三个小时吗   -不  我没有骗你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Do I have three hours?  - No, I'm not lying!
Dialogue: 0,0:34:02.07,0:34:04.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你为什么希望我和我的队员这么快离开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why do you want me and my team to leave here so fast?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:08.07,0:34:09.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,炸弹还在这里是吧  玛丽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The bomb's still here, isn't it, Marie?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:12.20,0:34:13.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:15.23,0:34:16.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:16.95,0:34:17.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,A队和B队\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Teams A and B,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:17.86,0:34:20.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要你们在机场外围做网格搜索\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you do a grid search on every outbuilding at the airport,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:20.93,0:34:23.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,从北面开始往南搜\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}starting northern and heading south.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:23.08,0:34:25.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,炸弹就在这里  我重复  炸弹就在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The bomb is on-site. I repeat: the bomb is on-site.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:31.90,0:34:33.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,玛丽\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, Marie.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:35.13,0:34:37.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们不可能及时找到的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're not gonna find it in time.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:39.30,0:34:40.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们都会死的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're all gonna die.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:54.14,0:34:56.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会睡在地上  你可以睡我的床\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll sleep on the floor. You can have my bed.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:57.26,0:34:59.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  电话已经接通\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President, your call's ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:00.69,0:35:02.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,兰利的史蒂夫·海伦伯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Steve Hillenburg at Langley.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:02.11,0:35:04.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  中情局的特工\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, a CIA operative.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:04.97,0:35:06.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他的信号是单独隔开的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's on an isolated feed.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:06.10,0:35:08.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只有你们三个人知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Nobody else knows about this but the three of you.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:10.64,0:35:11.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雪莉在等着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sherry's waiting.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:12.87,0:35:14.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很好  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good. Thanks.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:25.35,0:35:28.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你好啊  史蒂夫  -总统先生好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Hello, Steve. - Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:28.63,0:35:30.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你和这件事有什么关系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's your involvement in this?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:31.76,0:35:34.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大约四个月前  我接到雪莉的电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I got a call from Sherry about four months ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:35.62,0:35:38.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她和我说罗杰·斯坦顿想要招募她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She told me Roger Stanton was trying to recruit her
Dialogue: 0,0:35:39.32,0:35:41.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,来破坏你的总统任期\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}in an effort to undermine your presidency.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:41.75,0:35:44.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她想要一个独立的资源来证明\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She wanted an independent source to confirm
Dialogue: 0,0:35:44.54,0:35:46.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她这么做只是为了帮你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that she was only going along with this to help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:47.20,0:35:49.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以过去四个月以来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So you've been building a case against Roger Stanton
Dialogue: 0,0:35:49.75,0:35:53.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你一直背着我在调查罗杰·斯坦顿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}for the last four months without my knowledge.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:53.40,0:35:55.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,合理的推诿  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Plausible deniability, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:56.19,0:36:00.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,虽然我们所做的事不合法  但是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What we were doing was illegal, but...
Dialogue: 0,0:36:01.54,0:36:03.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们认为有必要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we felt it was necessary.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:04.03,0:36:07.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这有可能会适得其反  令我和雪莉入狱\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It could've backfired and landed both Sherry and me in prison.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:07.60,0:36:09.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果是这样  我们不希望事情牵扯到你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We didn't want this to touch you if that happened.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:10.40,0:36:13.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就当我接受这一点吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, let's say I accept that.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:13.94,0:36:17.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,除了你的话  你有什么证据能证明雪莉无罪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What proof do you have that exonerates Sherry beside your word?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:17.43,0:36:21.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我有照片  对话录音  情况报告\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have photographs, taped conversations, debriefs,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:21.75,0:36:24.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一大堆雪莉工作的文件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}files filled with the work Sherry did.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:24.30,0:36:27.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雪莉和罗杰的那些会议\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}These meetings that Sherry and Roger had,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:27.04,0:36:28.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是在哪里进行的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}where'd they take place?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:29.87,0:36:30.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雪莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sherry?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:37.03,0:36:38.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,第一个月\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For the first month,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:38.61,0:36:41.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们在希尔顿海德岛的一家酒店见面\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}we met at a hotel in Hilton Head.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:44.68,0:36:47.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我没和他上床  -我没问\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I didn't sleep with him. - I didn't ask.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:47.66,0:36:50.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你  史蒂夫  有需要我会联系你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you, Steve. I'll contact you if I need anything else.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:50.77,0:36:51.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:55.44,0:36:59.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不在乎你现在怎么看我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know, I don't care what you think of me right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:59.79,0:37:00.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最重要的是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The most important thing is
Dialogue: 0,0:37:00.90,0:37:04.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你意识到我从来不是  从来都不是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}that you realise that I never, and I mean never,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:04.57,0:37:06.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,斯坦顿阴谋的一部分\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}was a part of Stanton's conspiracy.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:09.21,0:37:10.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,知道吗  雪莉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what, Sherry?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:11.81,0:37:13.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你也许和我说的是真话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You might be telling me the truth.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:14.00,0:37:15.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还是那句话  你也许不是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then again, you might not.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:15.42,0:37:17.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在  我没有时间或精力\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right now, I don't have the time or energy
Dialogue: 0,0:37:17.51,0:37:19.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去搞清楚我是否能相信你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to figure out whether I can trust you.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:21.40,0:37:23.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你必须要相信我  大卫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You have to trust me, David.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:24.03,0:37:27.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的总统地位和这个国家现在都岌岌可危\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your presidency is in jeopardy and so is this country.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:27.70,0:37:29.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让我帮你吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me help you.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:31.23,0:37:33.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不用了  你现在就走吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No. You'll leave now.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:38.15,0:37:42.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大卫  你需要我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}David... you need me.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:49.01,0:37:50.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你以任何方式反抗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you resist in any way,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:51.37,0:37:53.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我别无选择  只能逮捕你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll have no choice but to place you under arrest.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:58.22,0:38:01.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-总统先生  -请护送帕尔默女士上车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Yes, sir? - Please escort Mrs. Palmer to her car.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.96,0:38:15.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里有通风系统和空气供给\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We got a ventilation system in here and an air supply,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:15.52,0:38:17.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但还是很冷\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but it still stays cold.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:17.55,0:38:20.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是不用担心  因为我们有很多被子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But don't worry because we got tons of blankets.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:22.59,0:38:24.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你累了吗  -我还好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You tired? - I'm OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:28.19,0:38:30.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你还在担心你家人吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're still worried about your family, aren't you?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:32.78,0:38:34.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,尽量不要太担心他们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Try not to think about them too much.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:35.97,0:38:37.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也许你说得对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're probably right.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:42.35,0:38:44.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你在洛杉矶长大的吗  -是的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- So, did you grow up in LA? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:45.55,0:38:47.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是吗  我也是  洛杉矶哪里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, yeah? Me too. What part?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:48.56,0:38:49.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们经常搬家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We moved around a lot.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:50.41,0:38:51.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3c&H2F2F2F&}止痛药
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.74,0:38:53.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,其实我的脚还很疼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Actually you know, my foot is still hurting.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:53.31,0:38:54.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你有止痛药吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you have any aspirin?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:54.25,0:38:56.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,当然有  我有很多\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, yeah, sure. I got tons.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:01.56,0:39:03.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你现在要放我出去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're gonna let me out of here right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:03.78,0:39:05.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道炸弹没爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know the bomb didn't go off.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:08.13,0:39:09.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-金  -别过来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Kim... - Stay away!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:09.72,0:39:12.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  好  冷静一点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, OK, it's OK. Just calm down.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.05,0:39:18.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我没打算伤害你  -那就放我走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I wasn't gonna hurt you. - Then let me go!
Dialogue: 0,0:39:19.69,0:39:22.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只是想有人陪我而已\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I... I just wanted some company, that's all.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:22.79,0:39:24.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你在这里干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then what are you doing out here?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:25.74,0:39:27.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我属于这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is where I belong.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:28.05,0:39:29.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不属于这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:33.16,0:39:34.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想你留下来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want you to stay.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:36.11,0:39:37.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不想留下来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't wanna stay.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:40.11,0:39:41.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why not?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:43.73,0:39:46.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我有什么问题  我不够好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's wrong with me? I'm... I'm not good enough?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:47.33,0:39:49.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-和你完全没关系  -那是为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Doesn't have nothing to do with you. - Then why?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:54.59,0:39:55.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你觉得我是神经病吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What? You think I'm psycho?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:55.80,0:39:57.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道你是不是神经病\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know if you're psycho.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:57.28,0:39:58.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我都不认识你  朗尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't even know you, Lonnie.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:59.44,0:40:02.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,难道你不想和一个愿意留在这里的人一起吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wouldn't you rather be with someone who wants to be here?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:06.09,0:40:07.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你甚至都不想了解我吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't even wanna get to know me?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:10.12,0:40:12.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请你放我走吧  朗尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please let me out of here, Lonnie.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:16.78,0:40:17.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,求你了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:49.53,0:40:51.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-给  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Here. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:51.55,0:40:52.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拿着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Take it.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:54.94,0:40:56.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,外面有美洲狮\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's cougars out there.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:57.33,0:40:57.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你遇到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you see one,
Dialogue: 0,0:40:57.85,0:41:00.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就向空中鸣枪  它们就会跑掉了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}fire a shot in the air and they'll take off.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:16.28,0:41:18.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,出了前门向右拐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You get out of the front door, turn right.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:18.66,0:41:20.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,大概182米后  你就会看到鹿的踪迹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}About 200 yards away, you'll see a deer trail.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:21.55,0:41:23.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,顺着走就会到公路了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That'll lead you to the highway.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:23.81,0:41:24.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:29.61,0:41:30.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kim?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:33.21,0:41:34.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也许你什么时候会再回来看看吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Maybe you'll come back sometime?
Dialogue: 0,0:41:35.88,0:41:37.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,应该不会的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:03.08,0:42:04.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,古德里奇  发生了什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Goodrich, what's going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:05.88,0:42:07.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所有探员  击中了一名敌人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All agents, one hostile down!
Dialogue: 0,0:42:12.45,0:42:13.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行动  行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go, go, go!
Dialogue: 0,0:42:14.78,0:42:15.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Over here!
Dialogue: 0,0:42:22.20,0:42:23.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们走  带他们进来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's go! Bring 'em in!
Dialogue: 0,0:42:43.20,0:42:45.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么情况  -是核弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What do we got? - It's nuclear.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:49.68,0:42:51.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有引爆器  错不了了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And there's the trigger. This is it.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:52.36,0:42:54.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是杰克·鲍尔  我们找到炸弹了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is Jack Bauer. We found the bomb.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:54.22,0:42:57.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,立即启动一级紧急疏散\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Initiate a level-one local evac now.
Dialogue: 0,0:43:10.57,0:43:13.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-保险已拔  -我们还剩多少时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It's armed. - How much time have we got?
Dialogue: 0,0:43:13.85,0:43:16.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说不准  有可能随时会爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't tell. Could be any second.

