[Script Info]
;SrtEdit 6.3.2012.1001
;Copyright(C) 2005-2012 Yuan Weiguo

Title: YYeTs
Original Script: YYeTs
Original Translation: 
Original Timing: 
Original Editing: 
Script Updated By: 
Update Details: 
ScriptType: v4.00+
Collisions: Reverse
PlayResX: 384
PlayResY: 288
Timer: 100.0000
Synch Point: 0
WrapStyle: 0
ScaledBorderAndShadow: no

[V4+ Styles]
Format: Name, Fontname, Fontsize, PrimaryColour, SecondaryColour, OutlineColour, BackColour, Bold, Italic, Underline, StrikeOut, ScaleX, ScaleY, Spacing, Angle, BorderStyle, Outline, Shadow, Alignment, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Encoding
Style: Default,方正黑体_GBK,20,&H00FFFFFF,&HF0000000,&H00000000,&H32000000,0,0,0,0,100,100,0,0,1,2,1,2,5,5,1,134

[Events]
Format: Layer, Start, End, Style, Name, MarginL, MarginR, MarginV, Effect, Text
Dialogue: 0,0:00:06.69,0:00:10.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\pos(197.4,200.557)}{\fn方正兰亭中黑_GBK\fs25\b1\bord0\shad0\c&H78BDE7&\fad(0,808)}24小时\N\N{\fs15}第二季  第二集
Dialogue: 0,0:00:11.49,0:00:13.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\move(189.6,121.6,193.8,105.6,0,356)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad3\3c&H2F2F2F&\4c&H336D99&}{\fs10}{\t(0,356,\fs20)\fn方正正中黑简体}前情提要
Dialogue: 0,0:00:14.14,0:00:15.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生  有紧急情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's a situation, Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.61,0:00:15.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(106.8,190.953)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.66,0:00:15.70,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(115.8,170.153)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.70,0:00:15.74,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(122.4,150.153)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.74,0:00:15.78,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs15\c&H449BA1&\pos(126.6,131.2)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.78,0:00:15.82,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(129,117.353)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:15.82,0:00:17.79,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(132,111.753)\fad(0,480)}大卫·帕尔默总统
Dialogue: 0,0:00:16.16,0:00:17.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有一个在恐怖组织控制之下的核装置\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's a nuclear device,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:18.02,0:00:20.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现正在美国境内\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}under terrorist control, that's on US soil.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:20.62,0:00:22.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-在哪里  -洛杉矶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where? - Los Angeles.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:22.40,0:00:24.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这枚炸弹今天会引爆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This bomb is going to go off today.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:25.03,0:00:27.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天将会是漫长的一天\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Today's gonna be a very long day,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:27.05,0:00:29.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不希望自己人阻碍我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and I don't want my own people working against me.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:29.35,0:00:32.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们俩  亲够了没\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, you two! Cut it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.04,0:00:32.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么  我都不能亲自己妻子了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What? I can't kiss my own wife?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.88,0:00:32.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(319.8,131.753)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.93,0:00:32.97,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(302.4,128.553)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:32.97,0:00:33.01,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(288,123.753)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.01,0:00:33.05,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs15\c&H449BA1&\pos(273.6,118.953)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.05,0:00:33.09,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(264,118.153)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:33.09,0:00:35.05,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(258.6,116.553)\fad(0,514)}凯特·华纳
Dialogue: 0,0:00:34.30,0:00:38.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她十多个小时之后才是你妻子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}She's not your wife for at least another 10 hours.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:38.16,0:00:40.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你让我调查雷扎·纳耶尔的背景时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When you asked for a background on Reza Naiyeer,
Dialogue: 0,0:00:40.50,0:00:43.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在为另一个人核实一份文件\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was proofing a file on another individual.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:43.67,0:00:44.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,雷扎的名字出现了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Reza's name came up.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:44.96,0:00:46.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有一个叫赛伊德·阿里的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's a man named Syed Ali
Dialogue: 0,0:00:46.69,0:00:49.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,与多个恐怖组织有联系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}with ties to terrorist organisations.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:49.43,0:00:50.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-亲爱的  -你来做什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Hey, sweetheart. - What are you doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.19,0:00:50.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(225.6,132.553)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.23,0:00:50.28,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(234,129.353)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.28,0:00:50.32,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(241.8,125.353)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.32,0:00:50.36,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs15\c&H449BA1&\pos(248.4,122.153)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.36,0:00:50.40,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(254.4,118.953)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:50.40,0:00:52.36,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(256.2,118.153)\fad(0,557)}金·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:00:51.62,0:00:53.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我就是想见见你  我很想你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just wanted to see you. I miss you.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:53.37,0:00:55.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,爸  我接受不了  我现在备受煎熬\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Dad, I'm not ready, it's too hard for me right now.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:55.62,0:00:56.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那你怎么不...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then why won't you...
Dialogue: 0,0:00:56.88,0:00:58.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,每次看见你  我都想起妈妈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Every time I see you, I think of Mom.
Dialogue: 0,0:00:59.54,0:01:01.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是个白痴吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you a complete idiot?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:01.89,0:01:03.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不喜欢他变成这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't like when he gets like this.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:03.27,0:01:05.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我离开前想和我女儿单独待几分钟  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need a few minutes with my daughter before I leave, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:05.89,0:01:08.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不是让你出去吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did I not tell you to get outta here?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:08.39,0:01:10.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,闭嘴  闭嘴  梅根\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Shut up! Shut up, Megan!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.72,0:01:15.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,叫我来干嘛  乔治\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What am I doing here, George?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.67,0:01:13.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs6\c&H449BA1&\pos(225.6,132.553)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.72,0:01:13.76,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs8\c&H449BA1&\pos(233.4,130.153)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.76,0:01:13.80,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs12\c&H449BA1&\pos(241.8,126.153)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.80,0:01:13.84,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs15\c&H449BA1&\pos(248.4,122.953)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.84,0:01:13.88,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\pos(252.6,120.553)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:13.88,0:01:15.84,Default,,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs20\c&H449BA1&\pos(256.2,119.753)\fad(0,555)}杰克·鲍尔
Dialogue: 0,0:01:15.42,0:01:17.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,洛杉矶城里有一件尚未发现的核武器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's a rogue nuclear weapon here in Los Angeles.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:17.76,0:01:19.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,头号嫌疑犯有眉目了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How close are you to IDing a prime suspect?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:19.75,0:01:21.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最有嫌疑的是约瑟夫·沃尔德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The most promising one's Joseph Wald.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:21.94,0:01:24.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有能在下一轮审讯中指认沃尔德的关键证人吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are there any witnesses against Wald in his trial?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:24.67,0:01:27.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,马歇尔·戈伦  显然没有他就不能立案了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Marshall Goren. Apparently without him there's no case.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:27.62,0:01:29.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你是马歇尔·戈伦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You are Marshall Goren?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:31.03,0:01:32.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不要  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, Jack!
Dialogue: 0,0:01:33.02,0:01:35.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你疯了吗  -你想找到这个炸弹吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Are you out of your mind? - You wanna find this bomb?
Dialogue: 0,0:01:35.77,0:01:38.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这就是代价  我需要一把锯子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is what it's gonna take. I'm gonna need a hacksaw.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:38.62,0:01:44.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad0\fs15\t(696,6577,\fs16)\c&H4BAAAD&\fad(1697,1183)\pos(187.2,191.79)}以下情节发生在上午9点到10点之间
Dialogue: 0,0:01:45.54,0:01:48.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\b1\bord0\shad2\fs18\c&H449BA1&\fad(358,349)\pos(189,210.953)}西北地区 作战中心
Dialogue: 0,0:01:49.34,0:01:51.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,匡提科请求将核威胁的消息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Quantico wants permission to relay
Dialogue: 0,0:01:51.43,0:01:53.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉他们的中层战术专家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}the nuclear threat to their mid-level tacticians.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:54.54,0:01:57.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-有多少人  -600到700人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How many people are we talking about? - Between 600 and 700.
Dialogue: 0,0:01:58.41,0:02:01.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们要保证不走漏风声才行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Only if they assure they can contain the information.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:01.60,0:02:04.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,在同意他们的请求前我会先确认的  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I will confirm that before I give them approval, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:05.06,0:02:06.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想让所有人都知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I want everyone to know that,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:06.85,0:02:10.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,除了洛杉矶的核威胁以外\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}besides the threat of a nuclear bomb in Los Angeles,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:10.29,0:02:11.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还心系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm just as concerned
Dialogue: 0,0:02:11.43,0:02:13.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,恐慌和歇斯底里造成的危害\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}with the dangers of panic and mass hysteria.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:13.78,0:02:14.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,明白\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Absolutely.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:15.18,0:02:16.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,其他事进展如何\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So where are we on everything else?
Dialogue: 0,0:02:17.77,0:02:21.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,国安局正在从两方面入手\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, NSA is taking a two-pronged approach.
Dialogue: 0,0:02:21.41,0:02:23.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们在追踪任何和"第二波"恐怖分子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're trying to pick up a trail on any known
Dialogue: 0,0:02:23.95,0:02:25.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有关的信息\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Second Wave terrorists,
Dialogue: 0,0:02:25.82,0:02:27.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,同时他们在努力找出\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and they're also trying to
Dialogue: 0,0:02:27.10,0:02:30.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,窃取武器级核材料的出处\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}source stolen weapons-grade nuclear materials.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:16.49,0:03:18.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,通知代表  告诉他们情况  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, call the rep, tell them what the matter is, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:19.69,0:03:21.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她为何不能再留一会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why can't she hang around?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:21.32,0:03:23.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我说了我晚几分钟就到\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I said I'd be back in a couple of minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:24.80,0:03:26.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢  没错...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you. Yes...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:26.27,0:03:29.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金  待着别动  她没事  听见了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Kim. Stay there. She's gonna be fine, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:29.71,0:03:31.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们等几分钟再解决这件事  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll work this out in a couple of minutes. All right?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:32.54,0:03:33.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,唐尼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Donny?
Dialogue: 0,0:03:36.57,0:03:39.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好  不...  没...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, no... Uh... It's... it's...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:39.99,0:03:41.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道晚了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know it's late.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:41.46,0:03:42.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她怎么就不能...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why can't she...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:43.28,0:03:44.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ok.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:44.60,0:03:49.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好的  就这样  我知道  她一直...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right, right. Yeah, do that. Yes, I know. She's being a...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:49.65,0:03:50.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, no, no.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:51.23,0:03:52.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  一切顺利  都很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, everything's fine. It's fine.
Dialogue: 0,0:03:54.51,0:03:55.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  我知道...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, I know...
Dialogue: 0,0:03:58.03,0:04:00.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金  拿我的钥匙  带她离开这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kim, take my keys. Get her away from here.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:00.85,0:04:01.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:05.58,0:04:07.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,让他们等我回来  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell them to wait until I get back, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:04:08.89,0:04:09.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我一会打给你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll call you back.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:15.32,0:04:16.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快啊  快啊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on! Come on!
Dialogue: 0,0:04:23.81,0:04:26.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金  停车  我会杀了你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kim! Stop the car. I will kill you.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:26.66,0:04:29.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,停车  被这样  金\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Stop the car! Do not do this, Kim.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:29.60,0:04:30.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别这样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do not do this.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:44.32,0:04:46.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,星牌卫星追踪  请说密码\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Star-Sat. Password, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:46.09,0:04:49.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,7073  我想追踪定位我的车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}7073. Yeah, I need to track the location of my car, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:55.20,0:04:57.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们把你放到离废品回收厂三条街外\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll drop you three blocks from the salvage yard.
Dialogue: 0,0:04:57.78,0:05:00.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-车备好了吗  -好了  后备箱有跟踪器\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What about the car? - Ready, with a tracker in the trunk.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:01.00,0:05:01.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:02.06,0:05:04.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们一直在监视  没看到沃尔德进入回收厂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We've been monitoring the yard. We haven't seen Wald come in yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:04.52,0:05:06.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他的同伙呢  -不清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What about his people? - We're not sure.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:07.24,0:05:08.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些人见过吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Any of these men look familiar?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:11.08,0:05:11.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:14.15,0:05:17.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这个见过  艾迪·格兰特  他是乔的心腹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, that's Eddie Grant. He's one of Joe's main go-to guys.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:17.35,0:05:19.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我当卧底时  我们是朋友  这很好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When I was undercover, we were friends.That's good.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:20.16,0:05:22.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等我进去了  我可不想见到有警察在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}As soon as I'm in, I don't wanna see any of our people.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:22.81,0:05:24.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你让他们都离远点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You keep everybody at a distance.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:26.90,0:05:29.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道炸弹的大小吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know any more information about the size of the bomb?
Dialogue: 0,0:05:29.60,0:05:30.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还不清楚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not yet.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:50.41,0:05:52.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先生  媒体开始起疑了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, the press is starting to ask questions.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:52.40,0:05:54.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们知道你缩短了钓鱼行程\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They know you cut your fishing trip short
Dialogue: 0,0:05:54.05,0:05:55.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们想知道原因\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and they'd like to know why.
Dialogue: 0,0:05:59.72,0:06:01.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只要你想  我可以让詹尼特出面解决\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you'd like, I can get Jennet to take care of it.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:02.41,0:06:05.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不用  我自己来吧  -好的  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- No, I'd better take care of it myself. - Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:06.50,0:06:08.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先生  我们有很多事要做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, we've got a lot to cover.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:08.74,0:06:09.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得把媒体搞定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I have to deal with the press.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:10.22,0:06:12.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,先生  我们有个大麻烦\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sir, we have a serious situation
Dialogue: 0,0:06:12.26,0:06:14.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把时间花在媒体身上...\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and taking time out to coddle the media...
Dialogue: 0,0:06:14.36,0:06:15.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,埃里克  你不明白\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What you don't get, Eric,
Dialogue: 0,0:06:15.90,0:06:19.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一旦谣言四起  我们就有两个麻烦了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}is that once the rumour mill starts, we've got two problems.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:19.58,0:06:21.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们可不想引起集体恐慌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The last thing we need is mass hysteria.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:35.10,0:06:37.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-梅森  -乔治  是我  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Mason. - George, it's Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:37.54,0:06:38.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要和托尼通话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me speak to Tony.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:38.22,0:06:40.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你想干嘛  -你接上金了没\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What do you need? - Have you picked up Kim yet?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:40.32,0:06:44.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,几分钟前格劳斯刚去过  金不在\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Grothy just got to the house a few minutes ago. Kim wasn't there.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:44.40,0:06:46.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么意思  她在哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you talking about? Where is she?
Dialogue: 0,0:06:46.26,0:06:48.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不知道  我们在找了 她不在家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We don't know. We're looking for her. She wasn't at the house.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:48.55,0:06:51.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,该死  乔治  我跟你说过有情况通知我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Damn it! George. I told you to tell me when you knew anything.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:51.07,0:06:53.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我刚接到电话  冷静  别紧张  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I was just picking up the phone. Calm down. Relax, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:54.18,0:06:56.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别跟我说放松  乔治\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't tell me to relax, George.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:57.03,0:06:59.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听着  格劳斯会等金回来的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, Grothy's gonna wait until Kim gets back.
Dialogue: 0,0:06:59.06,0:07:00.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,与此同时  你要坚持住\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Meantime, you hang in there.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:00.67,0:07:02.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治  找到金  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George, just find Kim, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:03.33,0:07:04.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们在找了  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's what we're doin', Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:04.46,0:07:07.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们会找到她  带她离开洛杉矶  好吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna find her and get her out of LA. OK
Dialogue: 0,0:07:08.38,0:07:10.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-相信我  -好  谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Trust me. - OK. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:26.59,0:07:28.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是金  请留言\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hi, this is Kim. Leave a message.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:28.79,0:07:30.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亲爱的  是你爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, sweetheart. It's your dad again.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:30.96,0:07:34.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你得赶快离开洛杉矶\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't tell you how important it is that you leave Los Angeles.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:34.35,0:07:37.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我从办公室派了个人  他叫罗伊·格劳斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sending a man over from my office. His name is Roy Grothy.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:37.45,0:07:40.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他会带你去卡罗尔姑姑那里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's gonna pick you up and take you over to Aunt Carol's.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:40.83,0:07:43.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亲爱的  拜托了  就当是为了我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Honey, please, do this for me, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:43.76,0:07:46.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听到留言请尽快回电话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Call me back as soon as you get these messages.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:46.51,0:07:48.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我爱你  再见\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I love you. Bye.
Dialogue: 0,0:07:54.68,0:07:57.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,宝拉  分局有新安排了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Paula, have we gotten a Division update yet?
Dialogue: 0,0:07:58.72,0:08:03.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有  托尼  我们不该搬到洛杉矶外办公吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Uh, yeah. Tony, shouldn't we be working from outside LA?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:03.74,0:08:04.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:05.07,0:08:07.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要是这个城市的某个地方有个核弹\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If there's a nuclear bomb somewhere in the city...
Dialogue: 0,0:08:08.79,0:08:10.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别去想这个  宝拉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Try to tune it out, Paula.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:10.79,0:08:12.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你永远都不知道情报到底准不准确\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You never know how good the intel is.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:17.02,0:08:18.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,阿尔梅达  我们有线索了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Almeida, we have a lead.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:18.82,0:08:20.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,刚刚在国界那抓到几个蛇头\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just caught a couple of coyotes at the border.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:21.16,0:08:22.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们要带谁进来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who were they bringing in?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:22.09,0:08:24.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是人  是东西  他们发现货车里有东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not who, what. They found something interesting in the van.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:24.22,0:08:25.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,米歇尔  把资料调出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Michelle, you want to pull it up?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:26.85,0:08:29.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,两本伪造的中东护照\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There are two forged Middle Eastern passports.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:29.04,0:08:30.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,伪造证件上的记号\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The markings on the paper forgeries
Dialogue: 0,0:08:30.52,0:08:33.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,跟我们的一些嫌疑人所用的工艺相符\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}conform to process used by some of the suspects on our list.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:33.23,0:08:35.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,发现了他们要去的卡尔弗城的地址\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They found address in Culver City where they were headed.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:35.23,0:08:36.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,现在就派人赶过去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let's get somebody over there now.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:36.70,0:08:38.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-派谁  -谁近就派谁  谁在那片\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Who? - Whoever is the closest. Who's in the area?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:39.05,0:08:42.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-只有罗伊·格劳斯在那  -好  就派他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- The only one in that section is Roy Grothy. - Good. Send him.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:42.65,0:08:43.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-乔治  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- George... - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:08:44.90,0:08:46.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们是派他去接金·鲍尔的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's who we sent to pick up Kim Bauer.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:46.54,0:08:48.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他在那边闲着  金也不在附近\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's idling over there. Kim's not around.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:49.52,0:08:51.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们刚答应过杰克要照顾好她\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We just promised Jack we'd take care of her.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:51.83,0:08:54.39,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  我们派个办事员过去等他回来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fine. We'll send a gofer over there until he gets back.
Dialogue: 0,0:08:54.40,0:08:56.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,同时  这个线索别跟丢了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}In the meantime, don't lose this window.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:39.60,0:09:41.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你好  牛仔  -能帮你做点什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Hey, cowboy. - Can I do for you?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:41.29,0:09:43.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我要找乔  -乔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I'm looking for Joe. - Joe?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:43.46,0:09:44.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,约瑟夫·沃尔德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Joseph Wald.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:45.79,0:09:47.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对不起  哥们  你走错地方了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sorry, man. I think you got the wrong place.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:48.47,0:09:51.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,伙计  我没那么多时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, cowboy. I ain't got a whole lot of time.
Dialogue: 0,0:09:52.06,0:09:55.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要不你告诉乔就说杰克回来了  看他怎么说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why don't you tell Joe Jack's back in town, see what he says?
Dialogue: 0,0:09:55.67,0:09:56.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么不让我告诉他呢  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why don't I tell him, Jack?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:00.91,0:10:03.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,怎么不让我告诉乔  杰克·劳什回来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why don't I tell Joe Jack Roush is here?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:03.04,0:10:05.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我敢肯定他乐意见到害他进监狱的人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sure he'd love to see the guy that put him in jail.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:07.41,0:10:08.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,艾迪  你好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, Eddie. How are you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:08.96,0:10:11.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是来跟乔了结恩怨的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, I just came to square things up with Joe.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:11.18,0:10:12.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你很清楚不是我害他进监狱的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know I didn't put him in jail.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:13.41,0:10:14.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不是你是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Sure you didn't.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:21.03,0:10:22.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把后面的房间准备好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get the back room ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:23.61,0:10:27.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,妈的  埃迪  我有东西要给乔看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Damm it, Eddie. I got something I need to show Joe.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:27.67,0:10:30.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔只想看到你死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The only thing he's gonna wanna see is you... dead.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:30.51,0:10:31.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,马歇尔·戈伦呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about Marshall Goren?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:33.70,0:10:34.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What about him?
Dialogue: 0,0:10:35.14,0:10:37.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有传言说他做了污点证人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Word on the street is that he turned state's evidence,
Dialogue: 0,0:10:37.01,0:10:38.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,能让乔把牢底坐穿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}gonna put Joe away for life.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:41.00,0:10:42.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去吧  埃迪  看看我包里有什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Go on, Eddie. Look in my bag.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:47.50,0:10:50.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-搞什么  杰克  -就当是给乔的见面礼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What for, Jack? - Think of it as a present for Joe.
Dialogue: 0,0:10:51.50,0:10:53.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我说过了  我想跟他了结恩怨\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I told you, I wanted to square things up with him.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:00.29,0:11:02.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,弗兰克  把包递给我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Frank, give me that bag.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:11.96,0:11:12.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,打开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just open it.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:24.41,0:11:25.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,见鬼  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What the hell, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:27.26,0:11:30.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,估计你们不需要再担心戈伦出庭作证了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't think you gotta worry about Goren testifying any more.
Dialogue: 0,0:11:51.29,0:11:52.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克回来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack's back.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:09.25,0:12:12.08,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对我来说  幸好副总统如期而至\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fortunately for me the vice president arrived when he did.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:12.81,0:12:15.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们都没有什么八卦可以聊了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We were both running out of small talk.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:17.18,0:12:18.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:19.85,0:12:22.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-总统先生  -简\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Mr. President? - Jane.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:22.19,0:12:24.85,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们听说您今天上午要去钓鱼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We were told you were going to be spending this morning fishing.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:24.86,0:12:27.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么事情让您这么早就回来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What brought you back to shore so early?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:27.27,0:12:29.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我今天该钓的都钓到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I already caught my quota for the day.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:29.45,0:12:32.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我那老一套的保护政策又来对付自己了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My old conservation policy is coming back to haunt me.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:33.50,0:12:35.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-总统先生  -好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Mr. President... - Look, look...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:35.18,0:12:37.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,咱们细水长流\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}let's not have so much fun all at once.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:37.43,0:12:38.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们会在这待好几天\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna be here for a couple of days.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:38.71,0:12:40.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们回头再聊\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll talk to you guys later.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:40.16,0:12:40.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. President...
Dialogue: 0,0:12:49.47,0:12:50.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,维兰德想干什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, what did Wieland want?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:50.58,0:12:51.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他在到处打探\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's sniffing around.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:51.51,0:12:53.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,估计他很快就知道真相了  先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think he's putting it together, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:53.79,0:12:54.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他怎么能知道真相呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How can he put it together?
Dialogue: 0,0:12:54.96,0:12:57.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我自己也是不到一个小时之前才弄清楚的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just found out myself less than an hour ago.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:57.30,0:12:58.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我敢肯定他不了解具体细节\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sure he doesn't know the details,
Dialogue: 0,0:12:58.58,0:12:59.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是你也了解维兰德这个人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but you know Wieland.
Dialogue: 0,0:12:59.42,0:13:02.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他谁都认识  大家都欠他的情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He knows everyone and they all owe him.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:05.83,0:13:08.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好吧  你从现在开始盯着他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK... Keep your eye on him for now.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:09.19,0:13:11.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果我们开始费尽心机推迟媒体发布\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If we start going out of our way to put off the press
Dialogue: 0,0:13:11.21,0:13:12.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,却又事与愿违的话  他们就会知道出事了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}of the back fire, they'll know something's up.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:12.78,0:13:13.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,赞同\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I agree.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:15.18,0:13:17.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我要回指挥中心了  -好的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I have to get back to the OC. - OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:31.38,0:13:32.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's this?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:35.25,0:13:39.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我头疼  -我知道  梅根  快到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- My head hurts. - I know, Megan. We'll be there real soon.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:39.34,0:13:41.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们去哪儿  -警察局\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where are we going? - The police station.
Dialogue: 0,0:13:44.69,0:13:45.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这样吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know what?
Dialogue: 0,0:13:48.57,0:13:50.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们从这条巷子穿过去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna go down this alley.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:02.84,0:14:05.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想个办法  金  求你让他走开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do something, Kim. Make him go away, please.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:20.73,0:14:22.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金  你要带我女儿去哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where are you going with my daughter, Kim?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:23.28,0:14:24.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你们要去哪儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Huh? Where you gonna go?
Dialogue: 0,0:14:26.84,0:14:29.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅根  宝贝  下车  上爸爸这来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Megan, honey, come on, get out of the car. Come to Daddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:39.29,0:14:40.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快想办法\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do something.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:44.68,0:14:45.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,下车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get out of the car.
Dialogue: 0,0:14:51.07,0:14:51.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hurry!
Dialogue: 0,0:14:57.99,0:14:59.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,闪开  闪开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Move! Move, move, move, move.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:05.97,0:15:06.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,金\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kim!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:17.88,0:15:18.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅根\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Megan!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:22.45,0:15:23.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅根  我是爸爸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Megan, it's Daddy.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:26.60,0:15:30.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,听我说  宝贝  金会伤害你的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen to me, pal. Kim is gonna hurt you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:31.67,0:15:35.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅根  应爸爸一声  好吗  我过去接你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Megan, just call out to Daddy, OK? I'll come get you.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:39.39,0:15:40.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅根\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Megan!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:42.59,0:15:43.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅根\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Megan!
Dialogue: 0,0:15:53.11,0:15:54.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别把线弄得乱成一团\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't get that stuff tangled.
Dialogue: 0,0:15:54.91,0:15:56.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们到那之后可没有时间把它们再解开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We won't have time to separate them once we get there.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:00.86,0:16:03.44,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他谁啊  -他是杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Who's that? - That's Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:04.57,0:16:06.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你这个节骨眼上随便带人来是不是疯了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are you outta your mind bringing somebody here today?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:07.16,0:16:08.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他以前跟咱们混过  戴夫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He used to work with us, Dave.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:10.89,0:16:13.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,跟我们混过这话是什么意思  埃迪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Used to work with us? What the hell is that supposed to mean, Eddie?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:13.51,0:16:14.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我以前是跟着乔混的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I used to work for Joe.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:15.28,0:16:16.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我刚刚在盖恩斯维尔替他坐了五年牢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just did a nickel for him up in Gainesville.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:16.91,0:16:18.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就这意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That's what it means.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:19.15,0:16:20.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是这么回事吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Is that a fact?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:21.88,0:16:24.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他偏偏赶在今天冒出来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And he happens to show up today of all days?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:24.41,0:16:25.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我才不信  埃迪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not buying this, Eddie.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:25.50,0:16:26.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他刚给乔办了件靠谱的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He did a solid for Joe.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:26.62,0:16:28.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他把戈伦解决了  戴夫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He took care of Goren, Dave. All right?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:28.73,0:16:31.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他能找上戈伦  那他一定是  -埃迪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Well, if he can get to Goren, he must be... - Hey, Eddie.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:31.83,0:16:35.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只需要跟乔聊聊  然后就走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Look, man, I just need to speak to Joe, OK? Then I'm outta here.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:35.85,0:16:37.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I hear you, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:37.46,0:16:39.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他要是待在这  我就要查查他\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If he's stayin, I'm checkin him out.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:40.42,0:16:41.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你就没别的事做了吗  戴夫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't you have something to do, Dave?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:42.08,0:16:44.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我两分钟就能挖出他的底细\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll bird-dog his records in two minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.03,0:16:45.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,想想后面的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Don't you think it's worth two minutes
Dialogue: 0,0:16:45.99,0:16:47.25,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不觉得这两分钟花得值吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}considering what's about to happen?
Dialogue: 0,0:16:50.39,0:16:51.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,查吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Check it out.
Dialogue: 0,0:16:56.20,0:16:59.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请坐  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Have a seat, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:04.22,0:17:08.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-姓啥  -劳什  劳动的劳  什锦的什\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Jack what? - Roush. R-o-u-s-h.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:15.14,0:17:17.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他进来了  他们刚刚上线了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's in. They just went online.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:17.04,0:17:18.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们在查杰克的背景\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're checking Jack's background now.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:18.94,0:17:21.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这么快  网址还没准备好呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Already? The network addresses aren't finished ready.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:21.56,0:17:23.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最好现在弄好然后发给我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Better do it now and send it to me.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:23.51,0:17:25.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,托尼  盖恩斯维尔的截止日期你填上了吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tony, did you backfill those Gainesville end dates?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:25.88,0:17:29.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-还没  -我现在就要  他们正查呢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Not yet. - I need them right away. They're looking for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:29.06,0:17:30.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这些人还真是猴急\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}These guys don't waste time.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:30.65,0:17:32.61,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不敢相信他们这么快就上线了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't believe they got in so quickly.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:32.76,0:17:35.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-要我塞些数据进去吗  -他们现在就要看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- You want me to stuff some data in? - They want this now.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:35.94,0:17:37.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在他们服务器上做点手脚\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna forge their server portal
Dialogue: 0,0:17:37.52,0:17:39.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,希望他们别较真\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and hope they don't look too closely.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:45.38,0:17:47.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这家伙一点公开信息都没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not finding any release documents on this guy.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:48.57,0:17:50.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这说明什么  戴夫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What does that mean, Dave?
Dialogue: 0,0:17:50.87,0:17:53.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,说明他撒谎  就这意思\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That means he's lying. That's what it means.
Dialogue: 0,0:17:57.31,0:17:58.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,接着查\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Keep lookin'.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:04.49,0:18:06.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  如果这次你在盖恩斯维尔坐牢的事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Listen, Jack, if this time you did in Gainesville
Dialogue: 0,0:18:06.11,0:18:07.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还查不出来的话\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}doesn't check out,
Dialogue: 0,0:18:08.56,0:18:10.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是不会让你活着离开的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I won't let you walk outta here.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:11.13,0:18:12.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,会确认的  埃迪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's gonna check out, Eddie.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:29.48,0:18:30.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Anything?
Dialogue: 0,0:18:31.33,0:18:32.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还没\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:38.72,0:18:39.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come on.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:39.76,0:18:43.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-托尼  快点  -快了  马上  马上\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Tony, I need it. - OK, I got it. Hold on, hold on.
Dialogue: 0,0:18:43.60,0:18:44.63,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还在搜索中\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's still looking.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:02.73,0:19:05.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,等等  我查到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Wait a second. I think I found it.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:07.75,0:19:08.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\fax0.1\frz348.3\move(183,129.6,187.8,130.4)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs12\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H2A1D52&}档案已找到
Dialogue: 0,0:19:09.94,0:19:11.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是的  找到了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, here it is.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:11.49,0:19:13.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,花的时间比我想的要久一点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It just took a little longer to come up than I thought it would.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:25.34,0:19:26.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,早就说了能查到的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Told you it would check out.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:30.66,0:19:32.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你害我差点杀了一个朋友  大卫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You almost made me shoot a friend, Dave.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:35.91,0:19:37.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry about that, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:38.09,0:19:40.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你还在开那辆野马吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You still got that '64 Mustang?
Dialogue: 0,0:19:42.38,0:19:43.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没  交给律师了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No, the lawyers got that.
Dialogue: 0,0:19:55.99,0:19:56.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,埃里克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Eric.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:01.65,0:20:03.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有缩小些搜查范围吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Are we narrowing things down at all?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:03.23,0:20:05.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有些进展了没\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, are we making any headway?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:05.41,0:20:07.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-现在还为时尚早  -还早吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- It's too soon to tell. - Too soon?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:08.37,0:20:12.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,难道核弹不是会随时爆炸吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Aren't we assuming that this bomb could go off at any moment?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:12.18,0:20:13.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我还能怎么说呢  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What can I say, Mr. President?
Dialogue: 0,0:20:13.68,0:20:16.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我从未抱希望我们能成功阻止爆炸\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've never been sanguine about our chances of stopping it.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:16.56,0:20:18.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们只有几个小时的时间\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not with just a few hours' warning.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:20.18,0:20:23.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这话是什么意思  -我没有放弃  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What is that supposed to mean? - I'm not giving up, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:23.17,0:20:27.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们遵循所有流程  动用了所有资源\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Every protocol is being followed, every resource is being tapped.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:27.13,0:20:29.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但如果我是你  若是炸弹真的引爆\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But if I were you, I would give serious thought to
Dialogue: 0,0:20:29.56,0:20:33.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我会慎言慎行\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}your plan of action if in fact we have a detonation.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:35.12,0:20:36.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我认为还是有必要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I still feel a discussion
Dialogue: 0,0:20:36.97,0:20:40.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,和国防部共议此事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}with the Pentagon this morning is in order.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:41.61,0:20:44.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行  谢谢  埃里克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Fine. Thanks, Eric.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:44.25,0:20:45.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:53.80,0:20:54.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,进来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Come in.
Dialogue: 0,0:20:57.78,0:21:00.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我刚刚和珍妮通话了  我们恐怕有麻烦了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just spoke with Jenny. I'm afraid we have a problem.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:01.03,0:21:03.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么了  -罗恩·维兰德\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What now? - Ron Wieland.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:03.40,0:21:04.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他已经说服广播公司\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's convinced the network
Dialogue: 0,0:21:04.50,0:21:08.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天中午会有十分钟他的报道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}to give him a 10-minute live report today at noon.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:08.76,0:21:09.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,报什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For what?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:09.75,0:21:11.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他已经知道警报状态的改变\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He's heard the alert condition has changed
Dialogue: 0,0:21:11.35,0:21:13.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,也知道你正在处理一些情况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and that you are managing a situation.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:14.41,0:21:15.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Damn it.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:16.40,0:21:19.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-他想怎么说  -珍妮不知道  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- He's going live based on what? - Jenny doesn't know, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:20.52,0:21:22.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我想他不会说出实情\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But I'm assuming that he will avoid the facts
Dialogue: 0,0:21:22.75,0:21:24.34,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而是会散播谣言\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and present the rumour.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:29.13,0:21:30.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,抱歉  林恩  我没有对你生气\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry, Lynne. I'm not mad at you.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:31.15,0:21:32.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,没必要道歉  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's no need to apologise, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:34.53,0:21:35.76,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,您要怎么行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}How would you like to proceed?
Dialogue: 0,0:21:40.97,0:21:44.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,准备一下我和维兰德先生的私人面谈\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Set up a private interview in 10 minutes with Mr. Wieland.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:44.89,0:21:47.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-这件事谁也不能知道  -好的  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- The condition is no one's to know. - Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:48.62,0:21:49.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还有  林恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And, Lynne...
Dialogue: 0,0:21:51.46,0:21:52.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,把阿莫斯叫来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get Armus over here.
Dialogue: 0,0:21:57.68,0:21:58.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  长官\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:15.40,0:22:16.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,兄弟  你最近怎么样\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Hey, man. How you doing?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:18.06,0:22:20.98,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-滚出去  -我只想点根烟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Get the hell outta here. - I just wanted to bum a smoke.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:20.98,0:22:23.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不抽烟  出去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't smoke, so get out.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:26.11,0:22:28.28,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你的引线包的太紧了  哥们\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're packing the fuses a little tight, sport.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:29.49,0:22:30.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What did you say?
Dialogue: 0,0:22:35.48,0:22:38.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-在交朋友吗  杰克  -这家伙太蠢了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Makin' friends, Jack? - The guy's a moron.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:38.83,0:22:42.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-乔怎么说  -乔很忙  也许得明天了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What did Joe say? - Joe's busy. Maybe tomorrow, bro.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:42.45,0:22:44.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我只需要见他五分钟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I just need to speak to him for five minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:44.67,0:22:46.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们今天有事忙  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We got this thing going down today, Jack,
Dialogue: 0,0:22:46.47,0:22:49.49,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,明天四点钟再来吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so swing by tomorrow around four.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:52.01,0:22:53.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行  没问题\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, OK. That's cool.
Dialogue: 0,0:22:57.33,0:22:58.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,见到你真好  兄弟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's good to see you, man.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:02.66,0:23:03.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,祝你好运\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good luck.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:08.61,0:23:09.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,时间到了  大卫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's time, Dave.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:37.56,0:23:39.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-梅森  -乔治  是我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Mason. - George, it's me.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:39.62,0:23:40.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你到沃尔德那儿了没\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Did you get to Wald yet?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:40.87,0:23:43.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,还没有  他的人不让我进去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Not yet. His crew are shutting me out.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:43.79,0:23:45.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治  我觉得你得把这些人抓起来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George, I think you gotta pick these guys up.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:45.87,0:23:46.31,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,为什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:46.53,0:23:48.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他们正在打包火药  他们也参与了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They're packing charges. They're involved.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:48.85,0:23:51.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果抓了他们  我们还能及时找到沃尔德吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If we pick 'em up, are they still gonna lead us to Wald in time?
Dialogue: 0,0:23:52.17,0:23:53.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不知道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't know.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:53.47,0:23:55.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,守住他们  直到能找到沃尔德为止\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, stick with them until they do.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:55.82,0:23:59.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,国安局刚刚把他的威胁程度升级了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}NSA just upgraded his probable role in today's threat.
Dialogue: 0,0:23:59.56,0:24:02.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就要赶上"第二波"的恐怖分子了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Put him just a click away from the Second Wave terrorists.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:02.88,0:24:04.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行  我再试试\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK, I'll try and figure something out.
Dialogue: 0,0:24:06.13,0:24:06.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,该死\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Damm it.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:27.21,0:25:28.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-梅森先生  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Mr. Mason? - Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:28.74,0:25:31.33,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我已经把您所要求的端口打开\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've opened up that socket to Division you asked for.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:31.85,0:25:32.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:25:41.64,0:25:42.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\frz354.3\move(221.4,40,182.4,40.8,0,1069)}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs13\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H48686F&}输入密码
Dialogue: 0,0:25:42.73,0:25:43.77,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an8\frz354.3\move(182.4,40.8,189,20.8)}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs13\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H48686F&}输入密码
Dialogue: 0,0:25:45.23,0:25:46.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\frz355.5\move(204.6,9.6,193.8,44.8,0,398)}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H201540&}紧急通知
Dialogue: 0,0:25:44.85,0:25:46.65,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an4\frz353.1\move(123,89.6,106.2,197.6,0,695)}{\fn方正黑体简体\fs14\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\fax-0.1\c&H000000&}给：乔治·梅森\N来自：总部\N{\\c&H201540&}优先度：极高
Dialogue: 0,0:25:55.86,0:25:57.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,{\an8\frz351.2\move(335.4,116,265.2,79.2,29,1447)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs13\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H201540&\fax0.1}爆炸可能：89%-93%
Dialogue: 0,0:25:57.32,0:25:59.83,Default,,0,0,0,,{\an8\frz351.2\move(265.2,79.2,242.4,100.8)}{\fn方正兰亭黑_GBK\fs13\b1\bord0\shad0\3c&H2F2F2F&\c&H201540&\fax0.1}爆炸可能：89%-93%
Dialogue: 0,0:26:56.85,0:26:58.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,乔治  你要去哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}George, where are you going?
Dialogue: 0,0:26:59.34,0:27:01.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-贝克斯菲尔德  -去那儿干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Bakersfield. - What for?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:02.53,0:27:03.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,追踪一个案子\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Following up on a lead.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:04.12,0:27:06.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天我们人手不足  我得亲自去处理\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're short-handed today so I gotta cover it myself.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:07.16,0:27:09.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,彼得被派去贝克斯菲尔德了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Peter's assigned to Bakersfield.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:09.15,0:27:10.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有别的事要他去做\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I put him on something else.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:10.35,0:27:12.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么  -不需要告诉你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What? - I don't have to tell you that.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:13.75,0:27:14.99,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这可不一定\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, I guess I disagree.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:16.57,0:27:18.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你只是想逃出爆炸范围\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I mean, if you're just trying to get outside the blast radius...
Dialogue: 0,0:27:24.48,0:27:25.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你以为你是谁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who the hell do you think you are?
Dialogue: 0,0:27:27.10,0:27:30.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你能看到我的情报吗  -不能\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Do you have access to my information? - No, George, I don't.
Dialogue: 0,0:27:30.48,0:27:32.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那闭嘴  做你自己该做的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Then keep your mouth shut and do your job.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:02.39,0:28:03.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,蹲下\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Get down!
Dialogue: 0,0:28:14.33,0:28:16.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我不舒服  -怎么了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I feel funny. - Why? What's wrong?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:16.78,0:28:18.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我头疼  -哪个地方\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- My head hurts. - Where?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:18.59,0:28:20.13,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这儿\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Right there.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:22.36,0:28:25.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-刚刚是不是撞到这儿了  -应该是\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Is that where you hit your head? - I think so.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:28.32,0:28:29.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,宝贝  我们不能躲在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Honey, we can't stay here.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:29.91,0:28:32.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我得打个电话  你待会就可以休息了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need to make a phone call. You can rest then, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:32.02,0:28:33.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不  -为什么不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- No! - Why not?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:33.40,0:28:35.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不行  我的头真的好痛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I can't. My head really hurts...I just really can't.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:35.70,0:28:37.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,就在那里  很快的  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's just over there. It'll be really quick, okay?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:38.28,0:28:40.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,拜托  你能做到的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please, for me. You can do it.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:40.50,0:28:43.68,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我做不到  我不舒服  -好吧  听着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- No, I can't. I don't feel good. - OK, listen, listen. Shh...
Dialogue: 0,0:28:43.68,0:28:45.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们得小声点  梅根\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We have to stay quiet, Megan.
Dialogue: 0,0:28:47.96,0:28:50.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想怎么做  你想躲在这儿吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you wanna do? Do you wanna stay here? Yeah?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:50.35,0:28:53.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,行  但是你得等我  你保证会待在这里吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK. But you have to wait. You promise you'll stay here?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:53.49,0:28:54.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,向我保证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You promise?
Dialogue: 0,0:28:56.60,0:28:59.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,躲在这些箱子下面  我马上就回来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We're gonna put you in these boxes. I'll be right back.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:03.12,0:29:05.96,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-躲在这里  别出来  -不会的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I don't want you moving. - I won't.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:05.96,0:29:09.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我很快就回来  千万别出来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm gonna be really quick. Please, just don't go anywhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:09.55,0:29:10.67,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我马上就回来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'll be right back.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:15.99,0:29:18.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我是伯顿  -你好  我是凯特·华纳\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- This is Burton. - Hi, it's Kate Warner.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:18.85,0:29:21.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-有找到什么吗  -我实在拿不到他的钱包\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Did you get something for me? - No, I couldn't get his wallet.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:22.18,0:29:23.86,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要查出他和阿里的关系\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There are only a few things we can use to
Dialogue: 0,0:29:23.86,0:29:26.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,只能用这几样东西\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}check out his connection to this guy Ali.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:26.85,0:29:29.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,其实护照也可以\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Actually, a passport would be ideal.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:29.38,0:29:31.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他应该不会随身携带护照吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't think he carries that around.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:31.06,0:29:32.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,肯定在他身边某个地方\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's gotta be around somewhere.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:33.24,0:29:36.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,检查他的手提包  看看他的车\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Check his briefcase. Look in his car.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:36.55,0:29:40.47,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-拉尔夫  我不能偷他的护照  -不用偷\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Ralph, I can't just steal his passport. - You won't have to.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:40.48,0:29:43.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你找到了  记下最近六个月\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you find it, just write down the countries that
Dialogue: 0,0:29:43.12,0:29:45.75,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他所去的国家\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}have been stamped for entry over the last six months.
Dialogue: 0,0:29:46.65,0:29:47.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,找到了跟我说  好吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let me know, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:31:30.18,0:31:30.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,凯特\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Kate!
Dialogue: 0,0:31:39.58,0:31:42.26,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你在干嘛  -我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What are you doing? - I, uh...
Dialogue: 0,0:31:42.43,0:31:46.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,克雷格说还有卡车要开过来  需要停车位\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Craig said more vans were coming and they needed the space.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:46.75,0:31:50.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-你没钥匙要怎么开车  -我不是在找嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- How you gonna drive it without the key? - I was looking for it.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:51.37,0:31:54.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-怎么不给我打电话呢  -你太忙了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Well, why didn't you call me? - You were busy.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:55.76,0:31:57.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要去买些草莓\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm running for strawberries.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:57.72,0:31:59.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,回来时我把车停到另一边去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}When I come back, I'll park on the other side.
Dialogue: 0,0:31:59.69,0:32:00.59,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Great.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:38.10,0:32:39.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你怎么还在这里\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What are you still doing here?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:40.55,0:32:44.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我的车熄火了  -那就打车  快走\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- My car won't start. - Well, take a cab. Beat it.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:46.98,0:32:48.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要学会别多管闲事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You need to learn to mind your own business.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:51.05,0:32:53.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-艾迪  -干嘛\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Hey, Eddie. - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:32:53.91,0:32:56.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,希望这个活不会太重要\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I hope this job isn't too important.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:56.18,0:32:57.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这小子把保险丝包得太紧了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Junior here packed your fuses too tight.
Dialogue: 0,0:32:57.91,0:33:00.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,炸弹是不会爆的  他把这活当成儿戏\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's no way it'll blow. He's a joke.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:04.20,0:33:05.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看到我和你说什么了吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}See what I'm telling ya?
Dialogue: 0,0:33:13.60,0:33:14.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Jack!
Dialogue: 0,0:33:19.99,0:33:22.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,脚断了 他刚刚弄断了我的脚踝\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's broken. He just broke my ankle.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:27.04,0:33:29.04,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你弄断了我的脚踝  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You broke his damn ankle, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:29.25,0:33:31.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,他就不该戏弄大人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}He shouldn't have been playing with adults.
Dialogue: 0,0:33:59.72,0:34:03.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这里是911紧急调度员  请稍等\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This is the 911 emergency operator. Please stay on the line.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:09.00,0:34:10.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你在打给谁  金\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Who are you calling, Kim?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:10.23,0:34:13.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,警察吗  你绑架了我女儿  警察都在找你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}The police? They are already looking for you for kidnapping my daughter.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:13.79,0:34:16.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-放开我  -好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Let go of me. - All right. OK.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:16.75,0:34:17.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,对不起\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm sorry.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:19.13,0:34:22.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不会伤害梅根的  我保证\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not gonna hurt Megan. I promise.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:23.90,0:34:25.97,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道推卡拉是我不对\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I know it was wrong of me to push Carla,
Dialogue: 0,0:34:26.45,0:34:29.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但我最近压力很大\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}but I have been under a lot of pressure lately.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:29.89,0:34:31.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不明白\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}OK? You don't... you don't understand.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:34.19,0:34:37.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不是坏人\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm not a bad person. OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:39.00,0:34:41.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你依照本能在那种情况下把梅根带走是对的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Your instincts were right to-to take Megan away from that situation.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:41.69,0:34:43.46,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,换做我也会这么做  我不怪你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I would have done the same thing. I don't blame you.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:44.84,0:34:49.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,但是我是她父亲\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}But, listen... I'm her father, OK?
Dialogue: 0,0:34:49.96,0:34:51.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要向她道歉\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I need to apologise to her
Dialogue: 0,0:34:51.52,0:34:53.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,叫她不用怕我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and tell her that she doesn't have to be afraid of me.
Dialogue: 0,0:34:59.44,0:35:00.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你明白吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You understand that, right?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:02.59,0:35:03.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,嗯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:06.93,0:35:07.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,她在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where is she?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:15.49,0:35:16.82,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不如你回家和卡拉好好谈谈吧\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why don't you go home and talk to Carla?
Dialogue: 0,0:35:16.82,0:35:19.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果她觉得没问题  我就把梅根带回去\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If it's OK with her, I'll bring back Megan.
Dialogue: 0,0:35:20.63,0:35:23.19,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-不  别告诉我该怎么做  -我没有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}-No. You don't tell me what to do, OK? - I'm not...
Dialogue: 0,0:35:23.19,0:35:26.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,别告诉我该怎么做  告诉我我女儿在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't tell me what to do. Tell me where my daughter is!
Dialogue: 0,0:35:26.32,0:35:27.52,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我女儿在哪\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Where is my daughter?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:00.86,0:36:02.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,告诉我我女儿在哪  金\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell me where my daughter is, Kim!
Dialogue: 0,0:36:03.87,0:36:04.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,快说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Tell me!
Dialogue: 0,0:36:18.59,0:36:22.23,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,最后一次在法兰克福入境  5月19日\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}And the last entry is Frankfurt, May 19th.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:22.33,0:36:25.54,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-很好  你帮了大忙  -这说明了什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Great. That's a big help. - So what does that tell us?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:25.64,0:36:28.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我们会对比雷扎和赛伊德·阿里的行程日期\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll compare Reza's travel dates with Syed Ali's.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:28.56,0:36:31.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看我们是否能找到和恐怖分子有关\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}See if we can find a terrorist connection.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:31.72,0:36:35.55,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,那样太好了  谢谢你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Um... OK. Yes, that would be great. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:36.77,0:36:38.06,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,新娘来了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's the bride.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:38.33,0:36:40.69,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我要和你说雷扎的父母会提早来\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I wanna let you know that Reza's parents are coming in early,
Dialogue: 0,0:36:40.70,0:36:42.37,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以我打给布伦特餐厅  订了午餐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}so I called Brent's and I ordered lunch.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:42.37,0:36:45.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-好  我会去拿的  -谢谢\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Good. I'll pick it up. - OK. Thank you.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:45.71,0:36:48.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我终于觉得一切尽在掌握中了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I finally feel like everything is under control.
Dialogue: 0,0:36:51.71,0:36:54.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-凯特  -什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Kate... - What?
Dialogue: 0,0:36:57.41,0:37:00.35,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我从没谢过你  -谢什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- I never thanked you. - For what?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:01.02,0:37:02.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你所做的一切\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For everything.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:03.22,0:37:06.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你当伴娘  谢谢你帮我筹备婚礼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}For being the maid of honour, for helping me with the wedding,
Dialogue: 0,0:37:06.58,0:37:10.24,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,谢谢你做我的姐姐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}for... being my big sister.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:11.12,0:37:13.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-玛丽  -我爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Marie... - I love you.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:14.79,0:37:16.05,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,亲爱的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, honey.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:16.80,0:37:18.38,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我也爱你\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, I love you too.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:22.00,0:37:23.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要干活了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Now, get to work.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:40.80,0:37:42.94,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-罗恩  -总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Ron. - Mr. President.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:43.38,0:37:44.88,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,很高兴见到你  请进\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good to see you. Come in.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:47.37,0:37:47.95,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,请坐\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Please, sit down.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:49.03,0:37:50.51,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,要喝点什么吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Can I offer you anything?
Dialogue: 0,0:37:50.51,0:37:51.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不用了  谢谢你  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Oh, no, thank you, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:37:57.81,0:38:00.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我知道你今天要直播一条新闻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I understand you're about to go live with a story today.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:01.32,0:38:03.07,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你认为发生了什么事\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Just what is it you think is going on?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:03.63,0:38:05.43,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我认为警戒状态已经升级\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think the alert condition has been elevated
Dialogue: 0,0:38:05.43,0:38:07.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,而你不想我们知道  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}and you don't want us to know that, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:08.88,0:38:09.77,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你认为吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You think?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:10.96,0:38:12.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你要我说出我的消息来源吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Do you want me to tell you my sources?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:12.78,0:38:14.53,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你知道我不能说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You know I can't do that.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:16.88,0:38:18.80,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你没搞清楚状况  罗恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You're barking up the wrong tree, Ron.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:19.88,0:38:21.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我不记得有\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I don't recall the last time
Dialogue: 0,0:38:21.93,0:38:24.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,记者与总统进行私人访谈时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}a journalist got a private interview with the president
Dialogue: 0,0:38:24.66,0:38:26.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是在几分钟前才接到通知的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}on a few minutes' notice.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:27.01,0:38:29.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以我在这行22年的经验告诉我\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So... my 22 years in the business tells me
Dialogue: 0,0:38:29.89,0:38:31.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我没搞错状况\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm barking up the right tree.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:33.76,0:38:35.00,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这么和你说吧  罗恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I tell you what, Ron.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:35.86,0:38:37.50,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,明天会有汇报会\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's gonna be a briefing tomorrow.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:37.90,0:38:40.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,如果你要提前三十分钟  我可以安排\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}If you want a 30-minute jump, I can arrange it.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:40.68,0:38:42.60,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你为什么要和我做交易  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Why are you horse-trading with me, Mr. President?
Dialogue: 0,0:38:42.60,0:38:43.66,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,因为如果你直播报道\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Because if you go live
Dialogue: 0,0:38:43.66,0:38:46.18,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一起未经证实的威胁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}with a story about unsubstantiated threats,
Dialogue: 0,0:38:46.52,0:38:48.20,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你会引发群众大恐慌\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}you will cause mass hysteria.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:49.34,0:38:51.41,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这可能比威胁本身更糟\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}That could be worse than the threat itself.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:51.73,0:38:52.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以的确有威胁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So there is a threat.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:53.69,0:38:56.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,罗恩  每天我们都收到威胁\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ron... we get them every day.
Dialogue: 0,0:38:58.91,0:39:00.62,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以你希望我不报道这则新闻\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So you're asking me to sit on this,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:00.72,0:39:02.29,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,即使我有职业权利\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}even though it's my professional right to
Dialogue: 0,0:39:02.29,0:39:03.72,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,去报道任何新闻吗\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}take what I've got on the air?
Dialogue: 0,0:39:08.60,0:39:09.83,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,罗恩  你知道我的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Ron, you know me.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:11.06,0:39:13.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,比起你所认识的任何一个政客\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I've been more forthcoming with the press and public
Dialogue: 0,0:39:13.27,0:39:15.16,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我对待新闻媒体及公众都更坦率\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}than any politician you know.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:15.87,0:39:17.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,所以在我请你帮忙时\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}So when I ask you for a favour,
Dialogue: 0,0:39:17.10,0:39:19.91,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是以美国人民的最佳利益为出发点的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I do it in the spirit of what's best for the American people.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:28.21,0:39:30.42,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-让我想一想  -当然\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Let me think about it. - Fair enough.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:31.97,0:39:33.84,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-谢谢你  总统先生  -谢谢你  罗恩\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Thank you, Mr. President. - Thank you, Ron.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:56.52,0:39:58.01,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-阿莫斯  -是  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Armus. - Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:39:59.73,0:40:01.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,看来我们必须开始采取行动\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I think we're gonna have to go ahead and deal with this.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:01.56,0:40:02.73,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,是  总统先生\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yes, sir.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:10.58,0:40:13.21,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,维兰德先生  我是理查德·阿莫斯\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Mr. Wieland, I'm Richard Armus.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:13.21,0:40:15.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我是总统特工处蓝队的特工\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm with the president's Secret Service Blue Unit.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:15.99,0:40:18.70,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你走之前  总统有东西想给你看\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's something the president wants you to see before you go.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:18.72,0:40:21.12,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么  -只需要几分钟就好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What? - It won't take more than a few minutes.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:21.12,0:40:21.93,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,放开我的手臂\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Let go of my arm.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:40.13,0:40:41.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你没怎么变嘛  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You haven't changed much, have you, Jack?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:43.70,0:40:44.45,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你想说什么\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What's your point?
Dialogue: 0,0:40:45.38,0:40:48.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我想说我少一个人手  时间又紧迫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My point is I'm short a man and I'm on a schedule.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:50.70,0:40:52.10,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我在找工作\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}I'm looking for work.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:52.79,0:40:55.58,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,这不是工作  你做这个没钱赚  杰克\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}This isn't a job. You're gonna do this for nothing, Jack.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:56.46,0:40:58.32,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,我的薪水是一千块一天\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}My price is a thousand a day.
Dialogue: 0,0:40:59.23,0:41:01.48,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,杰克  我想说你那样对大卫\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, Jack, I'd say you owe me a bit more than that
Dialogue: 0,0:41:01.48,0:41:02.74,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你欠我的可不止这一点\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}for what you did to Dave.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:03.42,0:41:05.27,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你照做  我就不告诉乔\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You do this, I don't tell Joe.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:06.02,0:41:07.14,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,你不照做  你就会忙着\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}You don't do it, you'll be too busy
Dialogue: 0,0:41:07.14,0:41:09.03,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,提心吊胆地找活干\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}lookin' over your shoulder to find work.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:14.02,0:41:17.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-什么活  -你肯定会喜欢的\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What's the job? - You're gonna like it.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:31.08,0:41:31.92,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅根\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Megan...
Dialogue: 0,0:41:33.19,0:41:33.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅根\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Megan.
Dialogue: 0,0:41:34.84,0:41:35.56,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅根\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Megan!
Dialogue: 0,0:41:36.44,0:41:36.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅根\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Megan!
Dialogue: 0,0:41:37.94,0:41:38.40,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅根\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Megan!
Dialogue: 0,0:41:40.78,0:41:42.78,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅根  不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Megan! No!
Dialogue: 0,0:41:49.70,0:41:52.90,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,不  梅根  不\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}No! Megan! No!
Dialogue: 0,0:41:53.28,0:41:54.09,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅根\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Megan!
Dialogue: 0,0:41:56.40,0:41:57.22,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅根\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Megan!
Dialogue: 0,0:42:08.28,0:42:09.02,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅根\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Megan!
Dialogue: 0,0:42:10.17,0:42:10.65,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,梅根\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Megan!
Dialogue: 0,0:42:14.70,0:42:16.11,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,时间正好\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Yeah, we're right on schedule.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:16.43,0:42:17.15,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,太好了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}It's great.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:18.30,0:42:19.89,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,一小时后再和你说\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}We'll talk to you in about an hour.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:20.15,0:42:22.30,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,太好了  好戏开始了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}All right, that's great. Rock out.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:23.72,0:42:25.81,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-我们要去哪  -洛杉矶西部\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- Where are we goin'? - West LA.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:26.53,0:42:29.64,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,-要做什么  -改变\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}- What are we doin'? - A conversion.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:30.35,0:42:31.71,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,什么改变\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}What do you mean a conversion?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:31.71,0:42:35.17,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,今天我们要把政府的一栋大楼变成公墓\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Well, today we're turning a government building into a cemetery.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:36.83,0:42:37.79,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,哪栋楼\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Which building?
Dialogue: 0,0:42:38.05,0:42:40.36,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,有一个对我们穷追不舍了多年的部门\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}There's a branch that's been dogging us for years.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:40.36,0:42:44.87,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,叫做洛杉矶反恐组\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}They call it the LA Counter Terrorist Unit, the CTU.
Dialogue: 0,0:42:46.65,0:42:47.57,Default,NTP,0,0,0,,好极了\N{\fn微软雅黑}{\fs14}Good.

