2
00:00:12,560 --> 00:00:14,120
Right now, terrorists are

3
00:00:14,120 --> 00:00:17,190
plotting to assassinate a presidential candidate.

4
00:00:18,330 --> 00:00:20,700
My wife and daughter have been targeted.

5
00:00:20,870 --> 00:00:24,200
And people that I work with may be involved in both.

6
00:00:25,140 --> 00:00:27,160
I'm Federal Agent Jack Bauer...

7
00:00:27,540 --> 00:00:30,870
...and today is the longest day of my life.

10
00:00:41,060 --> 00:00:46,060
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

11
00:00:41,060 --> 00:00:46,060
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

12
00:00:41,060 --> 00:00:46,060
{\an5}{\pos(145,252)}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

13
00:00:41,560 --> 00:00:46,060
{\pos(67,248)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

14
00:00:41,560 --> 00:00:46,060
{\pos(67,248)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

15
00:00:41,560 --> 00:00:46,060
{\pos(58,238)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

16
00:00:41,560 --> 00:00:46,060
{\pos(84,248)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

19
00:00:47,280 --> 00:01:17,280
{\an9}m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

20
00:00:46,780 --> 00:01:17,280
{\an2}{\pos(26,248)}m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

27
00:00:50,200 --> 00:00:51,220
Mom!

28
00:01:16,190 --> 00:01:17,160
Mom!

29
00:01:21,430 --> 00:01:22,400
Mom!

30
00:01:26,770 --> 00:01:29,070
Do you remember anything yet?

31
00:01:30,070 --> 00:01:31,040
No.

32
00:01:33,210 --> 00:01:34,800
Must be weird.

33
00:01:35,640 --> 00:01:39,410
I mean, I never met anyone that has amnesia before.

34
00:01:42,380 --> 00:01:45,050
I really appreciate you helping me out.

35
00:01:53,660 --> 00:01:56,250
- What's your name? -Tanya.

36
00:01:57,260 --> 00:01:58,530
Tanya.

37
00:02:00,400 --> 00:02:03,030
I hope you're not going too far out of your way.

38
00:02:03,140 --> 00:02:04,370
It's fine.

39
00:02:04,470 --> 00:02:06,840
The hospital isn't far from here.

40
00:02:09,610 --> 00:02:11,340
So, you come from money?

41
00:02:11,450 --> 00:02:14,140
You look like you might, or your husband.

42
00:02:15,350 --> 00:02:19,310
- My husband? - A little band of gold? On your finger?

43
00:02:24,430 --> 00:02:26,790
I don't have any memory of my husband.

44
00:02:44,040 --> 00:02:46,120
Agent Pierce? Jack Bauer.

45
00:02:46,120 --> 00:02:47,840
We met at the Senator's breakfast this morning.

46
00:02:47,950 --> 00:02:49,180
Yeah, I'm sorry about that.

47
00:02:49,280 --> 00:02:51,110
We didn't know the pressure you were under.

48
00:02:51,220 --> 00:02:52,330
Is your family doing okay?

49
00:02:52,330 --> 00:02:53,550
Yes, they're fine. Thank you.

50
00:02:53,650 --> 00:02:55,710
This is my partner, Nina Myers.

51
00:02:56,020 --> 00:02:57,510
Agents Johnson and Aleshire,

52
00:02:58,190 --> 00:02:59,380
they're our surveillance technicians.

53
00:02:59,380 --> 00:03:00,960
I believe you've already met Miss Nash,

54
00:03:00,960 --> 00:03:02,890
she's part of the Senator's advance team.

55
00:03:03,000 --> 00:03:04,830
Yes, from the Senator's staff meeting.

56
00:03:05,030 --> 00:03:08,130
Can I just say how sorry I am to have caused so much trouble?

57
00:03:08,370 --> 00:03:10,460
You didn't know who Alexis Drazen really was.

58
00:03:10,570 --> 00:03:11,610
Now you know he's a killer,

59
00:03:11,610 --> 00:03:13,770
it takes courage to walk into a room with him.

60
00:03:13,870 --> 00:03:15,840
I hate to interrupt, but we must get going.

61
00:03:15,940 --> 00:03:18,710
All right, Drazen is down here in room 1243.

62
00:03:18,910 --> 00:03:21,070
We went over it, there's nothing unusual.

63
00:03:21,180 --> 00:03:23,050
It's ready to rig however you want to.

64
00:03:23,150 --> 00:03:26,240
That gives us 30 minutes to set up visual and audio.

65
00:03:26,350 --> 00:03:27,910
- Fiber optics? - Yes.

66
00:03:28,020 --> 00:03:30,890
We also need to set up monitors in an adjacent room.

67
00:03:30,990 --> 00:03:34,450
All right. 1242 across the hallway has been vacated already.

68
00:03:34,630 --> 00:03:37,760
Okay, good. Gentlemen, I want you to get started right away.

69
00:03:37,870 --> 00:03:40,800
I want coverage of every square foot of this room by at least two angles.

70
00:03:40,900 --> 00:03:42,230
- Yes, sir. - Nina?

71
00:03:42,340 --> 00:03:43,390
Yeah.

72
00:03:44,740 --> 00:03:47,450
Take Miss Nash into 1242, start prepping her,

73
00:03:47,450 --> 00:03:49,070
we'll be there in a minute.

74
00:03:49,180 --> 00:03:50,800
Have you set up the other checkpoints?

75
00:03:50,910 --> 00:03:53,140
Yes. Every entrance to the hotel is covered.

76
00:03:53,250 --> 00:03:55,910
So is every approach from a block away on all four sides.

77
00:03:56,020 --> 00:03:57,510
Any civilians left on the floor?

78
00:03:57,620 --> 00:04:00,210
- No. We've sealed it off from guests I understand. - Good work.

79
00:04:00,320 --> 00:04:02,980
You let me know as soon as Drazen enters this hotel.

80
00:04:13,500 --> 00:04:15,800
There's a hospital at the bottom of the canyon.

81
00:04:15,900 --> 00:04:18,000
I'm not sure how good it is.

82
00:04:19,370 --> 00:04:21,200
Wait, pull over.

83
00:04:21,780 --> 00:04:24,470
- You see something you remember? - Yeah, I think so.

84
00:04:24,580 --> 00:04:26,670
- The restaurant? - Yeah.

85
00:04:57,210 --> 00:04:59,200
Do you recognize anything?

86
00:04:59,680 --> 00:05:01,000
I've been here before,

87
00:05:02,140 --> 00:05:03,510
I was with someone.

88
00:05:04,620 --> 00:05:06,250
With your husband?

89
00:05:08,260 --> 00:05:09,850
Not your husband?

90
00:05:11,530 --> 00:05:14,050
Maybe we should just keep going to the hospital.

91
00:05:14,160 --> 00:05:16,560
No, just being here helps.

92
00:05:18,400 --> 00:05:20,760
Hey, is there a maitre d' or manager?

93
00:05:21,030 --> 00:05:22,730
A manager, Mr. Martin.

94
00:05:22,970 --> 00:05:24,060
Is he here?

95
00:05:24,170 --> 00:05:26,640
No, but he should be in about 20 minutes.

96
00:05:26,740 --> 00:05:28,830
Thank you. I'm going to wait.

97
00:05:50,100 --> 00:05:53,120
Maybe this Mr. Martin knows something about me.

98
00:05:55,870 --> 00:05:57,860
This place seems so familiar.

99
00:06:05,410 --> 00:06:07,240
I think I'm going to stay.

100
00:06:07,380 --> 00:06:08,940
You don't have to wait with me.

101
00:06:09,620 --> 00:06:12,310
Listen, why don't you give me your number...

102
00:06:12,520 --> 00:06:15,750
...and when I'm better, I'll send you whatever I can afford.

103
00:06:19,330 --> 00:06:20,760
You know what?

104
00:06:23,230 --> 00:06:27,100
Send me whatever you can afford, plus $10.

105
00:06:28,770 --> 00:06:31,200
It's cab fare to the hospital.

106
00:06:32,340 --> 00:06:34,470
In case Mr. Martin can't help you.

107
00:06:36,680 --> 00:06:39,440
- Thank you. - Good luck.

108
00:06:55,160 --> 00:06:58,290
So, obviously, without compromising yourself...

109
00:06:58,400 --> 00:07:01,600
...we need you to behave the same way you always have with him.

110
00:07:02,640 --> 00:07:06,270
It's just the thought of letting him touch me again.

111
00:07:06,610 --> 00:07:08,010
I understand.

112
00:07:08,610 --> 00:07:11,840
What do you usually talk about with him? His work?

113
00:07:12,710 --> 00:07:14,530
The truth is we didn't talk much.

114
00:07:14,530 --> 00:07:16,510
It wasn't that kind of relationship.

115
00:07:16,620 --> 00:07:18,340
It was more, "Take the plunge,

116
00:07:18,340 --> 00:07:20,640
and worry about the consequences later."

117
00:07:20,750 --> 00:07:22,240
You know what I mean?

118
00:07:22,720 --> 00:07:23,690
Yeah.

119
00:07:24,490 --> 00:07:25,690
I'm waiting on a signal.

120
00:07:25,790 --> 00:07:27,090
Elizabeth.

121
00:07:28,330 --> 00:07:29,260
Hi.

122
00:07:29,460 --> 00:07:31,800
I heard what's going on. Are you sure about this?

123
00:07:31,900 --> 00:07:32,960
I'm sure.

124
00:07:33,070 --> 00:07:36,230
- If you have the slightest hesitation-- - No, I want to.

125
00:07:36,500 --> 00:07:37,830
Definitely.

126
00:07:41,980 --> 00:07:43,570
May I talk to you a minute?

127
00:07:43,680 --> 00:07:44,970
Yes, sir.

128
00:07:50,050 --> 00:07:52,480
I told you to look after her, not put her in danger.

129
00:07:52,590 --> 00:07:54,060
Senator, I don't need to remind you,

130
00:07:54,060 --> 00:07:56,850
but the threat against you is very real.

131
00:07:57,020 --> 00:07:59,010
That's no reason to put someone else at risk.

132
00:07:59,130 --> 00:08:00,390
I don't think I have.

133
00:08:00,490 --> 00:08:01,590
I'm going to be right across the hall with a squad of men

134
00:08:01,590 --> 00:08:03,930
in case something goes wrong.

135
00:08:04,870 --> 00:08:07,560
He's a professional killer, things can happen quickly.

136
00:08:07,670 --> 00:08:09,600
And we know Drazen is not working here alone.

137
00:08:09,700 --> 00:08:12,670
Arresting him won't stop the others. If you want to put an end to this now, sir

138
00:08:12,770 --> 00:08:14,830
we keep him on the hook.

139
00:08:18,250 --> 00:08:19,680
I know you've been through a lot.

140
00:08:19,780 --> 00:08:21,840
I know these people put your family through hell.

141
00:08:21,950 --> 00:08:24,140
What does that have to do with this?

142
00:08:24,520 --> 00:08:26,070
I hope you're not letting

143
00:08:26,070 --> 00:08:28,610
a desire for payback cloud your judgment.

144
00:08:30,720 --> 00:08:33,420
Sir, this has nothing to do with payback.

145
00:08:34,060 --> 00:08:37,000
This is simply the best way to nail these guys, period.

146
00:08:41,470 --> 00:08:43,700
Elizabeth's father is one of my oldest friends.

147
00:08:44,240 --> 00:08:46,730
I have known her since she was born.

148
00:08:47,270 --> 00:08:48,950
If anything happens to her,

149
00:08:48,950 --> 00:08:51,370
I'm holding you personally responsible.

150
00:08:51,580 --> 00:08:53,150
I understand, Senator,

151
00:08:53,590 --> 00:08:55,880
and I promise you, I will take care of her.

152
00:10:06,420 --> 00:10:07,530
CTU. Almeida.

153
00:10:09,620 --> 00:10:11,930
Hi, I'd like to speak to Jack Bauer.

154
00:10:12,060 --> 00:10:13,390
He's not here. Can I take a message?

155
00:10:13,660 --> 00:10:16,250
Listen, it's really important. I need to speak to him now.

156
00:10:17,440 --> 00:10:19,630
- Who is this? - Kim, his daughter.

157
00:10:20,130 --> 00:10:21,900
- Are you calling from the safe house? - No.

158
00:10:22,340 --> 00:10:23,880
The safe house has been attacked.

159
00:10:23,880 --> 00:10:26,510
The agents that were guarding us are dead,

160
00:10:26,510 --> 00:10:27,950
and my mother is gone.

161
00:10:28,280 --> 00:10:31,100
Whoa, slow down. The agents are dead?

162
00:10:31,530 --> 00:10:34,800
Yes, and I think they've kidnapped my mother again.

163
00:10:35,180 --> 00:10:36,940
I need to speak to my father.

164
00:10:37,120 --> 00:10:39,490
He's not here, Kim. Where are you calling from?

165
00:10:41,620 --> 00:10:43,270
Can I speak to Nina Myers?

166
00:10:44,210 --> 00:10:46,490
She's not here either. Where are you calling from?

167
00:10:46,650 --> 00:10:49,200
- A pay phone. - Kim?

168
00:10:49,440 --> 00:10:50,710
Who did you say this was again?

169
00:10:50,990 --> 00:10:52,940
It's Tony Almeida, I work for your father.

170
00:10:53,040 --> 00:10:55,450
Tell me where you are, I'll have someone come get you.

171
00:11:00,420 --> 00:11:01,170
Kim?

172
00:11:02,950 --> 00:11:04,290
That's what they said to my mother.

173
00:11:04,290 --> 00:11:06,970
That was Jamey Farrell, she was dirty. She's not here any more.

174
00:11:06,970 --> 00:11:08,280
That's not gonna happen again.

175
00:11:08,280 --> 00:11:10,310
Tell me where you are, I'll have someone get you.

176
00:11:10,310 --> 00:11:13,960
Listen to me, I need to speak to my father or Nina Myers.

177
00:11:14,070 --> 00:11:15,330
He's not here, Kim.

178
00:11:15,570 --> 00:11:16,890
Neither one of them are here.

179
00:11:17,890 --> 00:11:19,620
Kim? Hello?

180
00:11:23,730 --> 00:11:26,270
We got a problem. I just had a call from Jack's daughter.

181
00:11:26,270 --> 00:11:28,830
The safe house was hit and the agents are dead.

182
00:11:28,830 --> 00:11:29,880
Call over there right now.

183
00:11:34,940 --> 00:11:36,280
Nothing, not even ringing.

184
00:11:37,580 --> 00:11:38,520
- Parker. - Yeah.

185
00:11:38,520 --> 00:11:41,260
Get Biselli and go to the safe house on Pine Canyon.

186
00:11:41,260 --> 00:11:43,420
Heads up, this could be trouble.

187
00:11:43,420 --> 00:11:44,140
- Call me when you get there. - I'm on it.

188
00:11:44,140 --> 00:11:46,770
She said she thought her mother might have been recaptured.

189
00:11:47,320 --> 00:11:49,230
- How did the girl get out? - i don't know. She didn't say.

190
00:11:49,230 --> 00:11:51,730
She didn't even tell me where she was calling on a pay phone.

191
00:11:51,740 --> 00:11:53,420
Access phone company's computer.

192
00:11:53,420 --> 00:11:55,480
Get a list of all the pay phone calls that have been made

193
00:11:55,480 --> 00:11:57,350
within a five-mile radius of the safe house.

194
00:11:57,360 --> 00:11:59,770
Are you going to call Jack or you want me to?

195
00:11:59,770 --> 00:12:00,770
Not yet.

196
00:12:02,520 --> 00:12:05,280
- It's his wife and kid. - That's exactly why.

197
00:12:05,280 --> 00:12:07,370
His emotions will distract him,

198
00:12:07,370 --> 00:12:08,790
which puts Elizabeth Nash in jeopardy.

199
00:12:08,800 --> 00:12:10,350
She's meeting Drazen in 15 minutes.

200
00:12:10,350 --> 00:12:12,090
We need to keep Jack focused.

201
00:12:12,240 --> 00:12:14,040
All right, when do we tell him?

202
00:12:14,040 --> 00:12:15,360
We don't, I do.

203
00:12:15,360 --> 00:12:18,150
When the situation is under control and not until. Clear?

204
00:12:21,170 --> 00:12:23,540
Elevator's in transit. We're standing by. Copy?

205
00:12:23,810 --> 00:12:25,390
Copy. He's on his way down.

206
00:12:25,390 --> 00:12:27,250
- Are you finished yet? - Ready in 10.

207
00:12:27,310 --> 00:12:28,480
How is Elizabeth doing?

208
00:12:28,830 --> 00:12:31,480
She says she's okay, but Jack, I don't know.

209
00:12:31,800 --> 00:12:33,050
Are you sure we're doing the right thing?

210
00:12:33,200 --> 00:12:35,920
If she can plant the device, it'll lead us to everything else.

211
00:12:35,920 --> 00:12:37,210
Yes, we're doing the right thing.

212
00:12:37,520 --> 00:12:38,440
And if she can't?

213
00:12:38,590 --> 00:12:40,350
We'll arrest him and try to turn him.

214
00:12:40,380 --> 00:12:42,300
He can't touch her. We can protect her.

215
00:12:42,540 --> 00:12:45,340
- I hope so. - Stay focused and we can.

216
00:12:45,700 --> 00:12:46,930
What?

217
00:12:47,670 --> 00:12:48,600
Are you all right?

218
00:12:51,280 --> 00:12:52,170
I'm sorry.

219
00:12:58,790 --> 00:13:01,090
I can't stop worrying about Teri and Kim.

220
00:13:01,440 --> 00:13:03,860
When I think about what they've been through in last 12 hours.

221
00:13:03,860 --> 00:13:05,890
My little girl thought she was gonna die.

222
00:13:05,890 --> 00:13:07,980
Jack, we're going to get them, okay?

223
00:13:09,310 --> 00:13:11,930
If it's any help, from what I could tell,

224
00:13:11,930 --> 00:13:13,530
Teri and Kim seemed all right.

225
00:13:14,080 --> 00:13:15,100
- Really? - Yeah.

226
00:13:16,830 --> 00:13:20,170
- What did the doctor say? - Just some bruises, that's it.

227
00:13:22,360 --> 00:13:24,380
- Okay, thanks. - Okay?

228
00:13:28,940 --> 00:13:29,950
- Nina? - Yeah?

229
00:13:31,100 --> 00:13:33,330
You said that Paulson was going to finish the debrief?.

230
00:13:34,180 --> 00:13:36,210
- Yeah. - Why didn't you stay and finish it?

231
00:13:37,460 --> 00:13:40,220
I thought you wanted me back as soon as they were safe.

232
00:13:40,230 --> 00:13:42,820
No, I asked you to stay with them so that they would--

233
00:13:42,820 --> 00:13:45,630
- Hey, Nina! - Yeah, Mike. Just a minute.

234
00:13:47,540 --> 00:13:49,170
Go back. I will be there in a minute.

235
00:13:49,170 --> 00:13:50,220
- Yeah? - Yeah.

236
00:14:18,150 --> 00:14:19,980
I told you to take it off the hook!

237
00:14:27,630 --> 00:14:29,100
- Yeah. - Rick, it's me.

238
00:14:29,340 --> 00:14:31,630
I told you, you can't keep calling here.

239
00:14:31,630 --> 00:14:35,560
Look, the safe house was bad. The agents are dead,

240
00:14:35,560 --> 00:14:38,050
and my mother is kidnapped again. I know they're after me.

241
00:14:38,050 --> 00:14:39,060
You need to help me.

242
00:14:39,960 --> 00:14:42,180
- Listen to me, I'm coming to your place. - No.

243
00:14:42,410 --> 00:14:45,880
You're the only person who knows the people that have my mother.

244
00:14:46,200 --> 00:14:47,450
I don't.

245
00:14:47,670 --> 00:14:50,990
Rick, I can't go to the police, I don't trust them.

246
00:14:51,140 --> 00:14:53,060
After today, I don't trust anyone.

247
00:14:53,060 --> 00:14:54,690
But if you don't help me right now,

248
00:14:54,690 --> 00:14:56,790
I will tell the police everything.

249
00:15:00,090 --> 00:15:01,580
Now, what is your address?

250
00:15:06,970 --> 00:15:10,270
1804 Glade, in Echo Park.

251
00:15:10,360 --> 00:15:12,350
1804 Glade, in Echo Park.

252
00:15:12,440 --> 00:15:14,530
Okay, I'm going to call a taxi now.

253
00:15:14,820 --> 00:15:17,310
I'm going to meet you there as soon as I can.

254
00:15:17,320 --> 00:15:18,140
Wait for me.

255
00:15:21,660 --> 00:15:22,410
Okay.

256
00:15:24,390 --> 00:15:25,230
Who was that?

257
00:15:30,780 --> 00:15:31,870
Another wrong number?

258
00:15:54,010 --> 00:15:55,020
How's the election going?

259
00:15:57,600 --> 00:16:00,640
- Exit polls look very good. - That's great.

260
00:16:06,290 --> 00:16:07,390
Dad, I'm sorry.

261
00:16:08,610 --> 00:16:09,600
Sorry about what?

262
00:16:13,160 --> 00:16:14,760
You weren't covering up Ferragamo's death

263
00:16:14,760 --> 00:16:16,130
to protect your campaign.

264
00:16:18,800 --> 00:16:19,940
You did it to protect me.

265
00:16:23,070 --> 00:16:25,610
Where did you hear that, your mom?

266
00:16:26,720 --> 00:16:27,710
No, not Mom.

267
00:16:33,850 --> 00:16:37,610
There is some physical evidence, in George Ferragamo's office

268
00:16:37,730 --> 00:16:39,930
that leads directly to you.

269
00:16:40,580 --> 00:16:41,970
Subtle enough so the fire marshals

270
00:16:41,970 --> 00:16:43,750
didn't find it the first time around.

271
00:16:44,090 --> 00:16:46,640
But with a little help, they'll find it.

272
00:16:49,120 --> 00:16:50,930
So, I'll be framed for Ferragamo's murder.

273
00:16:51,310 --> 00:16:53,140
Like I said, whatever it takes.

274
00:16:54,010 --> 00:16:55,760
That's why your father backed off,

275
00:16:56,240 --> 00:16:57,720
and that's why you'll back off.

276
00:17:06,200 --> 00:17:08,200
Do you know how dangerous it was,

277
00:17:08,200 --> 00:17:10,710
to go see Carl, wearing a wire?

278
00:17:11,460 --> 00:17:12,540
Look, it doesn't matter.

279
00:17:13,200 --> 00:17:15,110
I got it. Now you can take it to the police.

280
00:17:18,550 --> 00:17:19,460
Give me the tape.

281
00:17:22,490 --> 00:17:23,350
What are you going to do with it?

282
00:17:27,390 --> 00:17:28,850
Do you trust me, Keith?

283
00:17:58,170 --> 00:18:00,330
It's me. There's been a development.

284
00:18:00,330 --> 00:18:03,080
Palmer is staying in Los Angeles after all.

285
00:18:03,210 --> 00:18:04,560
The Nash girl called you?

286
00:18:04,860 --> 00:18:07,650
Yes. I'm on my way to the hotel now.

287
00:18:09,090 --> 00:18:11,750
Did she say why the Senator changed his plans?

288
00:18:11,950 --> 00:18:13,780
No, he didn't tell her.

289
00:18:13,970 --> 00:18:17,300
Really? She's a highly placed aide.

290
00:18:18,260 --> 00:18:19,330
They've tightened security

291
00:18:19,340 --> 00:18:22,150
since the attempt on his life at breakfast.

292
00:18:22,250 --> 00:18:24,880
I wonder that she wants to see you again so quickly.

293
00:18:24,880 --> 00:18:26,580
You saw her a couple of hours ago.

294
00:18:26,580 --> 00:18:28,890
You don't understand women, Andre.

295
00:18:28,890 --> 00:18:30,380
I understand them well enough

296
00:18:30,380 --> 00:18:33,750
to know they can use as well as be used.

297
00:18:34,400 --> 00:18:35,380
Not this one.

298
00:18:35,740 --> 00:18:38,430
Palmer should have been killed hours ago.

299
00:18:38,700 --> 00:18:41,420
We can't afford any more mistakes, we're running out of time.

300
00:18:41,550 --> 00:18:43,330
He's as good as dead already.

301
00:18:43,690 --> 00:18:45,860
You have to trust me in this.

302
00:18:45,860 --> 00:18:48,080
The Nash woman will tell me Palmer's schedule.

303
00:18:48,080 --> 00:18:49,820
She doesn't suspect a thing.

304
00:18:50,030 --> 00:18:50,890
Maybe not.

305
00:18:53,870 --> 00:18:57,780
Just to be safe, when you're finished, kill her.

306
00:19:08,590 --> 00:19:09,920
Miss Nash, please follow me.

307
00:19:13,660 --> 00:19:15,860
We've planted fiber-optic cameras in the room.

308
00:19:15,860 --> 00:19:18,750
Here, there, and all through here as well.

309
00:19:18,750 --> 00:19:20,900
I'm not really sure what those are.

310
00:19:21,840 --> 00:19:23,770
I'm sorry. Please sit down.

311
00:19:28,590 --> 00:19:30,790
Fiber-optic cameras are tiny cameras.

312
00:19:30,790 --> 00:19:34,030
They're almost impossible to see even if you know where to look.

313
00:19:34,300 --> 00:19:35,830
So when you come into the room

314
00:19:35,840 --> 00:19:38,770
we will have complete visual coverage of the entire suite.

315
00:19:38,770 --> 00:19:40,320
And you'll be able to hear everything?

316
00:19:40,400 --> 00:19:43,900
Yes, every word. You all right?

317
00:19:44,980 --> 00:19:47,070
Okay, now he's going to be here in a few minutes.

318
00:19:48,250 --> 00:19:51,480
This is the tracking device that we want you to plant on Alexis.

319
00:19:51,730 --> 00:19:53,160
Once he leaves the hotel,

320
00:19:53,250 --> 00:19:55,610
we'll be able to track every move that he makes

321
00:19:55,700 --> 00:19:57,550
without exposing ourselves at all.

322
00:19:57,850 --> 00:19:58,930
Where do I put it?

323
00:19:58,930 --> 00:20:00,310
Preferably his wallet.

324
00:20:00,310 --> 00:20:03,310
He'll have it at all times, even if he changes clothes.

325
00:20:03,350 --> 00:20:05,130
As soon as you plant this device,

326
00:20:05,130 --> 00:20:06,860
I will call you on your cell phone.

327
00:20:06,940 --> 00:20:09,420
I will tell you the Senator is waiting for you.

328
00:20:09,640 --> 00:20:12,710
You make your excuses, and you get out of here.

329
00:20:12,710 --> 00:20:15,650
So, I plant the tracker, the phone rings--

330
00:20:15,650 --> 00:20:18,400
- And then you leave. - Okay.

331
00:20:18,590 --> 00:20:21,170
One more thing, if at any point you start to think

332
00:20:21,170 --> 00:20:23,840
he's getting suspicious or you're uncomfortable in any way,

333
00:20:23,840 --> 00:20:25,820
all you have to do here are the words:

334
00:20:25,820 --> 00:20:27,830
"I hope I'm not getting a cold."

335
00:20:28,000 --> 00:20:30,630
- "I hope I'm not getting a cold." - Yes.

336
00:20:30,790 --> 00:20:32,390
Then I'll be here in a few seconds

337
00:20:32,390 --> 00:20:34,430
with at least half a dozen other agents.

338
00:20:34,870 --> 00:20:36,480
But that would ruin the plan.

339
00:20:36,480 --> 00:20:37,760
That doesn't matter.

340
00:20:37,760 --> 00:20:39,040
Right now, all we're concerned

341
00:20:39,040 --> 00:20:41,020
with is your safety. Do you understand?

342
00:20:43,250 --> 00:20:44,330
I understand.

343
00:20:49,810 --> 00:20:51,340
You don't have to do this.

344
00:20:52,880 --> 00:20:54,130
If you're uncomfortable in any way,

345
00:20:54,140 --> 00:20:56,170
no one here will think any less of you.

346
00:20:57,090 --> 00:20:58,050
I'm fine.

347
00:20:59,950 --> 00:21:01,240
And, thank you

348
00:21:02,670 --> 00:21:05,410
for giving me this chance to redeem myself.

349
00:21:14,800 --> 00:21:15,810
You're going to be fine.

350
00:21:18,100 --> 00:21:18,920
Let's go.

351
00:21:22,970 --> 00:21:26,550
Mrs. Bauer? How good to see you.

352
00:21:29,000 --> 00:21:29,740
You know me?

353
00:21:29,940 --> 00:21:32,780
Of course. Will Dr. Parslow be joining you?

354
00:21:33,640 --> 00:21:34,700
Dr. Parslow?

355
00:21:36,600 --> 00:21:38,100
I'm sorry, what's your name?

356
00:21:39,120 --> 00:21:40,850
Mrs. Bauer, are you feeling all right?

357
00:21:41,880 --> 00:21:43,210
Actually, no.

358
00:21:43,210 --> 00:21:48,400
I must have been in an accident or something.

359
00:21:48,400 --> 00:21:52,000
I seem to have lost my memory.

360
00:21:52,710 --> 00:21:55,850
But I was driving by and this place looked familiar, so

361
00:21:57,230 --> 00:22:00,610
- You say my name is Bauer? - Yes.

362
00:22:01,330 --> 00:22:02,790
Does that sound familiar?

363
00:22:04,710 --> 00:22:08,780
Yes, it does, but this man you mentioned....

364
00:22:09,080 --> 00:22:10,340
Dr. Parslow.

365
00:22:11,720 --> 00:22:14,390
You two used to come here together quite often.

366
00:22:17,700 --> 00:22:19,520
But he's not my husband?

367
00:22:21,790 --> 00:22:25,280
He's a doctor, and he's a friend, maybe he can help.

368
00:22:25,760 --> 00:22:28,230
I happen to know the hospital that he works at.

369
00:22:28,230 --> 00:22:29,400
Shall I give him a call?

370
00:22:31,570 --> 00:22:32,450
Yes, please.

371
00:22:41,660 --> 00:22:42,550
We're set.

372
00:22:50,840 --> 00:22:52,780
- Is everything up and running? - Yep.

373
00:22:56,310 --> 00:22:57,200
How's Elizabeth?

374
00:22:57,480 --> 00:22:59,960
She's in her room, waiting for Alexis' call.

375
00:22:59,960 --> 00:23:01,710
She said she wanted to be alone.

376
00:23:01,990 --> 00:23:03,760
- Understandable. - Yes.

377
00:23:24,740 --> 00:23:26,090
You want to tell me what's going on?

378
00:23:27,840 --> 00:23:28,700
What do you mean?

379
00:23:29,440 --> 00:23:30,530
You've been holding something back

380
00:23:30,530 --> 00:23:32,510
ever since you got back from the safe house early.

381
00:23:33,970 --> 00:23:36,460
This isn't the time. Let's not get distracted.

382
00:23:36,480 --> 00:23:40,440
If you don't tell me, I am going to be distracted. So spit it out.

383
00:23:44,200 --> 00:23:45,050
All right.

384
00:23:47,190 --> 00:23:48,270
Teri knows about us.

385
00:23:52,150 --> 00:23:52,870
She guessed it.

386
00:23:52,870 --> 00:23:54,580
I don't know how she did, but she did.

387
00:23:55,750 --> 00:23:56,980
She asked me point-blank.

388
00:23:56,980 --> 00:23:58,860
I couldn't deny it, she would have known.

389
00:24:03,720 --> 00:24:05,330
Did you tell her that it was over?

390
00:24:06,930 --> 00:24:07,930
Of course I did.

391
00:24:12,170 --> 00:24:14,340
I think she was just shocked that it was me.

392
00:24:17,210 --> 00:24:18,370
Someone she knows.

393
00:24:31,350 --> 00:24:32,990
When Teri and I got back together...

394
00:24:36,720 --> 00:24:38,630
I tried to talk to her about this, but...

395
00:24:40,690 --> 00:24:43,700
she said she didn't want to know, so I just let it go.

396
00:24:45,050 --> 00:24:48,020
Look, Jake, you asked me to go to the safe house, so I did.

397
00:24:48,280 --> 00:24:50,470
- I was just trying to help. - I know. I know.

398
00:24:50,610 --> 00:24:53,950
This is my fault. This is all my fault.

399
00:24:54,770 --> 00:24:56,130
Agent Bauer, come in.

400
00:24:59,380 --> 00:25:00,110
Bauer.

401
00:25:00,400 --> 00:25:02,740
We're a go. Drazen dropped off the car with the valet.

402
00:25:02,740 --> 00:25:05,160
Should be upstairs in about two and a half minutes.

403
00:25:05,160 --> 00:25:08,550
Copy. All personnel in the lobby and on the floors,

404
00:25:08,700 --> 00:25:10,640
we are a go. We are a go.

405
00:25:29,500 --> 00:25:30,540
He's in the room.

406
00:25:31,430 --> 00:25:34,190
Copy. Advise when you are green to go.

407
00:25:41,070 --> 00:25:42,050
There's no wallet here.

408
00:25:42,340 --> 00:25:46,210
Let Elizabeth Nash know that the wallet is either in his pants...

409
00:25:46,210 --> 00:25:48,340
or the jacket on the bed.

410
00:25:48,540 --> 00:25:50,150
Copy that, Jack.

411
00:25:59,970 --> 00:26:02,340
Give me a sitrep in one minute. One minute.

412
00:27:01,790 --> 00:27:02,630
Hi.

413
00:27:13,390 --> 00:27:14,850
So good to see you.

414
00:27:24,960 --> 00:27:27,670
I can't believe how much I've missed you.

415
00:27:27,800 --> 00:27:29,090
Oh, me too.

416
00:27:30,600 --> 00:27:33,080
Even though it's only been two hours.

417
00:27:34,250 --> 00:27:36,100
It seems like two years.

418
00:27:42,410 --> 00:27:43,370
Are you okay?

419
00:27:45,300 --> 00:27:46,590
I'm fine. Why?

420
00:27:46,780 --> 00:27:48,620
You seem a little tense.

421
00:27:48,820 --> 00:27:49,760
No, not at all.

422
00:27:53,460 --> 00:27:54,460
Maybe a little.

423
00:27:55,350 --> 00:27:58,030
The polls back East close in less than an hour.

424
00:27:58,040 --> 00:28:00,200
We're all just on pins and needles.

425
00:28:05,410 --> 00:28:07,180
You must have some idea about the outcome.

426
00:28:07,180 --> 00:28:10,350
- Don't you, take-- - Exit polls.

427
00:28:10,350 --> 00:28:13,150
- Yes. - But they're not official.

428
00:28:16,490 --> 00:28:17,830
What can we do

429
00:28:18,420 --> 00:28:19,490
to help you

430
00:28:22,270 --> 00:28:23,620
relax?

431
00:28:25,320 --> 00:28:29,960
It's a little early, but a vodka might be nice.

432
00:28:32,460 --> 00:28:33,730
Nothing else?

433
00:28:35,310 --> 00:28:36,840
If you insist.

434
00:29:06,450 --> 00:29:09,530
- You feeling any better? - Much.

435
00:29:12,190 --> 00:29:14,150
You still don't seem like yourself.

436
00:29:15,350 --> 00:29:18,660
I'll feel better, after I splash some water on my face.

437
00:29:25,500 --> 00:29:26,650
She's going for the jacket.

438
00:29:27,020 --> 00:29:31,740
I want SWAT personnel ready at the door, quietly.

439
00:29:34,340 --> 00:29:35,430
She's got the wallet.

440
00:29:40,620 --> 00:29:42,220
God, Jack, she's dropped it.

441
00:29:50,200 --> 00:29:51,000
Come on.

442
00:29:51,510 --> 00:29:54,540
Come on, Elizabeth, you can do it.

443
00:30:00,740 --> 00:30:03,160
- To the future. - She's put it in her coat.

444
00:30:03,210 --> 00:30:07,410
SWAT team at the door, stand down. Stand down at the door.

445
00:30:18,490 --> 00:30:22,040
Sorry that this campaign is giving you so much stress.

446
00:30:24,680 --> 00:30:26,120
Goes with the territory.

447
00:30:27,340 --> 00:30:30,540
Maybe when the election is over,

448
00:30:30,540 --> 00:30:32,550
the two of us can go somewhere together.

449
00:30:35,270 --> 00:30:37,760
- Like where? - Doesn't matter to me.

450
00:30:40,750 --> 00:30:42,100
As long as we're together.

451
00:30:45,070 --> 00:30:50,250
So, who do I have to thank for keeping you in town?

452
00:30:50,370 --> 00:30:51,620
He's going to feel the wallet.

453
00:30:51,980 --> 00:30:55,150
Give her a second, she's all right.

454
00:30:56,980 --> 00:30:59,980
What made the Senator decide to change his plans?

455
00:31:00,350 --> 00:31:01,360
I don't know.

456
00:31:04,320 --> 00:31:06,140
Is he going to stay in town for long?

457
00:31:07,090 --> 00:31:08,140
It's hard to say.

458
00:31:10,670 --> 00:31:14,080
What about his victory speech?

459
00:31:15,000 --> 00:31:17,240
Will he be delivering it here at the hotel?

460
00:31:18,080 --> 00:31:21,800
Why are you so interested in the campaign all of a sudden?

461
00:31:22,070 --> 00:31:24,470
I have no interest in the campaign.

462
00:31:26,620 --> 00:31:28,760
My interest is in you...

463
00:31:30,020 --> 00:31:32,240
and I know that you go wherever he goes.

464
00:31:33,040 --> 00:31:34,850
I don't know where that is yet.

465
00:31:36,300 --> 00:31:39,870
Well then, I won't let you out of my sight.

466
00:31:40,700 --> 00:31:42,820
I must say I do find it a little strange

467
00:31:42,830 --> 00:31:44,240
that the Senator wouldn't

468
00:31:44,720 --> 00:31:48,770
include someone as smart and capable as you in his

469
00:31:48,950 --> 00:31:49,960
inner circle.

470
00:31:50,350 --> 00:31:51,710
How would you know how smart I am?

471
00:31:51,710 --> 00:31:54,350
We've spent, what, 15 hours together?

472
00:31:54,350 --> 00:31:55,920
And most of that has been in bed.

473
00:31:56,470 --> 00:31:57,710
That wasn't smart.

474
00:32:00,430 --> 00:32:05,310
Was that a complaint or a compliment?

475
00:32:09,540 --> 00:32:11,320
Both, I think.

476
00:32:16,840 --> 00:32:20,410
I just realized that I haven't eaten all day.

477
00:32:21,860 --> 00:32:25,440
Which may explain why I'm in such a foul mood.

478
00:32:27,650 --> 00:32:29,050
You think you could order something up?

479
00:32:30,650 --> 00:32:34,110
- What are you hungry for? - Where's the menu?

480
00:32:40,890 --> 00:32:43,140
I was hoping you would be hungry for something

481
00:32:43,760 --> 00:32:46,050
- other than food. - There you go. Good girl.

482
00:32:56,830 --> 00:32:57,740
It's in the jacket.

483
00:32:58,440 --> 00:33:01,600
She made the plant, clear the hallway.

484
00:33:01,710 --> 00:33:03,520
Copy. Clear the hallway.

485
00:33:12,110 --> 00:33:14,980
I know this might seem a little soon.

486
00:33:23,690 --> 00:33:25,220
I've fallen in love with you.

487
00:33:31,150 --> 00:33:32,210
The hallway's clear.

488
00:33:32,440 --> 00:33:34,040
Copy. I'm making the call.

489
00:33:42,300 --> 00:33:45,150
I thought that all women can sense these things.

490
00:33:54,560 --> 00:33:55,870
Pick up the phone.

491
00:33:58,290 --> 00:33:59,410
Aren't you going to answer it?

492
00:34:00,390 --> 00:34:01,920
It's just someone from the campaign.

493
00:34:01,970 --> 00:34:03,420
No, it could be important.

494
00:34:03,420 --> 00:34:04,530
They can call back.

495
00:34:16,590 --> 00:34:17,940
Say it again, Alexis.

496
00:34:19,120 --> 00:34:20,260
She hung up on me.

497
00:34:20,370 --> 00:34:21,720
Say that you love me.

498
00:34:21,870 --> 00:34:24,240
- What is she doing? - She's baiting him.

499
00:34:24,880 --> 00:34:25,940
I love you.

500
00:34:29,220 --> 00:34:31,170
If I'm not very much mistaken

501
00:34:32,030 --> 00:34:34,890
it seems that you are falling in love with me, too.

502
00:34:40,160 --> 00:34:41,580
I got her voice mail.

503
00:34:41,890 --> 00:34:43,220
Would you order me a hamburger?

504
00:34:46,690 --> 00:34:47,630
Of course.

505
00:34:51,520 --> 00:34:53,460
- What is she doing? - I don't know.

506
00:34:55,130 --> 00:34:56,940
Why did she take off her jacket?

507
00:35:05,240 --> 00:35:06,540
What is going on, here?

508
00:35:07,090 --> 00:35:09,410
She has no intention of leaving that room.

509
00:35:11,460 --> 00:35:12,970
Room Service, how may I help you?

510
00:35:12,970 --> 00:35:15,820
Hello, a hamburger please.

511
00:35:15,870 --> 00:35:19,220
- All rIght, everything on that? - Yes everything.

512
00:35:19,750 --> 00:35:21,600
- We'll send it right up. - Okay.

513
00:35:25,510 --> 00:35:26,600
What's that in her hand?

514
00:35:28,870 --> 00:35:30,450
So now

515
00:35:31,330 --> 00:35:33,120
is there anything else?

516
00:35:34,920 --> 00:35:35,890
Yes.

517
00:35:36,290 --> 00:35:37,560
Oh, my God, she's got a knife.

518
00:35:37,560 --> 00:35:40,170
SWAT team, hit the room! Hit the room, now!

519
00:35:42,700 --> 00:35:43,980
You son of a bitch!

520
00:35:49,740 --> 00:35:52,130
You son of a bitch!

521
00:35:52,130 --> 00:35:55,020
Hold your fire! Get me some towels from the bathroom.

522
00:35:58,230 --> 00:36:00,960
Nina, call in a medevac. We're losing him.

523
00:36:00,960 --> 00:36:02,380
We cannot let him die.

524
00:36:03,690 --> 00:36:04,480
Damn it!

525
00:36:33,240 --> 00:36:34,760
- Just a minute. - Yeah, sure.

526
00:37:10,540 --> 00:37:11,970
I'm looking for Rick.

527
00:37:12,880 --> 00:37:15,340
- Who are you? - A friend.

528
00:37:17,600 --> 00:37:19,070
Are you the one who keeps calling?

529
00:37:19,790 --> 00:37:23,080
- He said I could come over. - Not to me, he didn't.

530
00:37:25,650 --> 00:37:26,800
Maybe you should ask him, then.

531
00:37:26,810 --> 00:37:28,520
I was about to tell you.

532
00:37:29,090 --> 00:37:30,970
I just didn't think she'd get here so fast.

533
00:37:32,130 --> 00:37:33,510
What's going on, Rick?

534
00:37:34,340 --> 00:37:35,390
I'll explain everything.

535
00:37:36,960 --> 00:37:39,140
- I'm listening. - First let her come in.

536
00:37:41,720 --> 00:37:43,060
It's okay, baby.

537
00:37:46,410 --> 00:37:47,310
What does she want?

538
00:37:48,950 --> 00:37:51,230
Something got screwed up with Dan last night.

539
00:37:51,350 --> 00:37:54,550
Big surprise, right? That's why my arm is messed up.

540
00:37:54,820 --> 00:37:56,950
These guys Dan was with, they shot me--

541
00:37:57,130 --> 00:37:58,900
You said you cut your arm on a fence.

542
00:38:04,760 --> 00:38:08,140
These people Dan knows, I need to find them.

543
00:38:08,790 --> 00:38:10,870
And I was hoping that I could go in his room

544
00:38:11,110 --> 00:38:13,080
and find something, to lead me to them.

545
00:38:13,080 --> 00:38:14,490
A phone number, an address....

546
00:38:15,030 --> 00:38:16,920
So you just want to look through Dan's room?

547
00:38:17,390 --> 00:38:18,190
Yeah.

548
00:38:23,270 --> 00:38:25,710
I was wondering if I could borrow some money for the cab.

549
00:39:01,040 --> 00:39:01,750
Teri.

550
00:39:03,860 --> 00:39:04,640
You all right?

551
00:39:11,100 --> 00:39:12,130
You don't remember me?

552
00:39:19,670 --> 00:39:20,440
Phil.

553
00:39:23,440 --> 00:39:27,350
- Are you my doctor? - No, not exactly.

554
00:39:28,180 --> 00:39:29,940
Henry, thank you for calling me.

555
00:39:29,990 --> 00:39:31,560
Have you given her anything to eat or drink?

556
00:39:31,560 --> 00:39:33,660
I offered, but she didn't want anything.

557
00:39:37,900 --> 00:39:38,950
No, it's....

558
00:39:41,050 --> 00:39:42,130
Unless you want some water?

559
00:39:43,670 --> 00:39:45,220
- Sure. - Okay, some water.

560
00:39:47,800 --> 00:39:51,650
All right, we're going to figure out what this is all about.

561
00:39:51,650 --> 00:39:54,090
We're going to get you well again, you understand?

562
00:39:54,750 --> 00:39:55,640
It's going to be fine.

563
00:39:56,660 --> 00:39:57,780
Everything's going to be fine.

564
00:40:03,520 --> 00:40:04,910
Look, I don't know what you want me to say.

565
00:40:04,920 --> 00:40:06,590
We misjudged her emotional state.

566
00:40:06,590 --> 00:40:08,220
No, we didn't. You did.

567
00:40:08,220 --> 00:40:10,360
Mason, it was an unexpected outcome for everyone.

568
00:40:10,360 --> 00:40:13,800
- It's what I said it would be, a bad idea. - Fine, maybe.

569
00:40:13,800 --> 00:40:16,060
Right now we need to figure out our next move is.

570
00:40:16,070 --> 00:40:18,140
What's the status on Alexis?

571
00:40:18,140 --> 00:40:20,040
They're giving him a 50-50 shot.

572
00:40:20,040 --> 00:40:21,380
But even if he comes to live,

573
00:40:21,380 --> 00:40:23,080
they don't know how long it's gonna be until we talks.

574
00:40:23,080 --> 00:40:25,810
Did you find anything in his room? Any phone numbers, any documents?

575
00:40:26,550 --> 00:40:27,760
No, nothing yet.

576
00:40:27,760 --> 00:40:29,410
What am I supposed to tell District?

577
00:40:29,420 --> 00:40:31,450
Tell them whatever you have to. Just keep them off my back.

578
00:40:31,450 --> 00:40:33,890
I need some time before I have to start filling out bunch of field reports.

579
00:40:33,890 --> 00:40:35,420
- Let me in. - Hold on.

580
00:40:35,530 --> 00:40:36,110
Where's Elizabeth?

581
00:40:36,110 --> 00:40:38,330
- I heard someth about a stabbing. - She's fine, sir.

582
00:40:38,330 --> 00:40:41,510
- Where is she? - She's across the hall, she's in custody.

583
00:40:41,510 --> 00:40:43,860
- What! Why? - She stabbed Drazen.

584
00:40:44,070 --> 00:40:45,510
She must been defending herself.

585
00:40:45,510 --> 00:40:47,280
No, sir, that's not the way it went down.

586
00:40:47,280 --> 00:40:49,540
She broke from the plan, she attacked him.

587
00:40:49,540 --> 00:40:51,830
You should have never let her go through with it in the first place.

588
00:40:52,390 --> 00:40:53,460
I got to call you back.

589
00:40:53,510 --> 00:40:54,990
What the hell going on over there?

590
00:40:55,000 --> 00:40:55,870
Senator.

591
00:40:55,910 --> 00:40:57,480
- Let me in. - Certainly.

592
00:40:58,710 --> 00:40:59,460
Senator.

593
00:40:59,460 --> 00:41:01,960
Elizabeth, don't say anything until you speak to a lawyer.

594
00:41:01,960 --> 00:41:04,690
I'm sorry, I don't know what happened.

595
00:41:04,690 --> 00:41:06,290
It's all right, we're gonna work this out.

596
00:41:06,290 --> 00:41:09,260
Senator, please, step away, let us handle this.

597
00:41:09,260 --> 00:41:11,650
I let you take care of it before, and look where we are.

598
00:41:11,650 --> 00:41:13,710
Sir, you are not helping matters right now.

599
00:41:14,060 --> 00:41:14,880
Jack!

600
00:41:15,960 --> 00:41:18,630
Excuse me for one second. What?

601
00:41:18,860 --> 00:41:21,600
It's Alexis' phone. What do we do?

602
00:41:31,740 --> 00:41:33,030
We got to take a chance.

603
00:41:35,700 --> 00:41:36,340
Yeah?

604
00:41:36,340 --> 00:41:39,650
- You have the money? - Yeah.

605
00:41:39,840 --> 00:41:42,120
Okay. We'll meet in 45 minutes.

606
00:41:42,340 --> 00:41:44,110
- Where? - I already told you.

607
00:41:46,330 --> 00:41:48,220
At Connie's, downtown.

608
00:41:50,140 --> 00:41:51,380
How will I recognize you?

609
00:41:51,550 --> 00:41:52,980
I'll wear a red baseball cap.

