6
00:00:34,300 --> 00:00:39,300
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

7
00:00:34,300 --> 00:00:39,300
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

8
00:00:34,300 --> 00:00:39,300
{\an5}{\pos(145,252)}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

9
00:00:34,800 --> 00:00:39,300
{\pos(67,248)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

10
00:00:34,800 --> 00:00:39,300
{\pos(67,248)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

11
00:00:34,800 --> 00:00:39,300
{\pos(58,238)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

12
00:00:34,800 --> 00:00:39,300
{\pos(84,248)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

15
00:00:40,520 --> 00:01:15,520
{\an9}m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

16
00:00:40,020 --> 00:01:15,520
{\an2}{\pos(26,248)}m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

24
00:01:43,410 --> 00:01:44,390
Identify.

25
00:01:44,390 --> 00:01:46,810
Victor Rovner, requesting permission to transmit.

26
00:01:46,810 --> 00:01:47,890
Log in.

30
00:01:58,500 --> 00:01:59,750
Permission granted.

32
00:02:22,830 --> 00:02:26,100
Excuse me a moment. Let me catch up with you.

33
00:02:28,320 --> 00:02:29,310
This is Walsh.

34
00:02:29,310 --> 00:02:30,930
Sir, we just heard from Rovner.

35
00:02:30,990 --> 00:02:32,940
He confirmed there will be an attempt today.

36
00:02:33,020 --> 00:02:34,440
Did he find out who the target is?

37
00:02:34,440 --> 00:02:35,870
Senator David Palmer.

38
00:02:37,540 --> 00:02:40,080
As soon as the polls open, we'll be there.

39
00:02:40,080 --> 00:02:43,670
Senator Palmer seems poised for victory.

41
00:02:45,180 --> 00:02:48,130
I hate it. "On this historic occasion"?

42
00:02:48,130 --> 00:02:50,780
Well, it is an historic occasion, sir.

43
00:02:51,420 --> 00:02:53,040
It's self-serving to say it.

44
00:02:54,330 --> 00:02:56,940
- I want to stay low-key. - Wrong.

45
00:02:57,360 --> 00:02:59,310
Play it up, inspire people.

46
00:03:00,570 --> 00:03:03,690
- Honey, what do you think? - I agree with Patty.

47
00:03:07,160 --> 00:03:09,120
Okay, but not "occasion."

48
00:03:09,120 --> 00:03:10,650
It sounds like we're having brunch.

49
00:03:10,940 --> 00:03:14,270
- "On this historic day"? - Deal.

50
00:03:15,220 --> 00:03:17,510
- You going to bed? - How can I sleep?

51
00:03:17,560 --> 00:03:19,310
No, I'm going to write a few thank-you's.

52
00:03:19,320 --> 00:03:20,820
Call me if you need me.

53
00:03:21,670 --> 00:03:22,860
Thank you, angel.

54
00:03:24,990 --> 00:03:26,290
You're in trouble, Dad.

55
00:03:28,090 --> 00:03:30,900
- Really? - Yeah.

56
00:03:34,820 --> 00:03:36,040
So...

57
00:03:36,910 --> 00:03:39,850
Is she still giving you the cold shoulder?

58
00:03:41,960 --> 00:03:43,800
If by "she," you're referring to your mother...

59
00:03:43,800 --> 00:03:47,580
I'd appreciate it if you'd call her by her name, mom.

60
00:03:48,300 --> 00:03:50,150
And no, she's just busy.

61
00:03:50,150 --> 00:03:50,890
She's busy a lot.

62
00:03:52,420 --> 00:03:55,560
And it's a school night for you, so time for bed.

63
00:04:00,440 --> 00:04:01,860
- Good night. - I love you.

64
00:04:09,470 --> 00:04:11,080
I'm glad you moved back in, daddy.

65
00:04:14,840 --> 00:04:16,130
Me, too, sweet.

66
00:04:16,920 --> 00:04:18,220
Have a good sleep.

67
00:04:23,820 --> 00:04:26,000
- Good night, sweet pea. - Yeah.

68
00:04:34,120 --> 00:04:35,660
She still giving you a hard time?

69
00:04:36,780 --> 00:04:38,520
I don't know when I became the enemy.

70
00:04:39,310 --> 00:04:41,550
I think she blames me for you moving out.

71
00:04:41,650 --> 00:04:43,630
Well, I never gave her any reason to.

72
00:04:44,360 --> 00:04:45,590
Maybe not.

73
00:04:47,910 --> 00:04:50,870
But I think you let her manipulate you, Jack.

74
00:04:51,780 --> 00:04:52,960
No, I don't.

75
00:04:53,510 --> 00:04:54,450
Let me guess.

76
00:04:54,450 --> 00:04:56,300
Just now she was sweetness and light, right?

77
00:04:56,300 --> 00:04:57,980
Then she said something nasty about me?

78
00:04:57,980 --> 00:04:59,840
Yeah, and I just busted her on it.

79
00:05:00,050 --> 00:05:01,530
Why you're taking this so personally?

80
00:05:01,530 --> 00:05:03,640
It's just that mother-teenage daughter thing.

81
00:05:11,000 --> 00:05:12,070
Maybe you're right.

82
00:05:12,070 --> 00:05:13,730
Maybe we should talk to her right now.

83
00:05:14,090 --> 00:05:15,660
Tell her not to play us off each other,

84
00:05:15,660 --> 00:05:18,450
and that if she's insulting you, she's insulting me, too.

85
00:05:20,750 --> 00:05:21,950
Okay.

86
00:05:22,470 --> 00:05:23,640
Good.

87
00:05:23,870 --> 00:05:25,200
I really appreciate that.

88
00:05:31,230 --> 00:05:33,640
So, you just said that you appreciate that.

89
00:05:33,870 --> 00:05:35,280
Do you mean you kind of appreciate it?

90
00:05:35,280 --> 00:05:36,760
I really appreciate it.

91
00:05:36,960 --> 00:05:39,270
Do you really, really appreciate it?

92
00:05:40,710 --> 00:05:42,920
- How much do you appreciate it? - Jack.

93
00:05:46,230 --> 00:05:47,390
Kim?

94
00:05:52,320 --> 00:05:53,550
Kim?

95
00:05:56,740 --> 00:05:57,970
Honey?

96
00:06:06,210 --> 00:06:07,460
Kim!

97
00:06:10,030 --> 00:06:11,310
She snuck out.

98
00:06:12,190 --> 00:06:15,670
That's it. She's grounded for two months, no exceptions.

99
00:06:16,160 --> 00:06:18,510
She can forget about getting a driver's license.

100
00:06:23,090 --> 00:06:25,060
- Hello? - Hey, Teri, is Jack there?

101
00:06:25,060 --> 00:06:26,280
Yeah, he's right here.

102
00:06:26,590 --> 00:06:27,740
It's Nina.

103
00:06:28,260 --> 00:06:29,370
What?

104
00:06:29,370 --> 00:06:30,450
Hey, Nina.

105
00:06:31,600 --> 00:06:34,090
Now? No, I can't.

106
00:06:36,260 --> 00:06:37,410
Yeah.

107
00:06:39,370 --> 00:06:42,210
Okay, fine. Get a hold of the others and bring them in.

108
00:06:42,410 --> 00:06:43,730
Yeah, okay. Bye.

109
00:06:44,780 --> 00:06:46,420
It's Walsh. He's coming into the office.

110
00:06:46,420 --> 00:06:48,440
He wants everybody in as soon as possible.

111
00:06:48,860 --> 00:06:51,420
It's only a briefing. I should be back within an hour.

112
00:06:51,720 --> 00:06:53,360
If she's not here when I get back,

113
00:06:53,600 --> 00:06:55,010
we'll call all her friends,

114
00:06:55,030 --> 00:06:55,890
everyone we know

115
00:06:55,890 --> 00:06:57,720
until we find out where she's gone, okay?

116
00:06:58,210 --> 00:06:59,370
Okay.

117
00:06:59,560 --> 00:07:00,700
I'm sorry.

118
00:07:02,550 --> 00:07:03,870
I'll call you from the road.

119
00:07:17,960 --> 00:07:20,960
- What? - Vincent. Jack Bauer.

120
00:07:21,570 --> 00:07:23,420
Are you planning on seeing Kimberly tonight?

121
00:07:23,420 --> 00:07:25,850
No, man, we broke up. You know that.

122
00:07:25,870 --> 00:07:28,040
Yeah, I just wanted to make sure you know that.

123
00:07:28,420 --> 00:07:30,300
Snuck out on you, huh?

124
00:07:30,680 --> 00:07:32,060
Don't screw with me, Vincent.

125
00:07:32,060 --> 00:07:33,210
Chill, man, look...

126
00:07:33,210 --> 00:07:35,840
I don't know where she's at. You got my word.

127
00:07:35,840 --> 00:07:38,270
That's a real comfort, Vincent,

128
00:07:38,280 --> 00:07:39,320
knowing that I've got your word.

129
00:07:51,770 --> 00:07:54,120
Why are we meeting the guys at a furniture store?

130
00:07:54,260 --> 00:07:55,660
Dan works there.

131
00:07:56,610 --> 00:07:58,150
When are we supposed to be there?

132
00:07:58,150 --> 00:07:59,540
Midnight. We're late.

133
00:07:59,800 --> 00:08:01,200
Yeah, they'll wait.

134
00:08:01,670 --> 00:08:03,000
You're sure about that?

135
00:08:03,590 --> 00:08:05,050
Well, you told them I'm hot, right?

136
00:08:05,050 --> 00:08:06,870
And you're hot, so they'll wait.

137
00:08:07,840 --> 00:08:10,380
Dan's a sophomore at San Diego State.

138
00:08:10,850 --> 00:08:12,310
Yeah, you told me that.

139
00:08:13,300 --> 00:08:14,570
And so is Rick.

140
00:08:14,810 --> 00:08:17,420
I mean, they're not just, you know,

141
00:08:17,420 --> 00:08:19,230
a bunch of high-school idiots.

142
00:08:19,400 --> 00:08:23,100
- And your point is? - They're men, not boys.

143
00:08:23,750 --> 00:08:26,090
- Good, I'm glad to hear it. - Really?

144
00:08:27,540 --> 00:08:28,740
Yeah!

145
00:08:35,820 --> 00:08:37,100
CTU, this is Myers.

146
00:08:37,460 --> 00:08:39,650
This is Jack. What exactly did Walsh say?

147
00:08:39,830 --> 00:08:41,710
Just bring everyone in. No details.

148
00:08:42,490 --> 00:08:44,030
Why does this have to be tonight?

149
00:08:44,110 --> 00:08:45,360
Problems at home?

150
00:08:45,450 --> 00:08:47,250
I'm almost there, I'll see you in a few.

151
00:08:53,270 --> 00:08:54,660
How long is this going to take?

152
00:08:55,030 --> 00:08:57,070
Why? Are we interrupting your social life?

153
00:08:58,210 --> 00:08:59,480
At least I have one.

154
00:08:59,750 --> 00:09:00,880
Funny.

155
00:09:02,300 --> 00:09:03,400
Have you called Langley?

156
00:09:03,400 --> 00:09:05,280
I sure did, I called the Bureau, too,

157
00:09:05,530 --> 00:09:07,710
nobody knows anything, Jack on his way?

158
00:09:07,710 --> 00:09:10,680
Yeah, unfortunately for us, the mood he's in.

160
00:09:23,440 --> 00:09:24,850
- Hello? - Hey.

161
00:09:25,820 --> 00:09:28,090
- Did you hear from Kim yet? - No.

162
00:09:29,440 --> 00:09:30,740
I was thinking we should try and remember

163
00:09:30,740 --> 00:09:32,670
what it was like when we were kids, you know?

164
00:09:33,640 --> 00:09:35,950
It's a different world now, Jack.

165
00:09:35,950 --> 00:09:37,090
Yeah, I know.

166
00:09:38,030 --> 00:09:40,230
- Evening, Jack. - Hey, Paul.

167
00:09:40,240 --> 00:09:42,450
Listen, I was talking to Denise the other day,

168
00:09:42,770 --> 00:09:45,200
and she and Steve took Nicki to a therapist

169
00:09:45,200 --> 00:09:45,770
and they said it helped.

170
00:09:45,770 --> 00:09:47,200
Maybe we should think about that.

171
00:09:47,200 --> 00:09:48,470
Yeah, well, maybe.

172
00:09:48,600 --> 00:09:50,190
We can talk about it when I get home.

173
00:09:52,290 --> 00:09:53,610
Honey, I'm already here.

174
00:09:54,370 --> 00:09:56,120
Let me give you a call back in a little while.

175
00:09:58,310 --> 00:09:59,020
Who's here?

176
00:09:59,020 --> 00:10:01,190
Everyone, we're just waiting for Walsh.

177
00:10:01,190 --> 00:10:03,320
I've activated a satellite uplink in case you need one.

178
00:10:03,320 --> 00:10:04,100
Okay, good.

179
00:10:04,100 --> 00:10:05,850
Tony, I need detailed background

180
00:10:05,850 --> 00:10:07,820
on everyone on David Palmer's staff, now.

181
00:10:08,040 --> 00:10:08,690
Why?

182
00:10:08,690 --> 00:10:11,460
'Cause I think this is about him, I want us to be prepared.

183
00:10:11,530 --> 00:10:13,060
Bad time to play a hunch.

184
00:10:13,140 --> 00:10:15,620
If it leaks out that we're screening Senetor Palmer,

185
00:10:15,620 --> 00:10:17,270
people might think it's 'cause he's black.

186
00:10:17,270 --> 00:10:19,240
It is because he's black.

187
00:10:19,310 --> 00:10:21,230
It makes him the most likely target.

188
00:10:21,450 --> 00:10:23,710
Just saying it might not be interpreted that way on the outside.

189
00:10:23,710 --> 00:10:24,800
I don't care how it's interpreted.

190
00:10:24,800 --> 00:10:27,890
I just gave you an order and I'd like you to follow it, please.

191
00:10:28,680 --> 00:10:29,930
Good, thank you.

192
00:10:30,090 --> 00:10:31,320
Let me know as soon as Walsh gets here.

193
00:10:31,320 --> 00:10:32,690
I've got to make a phone call.

194
00:11:05,780 --> 00:11:08,000
- How are you? - Good.

195
00:11:14,090 --> 00:11:15,310
Come on, let's go in.

196
00:11:25,040 --> 00:11:26,220
You must be Rick.

197
00:11:26,700 --> 00:11:27,860
I must be.

198
00:11:28,330 --> 00:11:30,050
Janet said you guys like to party.

199
00:11:30,400 --> 00:11:31,780
As a matter of fact, yeah.

200
00:11:32,230 --> 00:11:33,800
As a matter of fact, me, too.

201
00:11:35,210 --> 00:11:36,450
Glad to hear it.

202
00:11:39,180 --> 00:11:40,910
Let's get this party started.

203
00:11:45,470 --> 00:11:46,610
Follow me.

204
00:12:13,460 --> 00:12:14,420
Come on!

205
00:12:14,420 --> 00:12:16,820
No, I'm not going up there.

206
00:12:19,000 --> 00:12:20,760
- You smoke? - Yeah.

208
00:12:25,230 --> 00:12:28,650
Polls open in less than seven hours here in California....

209
00:12:28,650 --> 00:12:30,260
Detective Castolano, please.

210
00:12:32,140 --> 00:12:33,280
Yeah.

211
00:12:33,760 --> 00:12:36,710
Senator Palmer arrived in Los Angeles this morning,

212
00:12:36,710 --> 00:12:38,610
and showed a young group of fans....

213
00:12:39,850 --> 00:12:42,720
Frank, it's Jack Bauer, over CTU.

214
00:12:42,990 --> 00:12:43,920
This is kind of embarrassing,

215
00:12:43,920 --> 00:12:45,910
but my daughter Kimberly snuck out of the house...

216
00:12:45,910 --> 00:12:49,190
and she's not back yet. I was wondering if we sent her vitals over...

217
00:12:49,190 --> 00:12:51,130
could you guys keep an eye out for her?

218
00:12:51,730 --> 00:12:54,520
Yeah, no, I'm sure she's okay. Yeah, that'd be great.

219
00:12:54,520 --> 00:12:56,400
Thanks a lot. I owe you. Bye.

220
00:12:56,610 --> 00:12:58,050
Richard. Everybody's inside. Come on.

221
00:12:58,050 --> 00:12:59,110
Good.

222
00:12:59,110 --> 00:13:00,660
- Mr. Walsh. - Hello, Nina

223
00:13:00,690 --> 00:13:02,090
- Shall we get started? - Please.

224
00:13:05,880 --> 00:13:07,980
We believe that by the end of the day,

225
00:13:07,980 --> 00:13:10,410
an attempt will be made on David Palmer's life.

226
00:13:12,300 --> 00:13:14,140
- How good's his security? - Very good.

227
00:13:14,140 --> 00:13:16,650
Maybe not good enough to handle what's coming in the end of today...

228
00:13:17,200 --> 00:13:19,430
A shooter, well-funded, from overseas.

229
00:13:19,430 --> 00:13:21,120
What foreign power wants Palmer dead?

230
00:13:21,120 --> 00:13:22,320
Probably none.

231
00:13:22,700 --> 00:13:24,060
Most likely a domestic hate-group

232
00:13:24,070 --> 00:13:25,820
hired someone from out of the country.

233
00:13:25,820 --> 00:13:27,080
It's harder to trace.

234
00:13:27,540 --> 00:13:29,800
Check the background of everyone around Palmer.

235
00:13:29,800 --> 00:13:31,710
Cross it with terrorist databases.

236
00:13:31,710 --> 00:13:33,940
- Start now. - Okay, we're on it. Let's go.

237
00:13:34,430 --> 00:13:35,570
Jack.

238
00:13:39,450 --> 00:13:40,630
I'll be right with you.

239
00:13:42,810 --> 00:13:43,950
How you doing?

240
00:13:45,820 --> 00:13:47,090
I can't complain.

241
00:13:47,670 --> 00:13:48,890
Can't or won't?

242
00:13:50,960 --> 00:13:52,210
Things better at home?

243
00:13:53,740 --> 00:13:55,460
Yeah. We're trying.

244
00:13:58,440 --> 00:14:00,680
What I'm about to tell you doesn't leave this room.

245
00:14:02,330 --> 00:14:03,500
Fine.

246
00:14:10,870 --> 00:14:13,300
There may be an element inside the Agency

247
00:14:13,300 --> 00:14:15,440
- involved with the hit on Palmer. - What?

248
00:14:15,440 --> 00:14:17,710
For the next 24 hours, I want you all over this.

249
00:14:17,710 --> 00:14:19,900
You're gonna interfacing with every division in the region.

250
00:14:19,900 --> 00:14:22,240
I am the last person on this planet

251
00:14:22,240 --> 00:14:23,780
you want to bring something like this to.

252
00:14:23,780 --> 00:14:25,590
- I don't agree. - Richard.

253
00:14:26,860 --> 00:14:28,800
I built a case against three of our own agents

254
00:14:28,810 --> 00:14:30,920
and busted them for taking bribes.

255
00:14:31,180 --> 00:14:33,910
If there's a conspiracy in the Agency to kill David Palmer,

256
00:14:33,910 --> 00:14:35,210
I'll never get near it.

257
00:14:35,210 --> 00:14:36,670
Well, you'll have to, Jack,

258
00:14:39,040 --> 00:14:41,620
'cause you're the only guy that I can trust.

259
00:14:51,280 --> 00:14:52,730
If Palmer gets hit...

260
00:14:53,200 --> 00:14:54,300
the first African-American

261
00:14:54,300 --> 00:14:56,290
with a real shot at the White House.

262
00:14:57,020 --> 00:14:58,720
It'll tear this country apart.

263
00:15:09,820 --> 00:15:11,490
I'll look into it. I'll do the best I can.

264
00:15:11,490 --> 00:15:13,180
Good.

265
00:15:14,310 --> 00:15:15,920
George Mason is coming from Division

266
00:15:15,920 --> 00:15:18,140
to give you a detailed briefing on Palmer.

267
00:15:18,220 --> 00:15:20,120
You think I should trust George Mason?

268
00:15:20,430 --> 00:15:22,280
Until we get a better handle on things,

269
00:15:22,570 --> 00:15:23,890
don't trust anybody.

270
00:15:27,270 --> 00:15:28,720
Not even your own people.

271
00:15:31,310 --> 00:15:32,960
We got to find the shooter, Jack.

272
00:15:34,460 --> 00:15:35,590
Whatever it takes.

273
00:15:40,890 --> 00:15:41,980
Excuse me.

274
00:15:42,650 --> 00:15:45,210
How much longer till we land in Los Angeles?

275
00:15:45,210 --> 00:15:47,060
Let's see. It's 12:20.

276
00:15:47,060 --> 00:15:48,050
Just over an hour.

277
00:15:48,240 --> 00:15:49,330
Thank you.

278
00:16:02,650 --> 00:16:04,850
- You want to hit the road? - Yeah, sure.

279
00:16:08,970 --> 00:16:10,100
Brooks here.

280
00:16:11,100 --> 00:16:14,210
Hey, Martin, how you doing? It's the photographer.

281
00:16:14,650 --> 00:16:17,070
It's very well, Patty. I'm landing in one hour.

282
00:16:17,770 --> 00:16:19,390
Are we still on for breakfast?

283
00:16:19,390 --> 00:16:21,100
Meet Secret Service in the lobby at 7:00

284
00:16:21,100 --> 00:16:22,520
and they'll take care of you.

285
00:16:22,900 --> 00:16:25,220
Will Senator Palmer be at the breakfast?

286
00:16:25,220 --> 00:16:26,360
You bet.

287
00:16:26,670 --> 00:16:27,800
Good.

288
00:16:28,310 --> 00:16:30,650
- I'll see you then. - Fly safe.

289
00:16:32,750 --> 00:16:36,110
Excuse me. You know David Palmer?

290
00:16:37,160 --> 00:16:41,390
Not yet. I am meeting him tomorrow.

291
00:16:41,400 --> 00:16:42,810
We have been sitting here...

292
00:16:43,670 --> 00:16:45,170
...this whole time making small-talk

293
00:16:45,170 --> 00:16:47,090
and you never even mentioned it.

294
00:16:48,590 --> 00:16:51,300
I'm going to be taking a few pictures of him.

295
00:16:52,310 --> 00:16:54,410
You're a photographer?

296
00:16:55,190 --> 00:16:59,290
Have I ever seen one of your photographs?

297
00:17:02,110 --> 00:17:03,250
What's next?

298
00:17:03,400 --> 00:17:05,620
George Mason will be here in a few minutes

299
00:17:05,620 --> 00:17:07,130
and then he's going to brief me.

300
00:17:08,160 --> 00:17:09,600
You, not us?

301
00:17:13,610 --> 00:17:16,710
You can't shut me out, Jack. Not here.

302
00:17:16,710 --> 00:17:18,930
It's Walsh. He wants me to meet Mason alone.

303
00:17:18,930 --> 00:17:20,420
- Why? - He didn't say.

304
00:17:21,540 --> 00:17:22,690
You're lying.

305
00:17:23,910 --> 00:17:27,170
Yes, I am, but you're still going to have to trust me.

306
00:17:28,510 --> 00:17:30,990
One of these days you're going to ask for too much.

307
00:17:33,110 --> 00:17:35,440
I'm terribly afraid that today's going to be that day.

308
00:17:35,440 --> 00:17:37,370
- Yeah? - Hi, it's me.

309
00:17:38,100 --> 00:17:40,520
- Did you hear anything? - No.

310
00:17:41,760 --> 00:17:42,680
What's wrong?

311
00:17:42,680 --> 00:17:44,650
I found three joints in her desk.

312
00:17:45,020 --> 00:17:45,800
Terrific.

313
00:17:45,800 --> 00:17:48,940
I know it's not the end of the world, but I don't like it.

314
00:17:49,060 --> 00:17:50,250
I don't either.

315
00:17:51,030 --> 00:17:52,830
Maybe you can get into her e-mail...

316
00:17:52,930 --> 00:17:54,570
check her messages or something.

317
00:17:54,760 --> 00:17:55,970
We gave her her own password to show

318
00:17:55,980 --> 00:17:57,640
that we trusted her, remember?

319
00:17:59,020 --> 00:18:00,220
Yeah.

320
00:18:00,700 --> 00:18:01,960
Honey, I....

321
00:18:03,310 --> 00:18:05,680
I'm so sorry that I can't be there with you right now.

322
00:18:06,450 --> 00:18:07,530
Look, I can't really talk right now.

323
00:18:07,530 --> 00:18:09,160
Let me call you back, Okay?

324
00:18:10,030 --> 00:18:12,060
- Okay. - Okay, bye.

325
00:18:15,340 --> 00:18:17,300
- Everything okay? - Yeah.

326
00:18:22,670 --> 00:18:24,820
When I got into San Diego State I figured,

327
00:18:24,820 --> 00:18:26,590
"What the hell? Give college a try."

328
00:18:29,060 --> 00:18:30,960
- Do you live near the beach? - Yeah.

329
00:18:33,070 --> 00:18:34,240
Do you surf?

330
00:18:34,680 --> 00:18:36,530
No. Surfing's way too motivated.

331
00:18:36,530 --> 00:18:38,880
You got to get wet, there's sharks...

332
00:18:39,230 --> 00:18:40,860
...you got to call everybody "Dude."

333
00:18:42,820 --> 00:18:45,250
- Why? - No reason.

334
00:18:45,970 --> 00:18:47,230
My dad surfs.

335
00:18:47,870 --> 00:18:48,860
Surfed.

336
00:18:48,860 --> 00:18:50,560
He doesn't anymore? He's too old?

337
00:18:51,940 --> 00:18:53,230
My father's dead.

338
00:18:55,190 --> 00:18:56,800
Hey, my bad.

339
00:18:58,910 --> 00:19:00,450
It's okay. He was this...

340
00:19:01,900 --> 00:19:03,650
...really great guy, and then...

341
00:19:04,770 --> 00:19:06,780
- ...six months ago, he.. - I'm sorry.

342
00:19:08,800 --> 00:19:10,150
Yeah. I'm over it.

343
00:19:11,440 --> 00:19:14,230
Getting over it. It's hard but I am.

344
00:19:23,610 --> 00:19:25,000
Mason's on his way up.

345
00:19:39,900 --> 00:19:42,500
- George. - Jack. How's it going?

346
00:19:42,500 --> 00:19:43,910
Good to see you. Come on in.

347
00:19:45,680 --> 00:19:47,370
How much did Walsh tell you down there?

348
00:19:47,580 --> 00:19:48,700
Not much.

349
00:19:49,120 --> 00:19:51,660
Palmer's the target, shooter's the real deal.

350
00:19:52,020 --> 00:19:53,180
That's about it.

351
00:19:53,720 --> 00:19:55,850
I can narrow it down for you a bit, if you like.

352
00:19:55,850 --> 00:19:56,990
Please do.

353
00:19:59,020 --> 00:20:01,500
We think the shooter's European, probably German...

354
00:20:02,040 --> 00:20:05,190
...and that he's either here already or he's coming today.

355
00:20:05,910 --> 00:20:07,900
This will get you into secured data nationwide.

356
00:20:07,900 --> 00:20:10,160
See if it clicks with anything you already have.

357
00:20:10,260 --> 00:20:11,610
Who's the source on this?

358
00:20:12,050 --> 00:20:13,440
That I can't give you.

359
00:20:14,530 --> 00:20:17,300
- Because? - Because I'm not authorized to.

360
00:20:18,670 --> 00:20:20,290
George, how can I cross-check the data

361
00:20:20,290 --> 00:20:22,880
if I don't know where the original information's coming from?

362
00:20:25,440 --> 00:20:27,920
What do you know about Palmer's politics?

363
00:20:30,450 --> 00:20:32,400
You know he's no friend to the Agency, right?

364
00:20:32,400 --> 00:20:34,550
And if he gets elected, this place gets gutted.

365
00:20:36,050 --> 00:20:38,590
- What are you trying to say? - I'm not saying anything.

366
00:20:38,960 --> 00:20:42,090
Saying do your job, and stay out of what doesn't concern you.

367
00:20:43,350 --> 00:20:44,490
Fair enough.

368
00:20:44,770 --> 00:20:46,420
Good. Then we're done.

369
00:20:49,420 --> 00:20:50,560
George.

370
00:20:51,650 --> 00:20:52,820
I need a favor.

371
00:20:53,330 --> 00:20:54,950
I need you to call your boss

372
00:20:54,960 --> 00:20:57,950
and ask him to give me clearance on the identification of this source.

373
00:20:57,950 --> 00:20:59,880
I thought we agreed that it didn't matter.

374
00:20:59,880 --> 00:21:01,190
But I still got to call Walsh

375
00:21:01,200 --> 00:21:03,180
and tell him that I did everything I could.

376
00:21:03,180 --> 00:21:05,260
I would like to cover my own ass.

377
00:21:05,670 --> 00:21:08,020
Jack, you're finally learning how to play the game.

378
00:21:09,150 --> 00:21:11,020
Sure, I'll call Chappelle for you.

379
00:21:11,100 --> 00:21:12,790
- Use your phone? - Please do.

380
00:21:13,430 --> 00:21:14,790
You want a cup of coffee?

381
00:21:14,970 --> 00:21:16,240
No, I'm good.

382
00:21:17,210 --> 00:21:18,330
Thanks.

383
00:21:26,060 --> 00:21:27,560
I want to hear Mason's call.

384
00:21:34,980 --> 00:21:36,670
At the sound of the tone,

385
00:21:36,680 --> 00:21:40,830
the time will be 12:29 and 30 seconds.

386
00:21:48,600 --> 00:21:50,780
At the sound of the tone, the time....

387
00:21:50,780 --> 00:21:53,150
Yeah, I'm talking to my boss, Jack.

388
00:21:53,400 --> 00:21:56,090
Right, you stupid chump.

389
00:22:00,960 --> 00:22:03,540
- What are you doing? - He's screwing with us.

390
00:22:03,830 --> 00:22:05,030
Get me that binder.

391
00:22:05,460 --> 00:22:07,380
- What? - The binder. Get me the binder

392
00:22:07,380 --> 00:22:09,040
At the sound of the tone...

393
00:22:12,050 --> 00:22:13,370
We need to talk about this?

394
00:22:25,200 --> 00:22:26,340
Nina?

395
00:22:40,280 --> 00:22:43,390
You can consider your ass officially covered. Chappelle said no.

396
00:22:57,220 --> 00:22:58,570
You are out of your mind.

397
00:23:00,950 --> 00:23:03,530
Mason's holding something back. I need some bargaining power.

398
00:23:03,530 --> 00:23:04,780
How are you going to get it?

399
00:23:05,860 --> 00:23:07,620
Remember Phillipe Darcet?

400
00:23:07,880 --> 00:23:10,270
Heroin dealer, Barcelona?

401
00:23:10,270 --> 00:23:11,430
Yeah.

402
00:23:11,500 --> 00:23:14,270
Mason was the point man on his bust last August.

403
00:23:14,360 --> 00:23:17,710
When they rolled up Darcet's assets, $200,000 was missing.

404
00:23:17,960 --> 00:23:20,350
I always thought it fell into Mason's pockets.

405
00:23:20,720 --> 00:23:22,210
Now I need proof.

406
00:23:23,850 --> 00:23:26,460
You're going to blackmail a District director?

407
00:23:27,480 --> 00:23:29,640
I want you to check Darcet's accounts.

408
00:23:30,050 --> 00:23:33,410
You can access them through the secured files. Use this.

409
00:23:34,470 --> 00:23:37,710
Nina, he's going to wake up in a half an hour or less.

417
00:24:08,030 --> 00:24:10,010
Senator Palmer, blending intelligence...

418
00:24:10,010 --> 00:24:12,880
...political courage, hard work, and luck....

419
00:24:15,520 --> 00:24:17,450
Damn it! Hello?

420
00:24:17,500 --> 00:24:20,750
I'm sorry to bother you at this hour. My name is Alan York.

421
00:24:20,790 --> 00:24:24,240
I found this number in my daughter's calendar.

422
00:24:24,270 --> 00:24:26,800
- Who's your daughter? - Janet York.

423
00:24:27,000 --> 00:24:30,120
- Do you have a son or a... - Daughter... Kimberly.

424
00:24:30,600 --> 00:24:33,010
She snuck out of the house. Is Janet gone, too?

425
00:24:33,010 --> 00:24:36,630
Yes, I bet they're together. Any idea where they might be?

426
00:24:36,630 --> 00:24:39,140
None. Did Janet say anything?

427
00:24:39,180 --> 00:24:41,210
She was gone when I came home from work.

428
00:24:42,080 --> 00:24:44,480
Can I give you my number in case you hear anything?

429
00:24:44,480 --> 00:24:45,980
Yeah, of course.

430
00:24:49,590 --> 00:24:51,310
I've got Darcet's account number.

431
00:24:51,580 --> 00:24:52,530
Good.

432
00:24:52,530 --> 00:24:54,360
It's encrypted. I can't get around it.

433
00:24:55,760 --> 00:24:57,990
- Ask Tony to do it. - He'll need a reason.

434
00:24:59,810 --> 00:25:02,940
If he thinks he's doing it for me. Not if he's doing it for you.

435
00:25:05,610 --> 00:25:07,180
I'm surprised you noticed.

436
00:25:08,310 --> 00:25:09,530
I noticed.

437
00:25:11,110 --> 00:25:12,520
Well, you shouldn't have.

438
00:25:27,780 --> 00:25:29,070
- Tony. - Yeah.

439
00:25:29,070 --> 00:25:30,290
I need you to do something for me.

440
00:25:30,290 --> 00:25:31,580
For you or for Jack?

441
00:25:33,720 --> 00:25:35,310
I need you to get into this account.

446
00:25:37,690 --> 00:25:39,130
What does Phillipe Darcet's bank account have to do

447
00:25:39,130 --> 00:25:40,870
with David Palmer?

448
00:25:40,880 --> 00:25:42,150
We don't know yet.

449
00:25:42,250 --> 00:25:43,660
We're trying to pick up a thread.

450
00:25:44,720 --> 00:25:46,260
That's interesting, because

451
00:25:46,870 --> 00:25:48,450
I've been trying to pick up a thread of my own.

452
00:25:48,450 --> 00:25:49,570
About what?

453
00:25:50,810 --> 00:25:52,450
Whether you're still sleeping with Jack.

454
00:25:54,550 --> 00:25:55,980
Who says I ever did?

455
00:25:57,820 --> 00:25:59,150
What do you see in him?

456
00:26:00,100 --> 00:26:02,720
- He turned in his own people. - They were dirty.

457
00:26:04,060 --> 00:26:05,430
And he's Mr. Clean?

458
00:26:05,990 --> 00:26:07,330
Yes, he is.

459
00:26:08,470 --> 00:26:11,310
Look, we don't have a lot of time. Will you help me out here?

460
00:26:12,520 --> 00:26:13,760
Please?

461
00:26:15,770 --> 00:26:17,080
I'll see what I can find.

462
00:26:19,660 --> 00:26:21,130
I'll see what I can find!

463
00:26:33,410 --> 00:26:36,380
Jamey, if I give you a phone number...

464
00:26:36,380 --> 00:26:39,340
...could you hack in and get all the passwords connected to it?

465
00:26:39,400 --> 00:26:40,770
Sure, if you have a warrant.

466
00:26:41,420 --> 00:26:43,210
And if I didn't have a warrant?

467
00:26:44,460 --> 00:26:45,690
It's important?

468
00:26:46,080 --> 00:26:47,360
It's very important.

469
00:26:52,570 --> 00:26:53,720
Go.

470
00:27:15,770 --> 00:27:18,050
- Hello? - Hey, it's me.

471
00:27:18,750 --> 00:27:20,210
I got her password.

472
00:27:20,210 --> 00:27:21,380
What is it?

473
00:27:22,060 --> 00:27:24,000
"Lifesucks," One word.

475
00:27:24,310 --> 00:27:25,530
Perfect.

476
00:27:26,020 --> 00:27:29,000
So, are you going to be around this weekend?

477
00:27:29,450 --> 00:27:30,710
I could be.

478
00:27:32,520 --> 00:27:33,670
Be.

479
00:27:43,870 --> 00:27:46,360
- Where are they? - I don't know.

480
00:27:55,760 --> 00:27:57,650
Did you ever meet Princess Di?

481
00:27:57,990 --> 00:27:59,090
Yeah.

482
00:27:59,350 --> 00:28:01,080
But I never took her picture.

483
00:28:02,780 --> 00:28:04,060
What was she like?

484
00:28:04,740 --> 00:28:06,000
She was cool.

485
00:28:10,540 --> 00:28:11,770
Can I....

486
00:28:14,850 --> 00:28:16,970
Can I see one of your photographs?

487
00:28:19,310 --> 00:28:21,110
- My photographs? - Yeah.

488
00:28:22,400 --> 00:28:23,610
Yeah.

489
00:28:28,390 --> 00:28:30,100
How about this one right here?

490
00:28:39,040 --> 00:28:40,560
That's very beautiful.

491
00:28:43,690 --> 00:28:45,600
- Munich? - Yeah.

492
00:28:54,720 --> 00:28:56,020
Finish the speech?

493
00:28:56,920 --> 00:28:58,210
Taking a break.

494
00:28:58,700 --> 00:29:00,730
The guys got tired of me yelling at them.

495
00:29:00,760 --> 00:29:02,450
Big, old, grumpy bear.

496
00:29:11,570 --> 00:29:12,780
How you doing?

497
00:29:13,020 --> 00:29:15,430
Fine, just a few dozen more to go.

498
00:29:15,750 --> 00:29:17,360
You don't have to do these yourself.

499
00:29:18,410 --> 00:29:20,260
The personal touch never hurts.

500
00:29:20,370 --> 00:29:22,090
- Sure doesn't. - Yes.

501
00:29:22,090 --> 00:29:23,520
Yes.

502
00:29:24,610 --> 00:29:25,870
Sir?

503
00:29:26,940 --> 00:29:31,080
Phone call, Senator. It's Maureen Kingsley from the network.

504
00:29:31,390 --> 00:29:33,210
Come on, Patty, it's after midnight.

505
00:29:33,210 --> 00:29:35,080
She says it's urgent.

506
00:29:41,450 --> 00:29:44,160
Maureen, this better be good.

507
00:29:44,380 --> 00:29:46,250
Can I get you some coffee or anything?

508
00:29:46,460 --> 00:29:47,760
Thank you, Patty.

509
00:29:47,760 --> 00:29:49,160
My response?

510
00:29:50,110 --> 00:29:51,660
Here's my response.

511
00:29:51,940 --> 00:29:54,970
You air that allegation, or anything remotely like it....

512
00:30:00,780 --> 00:30:02,530
This conversation is over, Maureen.

513
00:30:11,810 --> 00:30:13,080
That'll be all, Patty.

514
00:30:15,860 --> 00:30:16,990
Sweetheart?

515
00:30:17,560 --> 00:30:18,800
What was it?

516
00:30:19,450 --> 00:30:22,200
Just more media nonsense. Not important.

517
00:30:25,040 --> 00:30:26,780
It didn't sound not important.

518
00:30:29,640 --> 00:30:31,870
Since when don't we talk about things?

519
00:31:09,240 --> 00:31:11,920
This is Richard Walsh. At the tone, leave a message.

520
00:31:11,930 --> 00:31:13,390
Richard, it's Jack.

521
00:31:13,390 --> 00:31:14,850
Call me back. It's important.

522
00:31:23,290 --> 00:31:25,340
I thought you wanted to get your life back together.

523
00:31:25,810 --> 00:31:27,510
Make things right with your family.

524
00:31:28,520 --> 00:31:29,790
You think this is helping?

525
00:31:30,890 --> 00:31:32,730
He's got information that I need.

526
00:31:32,730 --> 00:31:34,050
What information?

527
00:31:36,090 --> 00:31:37,280
Never mind.

528
00:31:37,660 --> 00:31:39,390
You can't tell me, fine.

529
00:31:39,390 --> 00:31:41,900
But, Jack, if Tony doesn't find anything,

530
00:31:41,900 --> 00:31:43,040
you could end up in jail.

531
00:31:43,040 --> 00:31:44,220
Probably.

532
00:31:44,570 --> 00:31:46,290
Then what are you doing?

533
00:31:51,950 --> 00:31:53,120
Jack.

534
00:31:54,550 --> 00:31:55,890
Answer me.

535
00:31:57,970 --> 00:32:02,600
Nina, you can look the other way once and it's no big deal.

536
00:32:03,460 --> 00:32:06,110
Except it makes it easier for you to compromise the next time...

537
00:32:06,110 --> 00:32:08,160
...and pretty soon that's all you're doing is compromising...

538
00:32:08,160 --> 00:32:10,200
...because that's how you think things are done.

539
00:32:14,360 --> 00:32:16,180
You know those guys I blew the whistle on?

540
00:32:16,180 --> 00:32:17,670
You think they were the bad guys?

541
00:32:17,970 --> 00:32:19,780
'Cause they weren't. They weren't bad guys.

542
00:32:19,790 --> 00:32:21,290
They were just like you and me.

543
00:32:21,870 --> 00:32:24,290
Except they compromised... once.

544
00:32:36,490 --> 00:32:39,130
I'll see how Tony's coming along.

545
00:32:39,910 --> 00:32:41,130
Thank you.

546
00:32:56,820 --> 00:32:59,300
- Hello? - Hi, it's Teri Bauer.

547
00:32:59,300 --> 00:33:00,930
Hi, have you heard anything?

548
00:33:00,930 --> 00:33:02,990
Yeah, I broke into Kim's e-mail.

549
00:33:02,990 --> 00:33:03,970
Janet sent her one this morning.

550
00:33:03,970 --> 00:33:06,060
They're meeting two guys in the Valley.

551
00:33:06,230 --> 00:33:07,560
Did you get an address?

552
00:33:07,650 --> 00:33:09,190
Yep, I'm going right now.

553
00:33:09,780 --> 00:33:10,750
Would you mind if I came along?

554
00:33:10,750 --> 00:33:13,130
I'm getting a little stir-crazy sitting around here.

555
00:33:13,870 --> 00:33:14,770
All right.

556
00:33:14,770 --> 00:33:17,440
I'm leaving right now. Tell me where you live.

557
00:33:23,000 --> 00:33:24,250
Where are we going now?

558
00:33:24,630 --> 00:33:26,930
Wasn't there supposed to be a party at Lacy's?

559
00:33:26,930 --> 00:33:28,370
Anybody got a phone? I'll call.

560
00:33:28,370 --> 00:33:29,510
Yeah, I do.

561
00:33:36,110 --> 00:33:37,160
I got to go home.

562
00:33:37,170 --> 00:33:38,260
Why?

563
00:33:39,000 --> 00:33:40,670
My mother left five messages.

564
00:33:40,810 --> 00:33:42,140
Run home to mommy.

565
00:33:42,140 --> 00:33:43,900
Hey, her father just died, okay?

566
00:33:44,590 --> 00:33:45,990
Maybe her mother needs her.

567
00:33:46,430 --> 00:33:47,590
Your father?

568
00:33:48,710 --> 00:33:49,940
Shut up.

569
00:33:50,200 --> 00:33:51,450
Whatever.

570
00:33:52,420 --> 00:33:53,670
I don't want to go home.

571
00:33:54,300 --> 00:33:55,470
But....

572
00:33:56,890 --> 00:33:58,280
We'll drop you off, okay?

573
00:34:09,520 --> 00:34:10,700
Yeah.

574
00:34:32,720 --> 00:34:33,940
What's your name?

575
00:34:34,810 --> 00:34:35,930
Martin.

576
00:34:36,930 --> 00:34:38,140
I'm Mandy.

577
00:34:39,570 --> 00:34:42,480
Hey, maybe we can get together

578
00:34:42,480 --> 00:34:44,210
when we're in LA, or something.

579
00:34:46,130 --> 00:34:47,600
I'm going to be pretty busy.

580
00:34:51,490 --> 00:34:52,680
See ya.

581
00:34:56,590 --> 00:34:58,910
- Yeah? - I got into the Darcet account.

582
00:34:59,300 --> 00:35:00,670
Nina said you wanted it?

583
00:35:00,670 --> 00:35:02,380
Thank you. Send it to my screen.

584
00:35:02,500 --> 00:35:03,600
All right.

587
00:35:19,240 --> 00:35:20,370
Wake up.

588
00:35:26,680 --> 00:35:27,860
Sit down.

589
00:35:29,030 --> 00:35:30,400
Who's the source?

590
00:35:30,810 --> 00:35:32,550
Who tipped us on the Palmer hit?

591
00:35:36,890 --> 00:35:40,730
Last August when you led the take-down of Phillipe Darcet,

592
00:35:41,570 --> 00:35:42,870
all his assets were transferred

593
00:35:42,870 --> 00:35:45,440
to a custodial account in Langley, Virginia.

594
00:35:45,700 --> 00:35:48,380
$200,000 fell out along the way.

595
00:35:48,660 --> 00:35:52,370
I traced that money to an offshore account in Aruba.

596
00:35:53,120 --> 00:35:55,650
I got a funny feeling about that account, George.

597
00:35:56,210 --> 00:35:57,610
I think it's yours.

598
00:35:57,810 --> 00:35:59,530
Yeah, well, that's a lie.

599
00:36:00,720 --> 00:36:01,860
Good.

600
00:36:02,980 --> 00:36:06,110
Then you won't mind if I send Chappelle the information.

603
00:36:12,410 --> 00:36:13,670
The source, George.

604
00:36:18,190 --> 00:36:20,840
You have no idea what you're getting yourself into here.

605
00:36:21,010 --> 00:36:22,960
Why don't you explain it to me?

606
00:36:24,770 --> 00:36:26,730
You've got five seconds.

607
00:36:30,430 --> 00:36:31,590
Wait.

608
00:36:38,560 --> 00:36:39,790
There's your source.

609
00:36:48,220 --> 00:36:49,920
Thanks for your help, George.

610
00:36:50,110 --> 00:36:51,850
You'll live to regret this, Bauer.

611
00:36:52,150 --> 00:36:53,360
I promise you that.

612
00:37:09,720 --> 00:37:10,460
Excuse me.

613
00:37:10,460 --> 00:37:12,590
Ma'am, we're about to land. If you could please....

614
00:38:20,240 --> 00:38:22,070
Sir, would you please remain in your seat.

615
00:38:22,070 --> 00:38:23,400
I lost my wallet.

616
00:39:22,150 --> 00:39:24,010
- Hello? - Hey, it's me.

617
00:39:24,480 --> 00:39:25,850
Turn left at the light.

618
00:39:26,040 --> 00:39:27,170
What?

619
00:39:27,170 --> 00:39:29,140
I'm in a car with Alan York.

620
00:39:29,140 --> 00:39:31,340
He's the father of one of Kimberly's friends, Janet.

621
00:39:31,340 --> 00:39:32,500
What are you talking about?

622
00:39:32,500 --> 00:39:34,720
Kim got an e-mail this morning from Janet York.

623
00:39:34,720 --> 00:39:36,680
We think they might be out together.

624
00:39:36,770 --> 00:39:37,760
Where?

625
00:39:37,760 --> 00:39:38,640
I don't know yet.

626
00:39:38,640 --> 00:39:40,650
They were meeting some guys in the Valley.

627
00:39:41,550 --> 00:39:42,750
Wait a second.

628
00:39:43,020 --> 00:39:45,130
You're going to the Valley with this guy, Alan York?

629
00:39:45,360 --> 00:39:46,940
What are you going to do if she's not there?

630
00:39:47,630 --> 00:39:51,640
Well, we haven't thought that far ahead yet. I'll call.

631
00:39:53,280 --> 00:39:54,440
Hello?

632
00:39:55,090 --> 00:39:56,230
Teri?

633
00:40:10,310 --> 00:40:12,320
Would you do me a favor? Could you cover for me?

634
00:40:12,740 --> 00:40:13,870
Sure.

635
00:40:14,000 --> 00:40:15,650
Forward all my calls to my cell phone.

636
00:40:15,650 --> 00:40:17,100
I'll be back as soon as I can.

637
00:40:19,450 --> 00:40:20,600
Jack.

638
00:40:20,850 --> 00:40:21,990
What?

639
00:40:23,620 --> 00:40:26,330
A 747 just blew up over the Mojave desert.

640
00:40:26,430 --> 00:40:28,760
Preliminary reports make it sound like it was a bomb.

641
00:40:32,550 --> 00:40:34,890
The passenger list. Get me Walsh on the phone now.

642
00:40:50,450 --> 00:40:51,580
Janet?

643
00:41:01,780 --> 00:41:03,550
Turn here. I live on 10th.

644
00:41:06,460 --> 00:41:08,990
- Dan, I just told you-- - Why don't you just relax?

645
00:41:13,350 --> 00:41:15,450
Can you please tell him that he missed the turn?

646
00:41:15,500 --> 00:41:17,710
You heard him. Relax.

647
00:41:18,420 --> 00:41:20,070
The night's just getting started.

:51,300
I'm going to be taking a few pictures of him.

293
00:16:52,310 --> 00:16:54,410
You're a photographer?

294
00:16:55,190 --> 00:16:59,290
Have I ever seen one of your photographs?

295
00:17:02,110 --> 00:17:03,250
What's next?

296
00:17:03,400 --> 00:17:05,620
George Mason will be here in a few minutes

297
00:17:05,620 --> 00:17:07,130
and then he's going to brief me.

298
00:17:08,160 --> 00:17:09,600
You, not us?

299
00:17:13,610 --> 00:17:16,710
You can't shut me out, Jack. Not here.

300
00:17:16,710 --> 00:17:18,930
It's Walsh. He wants me to meet Mason alone.

301
00:17:18,930 --> 00:17:20,420
- Why? - He didn't say.

302
00:17:21,540 --> 00:17:22,690
You're lying.

303
00:17:23,910 --> 00:17:27,170
Yes, I am, but you're still going to have to trust me.

304
00:17:28,510 --> 00:17:30,990
One of these days you're going to ask for too much.

305
00:17:33,110 --> 00:17:35,440
I'm terribly afraid that today's going to be that day.

306
00:17:35,440 --> 00:17:37,370
- Yeah? - Hi, it's me.

307
00:17:38,100 --> 00:17:40,520
- Did you hear anything? - No.

308
00:17:41,760 --> 00:17:42,680
What's wrong?

309
00:17:42,680 --> 00:17:44,650
I found three joints in her desk.

310
00:17:45,020 --> 00:17:45,800
Terrific.

311
00:17:45,800 --> 00:17:48,940
I know it's not the end of the world, but I don't like it.

312
00:17:49,060 --> 00:17:50,250
I don't either.

313
00:17:51,030 --> 00:17:52,830
Maybe you can get into her e-mail...

314
00:17:52,930 --> 00:17:54,570
check her messages or something.

315
00:17:54,760 --> 00:17:55,970
We gave her her own password to show

316
00:17:55,980 --> 00:17:57,640
that we trusted her, remember?

317
00:17:59,020 --> 00:18:00,220
Yeah.

318
00:18:00,700 --> 00:18:01,960
Honey, I....

319
00:18:03,310 --> 00:18:05,680
I'm so sorry that I can't be there with you right now.

320
00:18:06,450 --> 00:18:07,530
Look, I can't really talk right now.

321
00:18:07,530 --> 00:18:09,160
Let me call you back, Okay?

322
00:18:10,030 --> 00:18:12,060
- Okay. - Okay, bye.

323
00:18:15,340 --> 00:18:17,300
- Everything okay? - Yeah.

324
00:18:22,670 --> 00:18:24,820
When I got into San Diego State I figured,

325
00:18:24,820 --> 00:18:26,590
"What the hell? Give college a try."

326
00:18:29,060 --> 00:18:30,960
- Do you live near the beach? - Yeah.

327
00:18:33,070 --> 00:18:34,240
Do you surf?

328
00:18:34,680 --> 00:18:36,530
No. Surfing's way too motivated.

329
00:18:36,530 --> 00:18:38,880
You got to get wet, there's sharks...

330
00:18:39,230 --> 00:18:40,860
...you got to call everybody "Dude."

331
00:18:42,820 --> 00:18:45,250
- Why? - No reason.

332
00:18:45,970 --> 00:18:47,230
My dad surfs.

333
00:18:47,870 --> 00:18:48,860
Surfed.

334
00:18:48,860 --> 00:18:50,560
He doesn't anymore? He's too old?

335
00:18:51,940 --> 00:18:53,230
My father's dead.

336
00:18:55,190 --> 00:18:56,800
Hey, my bad.

337
00:18:58,910 --> 00:19:00,450
It's okay. He was this...

338
00:19:01,900 --> 00:19:03,650
...really great guy, and then...

339
00:19:04,770 --> 00:19:06,780
- ...six months ago, he.. - I'm sorry.

340
00:19:08,800 --> 00:19:10,150
Yeah. I'm over it.

341
00:19:11,440 --> 00:19:14,230
Getting over it. It's hard but I am.

342
00:19:23,610 --> 00:19:25,000
Mason's on his way up.

343
00:19:39,900 --> 00:19:42,500
- George. - Jack. How's it going?

344
00:19:42,500 --> 00:19:43,910
Good to see you. Come on in.

345
00:19:45,680 --> 00:19:47,370
How much did Walsh tell you down there?

346
00:19:47,580 --> 00:19:48,700
Not much.

347
00:19:49,120 --> 00:19:51,660
Palmer's the target, shooter's the real deal.

348
00:19:52,020 --> 00:19:53,180
That's about it.

349
00:19:53,720 --> 00:19:55,850
I can narrow it down for you a bit, if you like.

350
00:19:55,850 --> 00:19:56,990
Please do.

351
00:19:59,020 --> 00:20:01,500
We think the shooter's European, probably German...

352
00:20:02,040 --> 00:20:05,190
...and that he's either here already or he's coming today.

353
00:20:05,910 --> 00:20:07,900
This will get you into secured data nationwide.

354
00:20:07,900 --> 00:20:10,160
See if it clicks with anything you already have.

355
00:20:10,260 --> 00:20:11,610
Who's the source on this?

356
00:20:12,050 --> 00:20:13,440
That I can't give you.

357
00:20:14,530 --> 00:20:17,300
- Because? - Because I'm not authorized to.

358
00:20:18,670 --> 00:20:20,290
George, how can I cross-check the data

359
00:20:20,290 --> 00:20:22,880
if I don't know where the original information's coming from?

360
00:20:25,440 --> 00:20:27,920
What do you know about Palmer's politics?

361
00:20:30,450 --> 00:20:32,400
You know he's no friend to the Agency, right?

362
00:20:32,400 --> 00:20:34,550
And if he gets elected, this place gets gutted.

363
00:20:36,050 --> 00:20:38,590
- What are you trying to say? - I'm not saying anything.

364
00:20:38,960 --> 00:20:42,090
Saying do your job, and stay out of what doesn't concern you.

365
00:20:43,350 --> 00:20:44,490
Fair enough.

366
00:20:44,770 --> 00:20:46,420
Good. Then we're done.

367
00:20:49,420 --> 00:20:50,560
George.

368
00:20:51,650 --> 00:20:52,820
I need a favor.

369
00:20:53,330 --> 00:20:54,950
I need you to call your boss

370
00:20:54,960 --> 00:20:57,950
and ask him to give me clearance on the identification of this source.

371
00:20:57,950 --> 00:20:59,880
I thought we agreed that it didn't matter.

372
00:20:59,880 --> 00:21:01,190
But I still got to call Walsh

373
00:21:01,200 --> 00:21:03,180
and tell him that I did everything I could.

374
00:21:03,180 --> 00:21:05,260
I would like to cover my own ass.

375
00:21:05,670 --> 00:21:08,020
Jack, you're finally learning how to play the game.

376
00:21:09,150 --> 00:21:11,020
Sure, I'll call Chappelle for you.

377
00:21:11,100 --> 00:21:12,790
- Use your phone? - Please do.

378
00:21:13,430 --> 00:21:14,790
You want a cup of coffee?

379
00:21:14,970 --> 00:21:16,240
No, I'm good.

380
00:21:17,210 --> 00:21:18,330
Thanks.

381
00:21:26,060 --> 00:21:27,560
I want to hear Mason's call.

382
00:21:34,980 --> 00:21:36,670
At the sound of the tone,

383
00:21:36,680 --> 00:21:40,830
the time will be 12:29 and 30 seconds.

384
00:21:48,600 --> 00:21:50,780
At the sound of the tone, the time....

385
00:21:50,780 --> 00:21:53,150
Yeah, I'm talking to my boss, Jack.

386
00:21:53,400 --> 00:21:56,090
Right, you stupid chump.

387
00:22:00,960 --> 00:22:03,540
- What are you doing? - He's screwing with us.

388
00:22:03,830 --> 00:22:05,030
Get me that binder.

389
00:22:05,460 --> 00:22:07,380
- What? - The binder. Get me the binder

390
00:22:07,380 --> 00:22:09,040
At the sound of the tone...

391
00:22:12,050 --> 00:22:13,370
We need to talk about this?

392
00:22:25,200 --> 00:22:26,340
Nina?

393
00:22:40,280 --> 00:22:43,390
You can consider your ass officially covered. Chappelle said no.

394
00:22:57,220 --> 00:22:58,570
You are out of your mind.

395
00:23:00,950 --> 00:23:03,530
Mason's holding something back. I need some bargaining power.

396
00:23:03,530 --> 00:23:04,780
How are you going to get it?

397
00:23:05,860 --> 00:23:07,620
Remember Phillipe Darcet?

398
00:23:07,880 --> 00:23:10,270
Heroin dealer, Barcelona?

399
00:23:10,270 --> 00:23:11,430
Yeah.

400
00:23:11,500 --> 00:23:14,270
Mason was the point man on his bust last August.

401
00:23:14,360 --> 00:23:17,710
When they rolled up Darcet's assets, $200,000 was missing.

402
00:23:17,960 --> 00:23:20,350
I always thought it fell into Mason's pockets.

403
00:23:20,720 --> 00:23:22,210
Now I need proof.

404
00:23:23,850 --> 00:23:26,460
You're going to blackmail a District director?

405
00:23:27,480 --> 00:23:29,640
I want you to check Darcet's accounts.

406
00:23:30,050 --> 00:23:33,410
You can access them through the secured files. Use this.

407
00:23:34,470 --> 00:23:37,710
Nina, he's going to wake up in a half an hour or less.

415
00:24:08,030 --> 00:24:10,010
Senator Palmer, blending intelligence...

416
00:24:10,010 --> 00:24:12,880
...political courage, hard work, and luck....

417
00:24:15,520 --> 00:24:17,450
Damn it! Hello?

418
00:24:17,500 --> 00:24:20,750
I'm sorry to bother you at this hour. My name is Alan York.

419
00:24:20,790 --> 00:24:24,240
I found this number in my daughter's calendar.

420
00:24:24,270 --> 00:24:26,800
- Who's your daughter? - Janet York.

421
00:24:27,000 --> 00:24:30,120
- Do you have a son or a... - Daughter... Kimberly.

422
00:24:30,600 --> 00:24:33,010
She snuck out of the house. Is Janet gone, too?

423
00:24:33,010 --> 00:24:36,630
Yes, I bet they're together. Any idea where they might be?

424
00:24:36,630 --> 00:24:39,140
None. Did Janet say anything?

425
00:24:39,180 --> 00:24:41,210
She was gone when I came home from work.

426
00:24:42,080 --> 00:24:44,480
Can I give you my number in case you hear anything?

427
00:24:44,480 --> 00:24:45,980
Yeah, of course.

428
00:24:49,590 --> 00:24:51,310
I've got Darcet's account number.

429
00:24:51,580 --> 00:24:52,530
Good.

430
00:24:52,530 --> 00:24:54,360
It's encrypted. I can't get around it.

431
00:24:55,760 --> 00:24:57,990
- Ask Tony to do it. - He'll need a reason.

432
00:24:59,810 --> 00:25:02,940
If he thinks he's doing it for me. Not if he's doing it for you.

433
00:25:05,610 --> 00:25:07,180
I'm surprised you noticed.

434
00:25:08,310 --> 00:25:09,530
I noticed.

435
00:25:11,110 --> 00:25:12,520
Well, you shouldn't have.

436
00:25:27,780 --> 00:25:29,070
- Tony. - Yeah.

437
00:25:29,070 --> 00:25:30,290
I need you to do something for me.

438
00:25:30,290 --> 00:25:31,580
For you or for Jack?

439
00:25:33,720 --> 00:25:35,310
I need you to get into this account.

444
00:25:37,690 --> 00:25:39,130
What does Phillipe Darcet's bank account have to do

445
00:25:39,130 --> 00:25:40,870
with David Palmer?

446
00:25:40,880 --> 00:25:42,150
We don't know yet.

447
00:25:42,250 --> 00:25:43,660
We're trying to pick up a thread.

448
00:25:44,720 --> 00:25:46,260
That's interesting, because

449
00:25:46,870 --> 00:25:48,450
I've been trying to pick up a thread of my own.

450
00:25:48,450 --> 00:25:49,570
About what?

451
00:25:50,810 --> 00:25:52,450
Whether you're still sleeping with Jack.

452
00:25:54,550 --> 00:25:55,980
Who says I ever did?

453
00:25:57,820 --> 00:25:59,150
What do you see in him?

454
00:26:00,100 --> 00:26:02,720
- He turned in his own people. - They were dirty.

455
00:26:04,060 --> 00:26:05,430
And he's Mr. Clean?

456
00:26:05,990 --> 00:26:07,330
Yes, he is.

457
00:26:08,470 --> 00:26:11,310
Look, we don't have a lot of time. Will you help me out here?

458
00:26:12,520 --> 00:26:13,760
Please?

459
00:26:15,770 --> 00:26:17,080
I'll see what I can find.

460
00:26:19,660 --> 00:26:21,130
I'll see what I can find!

461
00:26:33,410 --> 00:26:36,380
Jamey, if I give you a phone number...

462
00:26:36,380 --> 00:26:39,340
...could you hack in and get all the passwords connected to it?

463
00:26:39,400 --> 00:26:40,770
Sure, if you have a warrant.

464
00:26:41,420 --> 00:26:43,210
And if I didn't have a warrant?

465
00:26:44,460 --> 00:26:45,690
It's important?

466
00:26:46,080 --> 00:26:47,360
It's very important.

467
00:26:52,570 --> 00:26:53,720
Go.

468
00:27:15,770 --> 00:27:18,050
- Hello? - Hey, it's me.

469
00:27:18,750 --> 00:27:20,210
I got her password.

470
00:27:20,210 --> 00:27:21,380
What is it?

471
00:27:22,060 --> 00:27:24,000
"Lifesucks," One word.

473
00:27:24,310 --> 00:27:25,530
Perfect.

474
00:27:26,020 --> 00:27:29,000
So, are you going to be around this weekend?

475
00:27:29,450 --> 00:27:30,710
I could be.

476
00:27:32,520 --> 00:27:33,670
Be.

477
00:27:43,870 --> 00:27:46,360
- Where are they? - I don't know.

478
00:27:55,760 --> 00:27:57,650
Did you ever meet Princess Di?

479
00:27:57,990 --> 00:27:59,090
Yeah.

480
00:27:59,350 --> 00:28:01,080
But I never took her picture.

481
00:28:02,780 --> 00:28:04,060
What was she like?

482
00:28:04,740 --> 00:28:06,000
She was cool.

483
00:28:10,540 --> 00:28:11,770
Can I....

484
00:28:14,850 --> 00:28:16,970
Can I see one of your photographs?

485
00:28:19,310 --> 00:28:21,110
- My photographs? - Yeah.

486
00:28:22,400 --> 00:28:23,610
Yeah.

487
00:28:28,390 --> 00:28:30,100
How about this one right here?

488
00:28:39,040 --> 00:28:40,560
That's very beautiful.

489
00:28:43,690 --> 00:28:45,600
- Munich? - Yeah.

490
00:28:54,720 --> 00:28:56,020
Finish the speech?

491
00:28:56,920 --> 00:28:58,210
Taking a break.

492
00:28:58,700 --> 00:29:00,730
The guys got tired of me yelling at them.

493
00:29:00,760 --> 00:29:02,450
Big, old, grumpy bear.

494
00:29:11,570 --> 00:29:12,780
How you doing?

495
00:29:13,020 --> 00:29:15,430
Fine, just a few dozen more to go.

496
00:29:15,750 --> 00:29:17,360
You don't have to do these yourself.

497
00:29:18,410 --> 00:29:20,260
The personal touch never hurts.

498
00:29:20,370 --> 00:29:22,090
- Sure doesn't. - Yes.

499
00:29:22,090 --> 00:29:23,520
Yes.

500
00:29:24,610 --> 00:29:25,870
Sir?

501
00:29:26,940 --> 00:29:31,080
Phone call, Senator. It's Maureen Kingsley from the network.

502
00:29:31,390 --> 00:29:33,210
Come on, Patty, it's after midnight.

503
00:29:33,210 --> 00:29:35,080
She says it's urgent.

504
00:29:41,450 --> 00:29:44,160
Maureen, this better be good.

505
00:29:44,380 --> 00:29:46,250
Can I get you some coffee or anything?

506
00:29:46,460 --> 00:29:47,760
Thank you, Patty.

507
00:29:47,760 --> 00:29:49,160
My response?

508
00:29:50,110 --> 00:29:51,660
Here's my response.

509
00:29:51,940 --> 00:29:54,970
You air that allegation, or anything remotely like it....

510
00:30:00,780 --> 00:30:02,530
This conversation is over, Maureen.

511
00:30:11,810 --> 00:30:13,080
That'll be all, Patty.

512
00:30:15,860 --> 00:30:16,990
Sweetheart?

513
00:30:17,560 --> 00:30:18,800
What was it?

514
00:30:19,450 --> 00:30:22,200
Just more media nonsense. Not important.

515
00:30:25,040 --> 00:30:26,780
It didn't sound not important.

516
00:30:29,640 --> 00:30:31,870
Since when don't we talk about things?

517
00:31:09,240 --> 00:31:11,920
This is Richard Walsh. At the tone, leave a message.

518
00:31:11,930 --> 00:31:13,390
Richard, it's Jack.

519
00:31:13,390 --> 00:31:14,850
Call me back. It's important.

520
00:31:23,290 --> 00:31:25,340
I thought you wanted to get your life back together.

521
00:31:25,810 --> 00:31:27,510
Make things right with your family.

522
00:31:28,520 --> 00:31:29,790
You think this is helping?

523
00:31:30,890 --> 00:31:32,730
He's got information that I need.

524
00:31:32,730 --> 00:31:34,050
What information?

525
00:31:36,090 --> 00:31:37,280
Never mind.

526
00:31:37,660 --> 00:31:39,390
You can't tell me, fine.

527
00:31:39,390 --> 00:31:41,900
But, Jack, if Tony doesn't find anything,

528
00:31:41,900 --> 00:31:43,040
you could end up in jail.

529
00:31:43,040 --> 00:31:44,220
Probably.

530
00:31:44,570 --> 00:31:46,290
Then what are you doing?

531
00:31:51,950 --> 00:31:53,120
Jack.

532
00:31:54,550 --> 00:31:55,890
Answer me.

533
00:31:57,970 --> 00:32:02,600
Nina, you can look the other way once and it's no big deal.

534
00:32:03,460 --> 00:32:06,110
Except it makes it easier for you to compromise the next time...

535
00:32:06,110 --> 00:32:08,160
...and pretty soon that's all you're doing is compromising...

536
00:32:08,160 --> 00:32:10,200
...because that's how you think things are done.

537
00:32:14,360 --> 00:32:16,180
You know those guys I blew the whistle on?

538
00:32:16,180 --> 00:32:17,670
You think they were the bad guys?

539
00:32:17,970 --> 00:32:19,780
'Cause they weren't. They weren't bad guys.

540
00:32:19,790 --> 00:32:21,290
They were just like you and me.

541
00:32:21,870 --> 00:32:24,290
Except they compromised... once.

542
00:32:36,490 --> 00:32:39,130
I'll see how Tony's coming along.

543
00:32:39,910 --> 00:32:41,130
Thank you.

544
00:32:56,820 --> 00:32:59,300
- Hello? - Hi, it's Teri Bauer.

545
00:32:59,300 --> 00:33:00,930
Hi, have you heard anything?

546
00:33:00,930 --> 00:33:02,990
Yeah, I broke into Kim's e-mail.

547
00:33:02,990 --> 00:33:03,970
Janet sent her one this morning.

548
00:33:03,970 --> 00:33:06,060
They're meeting two guys in the Valley.

549
00:33:06,230 --> 00:33:07,560
Did you get an address?

550
00:33:07,650 --> 00:33:09,190
Yep, I'm going right now.

551
00:33:09,780 --> 00:33:10,750
Would you mind if I came along?

552
00:33:10,750 --> 00:33:13,130
I'm getting a little stir-crazy sitting around here.

553
00:33:13,870 --> 00:33:14,770
All right.

554
00:33:14,770 --> 00:33:17,440
I'm leaving right now. Tell me where you live.

555
00:33:23,000 --> 00:33:24,250
Where are we going now?

556
00:33:24,630 --> 00:33:26,930
Wasn't there supposed to be a party at Lacy's?

557
00:33:26,930 --> 00:33:28,370
Anybody got a phone? I'll call.

558
00:33:28,370 --> 00:33:29,510
Yeah, I do.

559
00:33:36,110 --> 00:33:37,160
I got to go home.

560
00:33:37,170 --> 00:33:38,260
Why?

561
00:33:39,000 --> 00:33:40,670
My mother left five messages.

562
00:33:40,810 --> 00:33:42,140
Run home to mommy.

563
00:33:42,140 --> 00:33:43,900
Hey, her father just died, okay?

564
00:33:44,590 --> 00:33:45,990
Maybe her mother needs her.

565
00:33:46,430 --> 00:33:47,590
Your father?

566
00:33:48,710 --> 00:33:49,940
Shut up.

567
00:33:50,200 --> 00:33:51,450
Whatever.

568
00:33:52,420 --> 00:33:53,670
I don't want to go home.

569
00:33:54,300 --> 00:33:55,470
But....

570
00:33:56,890 --> 00:33:58,280
We'll drop you off, okay?

571
00:34:09,520 --> 00:34:10,700
Yeah.

572
00:34:32,720 --> 00:34:33,940
What's your name?

573
00:34:34,810 --> 00:34:35,930
Martin.

574
00:34:36,930 --> 00:34:38,140
I'm Mandy.

575
00:34:39,570 --> 00:34:42,480
Hey, maybe we can get together

576
00:34:42,480 --> 00:34:44,210
when we're in LA, or something.

577
00:34:46,130 --> 00:34:47,600
I'm going to be pretty busy.

578
00:34:51,490 --> 00:34:52,680
See ya.

579
00:34:56,590 --> 00:34:58,910
- Yeah? - I got into the Darcet account.

580
00:34:59,300 --> 00:35:00,670
Nina said you wanted it?

581
00:35:00,670 --> 00:35:02,380
Thank you. Send it to my screen.

582
00:35:02,500 --> 00:35:03,600
All right.

585
00:35:19,240 --> 00:35:20,370
Wake up.

586
00:35:26,680 --> 00:35:27,860
Sit down.

587
00:35:29,030 --> 00:35:30,400
Who's the source?

588
00:35:30,810 --> 00:35:32,550
Who tipped us on the Palmer hit?

589
00:35:36,890 --> 00:35:40,730
Last August when you led the take-down of Phillipe Darcet,

590
00:35:41,570 --> 00:35:42,870
all his assets were transferred

591
00:35:42,870 --> 00:35:45,440
to a custodial account in Langley, Virginia.

592
00:35:45,700 --> 00:35:48,380
$200,000 fell out along the way.

593
00:35:48,660 --> 00:35:52,370
I traced that money to an offshore account in Aruba.

594
00:35:53,120 --> 00:35:55,650
I got a funny feeling about that account, George.

595
00:35:56,210 --> 00:35:57,610
I think it's yours.

596
00:35:57,810 --> 00:35:59,530
Yeah, well, that's a lie.

597
00:36:00,720 --> 00:36:01,860
Good.

598
00:36:02,980 --> 00:36:06,110
Then you won't mind if I send Chappelle the information.

601
00:36:12,410 --> 00:36:13,670
The source, George.

602
00:36:18,190 --> 00:36:20,840
You have no idea what you're getting yourself into here.

603
00:36:21,010 --> 00:36:22,960
Why don't you explain it to me?

604
00:36:24,770 --> 00:36:26,730
You've got five seconds.

605
00:36:30,430 --> 00:36:31,590
Wait.

606
00:36:38,560 --> 00:36:39,790
There's your source.

607
00:36:48,220 --> 00:36:49,920
Thanks for your help, George.

608
00:36:50,110 --> 00:36:51,850
You'll live to regret this, Bauer.

609
00:36:52,150 --> 00:36:53,360
I promise you that.

610
00:37:09,720 --> 00:37:10,460
Excuse me.

611
00:37:10,460 --> 00:37:12,590
Ma'am, we're about to land. If you could please....

612
00:38:20,240 --> 00:38:22,070
Sir, would you please remain in your seat.

613
00:38:22,070 --> 00:38:23,400
I lost my wallet.

614
00:39:22,150 --> 00:39:24,010
- Hello? - Hey, it's me.

615
00:39:24,480 --> 00:39:25,850
Turn left at the light.

616
00:39:26,040 --> 00:39:27,170
What?

617
00:39:27,170 --> 00:39:29,140
I'm in a car with Alan York.

618
00:39:29,140 --> 00:39:31,340
He's the father of one of Kimberly's friends, Janet.

619
00:39:31,340 --> 00:39:32,500
What are you talking about?

620
00:39:32,500 --> 00:39:34,720
Kim got an e-mail this morning from Janet York.

621
00:39:34,720 --> 00:39:36,680
We think they might be out together.

622
00:39:36,770 --> 00:39:37,760
Where?

623
00:39:37,760 --> 00:39:38,640
I don't know yet.

624
00:39:38,640 --> 00:39:40,650
They were meeting some guys in the Valley.

625
00:39:41,550 --> 00:39:42,750
Wait a second.

626
00:39:43,020 --> 00:39:45,130
You're going to the Valley with this guy, Alan York?

627
00:39:45,360 --> 00:39:46,940
What are you going to do if she's not there?

628
00:39:47,630 --> 00:39:51,640
Well, we haven't thought that far ahead yet. I'll call.

629
00:39:53,280 --> 00:39:54,440
Hello?

630
00:39:55,090 --> 00:39:56,230
Teri?

631
00:40:10,310 --> 00:40:12,320
Would you do me a favor? Could you cover for me?

632
00:40:12,740 --> 00:40:13,870
Sure.

633
00:40:14,000 --> 00:40:15,650
Forward all my calls to my cell phone.

634
00:40:15,650 --> 00:40:17,100
I'll be back as soon as I can.

635
00:40:19,450 --> 00:40:20,600
Jack.

636
00:40:20,850 --> 00:40:21,990
What?

637
00:40:23,620 --> 00:40:26,330
A 747 just blew up over the Mojave desert.

638
00:40:26,430 --> 00:40:28,760
Preliminary reports make it sound like it was a bomb.

639
00:40:32,550 --> 00:40:34,890
The passenger list. Get me Walsh on the phone now.

640
00:40:50,450 --> 00:40:51,580
Janet?

641
00:41:01,780 --> 00:41:03,550
Turn here. I live on 10th.

642
00:41:06,460 --> 00:41:08,990
- Dan, I just told you-- - Why don't you just relax?

643
00:41:13,350 --> 00:41:15,450
Can you please tell him that he missed the turn?

644
00:41:15,500 --> 00:41:17,710
You heard him. Relax.

645
00:41:18,420 --> 00:41:20,070
The night's just getting started.

