2
00:00:12,540 --> 00:00:14,880
Right now, terrorists are plottiing

3
00:00:14,890 --> 00:00:17,210
to assassinate a presidential candidate.

4
00:00:17,980 --> 00:00:20,400
My wife and daughter have been kidnapped.

5
00:00:21,110 --> 00:00:24,820
And the people that I work with may be involved in both.

6
00:00:25,260 --> 00:00:27,380
I'm Federal Agent Jack Bauer.

7
00:00:27,710 --> 00:00:30,820
This, is the longest day of my life.

10
00:00:49,920 --> 00:00:51,890
Secret Service thinks the photographer

11
00:00:51,890 --> 00:00:54,520
may have been in on the assassination attempt.

12
00:00:54,610 --> 00:00:57,020
He hasn't been seen since the breakfast.

13
00:00:57,450 --> 00:00:59,940
He was using the name "Martin Belkin."

14
00:01:00,160 --> 00:01:02,660
Follow up and report back to me in 30 minutes.

15
00:01:02,830 --> 00:01:04,320
I promised Division a threat assessment

16
00:01:04,320 --> 00:01:06,240
on Senator Palmer by noon.

17
00:01:06,240 --> 00:01:09,320
Check with Secret Service. I don't want any overlap.

18
00:01:12,940 --> 00:01:15,300
- Still no sign of Jack? - Nothing.

19
00:01:16,890 --> 00:01:21,890
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

20
00:01:16,890 --> 00:01:21,890
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

21
00:01:16,890 --> 00:01:21,890
{\an5}{\pos(145,252)}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

22
00:01:17,390 --> 00:01:21,890
{\pos(67,248)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

23
00:01:17,390 --> 00:01:21,890
{\pos(67,248)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

24
00:01:17,390 --> 00:01:21,890
{\pos(58,238)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

25
00:01:17,390 --> 00:01:21,890
{\pos(84,248)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

28
00:01:23,110 --> 00:01:53,110
{\an9}m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

29
00:01:22,610 --> 00:01:53,110
{\an2}{\pos(26,248)}m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

36
00:01:50,780 --> 00:01:51,600
Cofell here.

37
00:01:51,600 --> 00:01:53,200
It's Kevin. Something's come up.

38
00:01:53,200 --> 00:01:54,560
Meet me at the Nordhoff garage.

39
00:01:54,560 --> 00:01:56,940
That's inconvenient, I'm already on my way to the airport.

40
00:01:56,940 --> 00:01:59,340
This can't wait. Meet me there as soon as possible.

41
00:01:59,340 --> 00:02:00,110
All right.

42
00:02:04,640 --> 00:02:06,280
Mark, I have a change of plans.

43
00:02:06,280 --> 00:02:08,100
I'm meeting someone in the parking garage

44
00:02:08,110 --> 00:02:10,130
at the corner of Nordhoff and Willingham.

45
00:02:17,430 --> 00:02:18,280
You hear me?

46
00:02:23,940 --> 00:02:24,870
Who are you?

47
00:02:27,490 --> 00:02:28,610
Where's Mark?

48
00:02:32,700 --> 00:02:34,070
What's going on here?

49
00:02:36,400 --> 00:02:37,550
Stop the car.

50
00:02:39,620 --> 00:02:40,860
Stop the car!

51
00:03:00,650 --> 00:03:02,650
Give me the phone through the divider.

52
00:03:02,910 --> 00:03:04,840
Easy. Now.

53
00:03:14,960 --> 00:03:17,970
Get up against the door, and sit on your hands.

54
00:03:18,750 --> 00:03:19,660
Who are you?

55
00:03:19,950 --> 00:03:21,050
What do you want? Money?

56
00:03:21,270 --> 00:03:23,780
I don't have much with me, but I'm sure I can find some.

57
00:03:25,010 --> 00:03:26,020
Shut up!

58
00:03:26,900 --> 00:03:29,400
My name is Jack Bauer. Since midnight,

59
00:03:29,410 --> 00:03:30,660
my wife and daughter have been missing.

60
00:03:30,660 --> 00:03:31,550
I have reason to believe

61
00:03:31,560 --> 00:03:33,850
they're being held by a colleague of yours.

62
00:03:33,850 --> 00:03:35,440
A man named Gaines.

63
00:03:35,440 --> 00:03:36,770
Where are they?

64
00:03:38,470 --> 00:03:40,020
I don't know what you are talking about.

65
00:03:40,020 --> 00:03:42,060
Where's my wife and daughter?

66
00:03:43,970 --> 00:03:45,990
For God's sakes, I'm just a businessman.

67
00:03:45,990 --> 00:03:49,550
That's right, an ordinary businessman riding around in a bulletproof limousine.

68
00:03:50,240 --> 00:03:52,690
- Yes, for protection. - From what?

69
00:03:52,690 --> 00:03:54,230
People like you.

70
00:04:02,570 --> 00:04:04,290
This is your last chance.

71
00:04:05,570 --> 00:04:07,900
Where is my family?

72
00:04:10,700 --> 00:04:13,520
I swear to you, I don't know what you're talking about.

73
00:04:21,190 --> 00:04:22,710
You're a very good liar.

74
00:04:26,330 --> 00:04:27,710
But I've seen better.

75
00:04:30,170 --> 00:04:31,380
You stay put.

76
00:05:09,370 --> 00:05:10,830
It's Nina Myers.

77
00:05:10,830 --> 00:05:12,560
Hey, it's me. Can you talk?

78
00:05:12,560 --> 00:05:14,330
Let me open a secure line.

79
00:05:19,740 --> 00:05:20,940
Okay, we're clear.

80
00:05:20,980 --> 00:05:23,530
- Has Teri called back yet? - No.

81
00:05:24,030 --> 00:05:25,340
What's Green doing?

82
00:05:25,660 --> 00:05:27,780
She's making herself at home in your office.

83
00:05:27,780 --> 00:05:30,140
- She talk to you yet? - Yes.

84
00:05:30,860 --> 00:05:32,770
I told her I severed all ties with you.

85
00:05:33,400 --> 00:05:35,540
From now on, I play on the side of the angels.

86
00:05:35,540 --> 00:05:37,750
- Did she buy any of it? - Not a word.

87
00:05:37,970 --> 00:05:39,210
I've got Cofell.

88
00:05:39,450 --> 00:05:40,360
What do you mean "Got"?

89
00:05:40,360 --> 00:05:42,170
I've got him in the back of his limousine.

90
00:05:42,820 --> 00:05:45,150
- Has he told you anything? - I'm working on it.

91
00:05:45,150 --> 00:05:47,150
In other words, you've kidnapped him.

92
00:05:47,320 --> 00:05:49,750
He's the only link to Teri and Kim that I've got.

93
00:05:49,750 --> 00:05:52,350
You don't even know if he's the right Ted Cofell.

94
00:05:52,350 --> 00:05:55,330
Every time I talk to you, you go further out on a limb.

95
00:05:55,330 --> 00:05:57,230
From the second they were taken, you tell me one thing

96
00:05:57,230 --> 00:05:58,880
I could have done differently.

97
00:05:59,240 --> 00:06:01,460
I don't know, I guess you're right.

98
00:06:01,460 --> 00:06:04,450
But, Jack, I don't know how much longer I can cover for you.

99
00:06:04,450 --> 00:06:05,800
Nina, please.

100
00:06:06,010 --> 00:06:09,080
Just focus and stay calm, I need you right now.

101
00:06:09,080 --> 00:06:11,950
Look, I don't think Cofell will be easy to break. I need your help.

102
00:06:11,960 --> 00:06:12,780
You want me to put together

103
00:06:12,780 --> 00:06:15,130
an interrogation profile in what? 15 minutes?

104
00:06:15,130 --> 00:06:16,720
I'll give you about five.

105
00:06:17,660 --> 00:06:18,500
Nina.

106
00:06:18,840 --> 00:06:19,710
If I can't break Cofell,

107
00:06:19,710 --> 00:06:22,330
 I won't be able to find my family. Do you understand?

108
00:06:22,970 --> 00:06:24,110
I'll do what I can.

109
00:06:24,600 --> 00:06:25,580
Thank you.

110
00:06:26,010 --> 00:06:28,240
I'm gonna look for a place to lay low for a while.

111
00:06:28,240 --> 00:06:30,000
I'll get back to you as soon as I can.

112
00:06:59,530 --> 00:07:01,200
Your father will find us.

113
00:07:02,170 --> 00:07:04,350
If he doesn't, the people that work for him will.

114
00:07:04,860 --> 00:07:06,580
How? They don't know where we are.

115
00:07:06,590 --> 00:07:07,390
We don't know where we are.

116
00:07:07,390 --> 00:07:09,200
They were tracing the call, Kim.

117
00:07:11,340 --> 00:07:14,060
Did they find our location before the battery went dead?

118
00:07:14,290 --> 00:07:16,130
We have to hope that they did, yes.

119
00:07:21,160 --> 00:07:22,750
Sorry about the... phone.

120
00:07:29,830 --> 00:07:31,800
Thank you for helping us. We were hoping--

121
00:07:31,800 --> 00:07:33,560
I don't want to know anything.

122
00:07:33,890 --> 00:07:36,280
Trust me, it's better for you if I don't know anything.

123
00:07:36,280 --> 00:07:37,370
What do you mean?

124
00:07:38,570 --> 00:07:41,240
Eli sent me in here to a get information from you guys.

125
00:07:41,250 --> 00:07:43,880
But, can't tell him what I don't know, right?

126
00:07:45,980 --> 00:07:49,070
Whatever's going on, don't tell me about it.

127
00:07:50,150 --> 00:07:51,510
What's he gonna do to you?

128
00:07:53,100 --> 00:07:54,080
Rick?

129
00:08:10,970 --> 00:08:12,260
- What'd they say? - Nothing, man.

130
00:08:12,260 --> 00:08:13,770
Dude, don't hold out on me.

131
00:08:13,770 --> 00:08:14,980
I told you they don't trust me.

132
00:08:14,980 --> 00:08:16,500
I saw the way that kid looks at you,

133
00:08:16,500 --> 00:08:18,090
she must have said something.

134
00:08:18,610 --> 00:08:20,690
Who was the guy I talked to? Was it her father?

135
00:08:20,700 --> 00:08:22,690
- They wouldn't say. - You're lying.

136
00:08:26,250 --> 00:08:27,350
Stop it!

137
00:08:28,930 --> 00:08:30,300
Leave him alone.

142
00:08:58,560 --> 00:09:01,460
I was reviewing the report on the passenger list.

143
00:09:01,610 --> 00:09:03,390
There was an anomaly in first class?

144
00:09:03,400 --> 00:09:05,380
Yeah, the manifest had been altered to look like

145
00:09:05,380 --> 00:09:08,130
there was an empty seat, but we don't think there was one.

146
00:09:08,180 --> 00:09:09,730
Who was actually in the seat?

147
00:09:10,250 --> 00:09:12,380
The photographer, Martin Belkin.

148
00:09:12,830 --> 00:09:15,270
So the real photographer was killed in the explosion.

149
00:09:15,280 --> 00:09:17,760
And the assassin took his place at the breakfast.

150
00:09:18,200 --> 00:09:20,010
He was enough of a look-alike to fool security.

151
00:09:20,010 --> 00:09:21,470
And, according to Secret Service,

152
00:09:21,480 --> 00:09:23,780
he had a legitimate ID, not a forgery.

153
00:09:23,780 --> 00:09:24,890
How did he get it?

154
00:09:24,970 --> 00:09:26,470
That, we're still working on.

155
00:09:32,100 --> 00:09:34,400
- Myers? - Hey, it's me.

156
00:09:34,980 --> 00:09:37,460
Hi, Bill, can you hang on a minute?

157
00:09:38,310 --> 00:09:39,710
It's Bill Warner, at the Bureau.

158
00:09:39,710 --> 00:09:41,050
Shall I call him back?

159
00:09:41,870 --> 00:09:43,280
No, I need to speak to him.

160
00:09:43,280 --> 00:09:44,610
Let me have the phone.

161
00:09:46,790 --> 00:09:47,620
Alberta?

162
00:09:48,150 --> 00:09:49,820
I've got something you should probably take a look at.

163
00:09:50,840 --> 00:09:52,420
Tell Bill I'll call him later.

164
00:09:54,760 --> 00:09:55,530
The hitter's connection

165
00:09:55,530 --> 00:09:57,930
to Germany may actually lead to the Balkans.

166
00:09:57,930 --> 00:09:58,800
All right.

167
00:09:58,930 --> 00:10:01,450
Our sources say our guy is probably a Macedonian....

168
00:10:01,450 --> 00:10:02,710
Hey, I'm here.

169
00:10:02,840 --> 00:10:04,840
- Bad timing? - No problem.

170
00:10:04,850 --> 00:10:06,910
I could have used a few more minutes.

171
00:10:06,970 --> 00:10:08,930
I wish I had them. Give me what you've got.

172
00:10:10,380 --> 00:10:12,630
The guy's flight originated in Croatia

173
00:10:12,630 --> 00:10:14,950
All right, he's the oldest of three children

174
00:10:14,950 --> 00:10:16,990
his father died when he was a boy.

175
00:10:17,410 --> 00:10:19,460
That means he learned responsibility early.

176
00:10:20,390 --> 00:10:22,890
In college at 16. Intelligent.

177
00:10:23,070 --> 00:10:24,540
First in his class.

178
00:10:25,340 --> 00:10:27,030
Vice-president of a company three years later.

179
00:10:27,030 --> 00:10:30,320
So he's ambitious, driven, maybe too much so.

180
00:10:31,670 --> 00:10:32,880
He has a heart condition.

181
00:10:32,900 --> 00:10:34,590
I know, I've got his pills.

182
00:10:35,290 --> 00:10:36,960
He's very organized.

183
00:10:37,180 --> 00:10:39,750
No charities, no....

184
00:10:40,610 --> 00:10:42,940
He's not generous with time or money. Anal.

185
00:10:42,940 --> 00:10:45,680
I'm guessing he's passive-aggressive. Control freak.

186
00:10:45,680 --> 00:10:47,800
So make him sweat it out for a little while.

187
00:10:47,800 --> 00:10:50,060
Assume control, and then behave erratically.

188
00:10:50,240 --> 00:10:52,670
Yeah, one more thing.

189
00:10:52,690 --> 00:10:54,000
A hunch really.

190
00:10:54,000 --> 00:10:56,750
People this tightly wound, the threat of pain

191
00:10:56,750 --> 00:10:59,140
can be more effective than pain itself.

192
00:10:59,140 --> 00:11:00,320
Okay, I've got it.

193
00:11:01,260 --> 00:11:02,640
Jack, this is all just guesswork.

194
00:11:02,640 --> 00:11:04,780
I could have done more with a little time.

195
00:11:04,780 --> 00:11:06,260
Nina, you did great.

196
00:11:06,260 --> 00:11:07,780
I'll get back to you as soon as I can.

197
00:11:07,780 --> 00:11:08,610
Okay.

198
00:11:59,900 --> 00:12:01,700
Get up there! Now!

199
00:12:06,740 --> 00:12:08,510
This doesn't have to take long.

200
00:12:08,800 --> 00:12:10,020
It's up to you.

201
00:12:12,280 --> 00:12:14,240
Do you know a man named Penticoff?

202
00:12:15,470 --> 00:12:16,990
How about Alan York?

203
00:12:17,360 --> 00:12:18,270
David Palmer?

204
00:12:18,270 --> 00:12:20,380
Of course. He's running for president.

205
00:12:21,950 --> 00:12:23,880
The attempt on his life has failed.

206
00:12:24,300 --> 00:12:25,690
The perpetrators will be in custody soon.

207
00:12:25,690 --> 00:12:27,480
You've already been implicated.

208
00:12:27,480 --> 00:12:30,940
If you cooperate with me now, I might be able to help you.

209
00:12:32,070 --> 00:12:35,550
I can only repeat, I have no idea what you're talking about.

210
00:12:39,490 --> 00:12:40,880
Your hands are sweating.

211
00:12:41,210 --> 00:12:42,960
Of course, I'm scared.

212
00:12:43,800 --> 00:12:45,960
Who are you meeting on your way to the airport?

213
00:12:46,240 --> 00:12:47,950
A man named Kevin Carroll.

214
00:12:48,840 --> 00:12:49,820
Who is he?

215
00:12:49,990 --> 00:12:51,860
He's a businessman, like myself.

216
00:12:52,090 --> 00:12:53,420
He sells machine tools.

217
00:12:53,420 --> 00:12:55,720
Why were you meeting him in a parking garage?

218
00:12:55,720 --> 00:12:58,030
It was his choice, I don't know why.

219
00:12:58,810 --> 00:13:00,330
I told you everything I know.

220
00:13:09,260 --> 00:13:10,350
Hey, it's me.

221
00:13:10,730 --> 00:13:13,000
Run a background check on a Kevin Carroll.

222
00:13:13,440 --> 00:13:15,600
Allegedly a machine tools salesman.

223
00:13:15,980 --> 00:13:17,360
Probably an alias.

224
00:13:25,800 --> 00:13:27,590
Let me show you something.

225
00:13:46,890 --> 00:13:49,030
You ever hear about the Russian gulag?

226
00:13:49,280 --> 00:13:50,130
What?

227
00:13:50,390 --> 00:13:52,790
A string of prisons in northern Siberia.

228
00:13:54,000 --> 00:13:56,320
Russians didn't have a lot of high-tech equipment up there.

229
00:13:56,320 --> 00:13:59,750
So, they had to make do with what was around.

230
00:14:00,090 --> 00:14:01,910
Sort of like what I'm doing right now.

231
00:14:04,500 --> 00:14:05,240
You probably don't think

232
00:14:05,240 --> 00:14:07,420
that I can force this towel down your throat.

233
00:14:08,100 --> 00:14:10,610
Trust me, I can. All the way.

234
00:14:10,970 --> 00:14:13,480
Except I hold on to this little bit here.

235
00:14:14,180 --> 00:14:16,270
When your stomach starts to digest it

236
00:14:18,300 --> 00:14:19,380
I pull it out

237
00:14:20,190 --> 00:14:22,030
taking your stomach lining with it.

238
00:14:23,070 --> 00:14:25,230
Most people could take about a week to die.

239
00:14:25,900 --> 00:14:27,240
It's very painful.

240
00:14:28,070 --> 00:14:29,440
What kind of man are you?

241
00:14:30,020 --> 00:14:31,790
I don't want to hurt you

242
00:14:33,840 --> 00:14:36,950
but I will do everything I have to do to protect my family.

243
00:14:40,640 --> 00:14:42,190
I want to show you something.

244
00:14:43,420 --> 00:14:44,570
It's in my wallet.

245
00:14:54,530 --> 00:14:56,530
Open it, please.

246
00:15:01,020 --> 00:15:03,200
I know you want to see your family again,

247
00:15:04,480 --> 00:15:05,270
and I want to see mine

248
00:15:05,270 --> 00:15:07,090
more than anything in the world.

249
00:15:08,220 --> 00:15:11,240
Mr. Bauer, believe me,

250
00:15:11,240 --> 00:15:13,280
if I knew something that would help you,

251
00:15:14,200 --> 00:15:15,350
I would tell you.

252
00:15:51,180 --> 00:15:52,120
Mr. Drazen.

253
00:15:52,120 --> 00:15:53,130
- Found Bauer? - No.

254
00:15:53,130 --> 00:15:54,880
But we're doing everything possible.

255
00:15:54,890 --> 00:15:56,170
Scanning police frequencies,

256
00:15:56,170 --> 00:15:57,090
checking hospitals,

257
00:15:57,090 --> 00:15:57,960
and I'm still expecting

258
00:15:57,960 --> 00:16:00,060
to hear from my contact inside the CTU.

259
00:16:00,070 --> 00:16:02,710
And if Bauer comes here, as you suggested earlier?

260
00:16:02,710 --> 00:16:04,160
Then, we'll be ready for him.

261
00:16:06,000 --> 00:16:07,050
For an American operation,

262
00:16:07,050 --> 00:16:08,840
we thought we needed an American crew,

263
00:16:08,850 --> 00:16:12,270
perhaps we undervalued our own capabilities.

264
00:16:15,340 --> 00:16:16,970
- I'm pulling the plug on you. - You can't tell me

265
00:16:16,970 --> 00:16:18,210
you were supposed to frame

266
00:16:18,210 --> 00:16:19,540
Bauer for David Palmer's assassination.

267
00:16:19,540 --> 00:16:22,050
But Palmer's still alive.

268
00:16:22,280 --> 00:16:24,040
You don't even know where Bauer is, correct?

269
00:16:24,040 --> 00:16:25,900
- No, but I... - You've failed.

270
00:16:29,830 --> 00:16:32,540
For over a year now, you've been saying how important this is,

271
00:16:32,540 --> 00:16:33,990
now you're just gonna quit?

272
00:16:33,990 --> 00:16:34,870
Quit?

273
00:16:35,710 --> 00:16:36,900
Of course not.

274
00:16:38,070 --> 00:16:39,470
We have a contingency plan.

275
00:16:39,470 --> 00:16:42,520
Bauer and Palmer will both be dead by the end of the day.

276
00:16:42,520 --> 00:16:45,520
You never said anything to me about a contingency plan.

277
00:16:46,200 --> 00:16:47,530
It doesn't involve you.

278
00:16:52,100 --> 00:16:54,820
Just give me a little more time to find Bauer.

279
00:16:54,950 --> 00:16:56,770
Until...'til noon.

280
00:16:56,770 --> 00:16:58,610
That's not even two hours.

281
00:17:01,440 --> 00:17:03,280
I'll give you 30 minutes.

282
00:17:03,520 --> 00:17:06,310
If you don't find Bauer by then, I take over.

283
00:17:07,010 --> 00:17:08,420
Your last task will be to kill

284
00:17:08,420 --> 00:17:12,090
his wife and daughter, and pull your people out.

285
00:17:29,300 --> 00:17:33,380
I like your education program, but with all due respect

286
00:17:33,940 --> 00:17:35,830
I do have one or two suggestions.

287
00:17:35,830 --> 00:17:37,060
Well, that's why I'm here.

288
00:17:39,030 --> 00:17:40,670
I'm not one to say that teachers shouldn't

289
00:17:40,670 --> 00:17:42,960
be accountable for their performance, but--

290
00:17:42,960 --> 00:17:45,340
Would you excuse me for just a moment?

291
00:17:45,540 --> 00:17:46,350
Sure.

292
00:17:54,440 --> 00:17:55,260
Carl.

293
00:17:55,510 --> 00:17:56,620
Hello, David.

294
00:17:57,230 --> 00:17:58,620
Since you fired me from your staff,

295
00:17:58,620 --> 00:18:00,500
I assume this is a social call?

296
00:18:00,930 --> 00:18:03,150
I need to talk to you, in person.

297
00:18:03,800 --> 00:18:04,650
Why is that?

298
00:18:04,860 --> 00:18:07,600
I got a very disturbing call today, a little while ago.

299
00:18:09,940 --> 00:18:12,860
I was told that George Ferragamo's life may be in danger.

300
00:18:13,000 --> 00:18:15,260
Who told you that, Frank Ames?

301
00:18:15,500 --> 00:18:17,090
You know what an old lady he is,

302
00:18:17,090 --> 00:18:18,910
just don't pay any attention to him.

303
00:18:19,940 --> 00:18:22,270
I need to talk to you, now.

304
00:18:22,270 --> 00:18:24,590
It's a pretty busy day for me, David.

305
00:18:25,340 --> 00:18:27,220
I know a few things about you, Carl.

306
00:18:27,680 --> 00:18:29,410
Things you don't want spread around.

307
00:18:29,410 --> 00:18:31,040
Are you threatening me?

308
00:18:31,680 --> 00:18:33,810
Is that what it's come to after all these years?

309
00:18:34,690 --> 00:18:37,760
It's come to whatever it takes to get you over here now.

310
00:18:40,780 --> 00:18:41,300
Where are you?

311
00:18:41,300 --> 00:18:43,820
Grant Elementary, in the Valley.

312
00:18:46,070 --> 00:18:47,380
I'll be there by 11:00.

313
00:19:04,990 --> 00:19:06,910
- Nina Myers. - Hey, it's me.

314
00:19:06,910 --> 00:19:08,880
You got anything on Kevin Carroll yet?

315
00:19:08,940 --> 00:19:11,720
Yeah, I show six Kevin Carrolls.

316
00:19:11,720 --> 00:19:14,320
One does in fact work for a machine tool company.

317
00:19:15,410 --> 00:19:17,040
It's a cover. It's gotta be.

318
00:19:17,070 --> 00:19:18,630
There's another possibility.

319
00:19:18,640 --> 00:19:20,250
Maybe you've got the wrong Ted Cofell.

320
00:19:20,250 --> 00:19:23,560
No, he was implicated in Jamey's file, along with Gaines.

321
00:19:23,560 --> 00:19:25,160
That file was partially erased.

322
00:19:25,160 --> 00:19:27,230
We can't rely on its information.

323
00:19:27,230 --> 00:19:28,580
I think you're making a mistake.

324
00:19:28,580 --> 00:19:31,450
Nina, there's something about this guy, this is not a mistake.

325
00:19:31,620 --> 00:19:34,020
Jack, I know you think he's all you've got,

326
00:19:34,020 --> 00:19:36,980
but maybe that's affecting your judgment.

327
00:19:39,190 --> 00:19:40,230
Okay, thanks.

328
00:20:07,080 --> 00:20:09,280
We're going to see your friend Kevin Carroll.

329
00:20:30,610 --> 00:20:32,350
It looks like they're getting ready to leave.

330
00:20:34,600 --> 00:20:36,620
Mom, what's wrong?

331
00:20:36,810 --> 00:20:38,900
It's nothing, honey, I'm all right.

332
00:20:39,120 --> 00:20:41,440
Will you stop saying that, you're not all right.

333
00:20:42,360 --> 00:20:43,530
- What did he do to you? - Nothing.

334
00:20:43,530 --> 00:20:46,440
I've been having this pain in my stomach.

335
00:20:47,790 --> 00:20:48,770
How bad?

336
00:20:48,990 --> 00:20:50,300
It comes and goes.

337
00:20:51,020 --> 00:20:52,050
I can manage.

338
00:20:53,690 --> 00:20:55,350
- I should go tell somebody. - No.

339
00:20:56,060 --> 00:20:58,340
- Mom, you need help. - I said no.

340
00:21:02,430 --> 00:21:03,510
Your father is coming.

341
00:21:03,510 --> 00:21:05,540
Until then, we have to be strong.

342
00:21:10,270 --> 00:21:10,870
Okay.

343
00:22:11,950 --> 00:22:12,830
Thank you.

344
00:22:13,710 --> 00:22:14,800
How's the food?

345
00:22:15,180 --> 00:22:17,280
Oh, better than what we used to eat.

346
00:22:17,810 --> 00:22:19,960
You two went to the same elementary school?

347
00:22:19,960 --> 00:22:22,390
Oh, we've known each other all our lives.

348
00:22:23,390 --> 00:22:25,450
And still as much in love as ever.

349
00:22:27,020 --> 00:22:28,560
- Thank you so much. - You're welcome.

350
00:22:28,660 --> 00:22:30,140
I am due at another school,

351
00:22:30,140 --> 00:22:31,700
but it's been wonderful to meet you

352
00:22:31,700 --> 00:22:33,910
and all those great kids.

353
00:22:33,910 --> 00:22:34,830
Thank you.

354
00:22:35,060 --> 00:22:37,490
- Would you excuse us a second? - Of course.

355
00:22:43,440 --> 00:22:43,970
I need to know

356
00:22:43,970 --> 00:22:46,120
if you've talked to Carl since I fired him.

357
00:22:48,360 --> 00:22:49,740
Yes, I have.

358
00:22:50,280 --> 00:22:51,550
What did you talk about?

359
00:22:52,140 --> 00:22:54,860
I asked him if he could find a way to stop Maureen Kingsley

360
00:22:54,860 --> 00:22:57,970
from airing the story about Keith. He said he would.

361
00:22:59,270 --> 00:23:00,790
What did he say exactly?

362
00:23:02,170 --> 00:23:05,380
As near as I can remember, something about

363
00:23:06,190 --> 00:23:08,580
taking care of the evidence against Keith.

364
00:23:15,070 --> 00:23:16,610
And you didn't think

365
00:23:17,310 --> 00:23:19,100
that was worth mentioning to me?

366
00:23:20,070 --> 00:23:22,600
I wasn't sure what he meant, David.

367
00:23:25,280 --> 00:23:26,110
I'm trying to believe

368
00:23:26,110 --> 00:23:28,870
that when you deceived me seven years ago...

369
00:23:28,880 --> 00:23:30,430
...it was a one-time thing.

370
00:23:34,890 --> 00:23:36,760
This isn't making it any easier.

371
00:23:38,730 --> 00:23:40,760
That is so unfair.

372
00:23:47,020 --> 00:23:47,980
See you later.

373
00:23:51,310 --> 00:23:53,100
David, I don't know how important this is,

374
00:23:53,100 --> 00:23:54,140
but you asked me to have someone to check...

375
00:23:54,140 --> 00:23:55,830
...on Jack Bauer, the guy at breakfast.

376
00:23:55,830 --> 00:23:56,910
Yes. What did you find?

377
00:23:56,910 --> 00:24:00,150
Typical agency file. A lot of gaps. Classified.

378
00:24:00,150 --> 00:24:01,890
Was one of those gaps...

379
00:24:02,260 --> 00:24:03,980
...in the summer about two years ago?

380
00:24:04,740 --> 00:24:06,570
- How'd you know? - We'll get into that later.

381
00:24:06,570 --> 00:24:09,280
Right now, we've got other things to deal with.

382
00:24:21,610 --> 00:24:23,080
Move up to the other seat.

383
00:24:23,660 --> 00:24:24,540
Now!

384
00:25:02,670 --> 00:25:06,040
An average businessman, with a Microtech Halo in his car?

385
00:25:10,050 --> 00:25:11,300
What did you just say?

386
00:25:11,610 --> 00:25:12,680
Say it again...

387
00:25:13,170 --> 00:25:13,780
Say it again!

388
00:25:14,280 --> 00:25:16,090
Or I'll break your other wrist!

389
00:25:17,400 --> 00:25:19,520
This is not Cofell.

390
00:25:20,770 --> 00:25:22,030
You speak Serbian?

391
00:25:22,610 --> 00:25:24,120
What are you, from Belgrade?

392
00:25:24,130 --> 00:25:25,480
You got family there?

393
00:25:25,710 --> 00:25:28,420
You deserve everything that's happening to you.

394
00:25:28,540 --> 00:25:30,760
What do you know about what's happening to me?

395
00:25:30,930 --> 00:25:33,700
There's only one thing that you need to know, Bauer.

396
00:25:34,110 --> 00:25:35,500
You will pay.

397
00:25:38,200 --> 00:25:39,520
You will pay.

398
00:25:39,520 --> 00:25:40,510
Who are you?

399
00:25:41,260 --> 00:25:42,450
Who are you!

400
00:25:54,370 --> 00:25:57,370
What's the matter? Is it your heart?

401
00:26:00,750 --> 00:26:02,250
I got your medicine right here.

402
00:26:02,250 --> 00:26:03,830
All I want is a little information.

403
00:26:03,830 --> 00:26:07,920
Where is my wife and daughter? Where is my family?

404
00:26:07,920 --> 00:26:10,960
I'll give you the medicine! Tell me where my family is!

405
00:26:20,320 --> 00:26:21,780
Take the medicine!

406
00:26:31,590 --> 00:26:32,510
No!

407
00:26:32,790 --> 00:26:34,310
No! No!

408
00:26:41,410 --> 00:26:43,440
No! No!

409
00:26:44,870 --> 00:26:45,760
Please!

410
00:26:46,650 --> 00:26:48,270
Where's my family?

411
00:26:48,270 --> 00:26:52,240
Please, where is my wife and daughter? Please!

412
00:26:52,350 --> 00:26:54,510
Don't die! Don't Die.

413
00:27:18,460 --> 00:27:20,950
Hey, listen to me, okay?

414
00:27:21,210 --> 00:27:21,780
It's not your fault.

415
00:27:21,780 --> 00:27:23,910
There's no way you could have seen that coming.

416
00:27:24,950 --> 00:27:27,060
How am I going to find Teri and Kim?

417
00:27:27,690 --> 00:27:29,390
The man he's meeting, Kevin Carroll,

418
00:27:30,170 --> 00:27:31,410
maybe he knows something.

419
00:27:31,420 --> 00:27:33,650
If he shows up, he's already late.

420
00:27:36,000 --> 00:27:38,370
Nina, there's something very wrong about this whole situation.

421
00:27:38,370 --> 00:27:40,590
This is not just about David Palmer.

422
00:27:41,210 --> 00:27:43,480
This is personal, they're coming after me.

423
00:27:43,550 --> 00:27:45,690
What's the connection between you and Palmer?

424
00:27:45,850 --> 00:27:48,050
- Or you and Cofell? - I don't know!

425
00:27:56,520 --> 00:27:58,940
Look, this is what I want you to do...

426
00:27:59,720 --> 00:28:01,960
...I want you to dig deeper into Cofell's background.

427
00:28:01,960 --> 00:28:03,810
Check out his extended family.

428
00:28:03,810 --> 00:28:06,270
I also want you to access my field assignment files.

429
00:28:06,270 --> 00:28:09,080
- They're classified. - I know, find your way in.

430
00:28:09,390 --> 00:28:11,340
I want you to check out an assignment two years ago.

431
00:28:11,340 --> 00:28:12,640
I was in Belgrade

432
00:28:12,640 --> 00:28:13,890
then Kosovo.

433
00:28:13,890 --> 00:28:16,010
It was called Operation Nightfall.

434
00:28:16,010 --> 00:28:16,930
Now, I want you to crosscheck

435
00:28:16,930 --> 00:28:18,630
everything that you find out from that...

436
00:28:18,630 --> 00:28:19,880
...with Cofell's file.

437
00:28:19,880 --> 00:28:21,520
- Do you understand? - Yeah.

438
00:28:21,670 --> 00:28:23,030
Okay, do it now.

439
00:28:28,800 --> 00:28:32,710
Come on, Jack, come on, pull yourself together.

440
00:29:05,970 --> 00:29:07,400
- What's this? - Nothing.

441
00:29:07,400 --> 00:29:08,890
Just act like you're interested.

442
00:29:08,890 --> 00:29:12,090
Look, Alberta probably thinks we're already helping Jack, right?

443
00:29:12,090 --> 00:29:13,360
She can't prove it.

444
00:29:13,970 --> 00:29:16,960
Why don't we just come clean, tell her what's going on?

445
00:29:17,480 --> 00:29:18,840
Jack says no.

446
00:29:21,790 --> 00:29:24,140
Maybe you should stop thinking about Jack...

447
00:29:24,140 --> 00:29:26,180
...and start thinking about yourself.

448
00:29:26,860 --> 00:29:29,980
It's Jack's family, so it's Jack's call.

449
00:29:30,390 --> 00:29:31,770
After what happened with Jamey...

450
00:29:32,880 --> 00:29:34,420
...we don't know who we can trust.

451
00:29:34,590 --> 00:29:35,880
All right, come on.

452
00:29:35,880 --> 00:29:38,390
Green may be a hard-ass but I don't think she's dirty.

453
00:29:38,390 --> 00:29:40,810
I agree. But she does things by the book.

454
00:29:40,830 --> 00:29:41,700
If we tell her what's going on,

455
00:29:41,700 --> 00:29:43,250
she'll call Division. Before you know it...

456
00:29:43,250 --> 00:29:45,240
...there's gonna be 30 people in the loop.

457
00:29:48,240 --> 00:29:50,210
If just one of them is another Jamey...

458
00:30:10,160 --> 00:30:10,970
Kim.

459
00:30:11,580 --> 00:30:14,590
Kim, honey. Wake up. You can't fall asleep.

460
00:30:14,590 --> 00:30:16,670
- Come on. Hey. - Why?

461
00:30:17,120 --> 00:30:19,080
Because if Dad comes, we might have to move quickly.

462
00:30:19,080 --> 00:30:21,250
- Come on. - When we need to move, I will.

463
00:30:21,250 --> 00:30:23,590
- No, Kimberly, come on. - Mom, I'm tired.

464
00:30:23,590 --> 00:30:25,930
I know you're tired, honey. And you've been very brave.

465
00:30:25,930 --> 00:30:28,150
You just have to stay that way a little while longer.

466
00:30:28,770 --> 00:30:30,550
Kimberly, we can't miss our chance.

467
00:30:36,190 --> 00:30:37,220
Are you okay?

468
00:30:39,530 --> 00:30:40,390
Take it.

469
00:30:42,860 --> 00:30:44,700
It's Dan's, he left it in the van.

470
00:30:45,970 --> 00:30:46,960
It's loaded.

471
00:30:50,950 --> 00:30:52,020
It's all I can do.

472
00:30:53,880 --> 00:30:56,850
You know, I'm sorry about getting you into this.

473
00:30:57,440 --> 00:30:58,320
Sorry about...

474
00:31:00,470 --> 00:31:01,730
I'm sorry about everything.

475
00:31:10,480 --> 00:31:12,800
What are we supposed to do, shoot our way out?

476
00:31:22,220 --> 00:31:23,310
They're gonna kill us.

477
00:31:23,910 --> 00:31:25,200
This time they mean it.

478
00:31:27,030 --> 00:31:30,590
Oh, God... no.

479
00:31:30,660 --> 00:31:32,150
No.

480
00:31:34,270 --> 00:31:36,910
Kimberly, listen to me, we're alive.

481
00:31:36,910 --> 00:31:37,760
Come here.

482
00:31:40,260 --> 00:31:41,820
We're alive.

483
00:31:41,900 --> 00:31:43,500
As long as we're alive

484
00:31:43,500 --> 00:31:46,670
I'm not giving up and neither are you.

485
00:31:47,970 --> 00:31:48,890
Right?

486
00:31:51,870 --> 00:31:52,640
Right.

487
00:32:35,750 --> 00:32:36,860
Sorry I'm late.

488
00:32:37,730 --> 00:32:39,600
I had a couple of calls to make.

489
00:32:44,560 --> 00:32:45,760
Hello, Alan.

490
00:32:47,510 --> 00:32:48,780
Or is it Kevin?

491
00:32:52,840 --> 00:32:54,450
Where's my wife?

492
00:34:02,700 --> 00:34:04,020
I want you to check this out.

493
00:34:13,670 --> 00:34:14,700
Wake up.

494
00:34:28,400 --> 00:34:30,580
- Where's my wife? - She's safe.

495
00:34:30,910 --> 00:34:33,130
- And my daughter? - Safe.

496
00:34:34,280 --> 00:34:35,120
Where?

497
00:34:41,070 --> 00:34:43,520
Don't make this any harder than it has to be.

498
00:34:44,290 --> 00:34:46,940
I was just about to say the same to you.

499
00:34:47,070 --> 00:34:49,020
But I'm the man with the gun.

500
00:34:49,230 --> 00:34:52,200
If you kill me, how are you gonna find your family?

501
00:34:52,200 --> 00:34:54,180
Who said anything about killing?

502
00:34:59,550 --> 00:35:01,590
I'm pretty good at withstanding pain.

503
00:35:03,170 --> 00:35:05,950
But if you don't get there soon, it may be too late.

504
00:35:07,630 --> 00:35:11,380
Since you are no longer any use to us, Jack

505
00:35:13,370 --> 00:35:16,440
there's no reason to keep your family alive.

506
00:35:17,050 --> 00:35:19,070
So, we need to come to an agreement.

507
00:35:23,390 --> 00:35:24,480
I'm listening.

508
00:35:25,330 --> 00:35:26,470
You let me go...

509
00:35:27,330 --> 00:35:28,910
I tell you where they are.

510
00:35:34,410 --> 00:35:36,250
As soon as I know they're safe

511
00:35:38,480 --> 00:35:41,110
I'll let you go. You got my word on it.

512
00:35:42,280 --> 00:35:44,910
Your word. That works.

513
00:35:47,120 --> 00:35:51,050
We are talking about my family, do you understand me?

514
00:35:52,000 --> 00:35:54,070
All I want is to get them back.

515
00:35:54,070 --> 00:35:58,370
So, as soon as I know they are safe, I will let you go.

516
00:35:58,370 --> 00:36:00,460
That is the agreement.

517
00:36:03,410 --> 00:36:04,570
If I say no?

518
00:36:06,200 --> 00:36:09,650
We'll find out how good you really are at withstanding some pain.

519
00:36:20,560 --> 00:36:21,640
Drive the car.

520
00:36:55,140 --> 00:36:56,710
Your half hour's up.

521
00:36:58,000 --> 00:36:59,970
Kill Bauer's wife and daughter.

522
00:37:00,910 --> 00:37:03,270
Our contingency doesn't involve them.

523
00:37:10,970 --> 00:37:11,860
Eli!

524
00:37:21,030 --> 00:37:23,720
Tell the drivers to make their final preparations.

525
00:37:27,140 --> 00:37:28,310
Then kill the women.

526
00:37:40,650 --> 00:37:42,940
I'm well aware that all too often these days,

527
00:37:42,940 --> 00:37:44,450
you have to be surrogate parents...

528
00:37:44,450 --> 00:37:45,960
as well as teachers.

529
00:37:46,450 --> 00:37:49,120
What can be done about that at the federal level?

530
00:37:52,540 --> 00:37:53,890
That's a good question.

531
00:37:54,270 --> 00:37:57,260
One that Mike has become an expert on in the last few years

532
00:37:57,260 --> 00:37:58,460
haven't you, Mike?

533
00:37:58,710 --> 00:37:59,540
I've been in charge of

534
00:37:59,540 --> 00:38:01,940
preparing our position paper on education...

535
00:38:01,940 --> 00:38:05,290
and I've reached some conclusions I think you'll find interesting.

536
00:38:05,290 --> 00:38:06,320
Wonderful.

537
00:38:06,320 --> 00:38:08,730
Studies have proven that parental involvement....

538
00:38:19,340 --> 00:38:21,080
What's this about Ferragamo?

539
00:38:21,530 --> 00:38:24,360
What difference does it make, as long as you're protected?

540
00:38:24,360 --> 00:38:27,930
What difference does it make, that someone may be murdered?

541
00:38:28,320 --> 00:38:29,990
I didn't say anything about murder.

542
00:38:29,990 --> 00:38:31,660
You didn't deny it, either.

543
00:38:32,700 --> 00:38:35,840
Okay, I deny it. Satisfied?

544
00:38:37,910 --> 00:38:38,790
David.

545
00:38:39,400 --> 00:38:43,390
Power has a price and that price has to be paid. Always.

546
00:38:43,390 --> 00:38:45,340
Spare me the civics lesson.

547
00:38:45,610 --> 00:38:46,910
I will not permit anyone to

548
00:38:46,910 --> 00:38:49,610
be harmed in any way in the name of my candidacy.

549
00:38:49,610 --> 00:38:52,700
You don't permit or not permit anything.

550
00:38:52,700 --> 00:38:55,250
Don't you understand that by now?

551
00:38:57,220 --> 00:38:59,700
These are very serious people, David.

552
00:38:59,840 --> 00:39:01,880
They didn't put all this time and money behind you

553
00:39:01,880 --> 00:39:04,070
to let things fall apart now.

554
00:39:05,110 --> 00:39:07,720
They'll find someone to do what they need done.

555
00:39:09,280 --> 00:39:11,100
I can't believe you used to work for me.

556
00:39:11,100 --> 00:39:12,900
I never worked for you.

557
00:39:12,900 --> 00:39:16,540
You and I have have always worked for them.

558
00:39:23,110 --> 00:39:24,190
You maybe.

559
00:39:26,180 --> 00:39:27,130
Not me.

560
00:39:37,980 --> 00:39:40,320
Information. How can I direct your call?

561
00:39:40,320 --> 00:39:43,700
Yes. Give me the number on a Dr. George Ferragamo.

562
00:39:43,930 --> 00:39:46,040
Just put me through immediately, please.

563
00:39:56,840 --> 00:39:58,460
Dad isn't coming, is he?

564
00:39:59,650 --> 00:40:00,910
I don't know, baby.

565
00:40:09,640 --> 00:40:11,320
I guess your time's up.

566
00:40:11,960 --> 00:40:13,760
Don't worry, I'll make it fast.

567
00:40:26,720 --> 00:40:27,610
No!

568
00:41:01,650 --> 00:41:04,350
Whoever knew he came in to kill us was expecting two shots.

569
00:41:05,360 --> 00:41:06,570
That was the second shot.

570
00:41:08,790 --> 00:41:09,790
What do we do now?

571
00:41:13,080 --> 00:41:14,080
We hide the body.

572
00:41:18,780 --> 00:41:19,550
Come on.

573
00:41:32,620 --> 00:41:33,790
Turn left here.

574
00:41:44,380 --> 00:41:45,670
Where are we headed?

575
00:41:48,480 --> 00:41:49,640
Where are we headed?

576
00:41:51,880 --> 00:41:53,410
Just drive straight.

577
00:41:54,530 --> 00:41:56,320
I'm taking you to your family.

