4
00:00:21,450 --> 00:00:22,490
I'm prepping the IV.

5
00:00:26,250 --> 00:00:27,800
We have the CT Scan.

6
00:00:29,070 --> 00:00:29,970
Doctor.

7
00:00:31,520 --> 00:00:32,650
Let's see what we've got here.

8
00:00:35,050 --> 00:00:36,020
You see this right there?

9
00:00:37,010 --> 00:00:42,010
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

10
00:00:37,010 --> 00:00:42,010
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

11
00:00:37,010 --> 00:00:42,010
{\an5}{\pos(145,252)}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

12
00:00:37,510 --> 00:00:42,010
{\pos(67,248)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

13
00:00:37,510 --> 00:00:42,010
{\pos(67,248)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

14
00:00:37,510 --> 00:00:42,010
{\pos(58,238)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

15
00:00:37,510 --> 00:00:42,010
{\pos(84,248)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

18
00:00:43,230 --> 00:01:13,230
{\an9}m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

19
00:00:42,730 --> 00:01:13,230
{\an2}{\pos(26,248)}m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

26
00:00:53,850 --> 00:00:55,170
Doctor, she's prepped.

27
00:00:56,610 --> 00:00:58,020
- Here we go. - Okay.

28
00:01:00,770 --> 00:01:03,480
Can we get Maureen down here to assist?

29
00:01:04,070 --> 00:01:05,190
- On my count. - All right.

30
00:01:06,650 --> 00:01:07,680
Lift.

31
00:01:10,960 --> 00:01:13,120
I want two large bore IV's.

32
00:01:16,220 --> 00:01:17,160
Let's get 'em prepped.

33
00:01:40,010 --> 00:01:41,720
Excuse me. Hello?

34
00:01:42,780 --> 00:01:43,740
- Hello! - Hello?

35
00:01:44,180 --> 00:01:45,670
Hello. Excuse me.

36
00:01:45,950 --> 00:01:46,870
Hello!

37
00:01:48,430 --> 00:01:49,340
Excuse me!

38
00:01:50,460 --> 00:01:52,980
I'm looking for a teenage girl. She was in an accident.

39
00:01:53,830 --> 00:01:56,250
A teenage girl brought in a few minutes ago, traffic accident.

40
00:01:56,250 --> 00:01:57,410
I'll be right with you.

41
00:01:57,410 --> 00:01:59,800
We just called, there was a traffic accident.

42
00:02:00,090 --> 00:02:02,010
Certainly. Do you have our fax number?

43
00:02:03,490 --> 00:02:05,920
- Excuse me. - Thank you. You're welcome.

44
00:02:06,440 --> 00:02:09,710
Dr. Kinnard, did you get the message about the heart seminar?

45
00:02:09,710 --> 00:02:10,870
Yes, I did. Thank you.

46
00:02:11,110 --> 00:02:11,930
Car accident.

47
00:02:11,930 --> 00:02:14,660
Sorry. My shift starts at 4:00, I just got here.

48
00:02:14,660 --> 00:02:17,740
- Just please help me. - Teenage girl, traffic accident.

49
00:02:17,740 --> 00:02:18,630
The name?

50
00:02:19,300 --> 00:02:21,350
Kimberly Bauer or Janet York.

51
00:02:21,350 --> 00:02:23,810
B-a-u-e-r, y-o-r-k.

52
00:02:28,500 --> 00:02:29,500
No name listed.

53
00:02:30,030 --> 00:02:31,010
Just a Jane Doe.

54
00:02:31,980 --> 00:02:32,720
Maybe....

55
00:02:32,720 --> 00:02:35,130
Hey! You can't go in there!

56
00:02:42,710 --> 00:02:45,390
Oh, my God, Janet.

57
00:02:55,390 --> 00:02:56,820
I'm sure you're going to find Kim.

58
00:03:05,020 --> 00:03:06,840
- Hello? - Honey, it's me.

59
00:03:06,940 --> 00:03:08,870
Where have you been? I've been trying to reach you.

60
00:03:08,870 --> 00:03:10,170
Have you found Kim yet?

61
00:03:10,260 --> 00:03:12,380
No. We're at St. Mark's Hospital.

62
00:03:12,380 --> 00:03:13,340
Hospital?

63
00:03:13,830 --> 00:03:15,680
Kim's friend was in a car accident.

64
00:03:15,680 --> 00:03:16,550
What about Kim?

65
00:03:16,550 --> 00:03:19,500
I don't know. She tried to call me. She was in a panic.

66
00:03:19,500 --> 00:03:21,830
Sounded like she was in trouble. I tried to get her.

67
00:03:21,830 --> 00:03:23,660
We were stopped by this cop.

68
00:03:23,660 --> 00:03:25,430
Teri, calm down.

69
00:03:26,210 --> 00:03:28,550
I'm losing my mind. I really need you here.

70
00:03:28,550 --> 00:03:30,640
I know. I'll get there as soon as I can.

71
00:03:30,650 --> 00:03:31,790
You've got to tell me,

72
00:03:31,790 --> 00:03:33,790
where was Kim when she called the second time?

73
00:03:33,800 --> 00:03:35,600
I don't know, she was...

74
00:03:37,430 --> 00:03:38,680
...North Hollywood.

75
00:03:38,790 --> 00:03:40,660
It sounded like she was being chased.

76
00:03:40,660 --> 00:03:43,660
And then when we got there, she was gone.

77
00:03:43,900 --> 00:03:45,740
Kim's friend Janet, let me speak to her.

78
00:03:46,220 --> 00:03:47,170
She's in surgery.

79
00:03:47,460 --> 00:03:50,610
Surgery? Is she gonna make it?

80
00:03:50,610 --> 00:03:51,800
I don't know.

81
00:03:51,870 --> 00:03:52,970
Listen to me, Teri.

82
00:03:53,120 --> 00:03:55,810
What I'm trying to do right now is to find Kim.

83
00:03:55,810 --> 00:03:57,100
I need you to stay where you are,

84
00:03:57,100 --> 00:03:58,940
and I will get there as soon as I can.

85
00:03:59,100 --> 00:04:01,660
Kim? You've been trying to find her?

86
00:04:01,670 --> 00:04:03,790
I've been out all night trying to find Kim!

87
00:04:03,790 --> 00:04:05,610
Teri, I'm going to explain it to you later. Okay?

88
00:04:05,610 --> 00:04:07,190
You're gonna have to trust me.

89
00:04:08,920 --> 00:04:09,700
Teri.

90
00:04:10,750 --> 00:04:11,810
Honey, I love you.

91
00:04:13,060 --> 00:04:15,430
I promise you, we're going to get through this. Okay?

92
00:04:17,390 --> 00:04:19,010
I love you too, Jack.

93
00:04:19,750 --> 00:04:21,620
I'll get back to you as soon as I know anything.

94
00:04:39,140 --> 00:04:40,940
She's here. They say the other one's dead.

95
00:04:40,940 --> 00:04:42,190
Don't worry, I will.

96
00:04:45,560 --> 00:04:47,190
Ok, we're done. There's been a change of plan.

97
00:04:47,190 --> 00:04:49,460
Drive to the compound, you'll get your money there.

98
00:04:49,470 --> 00:04:50,310
No problem.

99
00:04:50,390 --> 00:04:51,350
Go by a different route.

100
00:04:51,350 --> 00:04:53,090
I don't want us to look like a caravan.

101
00:04:53,090 --> 00:04:54,030
Right. Okay.

102
00:04:56,700 --> 00:04:58,320
- Let's just split. - Are you crazy?

103
00:04:58,320 --> 00:04:59,800
We got $20,000 coming.

104
00:05:01,310 --> 00:05:02,830
I don't like it. This guy's psycho.

105
00:05:02,830 --> 00:05:04,330
You're forgetting something.

106
00:05:04,380 --> 00:05:07,600
All right. Last month, Phoenix? You owe me.

107
00:05:07,810 --> 00:05:10,970
So let's get the money, then split. All right?

109
00:05:28,160 --> 00:05:31,010
This is fine, Patty. We'll finish it after the breakfast.

110
00:05:33,020 --> 00:05:34,810
Still got a couple hours to grab some sleep.

111
00:05:34,810 --> 00:05:36,030
Only if you do.

112
00:05:37,310 --> 00:05:38,720
I made mochas.

113
00:05:39,580 --> 00:05:41,640
Hey, I thought you were down.

114
00:05:42,610 --> 00:05:43,580
I'm up.

115
00:05:43,860 --> 00:05:45,110
I couldn't sleep.

116
00:05:45,640 --> 00:05:50,430
The polls open in less than three hours, Mr. President-to-be.

117
00:05:50,870 --> 00:05:53,510
Heavy on the caffeine for me. Patty?

118
00:05:53,690 --> 00:05:54,770
Nothing for me.

119
00:05:55,370 --> 00:05:57,100
- Mom? - No.

120
00:05:58,940 --> 00:06:00,110
You look exhausted.

121
00:06:00,160 --> 00:06:02,080
Go to bed, that's an order.

122
00:06:03,400 --> 00:06:04,320
All right.

123
00:06:05,110 --> 00:06:06,700
Promise you'll wake me if you need anything?

124
00:06:06,700 --> 00:06:07,700
Absolutely.

125
00:06:08,510 --> 00:06:09,400
Okay.

126
00:06:13,430 --> 00:06:14,700
- Night. - Goodnight.

127
00:06:21,080 --> 00:06:21,990
David....

128
00:06:24,260 --> 00:06:27,140
You're not gonna say anything to Nicole about Keith, are you?

129
00:06:27,270 --> 00:06:29,910
We don't even know for sure whether Maureen Kingsley's gonna

130
00:06:29,910 --> 00:06:31,550
go forward with the story.

131
00:06:31,980 --> 00:06:33,950
- We have to, Sherry. - Why?

132
00:06:33,950 --> 00:06:35,970
Because the press is going to get a hold of this.

133
00:06:36,490 --> 00:06:38,580
Whether it's today, tomorrow, next week,

134
00:06:38,580 --> 00:06:40,360
Nicole should be prepared.

135
00:06:40,450 --> 00:06:42,780
I thought you said that Carl was going to take care of it.

136
00:06:42,780 --> 00:06:44,100
He's gonna do what he can.

137
00:06:44,430 --> 00:06:47,050
I don't want her to suddenly hear something on the news.

138
00:06:47,100 --> 00:06:48,190
She'd be devastated.

139
00:06:48,190 --> 00:06:49,920
She's so happy right now, David.

140
00:06:49,920 --> 00:06:52,330
We've got to take it one step at a time.

141
00:06:52,750 --> 00:06:53,970
Dad, it's ready.

142
00:07:07,240 --> 00:07:09,050
Daddy, I figured all it out,

143
00:07:09,050 --> 00:07:10,610
and even if we lose Orange County,

144
00:07:10,610 --> 00:07:11,900
we're still going to win.

145
00:07:12,490 --> 00:07:14,780
Assuming we take Ventura by a 10 percent margin.

146
00:07:14,780 --> 00:07:16,320
No, even seven.

147
00:07:16,370 --> 00:07:18,070
It's all right there, in last night's poll.

148
00:07:19,720 --> 00:07:21,860
You make it look like there's nothing to worry about.

149
00:07:22,870 --> 00:07:25,810
That's because there is nothing to worry about.

150
00:07:29,020 --> 00:07:30,220
Nicole.

151
00:07:30,880 --> 00:07:32,800
- No, go ahead. - No, you first.

152
00:07:33,100 --> 00:07:35,240
I talked to Suzy and Rachel Brenner this afternoon

153
00:07:35,240 --> 00:07:36,640
and they're flying out.

154
00:07:36,850 --> 00:07:38,530
I invited them to the victory party.

155
00:07:38,580 --> 00:07:40,840
My lord. I haven't seen them

156
00:07:40,840 --> 00:07:42,170
since you all were in high school.

157
00:07:42,170 --> 00:07:44,920
You're going to see them tomorrow. Actually, tonight.

158
00:07:45,220 --> 00:07:46,320
God, that's great.

159
00:07:46,600 --> 00:07:47,550
What were you gonna say?

160
00:07:49,500 --> 00:07:50,380
Nothing.

161
00:07:52,110 --> 00:07:53,740
CTU, this is Myers.

162
00:07:54,140 --> 00:07:55,460
Mason is still looking over your shoulder?

164
00:07:55,780 --> 00:07:56,450
No.

165
00:07:56,450 --> 00:07:57,940
He ended the lockdown as soon as

166
00:07:57,940 --> 00:07:59,320
he found out where you were.

167
00:07:59,770 --> 00:08:01,790
Jack, be careful. He'll come after you.

168
00:08:02,090 --> 00:08:02,840
I'm at the precinct.

169
00:08:02,840 --> 00:08:04,540
They've got a ring around the suspect.

170
00:08:04,540 --> 00:08:05,870
I'm gonna need help getting to him.

171
00:08:05,870 --> 00:08:07,600
Get hold of Ryan Sealey over at District.

172
00:08:07,600 --> 00:08:09,800
Tell him it's about Palmer, and I need an override.

173
00:08:09,990 --> 00:08:11,170
Okay, I'll take care of it.

181
00:08:20,220 --> 00:08:21,140
Damn it.

182
00:08:30,340 --> 00:08:31,670
Tony, I'm still off the Net.

183
00:08:31,680 --> 00:08:34,360
I need a contact number for Ryan Sealey at District Two.

184
00:08:40,980 --> 00:08:42,640
You still pissed off about the lockdown?

185
00:08:43,210 --> 00:08:44,390
Jack's never gonna trust you again.

186
00:08:44,390 --> 00:08:45,920
I'm not sure I will, either.

187
00:08:47,040 --> 00:08:48,810
You don't trust me, but you'll trust Jack?

188
00:08:49,900 --> 00:08:50,840
Come on, Nina.

189
00:08:51,510 --> 00:08:54,350
He's been lying. He's been hiding things from us.

190
00:08:54,740 --> 00:08:57,130
It maybe okay for you, but it's not okay for me.

191
00:08:58,340 --> 00:08:59,280
Do you have the number?

192
00:09:08,520 --> 00:09:09,380
Thank you.

193
00:09:16,700 --> 00:09:19,050
I'm sorry, Mr. Bauer, but this guy killed a cop.

194
00:09:19,050 --> 00:09:20,670
I'm not interfering with booking protocol.

195
00:09:20,670 --> 00:09:23,010
I told you, you were gonna get a call from Ryan Sealey,

196
00:09:23,010 --> 00:09:24,810
who is our liaison to the PD's office.

197
00:09:24,810 --> 00:09:26,480
Until then, you can have my badge and gun.

198
00:09:26,480 --> 00:09:28,210
And I promise I will not interfere with anything.

199
00:09:28,210 --> 00:09:29,650
But I need to see that man now.

200
00:09:29,650 --> 00:09:30,790
What can I tell you?

201
00:09:31,560 --> 00:09:33,010
Fine. Where's your Lieutenant?

202
00:09:33,030 --> 00:09:34,830
He checked out, at midnight.

203
00:09:35,520 --> 00:09:37,340
But if he was here, he'd tell you the same thing.

204
00:09:38,710 --> 00:09:39,630
Sergeant.

205
00:09:40,470 --> 00:09:42,960
The cop that was killed tonight, Officer Hampton.

206
00:09:42,960 --> 00:09:43,980
Did you know her?

207
00:09:47,440 --> 00:09:48,500
Yeah, I knew her.

208
00:09:48,660 --> 00:09:51,420
I'm investigating a federal case. She was helping me.

209
00:09:52,180 --> 00:09:54,020
Do you want her death to be in vain?

210
00:09:54,960 --> 00:09:57,070
Please forget about the damn chain of command.

211
00:09:57,070 --> 00:10:01,360
I need to see this man now, just for a few minutes, please.

212
00:10:16,030 --> 00:10:17,030
Where's the suspect?

213
00:10:18,580 --> 00:10:19,670
Move him to room two.

214
00:10:25,060 --> 00:10:27,500
- Thank you. - Follow me.

215
00:10:35,750 --> 00:10:37,200
Hold it, Sergeant.

216
00:10:37,530 --> 00:10:39,040
This man's under my authority.

217
00:11:05,730 --> 00:11:07,280
We shouldn't have let him take her!

218
00:11:07,800 --> 00:11:10,300
There's two of us, one of him, and we got a gun!

219
00:11:10,360 --> 00:11:13,400
Believe me, dude, you don't wanna pull a piece on Mr. Gaines.

220
00:11:13,430 --> 00:11:14,790
No? Just on girls?

221
00:11:14,840 --> 00:11:17,380
If you had the hots for her, then you should've done something.

222
00:11:20,220 --> 00:11:21,530
I just don't want her to get hurt.

223
00:11:22,590 --> 00:11:23,780
Get real, dude.

224
00:11:23,790 --> 00:11:26,280
She saw our faces, she saw his face.

225
00:11:26,360 --> 00:11:29,300
She's not walking. She never was.

226
00:11:30,190 --> 00:11:31,350
You think he's gonna to kill her?

227
00:11:31,540 --> 00:11:33,250
Maybe he already has.

228
00:11:35,650 --> 00:11:36,530
Rick.

229
00:11:36,680 --> 00:11:39,500
Dude. Come on, it's $10,000 a piece.

230
00:11:39,500 --> 00:11:41,840
All right, we just want to get paid and get gone.

231
00:11:42,040 --> 00:11:45,370
Forget Kimberly, man, she's history.

232
00:11:57,110 --> 00:11:58,000
Listen, Jack....

233
00:11:59,240 --> 00:12:00,300
Until you tell me what you were doing

234
00:12:00,300 --> 00:12:01,650
at Dunlop Plaza with Richard Walsh.

235
00:12:01,650 --> 00:12:03,350
I'm treating you as a prime suspect.

236
00:12:03,350 --> 00:12:05,880
Why would I kill the only ally in the Agency that I've got?

237
00:12:05,890 --> 00:12:06,790
You tell me.

238
00:12:06,870 --> 00:12:09,050
Why'd you blow the whistle on your own agents last year?

239
00:12:09,250 --> 00:12:10,410
Why'd you try to blackmail me?

240
00:12:10,410 --> 00:12:11,530
Because you were withholding information

241
00:12:11,530 --> 00:12:13,470
vital to the investigation, George.

242
00:12:13,470 --> 00:12:15,320
I was following orders.

243
00:12:16,100 --> 00:12:18,480
I realize that's a concept you may be unfamiliar with, Jack.

244
00:12:18,480 --> 00:12:21,970
But it's something that some of us actually do take seriously.

245
00:12:23,940 --> 00:12:25,730
On the other side of this wall is a suspect

246
00:12:25,730 --> 00:12:28,500
who's connected with the people that want Palmer dead.

247
00:12:29,440 --> 00:12:30,400
How do you know that?

248
00:12:30,650 --> 00:12:31,600
Walsh and Baylor were killed

249
00:12:31,600 --> 00:12:34,140
because they obtained information that led me to this guy.

250
00:12:34,140 --> 00:12:37,080
And if you interfere now, and something happens to Palmer

251
00:12:37,350 --> 00:12:39,250
you'll be seen as impeding this investigation

252
00:12:39,250 --> 00:12:40,410
because you have a grudge against me.

253
00:12:40,410 --> 00:12:41,970
So why don't we cut the crap?

254
00:12:44,410 --> 00:12:45,870
How do you want to play this?

255
00:12:53,530 --> 00:12:54,880
I'll talk to him myself.

256
00:12:55,780 --> 00:12:58,570
Look, you're lucky I haven't already put you in cuffs.

257
00:12:58,580 --> 00:13:00,290
Just sit down, read a magazine.

258
00:13:09,150 --> 00:13:10,930
- Gaines. - Have you heard from him?

259
00:13:10,930 --> 00:13:12,890
No, I'm gonna call him in 15 minutes.

260
00:13:12,890 --> 00:13:14,430
He should be done by then.

261
00:13:17,720 --> 00:13:20,610
I've got the girl, I'm on the way to the compound right now.

262
00:13:21,520 --> 00:13:22,350
Gotta go.

263
00:13:24,550 --> 00:13:26,340
Stop, please.

264
00:13:55,330 --> 00:13:57,810
Listen, I don't have time for this. You understand?

265
00:14:20,270 --> 00:14:21,800
Maureen, it's David Palmer.

266
00:14:21,800 --> 00:14:22,550
Senator?

267
00:14:22,550 --> 00:14:23,450
I'm sorry to wake you.

268
00:14:23,460 --> 00:14:25,990
No, no. That's okay. What's up?

269
00:14:25,990 --> 00:14:27,570
The matter you called about earlier.

270
00:14:29,450 --> 00:14:30,820
We need to talk about it.

271
00:14:31,000 --> 00:14:32,980
Okay, let's talk.

272
00:14:32,980 --> 00:14:35,660
Since we're just a few floors apart,

273
00:14:35,740 --> 00:14:37,720
I was thinking maybe we could get together.

274
00:14:37,720 --> 00:14:39,630
Okay, how about I meet you in the lobby?

275
00:14:39,630 --> 00:14:41,630
No, the lobby's too public.

276
00:14:42,010 --> 00:14:44,060
There's a conference room on the third floor.

277
00:14:44,070 --> 00:14:45,080
I'll have it opened.

278
00:14:45,370 --> 00:14:47,700
I just need about ten minutes to get dressed.

279
00:14:47,700 --> 00:14:48,890
How does that sound?

280
00:14:49,140 --> 00:14:50,070
Yeah, that's good.

281
00:14:50,510 --> 00:14:51,550
I'll see you in ten.

282
00:14:52,020 --> 00:14:53,680
- Thanks, Maureen. - Sure.

283
00:14:59,780 --> 00:15:01,850
Those are the only places you know your daughters were?

284
00:15:02,290 --> 00:15:03,130
Yes.

285
00:15:03,870 --> 00:15:07,570
What about this boy, Dan, who works at the furniture store?

286
00:15:08,220 --> 00:15:09,350
We don't know anything about him.

287
00:15:09,350 --> 00:15:11,690
But the owner of the store is Mr. Nowrasteh.

288
00:15:11,690 --> 00:15:13,110
I have his number in here.

289
00:15:15,310 --> 00:15:16,050
Here you are.

290
00:15:17,780 --> 00:15:18,670
Excuse me.

291
00:15:23,450 --> 00:15:24,080
Hello?

292
00:15:24,080 --> 00:15:25,290
Hey, it's me.

293
00:15:25,480 --> 00:15:26,910
Is Janet out of surgery yet?

294
00:15:26,910 --> 00:15:29,480
Yeah. The police showed up. We're talking to him now.

295
00:15:29,480 --> 00:15:32,250
- Anything new? - No. How about you?

296
00:15:32,310 --> 00:15:34,130
I'm at the Van Nuys police station.

297
00:15:34,610 --> 00:15:36,950
I think there's someone who knows where the girls were tonight.

298
00:15:36,950 --> 00:15:38,760
You mean one of the police officers?

299
00:15:38,840 --> 00:15:41,090
No. Someone they picked up in North Hollywood.

300
00:15:41,640 --> 00:15:42,760
I think he saw Kim.

301
00:15:42,960 --> 00:15:44,850
- Who? - I don't know, a man.

302
00:15:45,370 --> 00:15:46,240
What did he say?

303
00:15:46,300 --> 00:15:47,650
I'm waiting to talk to him.

304
00:15:47,660 --> 00:15:49,270
Look, you've got to talk to Janet

305
00:15:49,270 --> 00:15:51,230
as soon as she's out of surgery, okay?

306
00:15:51,230 --> 00:15:52,880
I know.

307
00:15:53,820 --> 00:15:55,970
I'll call you as soon as I can. I've got to go, bye.

308
00:16:02,580 --> 00:16:03,750
So, what did he say?

309
00:16:05,140 --> 00:16:07,290
He says he won't talk to anybody except you.

310
00:16:11,680 --> 00:16:12,720
So, can I go in?

311
00:16:14,860 --> 00:16:15,670
Yeah.

312
00:16:17,250 --> 00:16:18,090
Thank you.

313
00:16:33,550 --> 00:16:35,700
My colleague said you only wanted to speak to me.

314
00:16:39,400 --> 00:16:43,610
Guess what? Right now, you're speaking to everyone.

315
00:16:43,610 --> 00:16:44,650
What the hell is he doing?

316
00:16:45,530 --> 00:16:47,130
I thought we were going to talk alone.

317
00:16:47,740 --> 00:16:48,830
You killed a cop.

318
00:16:49,970 --> 00:16:53,410
What you need to do right now is start telling me the truth.

319
00:16:53,410 --> 00:16:55,550
It was self-defense. You guys were chasing me.

320
00:16:57,290 --> 00:16:58,210
What's he saying?

321
00:17:01,240 --> 00:17:02,150
Go to hell!

322
00:17:02,480 --> 00:17:05,350
I'm done talking. Get this guy out of my face!

323
00:17:13,060 --> 00:17:13,910
You get nothing!

324
00:17:13,910 --> 00:17:15,410
I want my lawyer.

325
00:17:15,410 --> 00:17:16,270
Chill down.

326
00:17:16,360 --> 00:17:17,360
Okay, come on!

327
00:17:18,250 --> 00:17:21,750
I want my phone call. I want my lawyer.

328
00:17:21,750 --> 00:17:23,620
I want my phone call, now!

329
00:17:23,620 --> 00:17:25,410
Jack. Great job.

330
00:17:26,200 --> 00:17:27,170
He knows something.

331
00:17:27,170 --> 00:17:29,200
What are you gonna do, beat it out of him?

332
00:17:29,290 --> 00:17:30,390
What's the plan, Jack?

333
00:17:31,680 --> 00:17:34,690
What's the plan? Take a walk.

334
00:17:43,480 --> 00:17:44,550
Yo, man, what's up?

335
00:18:16,770 --> 00:18:17,620
Bauer.

336
00:18:17,970 --> 00:18:19,100
Is this line safe?

337
00:18:19,290 --> 00:18:20,720
Tell me about my daughter.

338
00:18:20,900 --> 00:18:21,970
Not until you get me out.

339
00:18:21,970 --> 00:18:23,220
How did you know where she is?

340
00:18:23,220 --> 00:18:24,280
Heard some guys talking.

341
00:18:24,280 --> 00:18:25,400
Guys I work with.

342
00:18:26,050 --> 00:18:27,030
What guys?

343
00:18:27,170 --> 00:18:29,020
All you need to know right now is they have your daughter,

344
00:18:29,020 --> 00:18:30,810
and they're gonna call me in 20 minutes.

345
00:18:30,850 --> 00:18:31,670
Where?

346
00:18:32,020 --> 00:18:33,050
Back where you first saw me.

347
00:18:33,050 --> 00:18:34,270
San Fernando Road?

348
00:18:34,690 --> 00:18:37,240
If I don't answer, they'll know something's wrong.

349
00:18:37,240 --> 00:18:38,520
Get me out of here.

350
00:18:38,760 --> 00:18:39,800
Don't know if I can.

351
00:18:39,800 --> 00:18:42,160
I'm the one chance you got to find your daughter.

352
00:18:42,640 --> 00:18:45,070
I'm not there for that call, the chance is over.

353
00:18:45,650 --> 00:18:47,280
Better think of something fast.

354
00:19:02,320 --> 00:19:03,630
CTU, this is Myers.

355
00:19:03,630 --> 00:19:04,720
Hey, it's Jack.

356
00:19:05,120 --> 00:19:06,970
Suspect's name is Penticoff.

357
00:19:06,970 --> 00:19:09,230
He's expecting a call in the next 20 minutes

358
00:19:09,230 --> 00:19:12,230
at 18166 San Fernando Road.

359
00:19:12,230 --> 00:19:15,010
I need you to trace all available public lines.

360
00:19:17,960 --> 00:19:21,770
Okay, I see water lines, utilities, no phone lines.

361
00:19:21,770 --> 00:19:23,980
Keep looking. It's where he said he'd get the call.

362
00:19:23,980 --> 00:19:27,520
Wait, there's a pay phone halfway down the block.

363
00:19:27,910 --> 00:19:30,530
- And it's in service. - Set up a trace.

364
00:19:30,630 --> 00:19:33,250
- Not enough time for a warrant. - Forget about the warrant!

365
00:19:33,580 --> 00:19:35,770
Bigger problem. If they're expecting Penticoff,

366
00:19:35,770 --> 00:19:37,700
they'll hang up the second they hear your voice.

367
00:19:37,700 --> 00:19:38,740
They're not gonna hear my voice,

368
00:19:38,740 --> 00:19:39,990
they'll hear Penticoff's.

369
00:19:39,990 --> 00:19:41,950
- Did Mason get him out? - No.

370
00:19:42,800 --> 00:19:44,520
So what are you planning, a jailbreak?

371
00:19:45,340 --> 00:19:46,210
Jack?

372
00:19:49,250 --> 00:19:50,210
Set up the trace.

373
00:20:15,770 --> 00:20:19,330
Bauer's behavior is far from representative of this agency.

374
00:20:20,570 --> 00:20:22,980
Whether you like it not, we have to be involved.

375
00:20:29,490 --> 00:20:32,160
Hey, are you the officer that interviewed Penticoff?

376
00:20:32,400 --> 00:20:33,730
No, I just transferred him to a holding cell.

377
00:20:33,730 --> 00:20:35,260
I still need to see him.

378
00:20:36,500 --> 00:20:39,080
- You Bauer from CTU? - Yeah, that's right.

379
00:20:39,760 --> 00:20:44,730
Look, the cop he killed, she was my partner, understand?

380
00:20:47,100 --> 00:20:48,000
Sorry.

381
00:20:48,110 --> 00:20:49,740
I heard you went off on him before.

382
00:20:49,960 --> 00:20:51,560
I want him to go down for it,

383
00:20:51,560 --> 00:20:53,480
which means a clean bust.

384
00:20:53,880 --> 00:20:55,350
No more extracurricular activities.

385
00:20:55,350 --> 00:20:56,270
Understood.

386
00:20:58,820 --> 00:21:01,590
All right. But I've got the access card.

387
00:21:02,820 --> 00:21:06,830
Now, you go in with me, or you don't go in.

388
00:21:07,270 --> 00:21:08,210
I'm fine with that.

389
00:21:26,060 --> 00:21:27,320
Keep him away from me.

390
00:21:27,350 --> 00:21:28,910
He wants to ask a few questions.

391
00:21:28,910 --> 00:21:30,850
No more questions without my lawyer.

392
00:21:32,120 --> 00:21:33,210
Who are you working for?

393
00:21:34,490 --> 00:21:35,410
Are you deaf?

394
00:21:35,960 --> 00:21:38,220
I said, no questions without my lawyer.

395
00:21:40,130 --> 00:21:42,310
- Your lawyer can kiss my ass. - Yeah?

396
00:21:42,310 --> 00:21:44,790
- Who do you work for? - Hey, back off!

397
00:21:44,790 --> 00:21:45,790
Get your hands off me.

398
00:21:45,790 --> 00:21:47,430
I told you, he killed my partner.

399
00:21:47,430 --> 00:21:50,110
I know, I was there. Where were you?

400
00:21:50,400 --> 00:21:51,270
What?

401
00:21:51,480 --> 00:21:54,000
Where were you when your partner really needed you?

402
00:22:02,310 --> 00:22:03,330
Get him out of here.

403
00:22:05,860 --> 00:22:07,220
What's the matter with you?

404
00:22:07,220 --> 00:22:09,180
He's crazy, I'm filing charges!

405
00:22:15,490 --> 00:22:17,620
You ought to get yourself under control, Bauer.

406
00:22:21,570 --> 00:22:22,780
I'll take care of it.

407
00:22:59,180 --> 00:23:01,980
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to wake you.

408
00:23:02,200 --> 00:23:03,260
I wasn't asleep.

409
00:23:04,170 --> 00:23:05,400
I thought you might like some coffee.

410
00:23:05,400 --> 00:23:06,170
Thank you.

411
00:23:18,660 --> 00:23:19,640
She'll turn up.

412
00:23:21,500 --> 00:23:22,480
How's Janet?

413
00:23:26,340 --> 00:23:29,710
They're relieving some pressure on her spine.

414
00:23:30,270 --> 00:23:31,560
But she's gonna be okay.

415
00:23:31,770 --> 00:23:33,100
At least, that's what they say.

416
00:23:33,970 --> 00:23:34,870
Of course she will.

417
00:23:39,150 --> 00:23:41,680
- Any news from Jack? - No.

418
00:23:41,680 --> 00:23:43,820
As far as I know, he's still out looking for Kim.

419
00:23:44,540 --> 00:23:45,300
Well, that's good.

420
00:23:46,960 --> 00:23:49,480
You said he has resources the police don't have, right?

421
00:23:56,860 --> 00:23:57,700
Even so...

422
00:24:00,310 --> 00:24:02,650
I imagine you wish he were here.

423
00:24:12,640 --> 00:24:13,680
Arms out, please.

424
00:24:20,950 --> 00:24:21,750
Turn around.

425
00:24:23,100 --> 00:24:24,980
Enough, Maureen's an old friend.

426
00:24:24,980 --> 00:24:27,100
It's all right, he's just doing his job.

427
00:24:27,100 --> 00:24:29,510
- Thank you. - Your ID, ma'am.

428
00:24:31,180 --> 00:24:32,270
Would you excuse us?

429
00:24:37,350 --> 00:24:38,980
How long have we known each other, Maureen?

430
00:24:40,110 --> 00:24:43,010
Come on, Senator, that's not fair.

431
00:24:43,010 --> 00:24:47,530
No, I'm just saying, you, me, my family...

432
00:24:47,850 --> 00:24:49,200
we've made a journey together

433
00:24:50,050 --> 00:24:52,580
from local politics to where we are now.

434
00:24:53,210 --> 00:24:54,200
We helped each other along,

435
00:24:54,200 --> 00:24:56,680
because we cared about the same things.

436
00:24:57,270 --> 00:24:58,250
I know that.

437
00:24:58,930 --> 00:25:00,080
Have I ever lied to you?

438
00:25:00,620 --> 00:25:01,450
No.

439
00:25:02,580 --> 00:25:03,640
Embarrassed you?

440
00:25:03,670 --> 00:25:04,540
No.

441
00:25:05,500 --> 00:25:06,750
Then why are you doing this?

442
00:25:07,040 --> 00:25:08,020
Senator.

443
00:25:08,320 --> 00:25:11,050
I wish to God that I didn't get this information.

444
00:25:11,850 --> 00:25:13,650
But we're talking about murder.

445
00:25:13,660 --> 00:25:14,520
A rumor...

446
00:25:16,140 --> 00:25:17,710
started by my enemies...

447
00:25:18,630 --> 00:25:21,350
of whom, as you well know, I have many.

448
00:25:21,350 --> 00:25:24,880
That's what I thought, too, at first. But....

449
00:25:26,460 --> 00:25:28,180
Please, go on.

450
00:25:29,360 --> 00:25:31,220
You know I can't tell you my sources.

451
00:25:31,220 --> 00:25:34,990
Come on, Maureen, we're not in court here.

452
00:25:35,570 --> 00:25:36,960
I'm just an old friend with

453
00:25:36,970 --> 00:25:40,010
a career and family that you just may destroy.

454
00:25:41,160 --> 00:25:42,760
You owe me that much at least.

455
00:25:45,580 --> 00:25:46,420
Okay.

456
00:25:49,350 --> 00:25:50,580
Two sources.

457
00:25:52,670 --> 00:25:55,750
One, a man named George Ferragamo.

458
00:25:57,080 --> 00:25:59,620
He was your son's therapist for four years.

459
00:26:00,700 --> 00:26:02,400
He came to me with the story.

460
00:26:04,580 --> 00:26:05,590
The second source?

461
00:26:08,710 --> 00:26:10,700
The boy who raped your daughter,

462
00:26:10,760 --> 00:26:12,920
then threw himself off the balcony? Lyle Gibson?

463
00:26:12,920 --> 00:26:16,850
His autopsy showed that he had cuts and scratches...

464
00:26:16,850 --> 00:26:19,900
that pointed to a violent struggle.

465
00:26:21,030 --> 00:26:22,420
Nicole tried to fight him off.

466
00:26:24,240 --> 00:26:25,910
Yes. That was the explanation.

467
00:26:26,780 --> 00:26:27,630
But an hour later,

468
00:26:27,630 --> 00:26:31,800
an African-American teenager went to this emergency room one block away

469
00:26:32,100 --> 00:26:33,700
...with similar injuries.

470
00:26:34,540 --> 00:26:36,250
Name here says "Edward Johnson."

471
00:26:37,100 --> 00:26:37,630
The handwriting,

472
00:26:37,630 --> 00:26:41,510
where he filled out the form and signed his name...

473
00:26:43,430 --> 00:26:45,400
I had it analyzed by an expert.

474
00:26:47,390 --> 00:26:48,480
It's your son's.

475
00:27:03,450 --> 00:27:05,460
I don't give a damn about your expert.

476
00:27:05,460 --> 00:27:06,900
My son never killed anybody.

477
00:27:07,910 --> 00:27:09,820
Senator, I would never--

478
00:27:09,820 --> 00:27:11,820
You do what you have to do, Maureen.

479
00:27:12,990 --> 00:27:15,740
Just be prepared to accept the consequences.

480
00:28:19,610 --> 00:28:20,480
Dad.

481
00:28:23,870 --> 00:28:24,850
Is something wrong?

482
00:28:26,630 --> 00:28:28,170
I guess you'll have to tell me.

483
00:28:38,480 --> 00:28:40,080
The night your sister was raped...

484
00:28:40,900 --> 00:28:43,470
did you have any contact with the boy who raped her?

485
00:28:45,120 --> 00:28:47,150
- What? - You heard me.

486
00:28:49,980 --> 00:28:51,610
I don't believe this. I mean....

487
00:28:53,060 --> 00:28:54,640
What brought this up all of a sudden?

488
00:28:55,500 --> 00:28:58,040
I mean, let's leave all that in the past where it belongs.

489
00:28:59,350 --> 00:29:01,260
I'd like to, believe me.

490
00:29:03,430 --> 00:29:05,210
But as it happens, I can't.

491
00:29:11,120 --> 00:29:12,840
What did you do that night...

492
00:29:13,190 --> 00:29:16,080
after you found out that Nicole had been attacked?

493
00:29:16,200 --> 00:29:18,790
The truth, now. All of it.

494
00:29:20,750 --> 00:29:22,510
I don't think you have the right to ask me that.

495
00:29:29,690 --> 00:29:31,260
You don't think I have the right?

496
00:29:31,260 --> 00:29:32,280
No, I don't.

497
00:29:33,460 --> 00:29:34,960
See, this thing happened.

498
00:29:36,140 --> 00:29:37,630
Somebody had to deal with it,

499
00:29:38,160 --> 00:29:40,190
but you were in Chicago, giving a speech or...

500
00:29:40,190 --> 00:29:41,330
New York, receiving an civic award--

501
00:29:41,330 --> 00:29:43,930
We'll deal with my shortcomings as a father some other time.

502
00:29:43,930 --> 00:29:44,870
Right now, I wanna know

503
00:29:44,870 --> 00:29:47,740
what you did after you found that out your sister had been raped.

504
00:29:47,740 --> 00:29:49,120
And I told you...

505
00:29:49,150 --> 00:29:50,300
I'm not gonna answer.

506
00:29:50,400 --> 00:29:51,680
You will answer me!

507
00:30:17,880 --> 00:30:19,430
I apologize about Bauer,

508
00:30:19,430 --> 00:30:21,110
but I'd really appreciate

509
00:30:21,110 --> 00:30:23,660
it if we could handle this internally.

510
00:30:23,670 --> 00:30:25,160
I got no problem with that.

511
00:30:26,280 --> 00:30:27,230
Sergeant, excuse me,

512
00:30:27,230 --> 00:30:30,290
but if our federal colleagues are through with Penticoff...

513
00:30:30,290 --> 00:30:32,950
I'd like to start processing him into the system.

514
00:30:32,990 --> 00:30:34,560
What're you doing? Thought you left.

515
00:30:34,560 --> 00:30:37,510
I'm not leaving until Penticoff is behind bars without bail.

516
00:30:38,800 --> 00:30:41,270
The computer has you checked out five minutes ago.

517
00:30:41,270 --> 00:30:42,850
All right, guys, we're on the move.

518
00:30:44,310 --> 00:30:45,130
Damn it!

519
00:30:49,680 --> 00:30:51,540
I got this notice in the mail this afternoon.

520
00:30:52,710 --> 00:30:54,350
Actually, it was yesterday afternoon.

521
00:30:56,100 --> 00:30:58,060
Kimberly was failing Algebra.

522
00:30:59,650 --> 00:31:00,620
It was the second notice.

523
00:31:00,620 --> 00:31:02,010
She intercepted the first one、

524
00:31:02,010 --> 00:31:04,730
and threw it away.

525
00:31:06,480 --> 00:31:08,780
When she got home, I was so mad at her.

526
00:31:15,280 --> 00:31:16,660
I guess I accused her...

527
00:31:17,390 --> 00:31:21,560
and I said things to her I shouldn't have said.

528
00:31:21,670 --> 00:31:24,000
There isn't a parent in the world who hasn't been there.

529
00:31:26,350 --> 00:31:29,880
Last night, when I told her good night...

530
00:31:29,880 --> 00:31:31,450
she didn't even acknowledge me.

531
00:31:33,600 --> 00:31:35,410
I actually had the thought that I'd be....

532
00:31:36,480 --> 00:31:39,450
I'd be so glad when she got out of the house.

533
00:31:44,910 --> 00:31:46,200
When Janet wakes up,

534
00:31:46,310 --> 00:31:48,590
she'll know where Kim is, and we'll find her.

535
00:31:48,590 --> 00:31:50,310
I hope it's gonna be that easy. I don't know about that.

536
00:31:50,310 --> 00:31:50,900
It will be.

537
00:31:50,900 --> 00:31:52,820
Why wasn't she with Janet?

538
00:31:52,820 --> 00:31:54,760
- It doesn't make sense. - I don't know.

539
00:31:54,760 --> 00:31:56,130
Maybe she got freaked by the accident--

540
00:31:56,130 --> 00:31:56,700
We should have waited. That's what we should have done.

541
00:31:56,700 --> 00:31:59,350
No.

542
00:32:00,050 --> 00:32:01,510
We were right to come here.

543
00:32:02,230 --> 00:32:04,480
All we had to go on was the ambulance.

544
00:32:05,430 --> 00:32:07,120
We had to follow up on it.

545
00:32:13,460 --> 00:32:15,210
Listen, whatever happens...

546
00:32:16,940 --> 00:32:20,250
I'm gonna stay with you until we find Kim.

547
00:32:22,000 --> 00:32:23,000
You have my promise.

548
00:32:26,050 --> 00:32:26,890
Thank you.

549
00:32:29,970 --> 00:32:31,820
Come on, Davis, we need that uplink.

550
00:32:34,400 --> 00:32:36,010
He says we ought to have a picture by now.

551
00:32:38,600 --> 00:32:40,730
W7 satellite was in the southwest sector

552
00:32:40,730 --> 00:32:42,900
when Bauer helped Penticoff escape.

553
00:32:43,060 --> 00:32:45,060
With luck, we'll be able to pull up visuals

554
00:32:45,070 --> 00:32:47,070
that'll help us pinpoint his location.

555
00:32:48,100 --> 00:32:50,230
That's it, here we go.

556
00:32:50,680 --> 00:32:52,250
Davis, the link's up.

557
00:32:52,900 --> 00:32:54,170
Now I gotta get a back trace.

558
00:32:54,870 --> 00:32:57,040
This is the roof of the building from 200 miles up.

559
00:32:57,760 --> 00:33:00,210
About how long would you say since they got out?

560
00:33:00,320 --> 00:33:01,180
I don't know.

561
00:33:01,840 --> 00:33:03,040
Seven, eight minutes?

562
00:33:03,250 --> 00:33:06,000
Okay, Davis, I want to go back ten minutes..

563
00:33:06,000 --> 00:33:08,350
and give me stills at thirty second intervals.

564
00:33:08,390 --> 00:33:10,620
Look for two men exiting the building together.

565
00:33:12,320 --> 00:33:13,670
As of ten minutes ago...

566
00:33:14,910 --> 00:33:15,690
...thirty....

567
00:33:15,750 --> 00:33:16,600
There they are.

568
00:33:18,770 --> 00:33:20,010
Okay, you can speed it up.

569
00:33:20,030 --> 00:33:21,780
All right, speeding up.

570
00:33:23,330 --> 00:33:24,460
Slow it down now.

571
00:33:24,490 --> 00:33:25,390
You got it.

572
00:33:25,480 --> 00:33:26,530
You got a mark on that car?

573
00:33:31,580 --> 00:33:32,400
All right.

574
00:33:34,050 --> 00:33:35,610
Where are you headed, Jack?

575
00:34:06,860 --> 00:34:08,410
- You all set? - All set.

576
00:34:08,410 --> 00:34:09,590
How much time do you need?

577
00:34:09,650 --> 00:34:10,720
Just a few seconds.

578
00:34:12,420 --> 00:34:14,810
- Who are these guys? - I told you, I don't know.

579
00:34:14,820 --> 00:34:15,820
They tell me what to do,

580
00:34:15,820 --> 00:34:17,210
I do it, they pay me. That's it.

581
00:34:19,760 --> 00:34:20,550
It's ringing.

582
00:34:21,750 --> 00:34:23,720
- Yeah. - I'm not showing anything.

583
00:34:24,090 --> 00:34:25,720
-Yeah. -It's a cell phone.

584
00:34:26,360 --> 00:34:27,410
We're screwed.

585
00:34:27,760 --> 00:34:29,150
I don't have the frequency.

586
00:34:30,010 --> 00:34:31,350
- I'll get back to you. - Jack?

587
00:34:32,380 --> 00:34:34,670
It's Gaines, there's been a change of plans,

588
00:34:34,670 --> 00:34:36,260
but nothing you can't handle.

589
00:34:36,340 --> 00:34:37,650
Taped to the back of the phone

590
00:34:37,650 --> 00:34:39,800
is a set of keys with a remote.

591
00:34:42,720 --> 00:34:43,460
Got 'em.

592
00:34:43,460 --> 00:34:45,640
It's for a parked car on Avenue 26,

593
00:34:45,640 --> 00:34:48,460
Nevada plates 782MOF.

594
00:34:48,460 --> 00:34:51,560
Find it with the remote. There's a body in the trunk.

595
00:34:51,560 --> 00:34:52,490
Get rid of it.

596
00:34:53,550 --> 00:34:55,090
What did he mean, a body?

597
00:34:55,090 --> 00:34:55,810
I don't know!

598
00:34:55,810 --> 00:34:57,730
- Whose body is in the trunk? - I don't know.

599
00:35:15,510 --> 00:35:16,580
Walk in front of me.

600
00:35:18,840 --> 00:35:19,710
Come on.

601
00:35:34,730 --> 00:35:35,590
Kneel up against that wall,

602
00:35:35,590 --> 00:35:37,680
interlocking fingers behind your head now.

603
00:35:39,990 --> 00:35:40,910
Don't move.

604
00:35:46,960 --> 00:35:47,960
My God.

605
00:36:09,030 --> 00:36:09,950
Hey, Jack.

606
00:36:10,880 --> 00:36:12,820
- We had a deal. - Shut up.

607
00:36:14,270 --> 00:36:15,200
Put him in the car.

608
00:36:19,090 --> 00:36:20,700
That's pretty quick work, George.

609
00:36:20,870 --> 00:36:22,340
Tracking me on a satellite?

610
00:36:22,630 --> 00:36:23,890
I'm taking you in, Jack.

611
00:36:24,180 --> 00:36:26,010
He had evidence on the Palmer hit.

612
00:36:27,200 --> 00:36:28,690
That's why I broke him out.

613
00:36:33,620 --> 00:36:34,710
So, who was this?

614
00:36:35,690 --> 00:36:36,690
I don't know yet.

615
00:36:40,650 --> 00:36:42,670
You're having quite a night here, aren't you, Jack?

616
00:36:44,860 --> 00:36:47,060
Now, why don't you tell me what the hell is going on here?

617
00:36:47,730 --> 00:36:49,630
Unless you want me to throw you back to the cops.

618
00:36:49,750 --> 00:36:50,760
They're ready for you.

619
00:36:54,520 --> 00:36:55,790
There are people within the Agency

620
00:36:55,790 --> 00:36:57,590
that are supporting the Palmer hit.

621
00:36:58,760 --> 00:37:00,000
That's why Walsh and Baylor were killed.

622
00:37:00,000 --> 00:37:01,290
They found out about it.

623
00:37:01,970 --> 00:37:03,810
The truth is, I thought you were a part of it.

624
00:37:04,720 --> 00:37:06,370
I apologize if I was wrong.

625
00:37:07,350 --> 00:37:10,240
George, as crazy as this sounds, you're gonna have to trust me.

626
00:37:11,290 --> 00:37:12,750
This is gonna look very bad for us

627
00:37:12,750 --> 00:37:14,730
if something happens to Palmer tonight.

628
00:37:22,690 --> 00:37:23,870
So what's next?

629
00:37:24,110 --> 00:37:27,200
I need to take the body down to CTU and try to make an ID.

630
00:37:28,200 --> 00:37:30,810
I'll go grill Penticoff, get what I can out of him.

631
00:37:33,220 --> 00:37:35,000
We never had this conversation, all right?

632
00:37:35,000 --> 00:37:35,750
Right.

633
00:37:35,750 --> 00:37:36,790
I'll be at District.

634
00:37:37,580 --> 00:37:40,680
Okay, call the precinct, tell them we've recovered Penticoff.

635
00:37:58,370 --> 00:37:59,200
What have we got?

636
00:37:59,340 --> 00:38:01,260
Body. Male. Badly mutilated.

637
00:38:01,260 --> 00:38:03,140
I need a positive ID as soon as possible.

638
00:38:03,140 --> 00:38:04,380
Who's our best forensic?

639
00:38:04,380 --> 00:38:05,300
Tanaka.

640
00:38:05,300 --> 00:38:07,250
Bring him in. I'll be there in 10 minutes.

641
00:38:07,250 --> 00:38:08,890
- I'm on it. - Okay.

642
00:38:16,270 --> 00:38:16,830
Yes, doctor

643
00:38:17,570 --> 00:38:18,730
I need a clamp, please.

644
00:38:22,240 --> 00:38:23,700
- Hello? - Hey, it's me.

645
00:38:23,700 --> 00:38:25,320
Jack, did you find out anything?

646
00:38:25,810 --> 00:38:27,190
Maybe, I'm not sure yet.

647
00:38:27,200 --> 00:38:28,230
What have you been doing?

648
00:38:28,760 --> 00:38:31,310
I'll be there in 20 minutes. I'll explain to you then.

649
00:38:31,380 --> 00:38:33,460
- All right. - Is Janet out of surgery?

650
00:38:33,460 --> 00:38:35,730
Not yet. She should be soon.

651
00:38:35,920 --> 00:38:38,230
Good. It's really important that I talk to her.

652
00:38:38,570 --> 00:38:39,880
I know it sounds crass sweetheart,

653
00:38:39,880 --> 00:38:41,620
but she's our only link to Kimberly.

654
00:38:42,890 --> 00:38:44,060
Hang in there, honey.

655
00:38:44,760 --> 00:38:46,510
I love you. I'm on my way, okay?

656
00:38:46,620 --> 00:38:47,510
Okay.

657
00:39:14,090 --> 00:39:14,900
Just be cool.

658
00:39:31,300 --> 00:39:34,710
We'd like our money now, if that's, like, you know, okay.

659
00:39:37,520 --> 00:39:39,250
Just so we're, like, you know,

660
00:39:39,250 --> 00:39:41,930
clear, what happened to the other girl?

661
00:39:42,900 --> 00:39:45,760
Janet? Like I told you, we had to kill her.

662
00:39:47,440 --> 00:39:49,690
My people tell me, that someone that fits her description

663
00:39:49,690 --> 00:39:52,600
was taken to a hospital near to where you were.

664
00:39:53,960 --> 00:39:55,240
How do you explain that?

665
00:39:58,590 --> 00:39:59,570
Well, the thing is....

666
00:40:03,680 --> 00:40:06,530
maybe she wasn't quite dead.

667
00:40:08,770 --> 00:40:09,570
I'll tell you, Dan...

668
00:40:09,570 --> 00:40:12,490
you're either dead or you're not dead.

669
00:40:12,490 --> 00:40:15,290
There's no such thing as "Sort of dead."

670
00:40:15,530 --> 00:40:17,320
Here, let me show you.

671
00:40:17,770 --> 00:40:18,720
No!

672
00:40:26,620 --> 00:40:27,920
You've just been promoted.

673
00:40:30,880 --> 00:40:31,960
Congratulations.

674
00:40:58,810 --> 00:40:59,740
We're losing her.

675
00:41:05,730 --> 00:41:06,720
What's going on?

