6
00:00:29,670 --> 00:00:34,670
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

7
00:00:29,670 --> 00:00:34,670
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

8
00:00:29,670 --> 00:00:34,670
{\an5}{\pos(145,252)}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

9
00:00:30,170 --> 00:00:34,670
{\pos(67,248)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

10
00:00:30,170 --> 00:00:34,670
{\pos(67,248)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

11
00:00:30,170 --> 00:00:34,670
{\pos(58,238)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

12
00:00:30,170 --> 00:00:34,670
{\pos(84,248)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

15
00:00:35,890 --> 00:01:10,890
{\an9}m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

16
00:00:35,390 --> 00:01:10,890
{\an2}{\pos(26,248)}m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

25
00:01:14,540 --> 00:01:15,720
Walsh isn't answering.

26
00:01:16,260 --> 00:01:18,000
As soon as you reach him, you find me.

27
00:01:21,400 --> 00:01:23,570
- Is this the crew list from the 747? - Yeah.

28
00:01:23,660 --> 00:01:24,890
You want me contact NTSB,

29
00:01:24,890 --> 00:01:26,110
get a maintenance history on the plane?

30
00:01:26,110 --> 00:01:28,750
No. For now, let's just assume this was not an accident.

31
00:01:29,200 --> 00:01:31,260
- Why? - It originated out of Berlin.

32
00:01:31,260 --> 00:01:33,540
It's where Walsh said the shooter was coming from.

33
00:01:33,910 --> 00:01:36,350
I need you to give me a break down the crew and passenger list,

34
00:01:36,350 --> 00:01:38,100
political affiliation, criminal record,

35
00:01:38,100 --> 00:01:40,350
country of origin and residence.

36
00:01:40,630 --> 00:01:42,000
- Jack. - What?

37
00:01:43,860 --> 00:01:45,680
You want to tell me what's going on here tonight?

38
00:01:45,680 --> 00:01:46,840
What's going on?

39
00:01:47,210 --> 00:01:49,450
Besides a 747 falling out of the sky

40
00:01:49,450 --> 00:01:51,460
and a threat on a presidential candidate's life?

41
00:01:51,460 --> 00:01:52,840
That's right. Besides that.

42
00:01:54,030 --> 00:01:57,050
Look, George Mason comes in here, disappears up

43
00:01:57,060 --> 00:01:59,450
in your office for a half an hour, then he limps out.

44
00:02:00,660 --> 00:02:01,640
What's that all about?

45
00:02:04,140 --> 00:02:05,230
Tell him, Jack.

46
00:02:09,060 --> 00:02:10,780
- Fine, then I will. - Nina.

47
00:02:10,780 --> 00:02:13,550
The three agents that Jack brought down on bribery charges

48
00:02:13,550 --> 00:02:15,650
last year were close friends of Mason.

49
00:02:15,840 --> 00:02:17,790
He's been looking for payback ever since.

50
00:02:17,790 --> 00:02:18,700
He chose tonight to make

51
00:02:18,700 --> 00:02:21,040
some pretty nasty accusations about Jack

52
00:02:21,190 --> 00:02:23,150
as well as some other people in this office.

53
00:02:26,480 --> 00:02:27,950
In case you haven't noticed,

54
00:02:27,950 --> 00:02:30,250
Jack doesn't have a lot of tolerance for criticism.

55
00:02:31,240 --> 00:02:32,180
I need that right away.

56
00:02:35,330 --> 00:02:37,080
All right, look, I'll get you that list within the hour.

57
00:02:38,210 --> 00:02:39,180
Thank you.

58
00:02:48,900 --> 00:02:50,350
That was quite a story.

59
00:02:51,190 --> 00:02:52,490
It's better than the truth.

60
00:03:53,000 --> 00:03:54,350
Did you get the ID?

61
00:03:55,740 --> 00:03:56,560
Yes.

62
00:04:52,390 --> 00:04:53,680
It's funny. When you came to Jack's rescue back there

63
00:04:53,680 --> 00:04:55,770
with your little performance.

64
00:04:56,740 --> 00:04:58,280
It reminded me of something.

65
00:04:59,830 --> 00:05:00,930
Yeah, what?

66
00:05:02,370 --> 00:05:05,200
Remember that time we came into work together about a month ago?

67
00:05:05,560 --> 00:05:07,650
Lisa made some wisecrack remark

68
00:05:08,370 --> 00:05:11,150
and you came up with this really great B.S. story.

69
00:05:11,210 --> 00:05:14,570
An early breakfast meeting with District Three.

70
00:05:16,970 --> 00:05:19,990
I was really impressed with how convincing a liar you are.

71
00:05:22,970 --> 00:05:24,200
What's your point, Tony?

72
00:05:25,820 --> 00:05:28,580
I still want to know what happened up there between Jack and Mason.

73
00:05:28,620 --> 00:05:29,690
I already told you.

74
00:05:30,690 --> 00:05:31,790
And I don't believe you.

75
00:05:32,920 --> 00:05:34,210
Maybe I should ask Mason.

76
00:05:34,700 --> 00:05:37,000
A presidential candidate's life is at stake.

77
00:05:37,690 --> 00:05:39,040
Maybe you should get back to work.

78
00:05:48,530 --> 00:05:49,910
I think we need to turn right here.

80
00:06:01,770 --> 00:06:02,690
There it is.

81
00:06:18,520 --> 00:06:19,430
Janet?

82
00:06:22,070 --> 00:06:23,070
Janet?

83
00:06:26,380 --> 00:06:28,380
- Hello? - Hey, sweetheart.

84
00:06:28,800 --> 00:06:31,990
- Have you found the girls yet? - No. We just got here.

85
00:06:31,990 --> 00:06:34,510
Janet's car is parked out front. I just got into the store.

86
00:06:34,870 --> 00:06:36,900
It's all right. I'll wait 'til you check it out.

87
00:06:36,900 --> 00:06:38,440
No, let me call you back.

88
00:06:38,610 --> 00:06:39,230
I'll hold.

89
00:06:39,240 --> 00:06:43,190
- Kim? - Teri?

90
00:06:45,390 --> 00:06:46,410
Kim?

91
00:06:47,420 --> 00:06:48,490
They were here.

92
00:07:12,010 --> 00:07:13,330
What did you give her?

93
00:07:13,540 --> 00:07:14,990
Nothing she didn't want.

94
00:07:17,810 --> 00:07:20,800
Look, my dad is a government agent.

95
00:07:21,310 --> 00:07:22,910
I thought you said your dad was dead.

96
00:07:23,820 --> 00:07:26,830
He's not. If I'm not home in the next half hour,

97
00:07:26,830 --> 00:07:28,610
he's going to be all over this.

98
00:07:28,610 --> 00:07:30,450
Told you, you should have given her a roofie.

99
00:07:30,710 --> 00:07:32,730
I'm serious. You two are toast.

100
00:07:32,730 --> 00:07:34,540
She's giving me a headache, dude.

101
00:07:34,680 --> 00:07:36,950
- Just chill, okay? - You chill.

102
00:07:56,530 --> 00:07:57,540
Walsh.

103
00:08:05,120 --> 00:08:07,180
- Did anyone see you come in? - No.

104
00:08:07,530 --> 00:08:09,600
- You sure you weren't followed? - Take it easy.

105
00:08:09,610 --> 00:08:11,820
No, I'm not going to take it easy. I'm not.

106
00:08:13,990 --> 00:08:15,390
I should never have called you.

107
00:08:15,610 --> 00:08:18,310
If you have evidence that someone inside the Agency

108
00:08:18,320 --> 00:08:20,570
is involved in a plot against David Palmer,

109
00:08:20,570 --> 00:08:22,280
then you had no choice.

110
00:08:28,430 --> 00:08:29,440
Here.

111
00:08:29,980 --> 00:08:32,030
It's all yours. I'm out of this.

112
00:08:32,230 --> 00:08:33,620
Wait.

113
00:08:33,620 --> 00:08:34,910
A keycard?

114
00:08:35,060 --> 00:08:37,160
Yeah, it's just a simple keycard.

115
00:08:37,470 --> 00:08:39,670
The kind we use to get in and out of the building.

116
00:08:39,980 --> 00:08:40,790
I don't get it.

117
00:08:40,790 --> 00:08:44,300
Normally, the magnetic stripe has just an access code on it.

118
00:08:44,300 --> 00:08:46,670
But the stripe can hold a ton of data.

119
00:08:46,780 --> 00:08:48,660
On this one, I found a file

120
00:08:48,660 --> 00:08:50,400
filled with references to Palmer.

121
00:08:50,540 --> 00:08:51,920
What's the point?

122
00:08:52,000 --> 00:08:54,020
To smuggle confidential information.

123
00:08:54,620 --> 00:08:58,270
These get in and out of restricted areas without any scrutiny.

124
00:09:02,010 --> 00:09:04,070
I need you to be reachable throughout the day.

125
00:09:04,520 --> 00:09:06,170
You said after tonight I'm done.

126
00:09:06,280 --> 00:09:08,030
I can't help it, Scott.

127
00:09:08,260 --> 00:09:11,830
Until we defuse this situation, I need to be able to find you.

128
00:09:12,000 --> 00:09:15,250
I find out there's an agency conspiracy to kill David Palmer.

129
00:09:15,280 --> 00:09:17,350
The moment I realized what I stumbled onto,

130
00:09:17,350 --> 00:09:20,200
I put my wife and kid on a plane.

131
00:09:20,430 --> 00:09:22,070
I couldn't even tell them why.

132
00:09:23,330 --> 00:09:25,670
I've been with the Agency long enough to know what I'm dealing with.

133
00:09:25,670 --> 00:09:27,300
It's your thing now. I'm out.

134
00:09:27,300 --> 00:09:28,120
Scott.

135
00:09:28,830 --> 00:09:31,610
What you did took a lot of courage.

136
00:09:32,130 --> 00:09:35,960
I'm asking you to hang in there with me a little longer.

137
00:09:35,960 --> 00:09:37,910
I did my part. Get someone else.

138
00:09:49,040 --> 00:09:50,790
There is no one else.

139
00:09:57,320 --> 00:09:59,200
You got me for another 24 hours.

140
00:10:00,020 --> 00:10:01,530
Then I'm joining my family.

141
00:10:12,060 --> 00:10:13,970
Yes, I know Palmer gets a lot of death threats,

142
00:10:13,970 --> 00:10:15,560
but this one's got some weight.

143
00:10:15,560 --> 00:10:17,360
We're overloaded. We'll deal with it later.

144
00:10:17,360 --> 00:10:19,640
No, you're gonna have to make some adjustments in your schedule.

145
00:10:19,640 --> 00:10:21,320
You're gonna have to notify his advance team,

146
00:10:21,320 --> 00:10:23,060
tighten up security on your end.

147
00:10:23,060 --> 00:10:25,050
I understand...

148
00:10:25,050 --> 00:10:27,310
Look, I've gotta go. I'll update you in an hour.

149
00:10:27,320 --> 00:10:29,910
- You'll update-- One hour? - Yes. Fine.

150
00:10:33,620 --> 00:10:34,340
Teri?

151
00:10:34,340 --> 00:10:36,430
Jack, I need you.

152
00:10:36,430 --> 00:10:37,750
- Richard? - Yeah.

153
00:10:38,910 --> 00:10:41,270
I'm at 2350 Dunlop Plaza,

154
00:10:41,270 --> 00:10:42,780
I got two shooters trying to hit me...

155
00:10:42,780 --> 00:10:43,870
...and an agent down.

156
00:10:43,870 --> 00:10:44,910
Richard, what's going on?

157
00:10:45,290 --> 00:10:48,710
I've got hard information on who is behind the Palmer hit.

158
00:10:48,730 --> 00:10:50,350
Isley can get there before me.

159
00:10:50,580 --> 00:10:52,930
- He's in the area. - No, don't call anyone.

160
00:10:53,180 --> 00:10:55,260
We still don't know who we can trust.

161
00:10:55,660 --> 00:10:58,110
Just get me out of here.

162
00:10:58,220 --> 00:11:00,940
- I'll be there in 10 minutes. - I'll be on the roof.

163
00:11:02,570 --> 00:11:03,570
Richard?

164
00:11:04,260 --> 00:11:05,290
Richard?

165
00:11:23,320 --> 00:11:24,050
Hello?

166
00:11:24,050 --> 00:11:26,310
Hey, It's me. What's going on? Is Kim at the store?

167
00:11:26,560 --> 00:11:27,650
No, she's not here.

168
00:11:28,110 --> 00:11:29,800
I thought you said you saw their car.

169
00:11:29,800 --> 00:11:32,070
We think she left with the boys.

170
00:11:32,140 --> 00:11:34,640
This guy you're with, York...

171
00:11:34,950 --> 00:11:36,450
...does he know either of these boys?

172
00:11:36,450 --> 00:11:38,800
No, but one of them, Dan, works here.

173
00:11:39,420 --> 00:11:42,110
I'm starting to worry a little bit, can't you get over here?

174
00:11:42,550 --> 00:11:44,880
I can't. Not right now. I don't have time to explain,

175
00:11:44,880 --> 00:11:47,190
but some bad things are happening tonight.

176
00:11:47,190 --> 00:11:49,750
Our daughter's missing. I think that's bad, don't you?

177
00:11:49,850 --> 00:11:52,430
Teri, she's not missing, she's partying.

178
00:11:52,520 --> 00:11:54,250
Kim's smart enough to know her limits.

179
00:11:54,250 --> 00:11:56,090
Yeah? Maybe you should come over here

180
00:11:56,090 --> 00:11:58,190
and see what those limits are, Jack.

181
00:11:59,890 --> 00:12:01,260
What's that supposed to mean?

182
00:12:01,500 --> 00:12:02,340
Nothing.

183
00:12:02,740 --> 00:12:05,240
We're going to wait here for them to come back for the car.

184
00:12:05,890 --> 00:12:08,330
Call me when you're done with your emergency, okay?

185
00:12:08,850 --> 00:12:10,660
I will, I'm sorry, okay?

186
00:12:10,980 --> 00:12:12,490
I'll call you as soon as I can.

187
00:12:13,630 --> 00:12:14,530
Bye.

188
00:12:22,820 --> 00:12:26,340
Look, I know it seems like we're these really bad guys

189
00:12:26,490 --> 00:12:28,260
but we're cool, I swear.

190
00:12:28,770 --> 00:12:30,450
There's just some stuff we got to do.

191
00:12:30,530 --> 00:12:32,640
Just go along with it, and you guys won't get hurt.

192
00:12:32,840 --> 00:12:34,970
I don't even know what you want me to go along with.

193
00:12:35,160 --> 00:12:37,760
Is this some sort of fraternity stunt or something?

194
00:12:38,870 --> 00:12:40,790
Yeah. Something like that.

195
00:12:40,790 --> 00:12:43,950
Fine. Whatever. I'll tell your friends whatever you want me to.

196
00:12:44,060 --> 00:12:45,290
Just let us go.

197
00:12:45,660 --> 00:12:46,980
It's not that simple.

198
00:12:47,520 --> 00:12:49,100
- These people... - What people?

199
00:12:56,230 --> 00:12:58,000
Dan, pull over. She's choking.

200
00:13:00,480 --> 00:13:03,410
- She's not breathing, you idiot! - I don't care.

201
00:13:10,460 --> 00:13:12,440
- Stop. - Get back!

202
00:13:19,520 --> 00:13:20,740
Don't be a moron!

203
00:13:26,760 --> 00:13:28,040
Don't be a bitch.

204
00:13:43,540 --> 00:13:47,070
Brush fires set off by the wreckage are making the prospect

205
00:13:47,070 --> 00:13:48,130
of locating possible

206
00:13:48,130 --> 00:13:52,290
survivors of Flight 221 virtually impossible.

207
00:14:00,390 --> 00:14:02,360
- Has Carl called yet? - No, not yet.

208
00:14:02,960 --> 00:14:04,970
- Let me know as soon as he does. - Okay.

209
00:14:16,770 --> 00:14:18,120
It's twenty after one.

210
00:14:18,390 --> 00:14:20,220
Weren't the kids supposed to be back by now?

211
00:14:20,430 --> 00:14:23,520
They stopped to get pizza after the rally.

212
00:14:24,510 --> 00:14:26,180
- You seen this? - Yeah.

213
00:14:30,420 --> 00:14:31,330
It's horrible.

214
00:14:35,610 --> 00:14:39,860
Look. I'm sorry I walked away before.

215
00:14:39,860 --> 00:14:43,340
What did Maureen Kingsley say to you on the phone?

216
00:14:43,700 --> 00:14:45,240
It's nothing serious.

217
00:14:45,760 --> 00:14:48,070
I'm overreacting to everything right now.

218
00:14:51,090 --> 00:14:54,340
Today is going to be the second most important day of my life.

219
00:14:55,950 --> 00:14:58,040
And what would the first one be?

220
00:14:59,700 --> 00:15:00,950
I think you know.

221
00:15:02,390 --> 00:15:04,930
I still like to hear you say it.

222
00:15:06,520 --> 00:15:07,400
All right.

223
00:15:10,190 --> 00:15:12,250
The most important day of my life

224
00:15:16,590 --> 00:15:17,240
was when I hit the

225
00:15:17,240 --> 00:15:19,930
game-winning three against DePaul at the Final Four.

226
00:15:19,930 --> 00:15:22,240
You just lost my vote, Senator.

227
00:15:22,860 --> 00:15:26,200
Good night. Don't let this get to you.

228
00:15:32,540 --> 00:15:33,490
Thanks, honey.

229
00:15:34,000 --> 00:15:34,700
Good night.

230
00:15:56,800 --> 00:15:57,820
We already know about that.

231
00:15:57,820 --> 00:15:59,720
We've got another way around security.

232
00:15:59,720 --> 00:16:02,980
— I can explain. - No, I don't want an explanation.

233
00:16:02,980 --> 00:16:05,910
I just want him in place. Hold on.

234
00:16:07,540 --> 00:16:10,090
Gaines. Yeah, I'm finishing up with him right now.

235
00:16:10,090 --> 00:16:12,740
All right, get back to me.

236
00:16:12,740 --> 00:16:13,750
Hey, Mandy.

237
00:16:15,270 --> 00:16:16,700
Good. Everything put together?

238
00:16:16,700 --> 00:16:17,940
It is. Just get back to me.

239
00:16:17,950 --> 00:16:18,890
I'll get back to you.

240
00:16:21,820 --> 00:16:23,700
- You want something to drink? - No, thanks.

241
00:16:25,740 --> 00:16:28,000
They'll be ready to go by the time you get there.

242
00:16:28,000 --> 00:16:28,780
Leave now.

243
00:16:38,080 --> 00:16:39,080
It's all there.

244
00:16:45,700 --> 00:16:48,610
- What are you doing this summer? - Not interested.

245
00:16:49,470 --> 00:16:51,520
- You haven't heard my offer. - I don't care.

246
00:16:51,520 --> 00:16:54,620
I'm going to disappear for a while. Lay low.

247
00:16:56,510 --> 00:16:58,030
So when do I get the ID?

248
00:17:03,250 --> 00:17:04,220
Soon.

249
00:17:17,170 --> 00:17:17,950
Myers.

250
00:17:18,190 --> 00:17:21,000
Nina, it's Jack. Is this a secure line?

251
00:17:21,240 --> 00:17:22,650
No, you want me to transfer it?

252
00:17:22,670 --> 00:17:24,450
No time. I need an entry code.

253
00:17:24,790 --> 00:17:26,580
Entry code? Where are you?

254
00:17:27,200 --> 00:17:28,500
I needed to take care of something.

255
00:17:28,500 --> 00:17:30,070
Why didn't you check out with me?

256
00:17:30,170 --> 00:17:32,260
Nina, just get me the code, okay?

257
00:17:33,310 --> 00:17:36,570
2350 Dunlop Plaza, the north parking garage.

258
00:17:42,060 --> 00:17:43,270
Dunlop?

259
00:17:44,580 --> 00:17:45,480
Got it.

260
00:17:45,620 --> 00:17:47,930
9-1-3-6-7-star.

261
00:17:50,420 --> 00:17:51,250
I'm in.

262
00:17:51,690 --> 00:17:52,550
Jack.

269
00:19:23,240 --> 00:19:24,010
Jack.

270
00:19:26,160 --> 00:19:28,530
- Richard, are you okay? - I'm fine.

271
00:19:29,100 --> 00:19:30,370
You said there were two shooters.

272
00:19:30,370 --> 00:19:31,820
At least. Maybe three.

273
00:19:31,820 --> 00:19:32,700
They look like they were ours?

274
00:19:32,700 --> 00:19:33,570
I couldn't tell.

275
00:19:34,750 --> 00:19:36,540
How high does this conspiracy go?

276
00:19:36,540 --> 00:19:38,000
I don't know yet, Jack.

277
00:19:38,290 --> 00:19:40,500
- Did you see anyone downstairs? - No one.

278
00:19:41,030 --> 00:19:42,980
- Is this the only way out? - This is it.

279
00:19:43,410 --> 00:19:44,220
Okay.

280
00:20:05,340 --> 00:20:07,000
- I'm sorry. - No, no, no no.

281
00:20:07,100 --> 00:20:09,920
Come here. Come here.

282
00:20:17,160 --> 00:20:20,100
You look just like Martin Belkin.

283
00:20:22,170 --> 00:20:23,350
How'd they do that?

284
00:20:24,660 --> 00:20:26,020
Plastic surgery.

285
00:20:27,500 --> 00:20:28,930
That's amazing.

286
00:20:30,810 --> 00:20:32,850
You're going to kill David Palmer?

287
00:20:36,290 --> 00:20:37,300
Hey, where's Jack?

288
00:20:37,800 --> 00:20:38,590
I don't know.

289
00:20:40,190 --> 00:20:41,540
I thought you were on the phone with him.

290
00:20:42,220 --> 00:20:43,830
No, that was Division.

291
00:20:43,830 --> 00:20:44,590
Really?

292
00:20:48,600 --> 00:20:51,560
This is a military organization. There's a chain of command.

293
00:20:51,560 --> 00:20:52,760
I am your superior. I tell you

294
00:20:52,760 --> 00:20:55,300
what I want and you don't question it, got it?

295
00:20:56,290 --> 00:20:58,560
All right. I can accept that.

296
00:20:58,560 --> 00:20:59,410
Good.

297
00:21:00,160 --> 00:21:01,790
There's something you got to deal with.

298
00:21:01,790 --> 00:21:02,680
Yeah? What?

299
00:21:03,200 --> 00:21:05,420
You can boss me around all you want here

300
00:21:05,980 --> 00:21:07,780
but when you and I punch out,

301
00:21:08,800 --> 00:21:10,090
we're something else.

302
00:21:11,020 --> 00:21:11,750
Okay?

303
00:21:14,420 --> 00:21:15,660
Okay, Tony.

304
00:21:17,760 --> 00:21:18,490
Okay.

305
00:21:45,390 --> 00:21:47,660
Okay, we're clear. Give me your tie.

306
00:21:47,660 --> 00:21:48,460
I want to fix this.

307
00:21:54,730 --> 00:21:55,720
Sorry.

308
00:22:08,500 --> 00:22:10,350
I should've been more careful.

309
00:22:10,350 --> 00:22:12,160
Come on, they could have been following Baylor.

310
00:22:12,260 --> 00:22:13,480
This was my fault.

311
00:22:14,330 --> 00:22:15,400
I set it up wrong.

312
00:22:16,620 --> 00:22:18,060
We were sitting ducks.

313
00:22:22,550 --> 00:22:24,440
I'm sorry to put you through this, Jack.

314
00:22:24,870 --> 00:22:26,640
Don't you ever say that to me.

315
00:22:27,450 --> 00:22:28,710
You of all people.

316
00:22:29,480 --> 00:22:30,930
I owe you my life.

317
00:22:35,280 --> 00:22:36,230
Across the mezzanine,

318
00:22:36,230 --> 00:22:38,390
there’s a corridor that leads to a service exit.

319
00:22:38,580 --> 00:22:40,430
We're gonna take that straight to the street.

320
00:22:40,510 --> 00:22:43,430
My car is right there. You okay?

321
00:22:43,700 --> 00:22:45,090
Good. Let's get out of here.

322
00:23:22,710 --> 00:23:23,690
Take the wall.

323
00:25:03,650 --> 00:25:04,500
Jack!

324
00:25:19,670 --> 00:25:21,690
We got to find out who sent these guys.

325
00:25:27,300 --> 00:25:28,490
I'm gonna go ID him.

326
00:26:45,200 --> 00:26:46,110
It's okay.

327
00:27:07,920 --> 00:27:09,450
What the hell is this supposed to be?

328
00:27:10,740 --> 00:27:11,930
Give him the ID.

329
00:27:15,690 --> 00:27:16,880
It's okay.

330
00:27:17,360 --> 00:27:19,620
This'll be better for both of us. I figured it out.

331
00:27:19,620 --> 00:27:22,340
No, you don't figure anything out. This is not your play.

332
00:27:22,340 --> 00:27:23,920
Now, where is the damn ID?

333
00:27:24,300 --> 00:27:25,430
It is my play...

334
00:27:26,390 --> 00:27:29,810
...since I'm the only one who knows where the damn ID is.

335
00:27:38,340 --> 00:27:39,390
Go ahead.

336
00:28:11,640 --> 00:28:13,620
I didn't find anything useful in the back.

337
00:28:15,020 --> 00:28:16,430
Work schedule. Look.

338
00:28:16,430 --> 00:28:18,400
Dan-- Tuesday, Wednesday and Friday.

339
00:28:18,560 --> 00:28:20,010
Great. Is there a contact number?

340
00:28:20,010 --> 00:28:22,300
No. We can't get in the office, it's locked.

341
00:28:22,300 --> 00:28:24,180
My husband might be able to help us.

342
00:28:24,470 --> 00:28:26,250
How would he be able to do that?

343
00:28:26,520 --> 00:28:28,200
This is Jack Bauer. Leave a message.

344
00:28:28,200 --> 00:28:29,280
He turned his cell phone off.

345
00:28:30,270 --> 00:28:32,350
How would your husband be able to help?

346
00:28:32,810 --> 00:28:35,940
He works for the government, has access to things. Hang on.

347
00:28:38,480 --> 00:28:39,670
CTU, Nina Myers.

348
00:28:39,850 --> 00:28:42,010
Hi, Nina, it's Teri Bauer.

349
00:28:42,010 --> 00:28:42,890
Is Jack there?

350
00:28:44,350 --> 00:28:46,090
Teri, Jack's not here.

351
00:28:46,160 --> 00:28:48,980
I know, but he turned his phone off. I wonder if you could help me.

352
00:28:48,980 --> 00:28:50,090
Sure, what do you need?

353
00:28:50,660 --> 00:28:52,060
I need the name and number of

354
00:28:52,060 --> 00:28:54,400
the owner of a furniture store in the Valley...

355
00:28:54,400 --> 00:28:57,080
...in Van Nuys, uh, Paladio's Furniture.

356
00:28:57,600 --> 00:28:58,760
That's not something I should do.

357
00:28:58,760 --> 00:29:00,600
Can I wait 'til I talk to Jack about it?

358
00:29:00,760 --> 00:29:02,810
No, not really, um...

359
00:29:03,460 --> 00:29:04,740
Nina, it's Kim.

360
00:29:04,930 --> 00:29:06,370
She took off with some kids I don't know.

361
00:29:06,370 --> 00:29:08,580
One of the boys, Dan, works here.

362
00:29:08,580 --> 00:29:10,150
I was hoping to contact the owner.

363
00:29:12,350 --> 00:29:13,960
All right, um...

364
00:29:14,790 --> 00:29:16,290
Give me a couple of minutes, I'll see what I can do.

365
00:29:16,290 --> 00:29:17,390
What's your cell number?

366
00:29:23,120 --> 00:29:24,090
There you are.

367
00:29:24,730 --> 00:29:26,500
Heard you guys had quite a turnout tonight.

368
00:29:26,500 --> 00:29:28,440
Yeah, it was pretty insane.

369
00:29:28,440 --> 00:29:29,260
I thought I heard the sound

370
00:29:29,260 --> 00:29:31,520
of the young and the reckless generation.

371
00:29:32,030 --> 00:29:34,740
Dad, what are you doing up? - How you doing?

372
00:29:34,740 --> 00:29:35,410
Hey, Dad.

373
00:29:35,560 --> 00:29:37,170
Not enough hours in the day.

374
00:29:37,300 --> 00:29:38,490
How did it go?

375
00:29:38,630 --> 00:29:39,890
Mom, it was huge.

376
00:29:39,890 --> 00:29:41,150
I wish you could've been there.

377
00:29:41,150 --> 00:29:42,910
I wish I could have been there, too.

378
00:29:42,910 --> 00:29:45,320
I'm dead. See you guys in the morning.

379
00:29:45,510 --> 00:29:47,250
Okay, good night sweetie.

380
00:29:47,250 --> 00:29:48,450
Make sure you get some good rest

381
00:29:48,450 --> 00:29:50,250
because they're going to wake you up early.

382
00:29:50,360 --> 00:29:52,390
I will. Good night.

383
00:29:52,570 --> 00:29:53,490
I love you, honey.

384
00:29:56,130 --> 00:29:58,910
- So how was it? - Ah, dad, it was unbelievable.

385
00:29:58,910 --> 00:30:01,840
The chancellor introduces me, right? I'm totally killing.

386
00:30:02,220 --> 00:30:03,310
And just as I'm finishing,

387
00:30:03,630 --> 00:30:05,600
Green Day starts to play "Time of Your Life."

388
00:30:05,920 --> 00:30:07,970
- Mom, it was huge. - Hold on.

389
00:30:07,970 --> 00:30:10,430
The kids were going insane. Girls were screaming....

390
00:30:12,620 --> 00:30:13,400
Carl?

391
00:30:14,270 --> 00:30:15,180
What's the problem?

392
00:30:15,180 --> 00:30:17,100
I got a call tonight from Maureen Kingsley.

393
00:30:17,380 --> 00:30:18,250
Yeah, so what?

394
00:30:18,600 --> 00:30:20,360
I don't want to talk about it over the phone.

395
00:30:20,470 --> 00:30:22,120
Okay, I'll come by in the morning.

396
00:30:22,120 --> 00:30:25,340
No. We need to take care of this now.

397
00:30:29,150 --> 00:30:30,970
It's hard to know with teenage girls

398
00:30:30,970 --> 00:30:33,200
if they're angry at you or just angry.

399
00:30:33,940 --> 00:30:34,650
I know.

400
00:30:35,860 --> 00:30:38,730
I did feel guilty, though, when Jack and I separated.

401
00:30:39,850 --> 00:30:41,880
Separated? I didn't know.

402
00:30:42,720 --> 00:30:44,090
We're back together.

403
00:30:44,440 --> 00:30:45,640
I admire that.

404
00:30:45,940 --> 00:30:47,760
Trying to work through the problems together.

405
00:30:48,980 --> 00:30:52,560
My ex left and never looked back. Went home to Australia.

406
00:30:54,360 --> 00:30:58,530
She hasn't spoken with Janet or me for almost 10 years.

407
00:30:59,370 --> 00:31:00,900
I'm really sorry, Alan.

408
00:31:12,820 --> 00:31:14,360
- Hello? - Teri, I got it.

409
00:31:14,360 --> 00:31:16,310
Oh, great. Hang on a second.

410
00:31:17,160 --> 00:31:20,310
All right, go ahead.

411
00:31:20,420 --> 00:31:24,270
Nina, that's great. Thank you so much. I really appreciate it.

412
00:31:24,270 --> 00:31:26,080
Okay, 'bye.

413
00:31:26,760 --> 00:31:28,250
Owner's name and phone number.

414
00:31:30,880 --> 00:31:33,580
You have reached the Nowrastehs. Please leave a message.

415
00:31:33,580 --> 00:31:34,640
Is anybody home?

416
00:31:34,640 --> 00:31:37,210
Mr. Nowrasteh, if you're there, please pick up.

417
00:31:37,710 --> 00:31:38,670
My daughter is out with

418
00:31:38,670 --> 00:31:41,130
one of the boys who works at your store, Dan.

419
00:31:41,130 --> 00:31:42,470
I need to talk to you right away.

420
00:31:42,470 --> 00:31:43,980
I'm here in your store right now.

421
00:31:43,980 --> 00:31:44,980
Please call me.

422
00:31:45,190 --> 00:31:47,500
My name is Teri, and my number is....

423
00:31:47,500 --> 00:31:48,430
He said, "Tell your dad to

424
00:31:48,430 --> 00:31:51,270
reserve the Lincoln Bedroom for us when we tour the east coast."

425
00:31:51,270 --> 00:31:52,650
I'll bet he did.

426
00:31:53,580 --> 00:31:54,740
Hello, Mrs. Palmer.

427
00:31:54,740 --> 00:31:57,060
I'm Aaron Pierce, Secret Service.

428
00:31:59,470 --> 00:32:00,910
Is there a problem?

429
00:32:01,470 --> 00:32:03,270
I need to speak with the Senator.

430
00:32:04,580 --> 00:32:06,620
All right, I'll go get him for you.

431
00:32:14,260 --> 00:32:15,340
David?

432
00:32:16,960 --> 00:32:18,240
Where is he, Patty?

433
00:32:18,590 --> 00:32:20,600
I don't know. I thought he was in there.

434
00:32:20,900 --> 00:32:24,580
Palmer has left the suite. He's exposed. Find him.

435
00:32:24,580 --> 00:32:24,820
Tell me what's going on?

436
00:32:24,830 --> 00:32:27,920
If he left in one of the vehicles, it'll show up on our GPS.

437
00:32:27,920 --> 00:32:29,330
Would you tell me what's going on?

438
00:32:29,830 --> 00:32:30,750
We've been told to add

439
00:32:30,760 --> 00:32:32,880
another layer of security around your husband.

440
00:32:32,880 --> 00:32:33,540
Why?

441
00:32:34,780 --> 00:32:36,220
We have a very high confidence

442
00:32:36,220 --> 00:32:39,070
that there will be an attempt on his life sometime today.

443
00:33:50,490 --> 00:33:52,740
- Stay close, Richard. - I'm right behind you.

444
00:34:01,040 --> 00:34:02,350
I'm going to get you out of here.

445
00:34:04,800 --> 00:34:05,610
Jack....

446
00:34:09,500 --> 00:34:11,450
Jack, listen to me.

447
00:34:12,470 --> 00:34:15,340
Take this card and give it to Jamey.

448
00:34:15,670 --> 00:34:17,930
Baylor said that we could trust her.

449
00:34:17,930 --> 00:34:20,150
Richard, don't move. You'll draw fire.

450
00:34:20,150 --> 00:34:24,420
Take the card, give it to Jamey, she'll match it to a computer.

451
00:34:24,930 --> 00:34:28,590
Find the computer, you've got the dirty agent

452
00:34:29,180 --> 00:34:30,430
Richard!

453
00:35:41,440 --> 00:35:42,060
Farrell.

454
00:35:42,110 --> 00:35:43,230
Jamey, it's me.

455
00:35:43,540 --> 00:35:44,360
What do you need?

456
00:35:44,650 --> 00:35:47,850
Two agency personnel were killed tonight at 2350 Dunlop Plaza.

457
00:35:47,850 --> 00:35:50,320
I need you to phone Division, get their bodies picked up.

458
00:35:50,420 --> 00:35:52,370
- Okay. - That's not all.

459
00:35:52,770 --> 00:35:55,290
You know the key cards we use to get in and out of Division?

460
00:35:55,290 --> 00:35:57,120
- Yeah? - I've got one.

461
00:35:57,120 --> 00:35:58,650
I need you to pull some data off it for me.

462
00:35:58,650 --> 00:36:00,640
Do you have anything that can read it?

463
00:36:01,120 --> 00:36:03,820
Yeah, but if you're in your car you can just send it to me now.

464
00:36:04,420 --> 00:36:07,010
- How? - Use your mobile scanner.

465
00:36:07,210 --> 00:36:09,180
Switch it from optical to magnetic.

466
00:36:09,790 --> 00:36:10,570
Hold on.

472
00:36:28,000 --> 00:36:29,510
I'm sending this to you directly.

474
00:36:29,700 --> 00:36:33,140
You should be able to trace this to the person who encoded it.

475
00:36:33,170 --> 00:36:35,660
Yeah, I can match the electronic signature.

476
00:36:35,660 --> 00:36:36,560
Good, do it.

477
00:36:52,530 --> 00:36:53,340
Come on.

478
00:36:54,010 --> 00:36:55,200
What are you going to do to me?

479
00:36:55,200 --> 00:36:56,240
Take you to the prom.

480
00:36:58,770 --> 00:36:59,870
Come on, get out.

481
00:36:59,870 --> 00:37:01,330
Don't worry, it's going to be okay.

482
00:37:01,330 --> 00:37:03,820
Just tell her what you want her to do and then she'll do it.

483
00:37:11,110 --> 00:37:12,440
I said, "Get out!"

484
00:37:19,760 --> 00:37:21,010
It's time to call mommy.

485
00:37:21,890 --> 00:37:24,140
Tell her you're ok, you're at a party,

486
00:37:24,140 --> 00:37:26,270
you're sorry and you'll see her in a couple hours.

487
00:37:26,270 --> 00:37:27,230
Go to hell!

488
00:37:28,730 --> 00:37:30,540
Gaines said not to hurt her, remember?

489
00:37:34,520 --> 00:37:35,160
Fine.

490
00:37:48,990 --> 00:37:50,310
Call your mom!

491
00:38:00,730 --> 00:38:01,690
Hello?

492
00:38:02,020 --> 00:38:02,820
Mom?

493
00:38:03,100 --> 00:38:04,310
Kim, is that you?

494
00:38:05,300 --> 00:38:06,120
Hello?

495
00:38:06,120 --> 00:38:06,890
Mom?

496
00:38:07,940 --> 00:38:09,150
Honey, where are you?

497
00:38:09,490 --> 00:38:11,490
- I'm at a party. - What?

498
00:38:11,880 --> 00:38:13,290
I'm at a party.

499
00:38:13,670 --> 00:38:15,480
- With Janet York, right? - Yeah.

500
00:38:15,480 --> 00:38:16,780
How did you know that?

501
00:38:17,230 --> 00:38:19,290
I'm standing here with her dad.

502
00:38:20,590 --> 00:38:22,260
Do you have any idea how we worried about you?

503
00:38:22,260 --> 00:38:23,170
Can I talk to Janet?

504
00:38:23,230 --> 00:38:25,850
Honey listen, Janet's dad wants to talk to her.

505
00:38:25,860 --> 00:38:27,090
She went for a walk.

506
00:38:27,160 --> 00:38:30,540
- I will tell her to call when she gets back. - She went for a walk.

507
00:38:30,540 --> 00:38:33,840
We're okay and I'm really sorry I did this, I mean it.

508
00:38:33,840 --> 00:38:35,840
I'll be home as soon as I get a ride back.

509
00:38:35,840 --> 00:38:37,960
Honey you're not going to wait for a ride back.

510
00:38:37,960 --> 00:38:39,720
We'll come pick you up. Where are you?

511
00:38:40,280 --> 00:38:42,080
I don't even know how we got here.

512
00:38:42,780 --> 00:38:44,550
Kim?

513
00:38:44,560 --> 00:38:46,640
Honey, this is not the night you want to shine me on.

514
00:38:46,640 --> 00:38:48,900
- I promise you! - Mom, I got to go.

515
00:38:48,900 --> 00:38:49,410
Kim.

516
00:38:49,410 --> 00:38:51,340
Mom, I love you.

517
00:38:54,760 --> 00:38:55,760
"I love you."

518
00:38:57,570 --> 00:38:58,670
Nice touch.

519
00:39:00,150 --> 00:39:02,190
- Get in the van. - What happened?

520
00:39:02,580 --> 00:39:03,690
I can't believe it.

521
00:39:04,950 --> 00:39:05,760
She's at this party.

522
00:39:05,760 --> 00:39:08,680
She said she was sorry and that she'd be back.

523
00:39:08,840 --> 00:39:11,040
- And what about Janet? - She's fine.

524
00:39:15,420 --> 00:39:16,310
What's wrong?

525
00:39:17,960 --> 00:39:19,360
She said, "I love you."

526
00:39:20,870 --> 00:39:22,420
She never says that.

527
00:39:29,790 --> 00:39:32,100
Ok, Jack, I got a match on the card you sent me.

528
00:39:32,340 --> 00:39:33,640
Need a confidence on this?

529
00:39:33,640 --> 00:39:35,750
Yes, my eyes only, send it.

534
00:39:52,000 --> 00:39:53,550
- Thanks, Jamey. - You got it.

