2
00:00:12,390 --> 00:00:13,430
Right now,

3
00:00:13,440 --> 00:00:17,140
terrorists are plotting to assassinate a presidential candidate.

6
00:00:17,960 --> 00:00:20,350
My wife and daughter have been kidnapped.

7
00:00:21,270 --> 00:00:24,310
And people that I work with may be involved in both.

8
00:00:25,160 --> 00:00:27,210
I'm Federal Agent Jack Bauer.

9
00:00:27,550 --> 00:00:30,790
This, is the longest day of my life.

12
00:00:40,470 --> 00:00:45,470
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

13
00:00:40,470 --> 00:00:45,470
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

14
00:00:40,470 --> 00:00:45,470
{\an5}{\pos(145,252)}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

15
00:00:40,970 --> 00:00:45,470
{\pos(67,248)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

16
00:00:40,970 --> 00:00:45,470
{\pos(67,248)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

17
00:00:40,970 --> 00:00:45,470
{\pos(58,238)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

18
00:00:40,970 --> 00:00:45,470
{\pos(84,248)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

21
00:00:46,690 --> 00:01:11,690
{\an9}m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

22
00:00:46,190 --> 00:01:11,690
{\an2}{\pos(26,248)}m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

28
00:00:56,050 --> 00:00:57,310
Take the next exit.

29
00:00:57,310 --> 00:01:00,630
- Plesarita Canyon Road? - Yeah.

30
00:01:01,420 --> 00:01:02,890
How much further is this place?

31
00:01:02,890 --> 00:01:05,830
I told you I'd take you to your family, and I will.

32
00:01:05,830 --> 00:01:07,070
That was the deal.

33
00:01:07,070 --> 00:01:09,580
The deal is you'd better hope my wife and daughter are still alive.

34
00:01:09,580 --> 00:01:11,070
That's the deal.

35
00:01:20,620 --> 00:01:23,950
I'm sure my being here has been a big adjustment.

36
00:01:24,010 --> 00:01:27,980
I appreciate the hard work and long hours you're all putting in.

37
00:01:28,930 --> 00:01:30,120
There's a high probability

38
00:01:30,120 --> 00:01:32,290
that Senator Palmer is still in danger,

39
00:01:32,290 --> 00:01:34,930
but we are making progress on several fronts.

40
00:01:51,640 --> 00:01:55,110
Our most promising lead continues to be Jack Bauer.

41
00:01:55,220 --> 00:01:56,950
Local and federal law enforcement

42
00:01:56,950 --> 00:01:59,070
have made finding him a priority.

43
00:02:00,080 --> 00:02:01,430
We're also trying to locate

44
00:02:01,430 --> 00:02:03,570
the man who impersonated a photographer

45
00:02:03,570 --> 00:02:05,130
at the Senator's appearance this morning.

46
00:02:05,130 --> 00:02:07,450
This man may have been involved with Bauer.

47
00:02:07,890 --> 00:02:09,880
I've told the agencies we're working with

48
00:02:09,880 --> 00:02:13,140
that they can expect full cooperation from all of us.

49
00:02:15,280 --> 00:02:17,810
Hopefully we can repair some of the damage

50
00:02:17,810 --> 00:02:20,130
caused by Bauer's recent actions.

51
00:02:20,720 --> 00:02:22,160
Thank you. That's all.

52
00:02:30,310 --> 00:02:32,180
- Bauer. - Jack.

53
00:02:32,360 --> 00:02:34,010
You were right. Kevin Carroll showed up.

54
00:02:34,020 --> 00:02:36,140
He gave us the information we've been looking for.

55
00:02:36,140 --> 00:02:38,610
I'm on my way to where Teri and Kim are being held now.

56
00:02:39,260 --> 00:02:40,240
Where?

57
00:02:40,590 --> 00:02:41,890
Somewhere in the North Valley,

58
00:02:41,890 --> 00:02:44,370
east of the 5, between Tampa and Reseda.

59
00:02:44,370 --> 00:02:46,500
I'm coming up on some orange groves now.

60
00:02:46,500 --> 00:02:47,480
Look, I need you to activate

61
00:02:47,480 --> 00:02:49,930
the GPS function on the Palm Pilot that you sent me.

62
00:02:49,930 --> 00:02:52,970
I need satellite photos so that I can see what I'm going into.

63
00:02:53,010 --> 00:02:54,350
Make sure that they're hi-res.

64
00:02:54,360 --> 00:02:56,850
I need be able to identify structures and personnel.

65
00:02:56,850 --> 00:02:59,690
Okay, I'm gonna need time to download off the satellite.

66
00:02:59,720 --> 00:03:01,070
It won't be a fresh image.

67
00:03:01,070 --> 00:03:03,120
Alright, give me what you can. I'll wait.

68
00:03:03,480 --> 00:03:04,940
- Jack? - What?

69
00:03:05,840 --> 00:03:09,590
Green... she's still squeezing everyone here to bring you in.

70
00:03:10,780 --> 00:03:14,250
I will turn myself in as soon as I know my family is safe.

71
00:03:15,120 --> 00:03:16,710
She thinks I've been in contact with you.

72
00:03:16,710 --> 00:03:18,490
Deny it. I'll back you up as soon as I can.

73
00:03:18,490 --> 00:03:20,610
Nina look, I know you put yourself on the line here.

74
00:03:20,610 --> 00:03:23,230
No one's twisting my arm. I've got to go.

75
00:03:27,670 --> 00:03:28,780
Excuse me.

76
00:03:31,390 --> 00:03:32,610
- Was that Jack? - Yeah.

77
00:03:32,610 --> 00:03:34,220
- Where is he? - He's in the North Valley.

78
00:03:34,220 --> 00:03:36,020
He's closing in on Teri and Kim.

79
00:03:36,020 --> 00:03:37,430
You gonna tell Green about this?

80
00:03:37,430 --> 00:03:39,070
Not until he gets them out.

81
00:03:39,890 --> 00:03:41,130
What if he can't?

82
00:03:42,930 --> 00:03:44,750
I'm gonna have to live with my mistake.

83
00:03:45,830 --> 00:03:49,250
Tony, I appreciate you're looking the other way on this,

84
00:03:49,310 --> 00:03:51,910
but don't feel like you gotta help me cover for Jack anymore.

85
00:03:52,320 --> 00:03:53,830
I'm not doing this for Jack.

86
00:04:01,730 --> 00:04:03,950
I'll have that confirmed in five minutes.

87
00:04:04,230 --> 00:04:05,960
It will be downloaded to your computer.

88
00:04:26,970 --> 00:04:30,980
Kimberly, he tried to kill us.

89
00:04:32,300 --> 00:04:33,770
I didn't have a choice.

90
00:04:34,680 --> 00:04:36,960
Taking a person's life, believe me,

91
00:04:38,370 --> 00:04:39,260
I feel sick.

92
00:04:39,270 --> 00:04:42,180
That's just it, Mom. I don't feel bad at all.

93
00:04:42,790 --> 00:04:45,740
I don't feel anything except happy he's dead.

94
00:04:48,210 --> 00:04:49,680
They're looking for him.

95
00:05:07,160 --> 00:05:09,180
We have to get out of here before they find him.

96
00:05:09,180 --> 00:05:10,340
Cover up the blood.

97
00:05:20,240 --> 00:05:23,980
Yeah, that's right, man. No time for this.

98
00:05:26,410 --> 00:05:27,620
There's two of them.

99
00:05:28,960 --> 00:05:30,910
When they're gone, we'll move.

100
00:06:02,820 --> 00:06:03,460
Nina?

101
00:06:03,460 --> 00:06:06,440
I've got the satellite photos, but they're a few hours old.

102
00:06:06,510 --> 00:06:07,500
Hold on.

103
00:06:11,550 --> 00:06:14,280
- Okay, I'm ready to receive. - Are you there yet?

104
00:06:14,290 --> 00:06:15,860
I'm just outside the perimeter.

105
00:06:16,870 --> 00:06:18,710
I see a dozen or so people on the ground.

106
00:06:18,710 --> 00:06:20,510
Some look like they're carrying weapons.

107
00:06:20,830 --> 00:06:21,970
That looks right from here.

108
00:06:21,970 --> 00:06:23,970
There could be more people inside the buildings.

109
00:06:24,710 --> 00:06:27,390
Jack, I think we should bring Green into this.

110
00:06:27,510 --> 00:06:29,340
Come clean with her so she can authorize backup.

111
00:06:29,340 --> 00:06:31,000
I don't want backup!

112
00:06:31,640 --> 00:06:33,340
Not until I know my family is safe.

113
00:06:33,340 --> 00:06:35,230
You cannot go into an armed camp by yourself.

114
00:06:35,230 --> 00:06:37,520
- If something would've happened to you... - Nina!

115
00:06:37,550 --> 00:06:40,170
My family is being held hostage because of me.

116
00:06:40,170 --> 00:06:41,630
If you bring CTU into this,

117
00:06:41,630 --> 00:06:43,620
they could screw up and make this another Waco.

119
00:06:43,620 --> 00:06:45,760
Send me the photo now!

120
00:06:47,650 --> 00:06:48,790
I'm sending.

121
00:06:48,950 --> 00:06:52,280
Thank you. I'll get back to you.

122
00:07:10,400 --> 00:07:11,630
Get out of the car.

123
00:07:12,890 --> 00:07:14,250
What are you doing, Jack?

124
00:07:16,460 --> 00:07:18,910
Damn it, Jack, will you get a hold of yourself?

125
00:07:20,140 --> 00:07:21,540
We had an agreement.

126
00:07:21,880 --> 00:07:24,320
I bring you here, you let me go.

127
00:07:24,830 --> 00:07:28,540
The agreement was as soon as my family is safe,

128
00:07:28,710 --> 00:07:29,850
 I would let you go.

129
00:07:29,850 --> 00:07:31,040
Jack, don't be stupid.

130
00:07:31,040 --> 00:07:32,120
Even if you get in there,

131
00:07:32,120 --> 00:07:34,020
you're never gonna find them without me.

132
00:07:34,020 --> 00:07:35,030
Come on.

133
00:07:39,300 --> 00:07:40,870
Jack, please.

134
00:07:42,510 --> 00:07:43,910
All right, all right.

135
00:07:49,800 --> 00:07:50,920
You drive.

136
00:07:50,940 --> 00:07:55,220
Jack, if Gaines thinks for a moment that I brought you here,

137
00:07:55,220 --> 00:07:57,560
he'll have no problem killing us both.

138
00:07:58,050 --> 00:08:01,420
Then we should avoid Gaines. Get in the car.

139
00:08:02,520 --> 00:08:04,180
Okay. Okay

140
00:08:04,730 --> 00:08:06,060
Just relax.

141
00:08:30,740 --> 00:08:32,750
Real or not, the threat on your life

142
00:08:32,750 --> 00:08:35,360
will probably give you a bounce in the polls.

143
00:08:41,380 --> 00:08:42,690
What's wrong, David?

144
00:08:43,530 --> 00:08:46,680
- I'm tired. - It's something else.

145
00:08:47,350 --> 00:08:49,950
You've been off your game since you spoke to Carl.

146
00:08:55,170 --> 00:08:57,790
Carl's gonna stop the Kingsley story from coming out

147
00:08:58,020 --> 00:08:59,640
by cutting off her source.

148
00:09:00,170 --> 00:09:02,220
- Keith's therapist? - Yeah.

149
00:09:03,260 --> 00:09:05,460
Did Carl say how he planned to do this?

150
00:09:05,710 --> 00:09:08,490
No. He just said I'd better stay out of it.

151
00:09:08,710 --> 00:09:10,250
Maybe that's good advice.

152
00:09:13,400 --> 00:09:14,670
You don't seriously think

153
00:09:14,670 --> 00:09:17,420
Carl would do something to hurt this guy?

154
00:09:17,600 --> 00:09:20,070
You know Carl better than I do. You tell me.

155
00:09:23,070 --> 00:09:25,060
I think you're being paranoid,

156
00:09:25,490 --> 00:09:27,180
but if you're really concerned,

157
00:09:27,180 --> 00:09:30,350
I'll call this therapist, tell him to be careful.

158
00:09:31,140 --> 00:09:34,220
I already tried. I got his voice mail both times.

159
00:09:34,370 --> 00:09:35,520
You called him?

160
00:09:36,380 --> 00:09:38,010
Exposing yourself like that.

161
00:09:41,860 --> 00:09:45,200
For God's sakes, David, you're running for president.

162
00:09:45,980 --> 00:09:47,400
What were you thinking?

163
00:10:00,180 --> 00:10:01,650
If anything goes wrong,

164
00:10:01,650 --> 00:10:04,180
everyone around the car dies, starting with you.

165
00:10:12,750 --> 00:10:14,300
Gaines has been waiting for you.

166
00:10:14,300 --> 00:10:15,490
I know.

167
00:10:16,200 --> 00:10:17,530
What happened to you?

168
00:10:17,550 --> 00:10:19,650
I had a fight with your wife.

169
00:10:19,660 --> 00:10:23,100
Are you gonna open up the gate or do I have to do it myself?

170
00:10:30,100 --> 00:10:32,110
Roll up the window and go.

171
00:11:09,700 --> 00:11:10,860
Stop here.

172
00:11:15,770 --> 00:11:17,230
How may men on site?

173
00:11:18,510 --> 00:11:20,160
15, 20.

174
00:11:20,470 --> 00:11:22,400
Which is it, 15 or 20?

175
00:11:22,530 --> 00:11:24,330
I didn't do the hiring.

176
00:11:27,360 --> 00:11:30,080
My wife and daughter are in one of these buildings. Which one?

177
00:11:30,770 --> 00:11:31,950
I don't know.

178
00:11:32,490 --> 00:11:33,900
Take a guess.

179
00:11:36,800 --> 00:11:38,630
This whole rescue act,

180
00:11:38,940 --> 00:11:40,070
you really think it's gonna

181
00:11:40,070 --> 00:11:42,970
make up for how you screwed up your marriage, Jack?

182
00:11:44,150 --> 00:11:46,110
Teri's told me everything.

183
00:11:46,980 --> 00:11:50,510
How you were never around, the separation.

184
00:11:50,510 --> 00:11:52,720
- I mean... - You're wasting your time.

185
00:11:54,720 --> 00:11:56,480
Teri's been very lonely.

186
00:12:00,920 --> 00:12:05,460
For the last time, which building are they in?

187
00:12:09,830 --> 00:12:11,070
It's this one.

188
00:12:11,850 --> 00:12:14,410
It used to be used for cold storage.

189
00:12:25,950 --> 00:12:27,060
Damn it!

190
00:12:38,030 --> 00:12:40,290
- You understand my concern. - Yeah.

191
00:12:40,290 --> 00:12:43,040
You do realize what's at stake here, don't you?

192
00:12:43,450 --> 00:12:45,630
I assume you know we're working against the clock.

193
00:12:45,640 --> 00:12:47,190
Don't worry, Mr. Drazen.

194
00:12:47,190 --> 00:12:49,220
Yeah, we'll be out of here within the hour.

195
00:12:50,080 --> 00:12:52,270
If there's a problem, you'll be the first to know.

196
00:12:52,510 --> 00:12:55,140
- I want an update soon. - Yeah.

197
00:12:55,840 --> 00:12:59,820
Hey Rick, where's Eli?

198
00:12:59,900 --> 00:13:01,080
I haven't seen him.

199
00:13:01,240 --> 00:13:03,250
I sent him to take care of the women a half-hour ago.

200
00:13:03,260 --> 00:13:04,830
Find out what's taking so long.

201
00:13:04,830 --> 00:13:06,920
You want me to go load this up first?

202
00:13:07,910 --> 00:13:08,910
Yeah.

203
00:13:43,920 --> 00:13:45,230
Let's get to move.

204
00:14:38,280 --> 00:14:39,250
Damn it!

205
00:15:07,510 --> 00:15:08,290
Hello?

206
00:15:08,290 --> 00:15:09,930
This is Dr. Ferragamo.

207
00:15:09,930 --> 00:15:11,760
Thank you for returning my call.

208
00:15:12,120 --> 00:15:13,800
Your message said it was urgent.

209
00:15:13,800 --> 00:15:16,890
Yes, I wanted to talk to you about my son.

210
00:15:17,430 --> 00:15:20,160
You know I can't do that. Doctor-patient privilege.

211
00:15:20,160 --> 00:15:22,230
That didn't stop you from talking to the press.

212
00:15:23,160 --> 00:15:25,100
If you're calling to threaten me, Senator--

213
00:15:25,100 --> 00:15:27,410
I'm not the one who's threatening you.

214
00:15:27,410 --> 00:15:28,470
Really?

215
00:15:29,770 --> 00:15:31,730
Whatever you leaked to Kingsley,

216
00:15:31,730 --> 00:15:34,960
there are certain people who want to stop you from confirming it.

217
00:15:34,960 --> 00:15:38,150
By certain people, I assume you're referring to yourself.

218
00:15:38,190 --> 00:15:40,510
No. I'm trying to protect you.

219
00:15:40,510 --> 00:15:41,880
You've already covered up one murder

220
00:15:41,880 --> 00:15:44,720
and now you're threatening me if I don't keep quiet.

221
00:15:44,720 --> 00:15:46,230
You're twisting my words.

222
00:15:46,230 --> 00:15:47,760
I think I'm hearing you clearly.

223
00:15:54,270 --> 00:15:56,280
You've reached the office of Dr. Ferragamo.

224
00:15:56,280 --> 00:15:58,500
Leave your name at the sound of the tone.

225
00:15:58,840 --> 00:16:01,240
Dr. Ferragamo, pick up the phone, please.

226
00:16:01,240 --> 00:16:02,890
I need you to hear me out.

227
00:16:04,030 --> 00:16:05,470
Dr. Ferragamo.

228
00:16:10,520 --> 00:16:12,700
Doesn't sound like it went very well.

229
00:16:13,150 --> 00:16:15,610
I need to see him, Mike, talk to him face to face.

230
00:16:15,610 --> 00:16:17,390
- Later. - Now.

231
00:16:17,390 --> 00:16:20,610
David, You're supposed to be delivering your policy statement

232
00:16:20,610 --> 00:16:22,930
on public health care in one hour.

233
00:16:23,350 --> 00:16:24,650
I'll be late.

234
00:16:24,650 --> 00:16:25,970
What are you going to do,

235
00:16:26,370 --> 00:16:28,700
pull up to his office with your motorcade?

236
00:16:31,280 --> 00:16:33,110
I'll ride with the Secret Service.

237
00:16:36,100 --> 00:16:38,650
You're getting in way over your head.

238
00:16:40,170 --> 00:16:41,410
Pull over.

239
00:16:52,550 --> 00:16:54,680
They're gone. Let's go.

240
00:16:58,960 --> 00:16:59,980
Are you ready?

241
00:17:03,170 --> 00:17:03,920
Kimberly

242
00:17:03,920 --> 00:17:05,790
Mom, don't say anything, I know.

243
00:17:08,760 --> 00:17:10,050
I love you, too.

244
00:17:36,340 --> 00:17:38,340
Teri, it's me. It's Jack.

245
00:17:41,840 --> 00:17:43,110
It's me, baby.

246
00:17:49,280 --> 00:17:52,700
- You okay? Where's Kim? - She's here.

247
00:17:53,290 --> 00:17:54,930
Kim, sweetheart.

248
00:17:54,930 --> 00:17:55,980
Daddy! Oh my god!

249
00:17:58,750 --> 00:18:00,670
- It's gonna be okay. - I knew you'd come.

250
00:18:02,830 --> 00:18:05,050
It's all right, baby, it's all right.

251
00:18:09,300 --> 00:18:10,530
Can we leave now?

252
00:18:11,210 --> 00:18:14,140
Baby, we're gonna get out of here soon. Just one minute.

253
00:18:43,090 --> 00:18:44,600
Making any progress?

254
00:18:46,360 --> 00:18:48,660
We're working on the projected threat assessment.

255
00:18:48,660 --> 00:18:50,830
I think you both know where Jack is.

256
00:18:51,490 --> 00:18:53,240
Which means you are interfering

257
00:18:53,240 --> 00:18:56,000
with a criminal investigation, harboring a fugitive--

258
00:18:56,000 --> 00:18:57,720
Jack is not a threat to Palmer.

259
00:18:57,720 --> 00:18:59,410
How do you know that, if you haven't talked to him?

260
00:18:59,410 --> 00:19:01,460
And why is he still missing?

261
00:19:01,460 --> 00:19:02,840
Polygraph us if you think we're lying.

262
00:19:02,840 --> 00:19:04,470
So you can stall some more?

263
00:19:08,980 --> 00:19:10,410
Save us all a lot of time and trouble,

264
00:19:10,410 --> 00:19:12,140
and just tell me where he is.

265
00:19:17,460 --> 00:19:19,950
Tony, go to Holding Room 2. I'll be there in a few minutes.

266
00:19:19,950 --> 00:19:22,160
- Nina, go to 1. - What are you doing?

267
00:19:23,340 --> 00:19:25,500
- I'm suspending you both. - What?

268
00:19:25,500 --> 00:19:27,550
Until one of you tells me where to find Jack,

269
00:19:27,550 --> 00:19:28,630
you're both suspended.

270
00:19:28,640 --> 00:19:30,170
You don't have the authority to do that.

271
00:19:30,170 --> 00:19:33,120
The first one who tells me will have a career and a future here.

272
00:19:33,120 --> 00:19:36,480
The other one will be prosecuted and discharged.

273
00:19:58,570 --> 00:20:01,860
Rick, I thought I told you to go check on Eli.

274
00:20:02,310 --> 00:20:03,360
Yes, sir.

275
00:20:15,580 --> 00:20:16,610
Who is he?

276
00:20:17,150 --> 00:20:18,620
They sent him to kill us.

277
00:20:18,740 --> 00:20:21,690
- When? - About a half hour ago.

278
00:20:22,910 --> 00:20:25,040
That means someone's gonna come looking for him.

279
00:20:29,950 --> 00:20:31,640
Hey, sweetheart. Come here, come on.

280
00:20:31,640 --> 00:20:34,040
I'm fine. Really, I'm fine.

281
00:20:34,600 --> 00:20:35,850
Kim, it's me!

282
00:20:36,470 --> 00:20:37,900
Dad, it's okay. He's the one who gave us the gun.

283
00:20:37,900 --> 00:20:39,810
- Get away from the door. - Dad!

284
00:20:39,810 --> 00:20:41,040
Go back to your mother.

285
00:20:41,300 --> 00:20:42,280
Kim?

286
00:20:42,980 --> 00:20:43,960
Kim?!

287
00:20:44,860 --> 00:20:47,310
Dad, stop it! No!

288
00:20:47,910 --> 00:20:48,940
Jack.

289
00:20:49,230 --> 00:20:50,780
Jack, you're killing him!

290
00:20:50,780 --> 00:20:52,980
He wants to get out of here as much as we do.

291
00:20:53,820 --> 00:20:56,230
- It's true, Jack. - Please!

292
00:21:00,400 --> 00:21:02,030
Why are you helping them?

293
00:21:02,450 --> 00:21:03,860
Because I got Kim into this.

294
00:21:03,860 --> 00:21:05,910
But I didn't know how heavy it was gonna get.

295
00:21:06,420 --> 00:21:07,830
Get away from him.

296
00:21:08,450 --> 00:21:09,510
Get up.

297
00:21:14,690 --> 00:21:16,030
Is anyone else coming?

298
00:21:16,040 --> 00:21:18,220
- Not that I know of. - Good.

299
00:21:18,620 --> 00:21:20,260
Go sit with your partner.

300
00:21:22,540 --> 00:21:23,840
I'm glad you're okay.

301
00:21:36,490 --> 00:21:39,000
We both know why Nina's covering for Jack.

302
00:21:39,170 --> 00:21:40,310
But I think the only reason

303
00:21:40,310 --> 00:21:43,260
you're covering for him is to cover for Nina.

304
00:21:44,070 --> 00:21:46,660
From where I'm sitting, Tony, it looks like she's using you.

305
00:21:47,980 --> 00:21:49,830
You don't know what you're talking about.

306
00:21:49,890 --> 00:21:52,820
I'm just trying to help you see the situation clearly.

307
00:21:52,820 --> 00:21:55,330
Somehow, Jack Bauer is connected

308
00:21:55,330 --> 00:21:57,430
to the threat against Palmer.

309
00:21:57,720 --> 00:21:59,200
By not telling me where he is,

310
00:21:59,200 --> 00:22:01,120
you're endangering the life of a U.S. Senator

311
00:22:01,120 --> 00:22:04,850
who stands a damn good chance of becoming the next President.

312
00:22:28,920 --> 00:22:30,540
What's Jack doing, Tony?

313
00:22:30,540 --> 00:22:32,530
Why did he show up at the Palmer breakfast

314
00:22:32,530 --> 00:22:35,110
and grab the gun of a Secret Service Agent?

315
00:22:35,960 --> 00:22:37,630
He claims he was trying to create a diversion.

316
00:22:37,630 --> 00:22:38,820
I know what Jack said.

317
00:22:38,820 --> 00:22:40,520
I want to know what you think.

318
00:22:42,090 --> 00:22:45,210
Look, if I knew where Jack was--

319
00:22:45,220 --> 00:22:46,790
- You do know. - You're wrong.

320
00:22:46,790 --> 00:22:48,520
No, I'm not.

321
00:22:53,090 --> 00:22:54,560
Help me here, Tony,

322
00:22:54,560 --> 00:22:57,310
or getting fired will be the least of your problems.

323
00:22:57,310 --> 00:23:00,780
I will make sure you're prosecuted. You will go to prison.

324
00:23:04,740 --> 00:23:06,410
I'll give you 10 minutes.

325
00:23:07,460 --> 00:23:09,230
Take the time to decide

326
00:23:09,230 --> 00:23:12,190
if it's really worth ruining your life over this.

327
00:23:30,250 --> 00:23:32,000
The car is parked at the north end of the compound.

328
00:23:32,000 --> 00:23:32,960
I just need to go get it,

329
00:23:32,960 --> 00:23:35,300
and I'm gonna pick you both up right there, Okay?

330
00:23:35,980 --> 00:23:37,370
You're not leaving us.

331
00:23:37,510 --> 00:23:40,790
Sweetheart, I'm not leaving you. I'm going to be right back.

332
00:23:40,790 --> 00:23:43,920
Bad things have only happened to us because we weren't together.

333
00:23:44,220 --> 00:23:46,040
We're not separating again, Jack.

334
00:23:47,130 --> 00:23:50,130
Maybe you don't have to. There's another way out.

335
00:23:50,360 --> 00:23:52,100
A better way, I think.

336
00:23:56,760 --> 00:23:57,560
How?

337
00:23:57,560 --> 00:23:59,070
Gaines still thinks I'm on his side

338
00:23:59,070 --> 00:24:01,670
so I can get one of the vans without them noticing.

339
00:24:02,320 --> 00:24:04,850
Even if they stop me, your car will still be there

340
00:24:05,000 --> 00:24:06,720
and you can all be together.

341
00:24:10,750 --> 00:24:11,990
He's right, Jack.

342
00:24:15,710 --> 00:24:16,870
You trust him?

343
00:24:17,810 --> 00:24:18,930
I do.

344
00:24:19,810 --> 00:24:21,260
Rick, it's Gaines.

345
00:24:23,160 --> 00:24:24,880
Rick, what's going on down there?

346
00:24:26,840 --> 00:24:28,040
Answer him.

347
00:24:28,600 --> 00:24:29,810
Mr. Gaines?

348
00:24:29,960 --> 00:24:31,140
Where's Eli?

349
00:24:32,140 --> 00:24:32,980
He's outside.

350
00:24:32,980 --> 00:24:34,970
He's digging a hole to bury the girls.

351
00:24:34,980 --> 00:24:37,490
Get him, damn it! I need him back here right now.

352
00:24:39,750 --> 00:24:42,190
When Eli doesn't come back, Gaines is coming down here.

353
00:24:42,480 --> 00:24:43,810
Let me get the van.

354
00:24:49,060 --> 00:24:50,510
You've got five minutes.

355
00:26:07,040 --> 00:26:08,870
Stack those on the side, you know.

356
00:26:11,540 --> 00:26:13,470
Should I bring these down on the other side?

357
00:26:22,120 --> 00:26:23,970
We ain't got no time for lunch.

358
00:26:28,560 --> 00:26:29,690
I can handle it.

359
00:26:30,530 --> 00:26:32,310
There's been a change of plans.

360
00:26:32,320 --> 00:26:34,630
No, I need to know now, not later. Now.

361
00:26:36,420 --> 00:26:38,220
What's so hard to understand about that?

362
00:26:41,830 --> 00:26:43,140
Come on guys, let's go.

363
00:26:45,930 --> 00:26:47,810
Will you guys hurry with the truck down there.

364
00:26:57,940 --> 00:26:59,390
Hey Joe, where's Eli?

365
00:27:28,270 --> 00:27:29,310
What are you doing?

366
00:27:29,350 --> 00:27:30,340
Taking the van.

367
00:27:30,340 --> 00:27:33,160
I can see that, Rick. Where are you taking the van?

368
00:27:33,160 --> 00:27:35,820
To help Eli get the bodies from the guest house.

369
00:27:35,820 --> 00:27:38,330
You two can't move a couple of women yourselves?

370
00:27:38,390 --> 00:27:40,780
I don't know. He told me to get the van. So I'm getting the van.

371
00:27:40,780 --> 00:27:42,930
But if it's a problem, I don't have to.

372
00:27:43,840 --> 00:27:45,090
Mr. Gaines?

373
00:27:47,170 --> 00:27:48,140
What?

374
00:27:48,140 --> 00:27:50,630
I was out patrol and I found Kevin.

375
00:27:51,320 --> 00:27:53,810
What? Is he alive?

376
00:27:53,810 --> 00:27:57,150
Yeah, but he's out cold. Someone messed him up pretty good.

377
00:27:57,440 --> 00:27:58,690
Where are you?

378
00:27:58,690 --> 00:28:01,180
I'm in the North Grove, near the generator.

379
00:28:01,240 --> 00:28:04,510
I'll be right there. You're driving. Let's go.

380
00:28:09,520 --> 00:28:11,010
Open the damn door.

381
00:28:33,680 --> 00:28:37,250
At the very least, be careful what you say to Ferragamo.

382
00:28:37,980 --> 00:28:39,250
I'll be careful.

383
00:28:39,480 --> 00:28:43,490
I mean, it's not like he's so squeaky-clean in this thing.

384
00:28:43,520 --> 00:28:45,290
By talking about Keith to the press,

385
00:28:45,290 --> 00:28:47,620
he violated every professional ethic.

386
00:28:47,620 --> 00:28:49,270
I know what he did, Mike.

387
00:29:01,650 --> 00:29:02,660
Pull over here.

388
00:29:04,780 --> 00:29:06,230
Here's the office.

389
00:29:12,290 --> 00:29:15,180
No. Let me find out what happened.

390
00:29:15,900 --> 00:29:17,170
I'll be right back.

391
00:29:28,500 --> 00:29:31,710
What happened? What caused this?

392
00:29:32,010 --> 00:29:33,920
A possible gas explosion.

393
00:29:35,130 --> 00:29:36,270
- Thanks. - No problem.

394
00:29:47,680 --> 00:29:50,830
-It's Ferragamo, isn't it? -There was a fire.

395
00:29:51,010 --> 00:29:53,280
They say it might have been a broken gas line.

396
00:29:53,950 --> 00:29:55,750
He didn't get out in time.

397
00:29:55,960 --> 00:29:58,790
- Damn it! - They torched his office.

398
00:29:58,980 --> 00:30:01,000
And you can bet his records were destroyed.

399
00:30:01,570 --> 00:30:03,710
We don't know anything yet.

400
00:30:03,980 --> 00:30:06,090
It could have been an accident, David.

401
00:30:06,150 --> 00:30:09,020
But it wasn't. It was murder.

402
00:30:09,380 --> 00:30:11,070
David, stop! Wait. Listen to me.

403
00:30:11,080 --> 00:30:12,310
Get out of my way.

404
00:30:14,110 --> 00:30:15,980
Hear me out. Just hear me out.

405
00:30:15,990 --> 00:30:19,140
Look, David, think this through.

406
00:30:20,590 --> 00:30:22,280
Even if you're right,

407
00:30:22,280 --> 00:30:25,930
this is the absolute wrong way to play it.

408
00:30:36,280 --> 00:30:37,400
Damn it!

409
00:30:46,160 --> 00:30:47,100
Go.

410
00:31:01,860 --> 00:31:03,250
Time's up, Tony.

411
00:31:04,570 --> 00:31:06,210
Have you thought about what I said?

412
00:31:08,210 --> 00:31:09,340
I have.

413
00:31:10,150 --> 00:31:11,320
And?

414
00:31:19,630 --> 00:31:21,790
Excuse me. You have a call.

415
00:31:21,790 --> 00:31:23,280
I said no interruptions.

416
00:31:23,290 --> 00:31:24,640
It's Bauer.

417
00:31:29,910 --> 00:31:31,390
Where the hell are you, Jack?

418
00:31:31,400 --> 00:31:32,820
Alberta, you might have my office,

419
00:31:32,820 --> 00:31:35,020
but if you want to do my job, you'd better listen to me.

420
00:31:35,020 --> 00:31:36,680
I don't take orders from you.

421
00:31:36,680 --> 00:31:38,720
I located the people behind the Palmer hit.

422
00:31:38,720 --> 00:31:41,360
You're one of them, unless you can prove otherwise.

423
00:31:41,480 --> 00:31:42,810
They kidnapped my family,

424
00:31:42,820 --> 00:31:45,260
my wife and daughter. But I'm with them now.

425
00:31:45,260 --> 00:31:46,130
That's why had to work underground

426
00:31:46,130 --> 00:31:48,310
and why I couldn't contact CTU.

427
00:31:48,320 --> 00:31:50,250
You're telling me you haven't spoken to anyone here?

428
00:31:50,250 --> 00:31:51,290
I couldn't risk it.

429
00:31:51,290 --> 00:31:52,800
Believe me, I wish I could.

430
00:31:52,800 --> 00:31:56,010
It's not my job to believe you, Jack. It's my job to find you.

431
00:31:56,010 --> 00:31:57,360
I'm at an orange grove,

432
00:31:57,360 --> 00:31:59,700
three miles north of the split on the 5. Hold on.

433
00:32:01,210 --> 00:32:05,220
34 degrees, 17 minutes North, 118 degrees, 28 minutes West.

436
00:32:05,220 --> 00:32:06,610
- You got that? - Yeah.

437
00:32:06,610 --> 00:32:08,640
I've identified 11 hostiles.

438
00:32:08,800 --> 00:32:11,150
They're traveling west on the compound service road.

439
00:32:11,160 --> 00:32:12,540
Bring in air support.

440
00:32:12,620 --> 00:32:14,210
I'll get back in touch.

441
00:32:20,260 --> 00:32:22,010
Get me Central Dispatch.

442
00:32:22,440 --> 00:32:23,540
Find out where Jack's wife and daughter

443
00:32:23,540 --> 00:32:26,090
have been for the last six hours.

444
00:32:27,060 --> 00:32:28,210
Damn it.

445
00:32:49,310 --> 00:32:52,310
- You ready to go home? - Definitely.

446
00:32:55,850 --> 00:32:57,630
We'll finally finish our chess game.

447
00:32:57,640 --> 00:32:59,670
I'm two moves from checkmating you.

448
00:32:59,670 --> 00:33:02,350
Yeah yeah yeah yeah, we'll see.

449
00:33:12,520 --> 00:33:16,050
We're gonna be all right, I promise.

450
00:33:20,450 --> 00:33:22,090
Let me know as soon as you see him.

451
00:33:22,090 --> 00:33:24,540
Yeah, okay.

452
00:33:31,030 --> 00:33:34,030
Teri, it's gonna be okay.

453
00:33:35,960 --> 00:33:37,770
Between us, you and me.

454
00:33:41,700 --> 00:33:42,950
I love you.

455
00:33:44,000 --> 00:33:46,760
And I promise you, everything is gonna be different from now on.

456
00:34:09,280 --> 00:34:10,750
No, I want two choppers.

457
00:34:10,750 --> 00:34:13,350
If Villa has a problem with that, he can call me.

458
00:34:16,750 --> 00:34:18,550
Jack called with his location.

459
00:34:18,550 --> 00:34:20,770
I sent three field units to back him up.

460
00:34:21,250 --> 00:34:22,460
Is he all right?

461
00:34:23,480 --> 00:34:25,090
We'll find out soon enough.

462
00:34:25,680 --> 00:34:28,010
So, which one of us are you gonna suspend?

463
00:34:29,170 --> 00:34:30,370
Neither of you.

464
00:34:30,730 --> 00:34:33,020
Only because I don't have enough actionable evidence

465
00:34:33,020 --> 00:34:34,980
that you withheld information.

466
00:34:38,250 --> 00:34:40,030
But I plan to keep looking.

467
00:34:46,270 --> 00:34:48,630
I want to find out who's running point on the field units

468
00:34:48,630 --> 00:34:50,070
so we can monitor what's happening.

469
00:34:57,320 --> 00:34:58,340
You okay?

470
00:34:59,050 --> 00:35:01,090
Alberta worked me pretty hard in there.

471
00:35:02,800 --> 00:35:04,000
Yeah, I know.

472
00:35:06,440 --> 00:35:10,230
I gotta tell you, if Jack hadn't called when he did....

473
00:35:11,720 --> 00:35:13,820
You took a lot of chances for me.

474
00:35:14,460 --> 00:35:15,740
I won't forget it.

475
00:35:31,970 --> 00:35:34,840
Kevin.... Kevin!

476
00:35:35,710 --> 00:35:37,370
Kevin, what the hell happened?

477
00:35:40,320 --> 00:35:41,430
Bauer.

478
00:35:41,710 --> 00:35:43,780
- He's here. - What?

479
00:35:47,960 --> 00:35:52,110
I went to meet Cofell, but Bauer had already gotten to him.

480
00:35:52,730 --> 00:35:54,290
How long have you been here?

481
00:35:54,460 --> 00:35:55,720
I don't know.

482
00:36:02,850 --> 00:36:03,930
Rick!

483
00:36:08,150 --> 00:36:09,060
Bauer's on site.

484
00:36:09,060 --> 00:36:11,410
Whoever's near the guest house, we're going in strong.

485
00:36:11,460 --> 00:36:14,030
Seal the gate, make sure no one gets out.

486
00:36:20,730 --> 00:36:21,850
Stay in the door.

487
00:36:47,710 --> 00:36:49,480
It's him. He brought the van. Come on.

488
00:37:00,000 --> 00:37:01,930
Gaines is coming. He found the guy you came in with.

489
00:37:01,940 --> 00:37:03,170
I'll drive.

490
00:38:17,960 --> 00:38:18,920
Hold on!

491
00:38:35,490 --> 00:38:36,890
Get down, get down.

492
00:38:42,470 --> 00:38:43,510
Hold on.

493
00:38:54,710 --> 00:38:55,820
Stay down!

494
00:39:02,300 --> 00:39:03,290
Get up to the van.

495
00:39:03,290 --> 00:39:05,250
Everybody out. Stay low.

496
00:39:08,970 --> 00:39:11,650
Get to the back of the van. Use the wheels for cover.

497
00:39:17,670 --> 00:39:18,820
Take cover.

498
00:39:26,620 --> 00:39:29,410
- Cover me, I'm going across. - Move, move!

499
00:39:31,380 --> 00:39:32,700
On the satellite photo you'll see

500
00:39:32,700 --> 00:39:35,580
an old water tower down by the service road.

501
00:39:35,580 --> 00:39:36,420
Go straight through these woods,

502
00:39:36,420 --> 00:39:38,310
follow the creek bed and run like hell.

503
00:39:38,320 --> 00:39:40,470
I'll make sure CTU finds you.

504
00:39:47,830 --> 00:39:50,930
- What about you, Jack? - I'll be right behind you.

505
00:39:52,620 --> 00:39:55,290
- There's too many of them. - Not if I help.

506
00:39:55,600 --> 00:39:57,910
- You know how to use that thing? - Yeah.

507
00:39:58,420 --> 00:39:59,930
Teri, stay there!

508
00:40:06,250 --> 00:40:07,600
I got a clear shot.

509
00:40:07,890 --> 00:40:09,750
I'm not leaving you, Jack.

510
00:40:09,750 --> 00:40:12,460
You won't be leaving, you'll be taking care of our daughter.

511
00:40:12,460 --> 00:40:14,840
- But Dad... - Don't argue with me, sweetheart, please.

512
00:40:14,840 --> 00:40:16,500
Both of you go, now.

513
00:40:19,140 --> 00:40:20,280
Go! Run!

514
00:40:36,220 --> 00:40:37,570
Keep covering me.

515
00:40:55,280 --> 00:40:56,890
Go to the tree line.

516
00:41:01,530 --> 00:41:02,900
Go.

517
00:41:09,720 --> 00:41:10,730
Stay down.

518
00:41:24,720 --> 00:41:25,810
Come on, get up.

519
00:41:27,770 --> 00:41:28,860
Move!

520
00:41:36,030 --> 00:41:37,130
Let's go.

521
00:41:47,470 --> 00:41:48,540
Keep moving.

522
00:41:59,230 --> 00:42:01,840
I'll be able to stop the bleeding as soon as we get through the trees.

523
00:42:01,840 --> 00:42:03,700
Come on, I'm not leaving you behind.

