2
00:00:12,270 --> 00:00:14,490
Right now, terrorists are

3
00:00:14,490 --> 00:00:17,420
plotting to assassinate a presidential candidate.

4
00:00:17,900 --> 00:00:19,970
My teenage daughter is missing.

5
00:00:20,620 --> 00:00:24,530
And people that I work with may be involved in both.

6
00:00:24,840 --> 00:00:27,170
I'm Federal Agent Jack Bauer.

7
00:00:27,290 --> 00:00:31,100
Today is going to be the longest day of my life.

10
00:00:41,060 --> 00:00:46,060
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

11
00:00:41,060 --> 00:00:46,060
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

12
00:00:41,060 --> 00:00:46,060
{\an5}{\pos(145,252)}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

13
00:00:41,560 --> 00:00:46,060
{\pos(67,248)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

14
00:00:41,560 --> 00:00:46,060
{\pos(67,248)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

15
00:00:41,560 --> 00:00:46,060
{\pos(58,238)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

16
00:00:41,560 --> 00:00:46,060
{\pos(84,248)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

19
00:00:47,280 --> 00:01:12,280
{\an9}m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

20
00:00:46,780 --> 00:01:12,280
{\an2}{\pos(26,248)}m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

26
00:01:16,290 --> 00:01:18,990
It is just after 7:00 A.M. on the West Coast

27
00:01:18,990 --> 00:01:22,090
and the California Primary is now officially underway.

28
00:01:22,090 --> 00:01:25,710
We're here outside the San Clarita Power Plant in Los Angeles

29
00:01:25,710 --> 00:01:27,430
where Senator David palmer

30
00:01:27,440 --> 00:01:29,210
will be addressing local labor leaders

31
00:01:29,210 --> 00:01:31,850
and some members of the state energy council.

32
00:01:31,850 --> 00:01:35,800
The senator has pledged support for renovations

33
00:01:35,800 --> 00:01:37,840
that would advance this power plant to production.

34
00:01:37,840 --> 00:01:40,440
- Yeah? - Bauer's on his way. Are you in yet?

35
00:01:40,440 --> 00:01:42,520
- Just about. - Good.

36
00:01:42,590 --> 00:01:44,910
...create thousands of new jobs.

37
00:01:44,910 --> 00:01:47,180
This promises to be a landmark day...

38
00:01:47,180 --> 00:01:48,570
as it is expected that

39
00:01:48,570 --> 00:01:50,880
Senator Palmer will get the delegates he needs

40
00:01:50,880 --> 00:01:54,460
to become the first African-American presidential candidate

41
00:01:54,470 --> 00:01:56,620
of a major political party.

42
00:01:56,620 --> 00:01:59,580
Of the 11 states that will be looking for delegates today,

43
00:01:59,580 --> 00:02:02,120
California is expected to be crucial.

44
00:02:02,120 --> 00:02:03,940
And most of the polls say

45
00:02:03,940 --> 00:02:07,980
that David Palmer will win by a decisive margin.

46
00:02:09,870 --> 00:02:11,580
Have you decided?

47
00:02:18,260 --> 00:02:20,760
I've rewritten the speech I was going to give this morning.

48
00:02:23,220 --> 00:02:25,030
I'm going to tell them about Keith.

49
00:02:28,060 --> 00:02:29,780
What are you going to say?

50
00:02:30,060 --> 00:02:31,360
The truth.

51
00:02:32,350 --> 00:02:35,650
That seven years ago he was involved in an accidental death.

52
00:02:35,990 --> 00:02:38,000
I need you to stand by me, Sherry.

53
00:02:38,000 --> 00:02:39,920
It's the only way to protect Keith.

54
00:02:43,540 --> 00:02:45,920
For the man they see as the best hope

55
00:02:45,990 --> 00:02:48,440
for their country's financial future.

56
00:02:49,220 --> 00:02:53,150
I will never forgive you if something bad happens to my son.

57
00:02:54,370 --> 00:02:55,910
He's my son, too.

58
00:02:57,250 --> 00:02:58,760
We'll get through this.

59
00:03:00,450 --> 00:03:02,210
I hope so, David.

60
00:03:02,320 --> 00:03:06,410
We caught up with some voters who started lining up at 6:00 A. M.

61
00:03:07,380 --> 00:03:08,410
Hey, ma.

62
00:03:09,560 --> 00:03:10,990
Good morning, honey.

63
00:03:11,130 --> 00:03:12,410
Where's your sister?

64
00:03:12,410 --> 00:03:14,340
Oh, she changed her mind. She's not going.

65
00:03:14,340 --> 00:03:15,550
Really?

66
00:03:15,640 --> 00:03:16,510
Yeah, she went to the airport

67
00:03:16,510 --> 00:03:18,420
to pick up Suzy and Rachel instead.

68
00:03:18,420 --> 00:03:21,590
Oh, that's right. The Brenner girls are flying in.

69
00:03:22,300 --> 00:03:24,880
So, uh... what's gonna to happen this morning?

70
00:03:26,140 --> 00:03:28,230
We have to put this thing behind us, Keith.

71
00:03:28,230 --> 00:03:31,790
By me being in prison and you in the Oval Office?

72
00:03:31,790 --> 00:03:33,330
Is that how we're going to put it behind us?

73
00:03:33,330 --> 00:03:34,610
You're not going to prison.

74
00:03:34,610 --> 00:03:36,300
You didn't do anything wrong.

75
00:03:36,920 --> 00:03:39,000
That's not how a jury will see it.

76
00:03:39,150 --> 00:03:41,600
Why don't you just have a little faith in the system?

77
00:03:42,040 --> 00:03:44,210
What's this fairy tale that you're living in?

78
00:03:44,640 --> 00:03:46,230
The world's going to believe

79
00:03:46,230 --> 00:03:48,730
that I killed a white kid who raped my sister.

80
00:03:48,820 --> 00:03:51,490
Do you think that anyone will believe it was an accident?

81
00:03:51,490 --> 00:03:52,420
Yes, I do.

82
00:03:52,420 --> 00:03:53,960
- Then you're a fool. - Keith, no.

83
00:03:53,960 --> 00:03:55,370
No, that's all right.

84
00:03:56,330 --> 00:03:58,110
You talk about fairy tales.

85
00:03:58,600 --> 00:04:00,300
You think you can run from this?

86
00:04:00,670 --> 00:04:02,340
You think it's going to make things better?

87
00:04:03,320 --> 00:04:05,240
I'm not running anywhere.

88
00:04:05,870 --> 00:04:08,350
I'd just rather not spend my last hour of freedom with you.

89
00:04:12,490 --> 00:04:14,000
Let's go and get this over with.

90
00:04:19,610 --> 00:04:20,860
Martin Belkin?

91
00:04:21,100 --> 00:04:22,130
Yes.

92
00:04:22,130 --> 00:04:24,110
Hi, I'm Jessica Abrams.

93
00:04:24,110 --> 00:04:25,620
I work for Senator Palmer.

94
00:04:26,120 --> 00:04:27,780
- Hi. - Pleasure to meet you.

95
00:04:27,780 --> 00:04:28,910
Can I help you with..

96
00:04:28,910 --> 00:04:31,640
- I got it. - Okay. Great. Follow me.

97
00:04:32,280 --> 00:04:33,550
Is the senator here yet?

98
00:04:33,550 --> 00:04:35,580
Not yet, but he is on his way.

99
00:04:35,580 --> 00:04:36,270
Great.

100
00:04:36,270 --> 00:04:38,260
I am a huge fan of your work.

101
00:04:38,710 --> 00:04:40,940
- Thank you. - Right this way, please.

102
00:04:42,790 --> 00:04:43,740
Hi.

103
00:04:44,320 --> 00:04:47,130
I'm going to be taking some photographs of the senator.

104
00:04:53,510 --> 00:04:58,120
I need a check on a Belkin: B-E-L-K-I-N.

105
00:04:58,120 --> 00:04:59,850
First name, Martin.

106
00:05:05,540 --> 00:05:06,910
Clear on Belkin.

107
00:05:06,910 --> 00:05:08,870
All right, copy that. Thank you.

108
00:05:10,430 --> 00:05:11,760
You can go in.

109
00:05:37,940 --> 00:05:39,560
Turn right at the light.

110
00:05:45,240 --> 00:05:47,010
You see the bus stop on your left?

111
00:05:47,080 --> 00:05:48,090
Yes.

112
00:05:48,090 --> 00:05:49,500
Pull over to it.

113
00:06:09,380 --> 00:06:10,770
Hey, Jack.

114
00:06:14,060 --> 00:06:15,310
How are you doing?

115
00:06:17,570 --> 00:06:19,770
Don't touch it until I tell you to. Now, go.

116
00:06:19,770 --> 00:06:20,750
I'm not going anywhere

117
00:06:20,750 --> 00:06:22,810
until I can talk to my wife and my daughter.

118
00:06:22,810 --> 00:06:25,610
Oh, you'll do this, because it really isn't an inconvenience

119
00:06:25,610 --> 00:06:27,450
for me to hurt your daughter.

120
00:06:27,450 --> 00:06:30,390
Or your wife, for that matter. In fact, here she is.

121
00:06:31,060 --> 00:06:33,580
Would you like to speak to your husband?

122
00:06:34,450 --> 00:06:36,870
Say anything you want. Tell him you love him.

123
00:06:39,090 --> 00:06:40,540
- Jack. - Teri?

124
00:06:40,540 --> 00:06:43,090
I don't know where I am yet, and I haven't seen Kimberly--

125
00:06:43,360 --> 00:06:46,890
You were saying, Jack, you're not sure you wanted to do this?

126
00:06:48,280 --> 00:06:49,560
That's what I thought.

127
00:06:49,560 --> 00:06:52,930
San Clarita Power Station. 417 Ridgeway Road.

128
00:06:52,930 --> 00:06:54,370
Get over there now.

129
00:07:03,350 --> 00:07:05,370
This is only temporary, Mrs. Bauer.

130
00:07:05,370 --> 00:07:08,790
If Jack follows instructions, you'll be released within the hour.

131
00:07:08,790 --> 00:07:10,260
Where's my daughter?

132
00:07:10,370 --> 00:07:12,080
She's here and she's safe.

133
00:07:12,080 --> 00:07:13,830
Could you take me to her, please?

139
00:07:59,020 --> 00:08:00,560
What, Milo?

140
00:08:00,560 --> 00:08:02,580
- What happened to Nina? - She got called out.

141
00:08:02,830 --> 00:08:04,500
What am I supposed to do about this keycard?

142
00:08:04,500 --> 00:08:05,540
Because this was supposed to be

143
00:08:05,540 --> 00:08:06,690
the most important thing we're doing.

144
00:08:06,700 --> 00:08:08,490
They brought me in here on the highest priority

145
00:08:08,490 --> 00:08:09,800
and now I'm just sitting around.

146
00:08:09,800 --> 00:08:12,140
I think Nina's got some new intel that preempts this.

147
00:08:12,140 --> 00:08:13,730
That's why she had to run out.

148
00:08:14,200 --> 00:08:15,750
So, what should I be doing?

149
00:08:15,750 --> 00:08:17,770
Why don't you help me format some files?

150
00:08:17,770 --> 00:08:21,420
They didn't bring me in here at 5:00 A.M. to format files!

156
00:08:54,100 --> 00:08:56,820
Does this kid Milo know he's working on the wrong keycard?

166
00:09:07,430 --> 00:09:09,050
Is this going to be a problem?

169
00:09:14,290 --> 00:09:15,890
Nina Myers is dead.

170
00:09:16,050 --> 00:09:18,040
Make up a story for why she's not there.

173
00:09:37,880 --> 00:09:39,310
- Mom! - Kimberly!

174
00:09:50,800 --> 00:09:51,650
It's okay.

175
00:09:51,650 --> 00:09:53,040
It's okay, honey.

176
00:10:24,540 --> 00:10:25,900
Where's Dad?

177
00:10:25,900 --> 00:10:27,140
I don't know.

178
00:10:27,640 --> 00:10:28,770
He knows we're in trouble?

179
00:10:28,770 --> 00:10:30,130
Yeah, he does.

180
00:10:30,470 --> 00:10:32,530
He's doing everything he can, baby.

181
00:10:33,720 --> 00:10:35,420
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.

182
00:10:35,420 --> 00:10:38,580
No, no, no, no. It's not your fault.

183
00:10:39,870 --> 00:10:41,610
It's not your fault, honey.

184
00:10:45,400 --> 00:10:47,320
Why don't you tell me about these boys?

185
00:10:52,430 --> 00:10:54,460
I met them through Janet, and...

186
00:10:55,120 --> 00:10:57,790
She started dating this guy, Dan,

187
00:10:57,920 --> 00:10:59,220
and his friend Rick came into town

188
00:10:59,220 --> 00:11:02,200
- and we just hang out and... - Oh, God.

189
00:11:04,540 --> 00:11:06,280
They kept you here the whole time?

190
00:11:06,470 --> 00:11:07,700
Yes.

191
00:11:13,950 --> 00:11:15,660
Janet was hit by a car.

192
00:11:18,270 --> 00:11:19,480
I know.

193
00:11:19,930 --> 00:11:21,170
You do?

194
00:11:27,360 --> 00:11:29,280
We are going to get through this.

195
00:11:29,980 --> 00:11:31,410
I promise you.

196
00:11:58,420 --> 00:11:59,670
Hello?

197
00:12:30,200 --> 00:12:31,970
Come on, Jamey! Pick up!

198
00:12:54,010 --> 00:12:55,420
- Almeida. - Tony.

199
00:12:55,420 --> 00:12:57,470
Nina, where've you been?

200
00:12:57,470 --> 00:12:58,720
I can't get into it.

201
00:12:58,720 --> 00:13:00,620
Well, force yourself. Where are you?

202
00:13:01,800 --> 00:13:03,540
Just east of downtown.

203
00:13:04,350 --> 00:13:05,640
What are you doing there?

204
00:13:05,640 --> 00:13:08,820
Tony, you have to listen to me carefully.

205
00:13:09,120 --> 00:13:11,960
No one at CTU can know I'm alive.

206
00:13:12,430 --> 00:13:13,820
Who would think you were dead?

207
00:13:13,920 --> 00:13:16,090
I can't tell you any more right now.

208
00:13:16,090 --> 00:13:17,390
Where's Jamey?

209
00:13:17,390 --> 00:13:18,790
She's working with Milo.

210
00:13:19,390 --> 00:13:20,400
Get her for me.

211
00:13:20,400 --> 00:13:22,520
No, not until you tell me what's going on.

212
00:13:22,530 --> 00:13:24,470
Please, Tony. This is an order.

213
00:13:24,480 --> 00:13:25,980
I need your help.

214
00:13:26,620 --> 00:13:27,740
All right.

215
00:13:36,290 --> 00:13:38,410
Threatening emails, hate mail for Palmer.

216
00:13:38,420 --> 00:13:40,260
This is a giant waste of time.

217
00:13:40,260 --> 00:13:41,850
When is Nina coming back?

218
00:13:41,850 --> 00:13:43,920
Probably not for a couple of hours.

219
00:13:44,240 --> 00:13:45,640
What makes you say that?

220
00:13:46,700 --> 00:13:48,040
I just talked to her.

221
00:13:48,810 --> 00:13:49,810
When?

222
00:13:50,270 --> 00:13:51,220
A couple minutes ago.

223
00:13:51,220 --> 00:13:52,690
She's at Division.

224
00:13:52,690 --> 00:13:54,340
It's possible she'll be there all day.

225
00:13:57,430 --> 00:13:58,550
What do you need?

226
00:14:01,660 --> 00:14:02,820
Never mind.

227
00:14:04,680 --> 00:14:07,180
Look, if somebody doesn't tell me what's going on right now

228
00:14:07,180 --> 00:14:08,480
I'm going straight to Chapelle.

229
00:14:08,480 --> 00:14:10,600
I told you, I have to speak to Jamey.

230
00:14:10,820 --> 00:14:12,100
Yes, and I just heard her tell Milo

231
00:14:12,100 --> 00:14:14,440
that you'll be at Division all day.

232
00:14:15,650 --> 00:14:17,070
Oh, my God.

233
00:14:17,070 --> 00:14:19,030
- What? - Who did she hear that from?

234
00:14:19,370 --> 00:14:21,400
She said she talked to you minutes ago.

235
00:14:21,400 --> 00:14:22,980
Nina, what is going on?

236
00:14:22,980 --> 00:14:24,680
We can't trust Jamey.

237
00:14:26,270 --> 00:14:28,400
Jack said CTU had been infiltrated.

238
00:14:28,400 --> 00:14:30,110
Are you saying Jamey's a spy?

239
00:14:30,110 --> 00:14:32,010
Why else would she lie?

240
00:14:32,300 --> 00:14:33,550
She must think I'm dead.

241
00:14:33,550 --> 00:14:34,970
Why would she think that?

242
00:14:35,340 --> 00:14:36,280
I'll explain later.

243
00:14:36,280 --> 00:14:38,430
Tony, you have to bring me back in now.

244
00:14:38,480 --> 00:14:40,540
Okay, I'll come get you.

245
00:14:40,540 --> 00:14:41,690
No, stay there.

246
00:14:41,690 --> 00:14:43,490
Act as if everything is all right.

247
00:14:43,690 --> 00:14:46,120
Jack was behaving very strangely when he was back at CTU.

248
00:14:46,120 --> 00:14:48,090
These people they must be watching us.

249
00:14:48,090 --> 00:14:50,350
I don't know, probably through our own surveillance.

250
00:14:51,350 --> 00:14:54,770
All right, look. I'll send a car. What's your address?

251
00:15:21,280 --> 00:15:22,850
- Senator. - How are you?

252
00:15:43,610 --> 00:15:44,740
Copy that.

253
00:15:59,140 --> 00:16:02,040
All you have to do now Jack, is get through security.

254
00:16:11,750 --> 00:16:14,560
Jack Bauer, CTU. I've been cleared by Frank Simes.

255
00:16:22,260 --> 00:16:24,210
All right, I'll need you to open the case.

256
00:16:25,070 --> 00:16:26,020
Sure.

257
00:16:39,060 --> 00:16:40,860
What do you need a laptop for?

258
00:16:41,290 --> 00:16:42,560
Everything that we've compiled

259
00:16:42,560 --> 00:16:44,860
on Palmer over the last eight hours is in there.

260
00:16:46,550 --> 00:16:48,650
You want to lift that up, please?

261
00:16:59,010 --> 00:17:00,270
Turn it on.

262
00:17:01,420 --> 00:17:03,140
Just press any two buttons, Jack.

263
00:17:15,500 --> 00:17:16,590
All right, go ahead.

264
00:17:16,590 --> 00:17:17,740
Thank you.

265
00:17:23,210 --> 00:17:24,360
Thank you.

266
00:17:24,430 --> 00:17:25,760
Where is Senator Palmer now?

267
00:17:25,760 --> 00:17:26,850
He's on his way up.

268
00:17:26,850 --> 00:17:27,860
Good.

269
00:17:31,870 --> 00:17:33,040
Excuse me.

270
00:17:39,420 --> 00:17:40,660
Jack Bauer?

271
00:17:41,910 --> 00:17:43,380
Jessica Abrams?

272
00:17:43,800 --> 00:17:47,160
Yeah, Hi. What are you doing here?

273
00:17:47,340 --> 00:17:49,250
I'm working security.

274
00:17:49,940 --> 00:17:51,230
How many years has it been?

275
00:17:51,500 --> 00:17:52,750
Since high school?

276
00:17:53,100 --> 00:17:55,600
Yes. I'm sorry, I've got to get going.

277
00:17:55,600 --> 00:17:57,860
Are you still racing motorcycles?

278
00:17:57,860 --> 00:17:59,430
Keep moving, Jack.

279
00:17:59,510 --> 00:18:01,450
Not since my daughter was born.

280
00:18:02,200 --> 00:18:03,000
I'd like to catch up.

281
00:18:03,000 --> 00:18:04,980
Maybe later. I've just got to get going.

282
00:18:04,980 --> 00:18:06,350
Great, I'll be here.

283
00:18:06,350 --> 00:18:07,530
Okay.

284
00:18:11,160 --> 00:18:12,780
What do I do now?

285
00:18:12,780 --> 00:18:15,530
You'll hand the briefcase to one of our people.

286
00:18:15,540 --> 00:18:16,630
Who?

287
00:18:16,630 --> 00:18:18,460
I'll tell you when it's time.

288
00:18:18,610 --> 00:18:20,850
Go wait by the buffet table.

289
00:18:37,650 --> 00:18:41,270
But now our election coverage shifts to the polls.

290
00:18:41,340 --> 00:18:44,710
Back east, we've had some interesting developments.

291
00:19:16,580 --> 00:19:17,970
Good to see you.

292
00:19:22,990 --> 00:19:25,940
Senator, I'd like you to meet Martin Belkin.

293
00:19:26,790 --> 00:19:28,310
Good you could make it, Martin.

294
00:19:28,310 --> 00:19:29,620
Jessica says you're the best.

295
00:19:29,620 --> 00:19:30,820
Thank you.

296
00:19:32,660 --> 00:19:34,600
I look forward to working with you.

297
00:19:50,950 --> 00:19:54,300
Honey, you're so tired.

298
00:20:26,700 --> 00:20:28,050
Hi.

299
00:20:31,770 --> 00:20:33,630
I brought you some breakfast.

300
00:20:42,060 --> 00:20:43,430
Is Kim okay?

301
00:20:43,430 --> 00:20:44,730
Who are you?

302
00:20:45,420 --> 00:20:46,470
Rick.

303
00:20:46,500 --> 00:20:48,070
You kidnapped my daughter.

304
00:20:48,080 --> 00:20:49,060
I didn't know.

305
00:20:49,060 --> 00:20:50,400
How could you not know?

306
00:20:51,680 --> 00:20:53,110
I tried to help her get out, okay?

307
00:20:53,110 --> 00:20:55,400
Gaines wants to go over some stuff with us.

308
00:20:58,290 --> 00:20:59,630
What's going on here, Rick?

309
00:20:59,630 --> 00:21:00,870
Nothing.

310
00:21:02,520 --> 00:21:03,990
Better if you don't make friends.

311
00:21:03,990 --> 00:21:04,850
I wasn't.

312
00:21:04,850 --> 00:21:06,910
Good, they ain't gonna be around much longer.

313
00:21:06,910 --> 00:21:08,280
- What do you mean? - Move it.

314
00:21:20,640 --> 00:21:23,640
Okay, time to move, Jack. Head across the floor.

315
00:21:25,190 --> 00:21:26,520
Excuse me.

316
00:21:28,360 --> 00:21:29,720
Excuse me.

317
00:21:32,640 --> 00:21:34,980
Okay, Jack, head towards the south wall.

318
00:21:35,890 --> 00:21:37,190
Hello, Jack.

319
00:21:37,190 --> 00:21:38,450
Hello, Jess.

320
00:21:39,840 --> 00:21:42,250
Do you remember Tracy Zigler?

321
00:21:42,250 --> 00:21:44,670
Yes. I just saw her last winter.

322
00:21:44,680 --> 00:21:48,990
Well, we keep in touch and she said you and Teri got divorced.

323
00:21:48,990 --> 00:21:50,680
Get out of there, Jack.

324
00:21:50,680 --> 00:21:54,280
No, we just got separated.

325
00:21:59,420 --> 00:22:01,130
Jared, take care of this.

326
00:22:01,290 --> 00:22:05,580
If you want to get in touch, reach me at this number here.

327
00:22:09,090 --> 00:22:10,110
Are you all right?

328
00:22:10,110 --> 00:22:11,180
No, I'm fine.

329
00:22:11,180 --> 00:22:13,380
- Sorry. - No, it's fine.

330
00:22:13,380 --> 00:22:14,920
- You sure? - Yeah.

331
00:22:23,170 --> 00:22:24,960
He's heading across now.

332
00:22:27,850 --> 00:22:30,310
Make a left in front of the turbines, Jack.

333
00:22:38,340 --> 00:22:39,830
Show him your ID.

334
00:22:40,680 --> 00:22:42,440
Jack Bauer, CTU.

335
00:22:42,620 --> 00:22:44,190
That's my boy.

336
00:22:47,980 --> 00:22:49,760
- Thank you. - Thank you.

337
00:23:00,350 --> 00:23:01,740
Go to the end.

338
00:23:04,650 --> 00:23:07,580
On the left is Medical Station 3.

339
00:23:17,060 --> 00:23:18,150
I'm here.

340
00:23:18,150 --> 00:23:20,420
It's where I want you. Go in and wait.

341
00:23:46,450 --> 00:23:48,130
Oh, my god. What happened to you?

342
00:23:49,110 --> 00:23:50,420
I'm okay.

343
00:23:51,960 --> 00:23:53,220
You don't look okay.

344
00:23:58,670 --> 00:23:59,850
Is it safe to come in here?

345
00:23:59,850 --> 00:24:02,020
Yeah, I looped the cameras between here and the ITS room.

346
00:24:02,020 --> 00:24:03,000
They can't see us.

347
00:24:05,270 --> 00:24:06,990
Why is Jack doing all this?

348
00:24:07,030 --> 00:24:09,040
They've kidnapped his wife and daughter.

349
00:24:10,030 --> 00:24:11,300
How long have you known this?

350
00:24:11,300 --> 00:24:12,450
Not long.

351
00:24:12,940 --> 00:24:14,630
You chose not to tell me.

352
00:24:14,630 --> 00:24:16,620
That's right. I was acting on orders.

353
00:24:16,620 --> 00:24:17,820
Screw orders!

354
00:24:17,820 --> 00:24:19,590
Tony, I'm sorry.

355
00:24:20,500 --> 00:24:21,530
Where's Jamey?

356
00:24:21,530 --> 00:24:23,280
She's still working with Milo.

357
00:24:24,330 --> 00:24:25,560
So what do you want to do?

358
00:24:25,560 --> 00:24:28,270
You want to restrain her and call in Division?

359
00:24:28,270 --> 00:24:30,130
No, we can't call anyone yet.

360
00:24:30,430 --> 00:24:32,230
- We've gotta do something. - I know.

361
00:24:32,780 --> 00:24:35,140
This whole thing must be about Palmer.

362
00:24:35,280 --> 00:24:37,460
They're using Jack to stop the investigation?

363
00:24:37,460 --> 00:24:38,610
Maybe.

364
00:24:38,910 --> 00:24:41,050
Hang on. We've got to do something.

365
00:24:44,220 --> 00:24:45,420
Are you sure this room is dark?

366
00:24:45,420 --> 00:24:48,050
I checked the log. There are no active cameras.

367
00:24:50,500 --> 00:24:52,250
We should've called Secret Service.

368
00:24:52,430 --> 00:24:53,920
No. But if we do that, that's possible

369
00:24:53,920 --> 00:24:56,430
the people holding Teri and Kim will think Jack gave the order.

370
00:24:56,430 --> 00:24:57,410
I hate to be the one to say it,

371
00:24:57,410 --> 00:24:58,390
but it's not our problem.

372
00:24:58,390 --> 00:25:00,330
We have one mandate, protect Palmer.

373
00:25:00,330 --> 00:25:01,860
We got to make the call now.

374
00:25:02,010 --> 00:25:02,920
Wait.

375
00:25:03,400 --> 00:25:05,690
Jack wouldn't put Palmer's life in danger.

376
00:25:05,870 --> 00:25:08,360
Let's try to find out more before we do anything.

377
00:25:08,530 --> 00:25:10,680
Are you ordering me not to call Secret Service?

378
00:25:15,660 --> 00:25:16,970
No, you're right.

379
00:25:22,440 --> 00:25:25,170
Hi, it's Tony. Can you get me Agent Pierce's number?

380
00:25:47,870 --> 00:25:49,220
Assemble it.

381
00:26:30,910 --> 00:26:32,760
You want my prints on this weapon?

382
00:26:35,770 --> 00:26:36,660
Do you really think that

383
00:26:36,660 --> 00:26:39,440
anybody's going to believe that I shot David Palmer?

384
00:26:55,690 --> 00:26:58,560
You better put that away. Somebody might get hurt.

385
00:27:23,520 --> 00:27:25,440
Well, we're watching Senator Palmer

386
00:27:25,440 --> 00:27:28,810
work the room here for a little bit before he gives the speech.

387
00:27:35,410 --> 00:27:36,620
Milo, come here.

388
00:27:38,510 --> 00:27:39,660
You were right.

389
00:27:40,120 --> 00:27:41,250
About what?

390
00:27:41,520 --> 00:27:44,450
The keycard was a forgery. We found the original.

391
00:27:44,450 --> 00:27:46,530
- Where? - Jack's office.

392
00:27:46,940 --> 00:27:48,270
Why did he swap it out?

393
00:27:48,270 --> 00:27:49,360
It doesn't matter.

394
00:27:49,370 --> 00:27:52,770
Look, I sent it to Archiving to make a backup of all the data.

395
00:27:52,770 --> 00:27:54,690
When it's done, it's going straight to you.

396
00:27:54,690 --> 00:27:56,200
You'll have to work quickly.

397
00:27:56,200 --> 00:27:57,840
Just get it to me.

398
00:28:01,020 --> 00:28:02,760
A forged keycard?

399
00:28:02,870 --> 00:28:04,320
What's that about?

400
00:28:04,640 --> 00:28:05,970
I have no idea.

401
00:28:18,380 --> 00:28:19,750
She's squirming.

402
00:28:24,830 --> 00:28:26,010
Almeida.

403
00:28:26,390 --> 00:28:28,050
This is Pierce from Secret Service.

404
00:28:28,050 --> 00:28:30,120
Yeah, Aaron. I called you because we have

405
00:28:30,120 --> 00:28:32,030
some new information you should know about.

406
00:28:32,150 --> 00:28:33,760
One of our agents, Jack Bauer,

407
00:28:33,770 --> 00:28:34,790
might be there this morning.

408
00:28:34,790 --> 00:28:36,710
Yes, he's here. I cleared him.

409
00:28:36,710 --> 00:28:38,230
Well...

410
00:28:38,420 --> 00:28:40,430
we learned that he may have been compromised.

411
00:28:40,820 --> 00:28:42,930
He may not be acting to protect the senator.

412
00:28:42,940 --> 00:28:44,610
Are you saying he's a threat?

413
00:28:46,820 --> 00:28:50,200
Yeah. Take the appropriate actions.

414
00:28:51,010 --> 00:28:52,230
She's on the move.

415
00:29:05,580 --> 00:29:08,470
Okay, ladies restroom. Second to last stall.

416
00:29:08,470 --> 00:29:10,610
Remember, these cameras are on a 20-second loop.

417
00:29:10,610 --> 00:29:11,600
Am I clear?

418
00:29:11,600 --> 00:29:12,970
No, not yet.

419
00:29:28,210 --> 00:29:30,170
Go. Got 20 seconds.

420
00:29:38,530 --> 00:29:40,340
Get out! Now!

421
00:29:40,590 --> 00:29:41,760
Get out!

422
00:29:43,550 --> 00:29:46,500
Pick it! Grab it! All of it. Go!

423
00:29:53,590 --> 00:29:58,040
Can you tell if expectations are high in the party for the speech?

424
00:29:58,940 --> 00:30:00,420
I got to keep you guys working.

425
00:30:00,420 --> 00:30:03,310
The fatter your paycheck, the more taxes you can afford.

426
00:30:04,970 --> 00:30:06,300
That's right, Senator.

427
00:30:06,950 --> 00:30:08,320
Excuse me, guys.

428
00:30:09,540 --> 00:30:10,530
What's up?

429
00:30:10,530 --> 00:30:12,350
I just got a call from CTU.

430
00:30:12,350 --> 00:30:14,040
We need to get you out, sir.

431
00:30:14,040 --> 00:30:15,030
Why?

432
00:30:15,030 --> 00:30:17,570
There's a problem with one of their agents.

433
00:30:17,750 --> 00:30:18,990
What kind of problem?

434
00:30:18,990 --> 00:30:20,780
He could be a threat to you.

435
00:30:21,820 --> 00:30:22,730
If he's one of ours,

436
00:30:22,730 --> 00:30:25,160
why don't you find him and take care of this quietly?

437
00:30:25,160 --> 00:30:26,880
We are trying, sir.

438
00:30:29,070 --> 00:30:30,270
I'll tell you what.

439
00:30:30,540 --> 00:30:33,120
I'll lose the face time, but the speech stays.

440
00:30:33,130 --> 00:30:35,240
There's something I have to say this morning.

441
00:30:35,250 --> 00:30:37,680
With all due respect, I think it's a mistake, sir.

442
00:30:37,680 --> 00:30:41,220
This information comes directly from CTU headquarters.

443
00:30:43,030 --> 00:30:46,450
I am sure your people will take care of this.

444
00:30:54,440 --> 00:30:57,120
All Right! Everyone on the floor, listen up. This is Pierce.

445
00:30:57,860 --> 00:31:00,080
Palmer has decided to proceed.

446
00:31:00,080 --> 00:31:02,540
I repeat, Palmer will remain.

447
00:31:02,890 --> 00:31:05,920
We need to locate and detain a suspect...

448
00:31:05,920 --> 00:31:08,470
...whose name is Jack Bauer.

449
00:31:08,470 --> 00:31:10,520
Bauer is 5'11".

450
00:31:10,530 --> 00:31:13,030
Blond hair, 160 pounds.

451
00:31:13,030 --> 00:31:18,370
He is wearing a dark brown jacket that may display CTU ID.

452
00:31:18,560 --> 00:31:20,820
This is Hayes. I have possible 20 on Bauer.

453
00:31:20,820 --> 00:31:22,290
How would you like me to proceed?

454
00:31:22,290 --> 00:31:24,330
All right. Hold your position. I'll be right there.

455
00:31:24,330 --> 00:31:25,520
Copy.

456
00:31:35,410 --> 00:31:36,640
Hi, Jamey.

457
00:31:39,250 --> 00:31:40,640
What's this all about?

458
00:31:41,820 --> 00:31:43,200
Why don't you tell us?

459
00:31:43,400 --> 00:31:45,170
I have no idea what you're talking about.

460
00:31:45,220 --> 00:31:47,370
Who were you contacting in the bathroom?

461
00:31:47,370 --> 00:31:49,160
None of your business. It was personal.

462
00:31:49,210 --> 00:31:51,690
Are they the same people who set me up to be killed?

463
00:31:51,810 --> 00:31:54,430
Set you up to be killed? What are you talking about?

464
00:31:54,430 --> 00:31:55,930
We don't have time for this.

465
00:31:55,930 --> 00:31:59,060
Talk to us, Jamey. Who's got Jack's wife and daughter?

466
00:31:59,860 --> 00:32:02,300
- What are they making Jack do? - I don't know.

467
00:32:03,560 --> 00:32:06,360
Richard Walsh is dead. So is Scott Baylor.

468
00:32:06,360 --> 00:32:08,290
You'll be charged with murder and treason.

469
00:32:08,300 --> 00:32:10,860
I suggest you start telling me what's going on.

470
00:32:12,300 --> 00:32:13,920
They said no one would get hurt.

471
00:32:13,920 --> 00:32:15,340
Who are they?

472
00:32:15,880 --> 00:32:17,010
I can't tell you.

473
00:32:17,010 --> 00:32:18,590
Tell us everything you know!

474
00:32:18,590 --> 00:32:19,800
It's your only way out of this!

475
00:32:19,800 --> 00:32:21,120
Do you understand!

476
00:32:23,480 --> 00:32:24,550
I was just supposed to tap

477
00:32:24,550 --> 00:32:27,970
into the surveillance of all the security cameras.

478
00:32:28,480 --> 00:32:31,220
Then they asked me to send messages from inside.

479
00:32:31,220 --> 00:32:32,680
What messages?

480
00:32:33,460 --> 00:32:34,930
What messages!

481
00:32:38,460 --> 00:32:40,090
Mostly about Jack.

482
00:32:41,320 --> 00:32:43,040
Then about the keycard.

483
00:32:45,100 --> 00:32:47,950
I didn't know this was going to happen. You have to believe that.

484
00:32:47,950 --> 00:32:51,180
OK, fine, we do. But now you have to help us.

485
00:32:51,570 --> 00:32:53,320
Who were you doing all this for?

486
00:32:55,740 --> 00:32:57,830
No. I have to talk to someone first.

487
00:32:57,830 --> 00:33:00,390
What? No! There is no time, Jamey.

488
00:33:00,390 --> 00:33:03,120
Palmer is exposed. Jack's family is in danger.

489
00:33:03,120 --> 00:33:05,750
You have to start talking to us now!

490
00:33:09,060 --> 00:33:10,480
All right, Jamey.

491
00:33:10,830 --> 00:33:12,090
I'll make sure everything you tell us

492
00:33:12,090 --> 00:33:13,620
goes into cutting you a deal, okay?

493
00:33:17,450 --> 00:33:21,890
No. I'm not saying anything, not until i get agency counsel

494
00:33:45,790 --> 00:33:47,070
Sit!

495
00:33:48,370 --> 00:33:51,880
As Mayor of LA, I'm often given the opportunity

496
00:33:51,880 --> 00:33:54,640
to meet some truly remarkable people.

497
00:33:54,640 --> 00:33:56,560
People that strive for the greater unity.

498
00:33:56,560 --> 00:33:59,270
People that work to make our world a better place.

499
00:33:59,270 --> 00:34:01,470
One of those people is here today.

500
00:34:01,470 --> 00:34:04,900
And "remarkable" only begins to describe this man.

501
00:34:04,900 --> 00:34:08,120
Ladies and gentlemen, the next president of the United States

502
00:34:08,120 --> 00:34:10,940
and my good friend, David Palmer.

503
00:34:34,090 --> 00:34:35,460
I love you, Kimberly.

504
00:34:36,620 --> 00:34:37,810
You know that?

505
00:34:38,740 --> 00:34:39,710
Yeah.

506
00:34:42,800 --> 00:34:43,910
Good.

507
00:34:46,080 --> 00:34:47,890
It's important that you know that.

508
00:34:50,440 --> 00:34:53,090
Mom, if you're feeling guilty about our fight yesterday

509
00:34:53,880 --> 00:34:55,030
I'm over it.

510
00:34:55,590 --> 00:34:56,650
I just want to get home.

511
00:34:56,650 --> 00:34:58,010
It's not why I'm saying that.

512
00:34:58,820 --> 00:35:01,250
We're stuck in this awful place

513
00:35:01,250 --> 00:35:03,970
and I just want you to know that you're not alone.

514
00:35:07,790 --> 00:35:09,240
Mom, you're scaring me.

515
00:35:11,870 --> 00:35:14,690
Sounds like you're saying this 'cause something bad will happen.

516
00:35:15,640 --> 00:35:17,070
No, no.

517
00:35:20,070 --> 00:35:21,270
It's just....

518
00:35:24,360 --> 00:35:27,130
I'm trying to explain to you what a simple,

519
00:35:27,130 --> 00:35:29,900
powerful thing my love for you is.

520
00:35:32,550 --> 00:35:34,450
So, no matter how bad things get...

521
00:35:34,450 --> 00:35:37,950
or how good they get, that's not going to change.

522
00:35:41,340 --> 00:35:44,300
I just don't know how to do anything but love you.

523
00:36:05,200 --> 00:36:06,320
Thank you.

524
00:36:07,080 --> 00:36:08,440
Thank you very much.

525
00:36:10,350 --> 00:36:11,540
Thank you.

526
00:36:12,320 --> 00:36:13,640
I'll be right back.

527
00:36:14,230 --> 00:36:15,560
Thank you.

528
00:36:17,700 --> 00:36:19,190
Thank you, Mayor Nelson.

529
00:36:20,150 --> 00:36:23,590
And thank you, kind citizens of Los Angeles.

530
00:36:29,360 --> 00:36:31,220
Identification, please.

531
00:36:31,310 --> 00:36:32,140
You know, this country

532
00:36:32,140 --> 00:36:35,010
depends on a healthy economy in California.

533
00:36:37,950 --> 00:36:41,450
And the nucleus of that economy is energy.

534
00:36:41,760 --> 00:36:43,470
All right, Jack. Step out.

535
00:36:43,640 --> 00:36:45,210
We're ready for you.

536
00:36:46,670 --> 00:36:48,070
To do what?

537
00:36:48,300 --> 00:36:50,980
Relax. It will be over in five minutes.

538
00:36:52,130 --> 00:36:55,400
...is standing right here in this room today.

539
00:36:59,740 --> 00:37:01,250
It's you!

540
00:37:01,320 --> 00:37:03,300
Do you see the photographer?

541
00:37:03,300 --> 00:37:05,390
The men and women who serve this industry

542
00:37:05,390 --> 00:37:06,420
Yes.

543
00:37:07,100 --> 00:37:08,820
Go over and join him.

544
00:37:18,610 --> 00:37:22,010
After he shoots Palmer, he will hand you his weapon.

545
00:37:22,600 --> 00:37:24,130
You've got to be kidding me.

546
00:37:24,130 --> 00:37:25,860
I know you'll be tempted to intervene

547
00:37:25,860 --> 00:37:27,540
but you must believe me, Jack

548
00:37:27,540 --> 00:37:31,300
if you do, your family dies and we'll get Palmer anyway.

549
00:37:33,460 --> 00:37:34,840
I understand.

550
00:37:34,840 --> 00:37:38,600
When I started my campaign, over a year ago...

551
00:37:39,460 --> 00:37:42,410
I made a promise to you who've supported me.

552
00:37:42,960 --> 00:37:47,280
That my campaign would be built on integrity, commitment

553
00:37:47,280 --> 00:37:49,230
and above all, honor.

554
00:37:53,420 --> 00:37:54,530
Thank you.

555
00:37:57,690 --> 00:37:59,020
Thank you.

556
00:38:03,310 --> 00:38:04,940
Palmer!

557
00:38:04,940 --> 00:38:06,030
Thank you.

558
00:38:08,740 --> 00:38:11,620
Integrity, commitment, honor.

559
00:38:12,540 --> 00:38:15,270
Anything less would be unacceptable.

560
00:38:15,980 --> 00:38:17,340
Agent Bauer.

561
00:38:18,370 --> 00:38:21,510
Alan Hayes, Secret Service. I need you to come with me.

562
00:38:21,510 --> 00:38:23,960
- What's the matter? - No problem. Just come with me.

563
00:38:30,230 --> 00:38:32,190
Seven years ago

564
00:38:33,650 --> 00:38:34,800
Gun!

565
00:38:35,800 --> 00:38:37,230
Blanket Palmer.

566
00:38:41,130 --> 00:38:42,920
- Get him out of here. - Get Sherry.

567
00:38:43,970 --> 00:38:45,230
I can't see exactly

568
00:38:45,230 --> 00:38:46,830
Palmer's being shielded.

569
00:38:46,830 --> 00:38:48,050
But why?

570
00:38:48,410 --> 00:38:50,350
Bauer? Bauer? What's happening?

571
00:38:50,350 --> 00:38:51,960
Did you screw me?

572
00:38:52,680 --> 00:38:53,950
I didn't do this.

573
00:38:54,040 --> 00:38:55,250
Do you understand?

574
00:38:55,250 --> 00:38:57,630
Please, don't hurt my family.

575
00:39:00,270 --> 00:39:01,450
Don't hurt my family.

576
00:39:01,450 --> 00:39:03,780
I'll help. I promise. Please!

577
00:39:03,780 --> 00:39:05,820
That's it, we're done. Kill the wife and kid!

578
00:39:13,170 --> 00:39:14,630
Get out of here!

580
00:39:33,840 --> 00:39:35,570
I don't have time for this.

581
00:39:46,830 --> 00:39:48,280
- Hello? - What do you want?

582
00:39:48,280 --> 00:39:51,160
I just find out Division picked up Bauer at the power plant.

583
00:39:51,210 --> 00:39:52,620
They've been looking for him all night.

584
00:39:52,620 --> 00:39:53,380
Why?

585
00:39:53,380 --> 00:39:55,420
I assume it's because he's been breaking protocol

586
00:39:55,420 --> 00:39:56,670
since you got to him.

587
00:39:56,670 --> 00:39:57,770
Damn it!

588
00:39:59,920 --> 00:40:00,910
Take me!

589
00:40:03,360 --> 00:40:04,280
No!

590
00:40:07,810 --> 00:40:08,950
No!

591
00:40:18,550 --> 00:40:20,760
Mom! No!

592
00:40:25,270 --> 00:40:26,470
No!

593
00:40:31,840 --> 00:40:32,510
Don't!

594
00:40:32,510 --> 00:40:34,670
Please don't....

595
00:40:48,970 --> 00:40:50,190
Eli.

596
00:40:50,670 --> 00:40:51,770
Yeah.

597
00:40:52,510 --> 00:40:54,330
I still need them alive.

598
00:40:55,280 --> 00:40:56,540
Both of them?

599
00:41:09,180 --> 00:41:11,750
Yes. Take them back.

600
00:41:24,060 --> 00:41:27,550
No! No!

