4
00:00:20,190 --> 00:00:23,320
She's crashing, BP's falling. Get Dr. Collier.

5
00:00:23,320 --> 00:00:25,540
- She's on her way. - What have we got?

6
00:00:25,540 --> 00:00:27,580
BP's dropping. She's in V-tach.

7
00:00:27,580 --> 00:00:29,200
BP's crashing at 90/50.

8
00:00:29,200 --> 00:00:31,470
Give her an amp of epi, and let's go at 200.

9
00:00:31,470 --> 00:00:32,700
Yes, Doctor.

10
00:00:33,520 --> 00:00:34,540
Epi's in.

11
00:00:36,670 --> 00:00:38,610
- Go ahead. - Start.

12
00:00:38,760 --> 00:00:39,980
- Clear. - Clear.

13
00:00:42,540 --> 00:00:43,420
Nothing.

14
00:00:44,030 --> 00:00:46,260
- Again, 300. - 300.

15
00:00:46,260 --> 00:00:48,340
- 300. Charge. - Clear.

16
00:00:50,480 --> 00:00:51,800
Blood pressure still dropping.

17
00:00:51,800 --> 00:00:52,790
Nothing.

18
00:00:53,880 --> 00:00:54,860
Doctor.

19
00:00:55,760 --> 00:00:58,680
- Go again. - 360. Charge.

20
00:00:58,680 --> 00:01:00,830
Clear.

21
00:01:02,350 --> 00:01:04,500
No rhythm.

22
00:01:08,230 --> 00:01:10,990
One more time.

23
00:01:11,000 --> 00:01:13,000
- Charge. - 360. Charge.

24
00:01:13,000 --> 00:01:16,380
- All right, clear. - Clear.

25
00:01:20,500 --> 00:01:22,210
- Hello? - Hey, it's me.

26
00:01:22,210 --> 00:01:23,210
Jack, where are you?

27
00:01:23,210 --> 00:01:24,910
I'm still on the West Side.

28
00:01:24,910 --> 00:01:26,910
You said you were coming to the hospital.

29
00:01:26,910 --> 00:01:28,910
I'll be there soon. Is Janet out of surgery yet?

30
00:01:28,910 --> 00:01:32,420
There's been a complication. They're working on it now.

31
00:01:32,420 --> 00:01:33,480
Listen to me. Do not let

32
00:01:33,480 --> 00:01:35,890
anyone near Janet who doesn't belong there.

33
00:01:35,890 --> 00:01:37,220
What do you mean?

34
00:01:37,220 --> 00:01:38,220
I think she might be in danger.

35
00:01:38,220 --> 00:01:39,220
From whom?

36
00:01:39,220 --> 00:01:40,720
I'll explain when I get there.

37
00:01:40,720 --> 00:01:43,260
- Until then, do not mention this to anyone, okay? - Okay.

38
00:01:43,260 --> 00:01:44,990
- I'll be there soon. - Okay.

39
00:01:45,000 --> 00:01:46,780
Give her another amp of epi at 360.

40
00:01:46,780 --> 00:01:48,280
Epi's in.

41
00:01:48,280 --> 00:01:50,180
Clear!

42
00:01:58,160 --> 00:01:59,160
Whose car?

43
00:01:59,160 --> 00:02:01,870
Penticoff was paid to pick it up and get rid of this.

44
00:02:05,470 --> 00:02:07,910
Oh, my God. Who is it?

45
00:02:07,910 --> 00:02:08,970
That's what you're gonna find out.

46
00:02:08,970 --> 00:02:11,630
But somehow all of this is connected to Senator Palmer.

47
00:02:13,890 --> 00:02:15,240
Didn't leave much of his face.

48
00:02:15,240 --> 00:02:17,490
They also cut his fingers and pulled his teeth.

49
00:02:17,490 --> 00:02:18,150
Is forensics here yet?

50
00:02:18,150 --> 00:02:19,910
Not yet, he's on his way.

51
00:02:21,450 --> 00:02:23,410
Call me as soon as you've got a name.

52
00:02:28,810 --> 00:02:31,420
Nina, I need a favor.

53
00:02:31,820 --> 00:02:33,760
It's starting to add up, Jack.

54
00:02:34,130 --> 00:02:37,450
Don't let anyone know I requisitioned this for personal use.

55
00:02:37,450 --> 00:02:38,510
Personal use?

56
00:02:38,510 --> 00:02:41,900
Yes, could you please pass me through to hospital security?

57
00:02:42,280 --> 00:02:43,460
Thank you.

58
00:02:43,840 --> 00:02:46,290
You know Kim's friend, the one she went out with tonight?

59
00:02:46,560 --> 00:02:49,340
She turned up at St. Mark's ER. She got hit by a car.

60
00:02:49,340 --> 00:02:51,140
Does she know where Kimberly is?

61
00:02:51,140 --> 00:02:52,210
It's the only chance I've got.

62
00:02:52,210 --> 00:02:53,890
I'm meeting Teri at the hospital now.

63
00:02:53,890 --> 00:02:56,360
Get me that name. Yes, hello?

64
00:02:56,360 --> 00:02:58,770
My name is Jack Bauer, I'm a federal agent.

65
00:02:58,770 --> 00:03:00,190
I'm coming to you now.

66
00:03:00,190 --> 00:03:03,100
But I wanted to give you a heads-up on one of your patients.

67
00:03:03,110 --> 00:03:05,880
I think her life might be in danger.

68
00:03:06,570 --> 00:03:10,350
Yes, I'll be there in 10 minutes. Her name is Janet York.

69
00:03:15,420 --> 00:03:17,730
Jack requisitioned a chopper 15 minutes ago

70
00:03:17,740 --> 00:03:20,310
but he didn't log a destination. Where's he going?

71
00:03:20,380 --> 00:03:21,590
He's tracking a lead.

72
00:03:21,590 --> 00:03:22,960
Ignoring protocol again.

73
00:03:22,960 --> 00:03:25,390
First he assaults an agent to avoid lockdown.

74
00:03:25,390 --> 00:03:27,000
Then he breaks a prisoner out of jail.

75
00:03:27,000 --> 00:03:27,820
What's the hell's going on here?

76
00:03:27,820 --> 00:03:29,010
I thought we were suppose to be...

77
00:03:29,020 --> 00:03:30,790
Stop following me, Tony!

78
00:03:33,140 --> 00:03:35,460
I prefer to think of it as watching your back.

79
00:03:35,470 --> 00:03:38,070
When I need your help, I'll ask for it.

80
00:03:56,900 --> 00:03:59,470
Yeah, we got a little off-schedule, but we're good now.

81
00:04:00,040 --> 00:04:02,160
Yeah, I know. It's already done.

82
00:04:09,200 --> 00:04:11,000
See what happens when you lie?

83
00:04:14,170 --> 00:04:15,820
Don't ever lie to me, Rick.

84
00:04:15,830 --> 00:04:16,910
I won't.

85
00:04:17,090 --> 00:04:18,540
Oh, I know you won't.

86
00:04:19,700 --> 00:04:21,270
Now bury your friend.

87
00:04:21,780 --> 00:04:24,210
- Where? - In the ground.

88
00:04:25,280 --> 00:04:30,280
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

89
00:04:25,280 --> 00:04:30,280
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

90
00:04:25,280 --> 00:04:30,280
{\an5}{\pos(145,252)}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

91
00:04:25,780 --> 00:04:30,280
{\pos(67,248)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

92
00:04:25,780 --> 00:04:30,280
{\pos(67,248)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

93
00:04:25,780 --> 00:04:30,280
{\pos(58,238)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

94
00:04:25,780 --> 00:04:30,280
{\pos(84,248)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

97
00:04:31,500 --> 00:04:56,500
{\an9}m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

98
00:04:31,000 --> 00:04:56,500
{\an2}{\pos(26,248)}m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

104
00:04:51,980 --> 00:04:53,400
We've got to get out of here.

105
00:04:53,680 --> 00:04:55,120
What do you mean, "we"?

106
00:04:55,120 --> 00:04:56,800
I don't know how you hooked up with these guys.

107
00:04:56,800 --> 00:04:58,820
They obviously don't trust you.

108
00:04:58,820 --> 00:05:01,230
You just saw Gaines kill your friend.

109
00:05:01,420 --> 00:05:02,570
He's not gonna let you walk away.

110
00:05:02,570 --> 00:05:03,650
Shut up.

111
00:05:03,660 --> 00:05:06,310
The only way either of us is going to stay alive is if get..

112
00:05:06,310 --> 00:05:07,930
I said shut up!

113
00:05:20,620 --> 00:05:23,510
Sources close to the campaign say the Senator spent the night

114
00:05:23,510 --> 00:05:25,320
working on a party unification speech

115
00:05:25,320 --> 00:05:27,440
which he's set to deliver later.

116
00:05:28,430 --> 00:05:30,880
How did you get past Secret Service?

117
00:05:31,260 --> 00:05:32,810
Good to see you too, Sherry.

118
00:05:32,810 --> 00:05:35,920
You listen. David has to prep for a breakfast meeting.

119
00:05:35,930 --> 00:05:38,310
And the polls are opening in an hour, so whatever you're doing...

120
00:05:38,310 --> 00:05:39,980
David asked me to come.

121
00:05:40,090 --> 00:05:41,890
- Why, Carl? - I don't know.

122
00:05:52,880 --> 00:05:56,040
I gotta get ready, and so do you.

123
00:06:01,650 --> 00:06:03,530
So, what's the big emergency, David?

124
00:06:03,530 --> 00:06:06,030
- Thought we had a game plan. - We did.

125
00:06:06,480 --> 00:06:08,980
Until I found out that my son lied to me.

126
00:06:10,220 --> 00:06:12,660
That he's been lying for seven years.

127
00:06:13,380 --> 00:06:14,620
What's going on?

128
00:06:16,340 --> 00:06:18,420
Why would Maureen Kingsley

129
00:06:19,240 --> 00:06:21,750
run a story this big unless it were true?

130
00:06:21,840 --> 00:06:24,790
Are you saying you believe her accusation about Keith?

131
00:06:25,040 --> 00:06:27,960
I'm saying, my son was involved in Gibson's death

132
00:06:28,330 --> 00:06:29,780
and you covered it up.

133
00:06:30,090 --> 00:06:33,410
Not only from the law, from me.

134
00:06:34,610 --> 00:06:37,270
- David. - Someone altered the hospital records

135
00:06:37,270 --> 00:06:39,780
to make it look like Keith wasn't involved.

136
00:06:40,040 --> 00:06:41,710
That could only have been you.

137
00:06:45,540 --> 00:06:46,970
Look me in the eye

138
00:06:49,020 --> 00:06:50,550
and tell me what happened.

139
00:06:53,560 --> 00:06:54,900
You sure you want to know?

140
00:06:55,230 --> 00:06:58,020
You might not like what you find if you open that door.

141
00:06:59,380 --> 00:07:02,450
It's already open. I'm listening.

142
00:07:13,280 --> 00:07:15,910
The night Gibson raped Nicole

143
00:07:16,290 --> 00:07:18,380
while Sherry was still at the hospital

144
00:07:18,380 --> 00:07:20,030
and you were flying back,

145
00:07:20,030 --> 00:07:22,250
Keith went to see Gibson.

146
00:07:24,310 --> 00:07:25,590
How do you know this?

147
00:07:26,850 --> 00:07:30,050
Keith told me. Your son came to me, David.

148
00:07:30,100 --> 00:07:31,950
He said Gibson pulled a knife.

149
00:07:31,950 --> 00:07:35,040
I... took him at his word. It was an accident.

150
00:07:35,040 --> 00:07:36,650
He was defending himself.

151
00:07:38,690 --> 00:07:42,050
So you made it look like...Keith was never there.

152
00:07:42,050 --> 00:07:44,550
As far as I was concerned, he never was.

153
00:07:44,730 --> 00:07:46,830
Why didn't we just go to the police?

154
00:07:47,240 --> 00:07:50,190
If it really was self-defense, Keith would have been cleared.

155
00:07:50,190 --> 00:07:52,500
Maybe. But your career would have been over.

156
00:07:53,170 --> 00:07:55,030
Gibson was white, David.

157
00:07:58,760 --> 00:08:01,190
I still wouldn't have covered it up.

158
00:08:01,780 --> 00:08:03,040
Are you so sure?

159
00:08:03,040 --> 00:08:05,750
It was my decision, not yours.

160
00:08:11,170 --> 00:08:13,570
I don't want you anywhere near me

161
00:08:15,820 --> 00:08:18,740
or my family, ever again.

162
00:08:19,890 --> 00:08:23,450
You have never needed me more than you need me now.

163
00:08:28,890 --> 00:08:29,930
Get out.

164
00:08:37,380 --> 00:08:39,850
Before you finish crucifying me,

165
00:08:42,270 --> 00:08:44,290
save some nails for your wife.

166
00:08:45,750 --> 00:08:47,890
Sherry didn't know anything about this.

167
00:08:48,000 --> 00:08:48,960
No?

168
00:08:49,320 --> 00:08:51,850
How do you think Keith got to me in the first place?

169
00:09:30,260 --> 00:09:32,620
- What are you doing? - What does it look like?

170
00:09:34,660 --> 00:09:37,340
- I said, I don't need.. - I heard.

171
00:09:55,660 --> 00:09:57,480
You think I wanted to leave Janet there?

172
00:09:59,570 --> 00:10:01,340
Everything just got so crazy.

173
00:10:05,560 --> 00:10:07,870
All we had to do was hang out with you guys.

174
00:10:07,870 --> 00:10:09,710
No one was supposed to get hurt.

175
00:10:09,850 --> 00:10:11,450
None of this was supposed to go down.

176
00:10:11,450 --> 00:10:12,630
What did you think was gonna happen?

177
00:10:12,630 --> 00:10:13,820
I don't know.

178
00:10:15,130 --> 00:10:16,720
Smoking that's really gonna help.

179
00:10:18,350 --> 00:10:19,950
I can't believe this is happening.

180
00:10:19,950 --> 00:10:22,890
It is, and you can sit there feeling sorry for yourself

181
00:10:22,890 --> 00:10:23,530
or you can get up and

182
00:10:23,530 --> 00:10:25,720
help me figure out a way to get us out of here.

183
00:10:52,120 --> 00:10:53,700
- West side. - Copy that.

184
00:10:55,580 --> 00:10:56,640
Claude Davenport, Hospital Security.

185
00:10:56,650 --> 00:10:57,330
Jack Bauer.

186
00:10:57,330 --> 00:10:59,720
Thanks for mobilizing your people on such short notice.

187
00:10:59,720 --> 00:11:01,510
I put a man at each end of the ICU corridor,

188
00:11:01,510 --> 00:11:02,820
it should lock it down pretty tight.

189
00:11:02,820 --> 00:11:04,290
They know not to let anyone in or out?

190
00:11:04,290 --> 00:11:06,630
- Only hospital staff, like you asked. - Good.

191
00:11:06,630 --> 00:11:07,960
Wanna let me know what this is about?

192
00:11:07,960 --> 00:11:09,430
I wish I could.

193
00:11:10,530 --> 00:11:12,430
- Teri. - Jack.

194
00:11:14,050 --> 00:11:16,640
- Thank God. - It's okay. It's okay. I'm here now.

195
00:11:19,540 --> 00:11:22,310
Oh, Don't leave me. Don't ever leave me again, okay?

196
00:11:22,310 --> 00:11:23,920
I promise. I won't leave.

197
00:11:25,450 --> 00:11:28,220
Agent Bauer, I'm gonna be walking the floor if you need anything.

198
00:11:28,220 --> 00:11:29,630
Thank you, Claude.

199
00:11:35,060 --> 00:11:36,390
It's gonna be okay.

200
00:11:40,600 --> 00:11:43,850
- Tell me about Janet. - She's stable.

201
00:11:44,170 --> 00:11:46,720
- Can she talk? - No, not yet.

202
00:11:47,560 --> 00:11:50,050
What did you mean before about her being in danger?

203
00:11:50,580 --> 00:11:51,670
Danger from whom?

204
00:11:51,670 --> 00:11:53,730
Someone who doesn't want her talking to me.

205
00:11:53,980 --> 00:11:55,250
You must be Jack?

206
00:11:56,290 --> 00:11:59,650
Alan, yeah, this is my husband, Jack.

207
00:11:59,650 --> 00:12:01,050
- Hi. - Hi.

208
00:12:01,580 --> 00:12:03,870
Alan's been a great friend tonight, Jack.

209
00:12:04,350 --> 00:12:05,600
I'm glad your daughter's okay.

210
00:12:05,600 --> 00:12:07,520
Thank You. Thank you very much.

211
00:12:08,030 --> 00:12:11,020
Gave us a good scare, but she pulled through.

212
00:12:11,020 --> 00:12:11,790
When she's up to it,

213
00:12:11,790 --> 00:12:13,690
I'm going to need to ask her a few questions.

214
00:12:14,180 --> 00:12:16,260
Jack, my daughter's been through a lot.

215
00:12:19,500 --> 00:12:21,210
If the doctor says it's okay.

216
00:12:24,360 --> 00:12:26,360
The guys that Kim and Janet were with tonight,

217
00:12:26,360 --> 00:12:28,120
Teri told me you didn't know them.

218
00:12:29,130 --> 00:12:31,230
No... no, Janet never mentioned them.

219
00:12:31,750 --> 00:12:33,210
Are you close to Janet?

220
00:12:35,490 --> 00:12:36,700
She's my daughter.

221
00:12:36,700 --> 00:12:38,460
But you don't know who she goes out with on a school night?

222
00:12:38,460 --> 00:12:41,550
- Jack? - No, not tonight, I didn't.

223
00:12:41,550 --> 00:12:43,240
But apparently you didn't either.

224
00:12:43,240 --> 00:12:45,680
- What are you doing? - Trying to find where our daughter is.

225
00:12:45,680 --> 00:12:47,420
By treating Alan as a suspect?

226
00:12:47,420 --> 00:12:48,310
He can handle a few questions. I mean,

227
00:12:48,320 --> 00:12:50,890
you understand that right? Our daughter's still missing.

228
00:12:51,190 --> 00:12:52,250
Of course I do.

229
00:12:52,280 --> 00:12:54,620
Alan, would you excuse us for a minute, please?

230
00:12:55,100 --> 00:12:58,680
Jack, what's going on? I don't know what you've been doing

231
00:12:58,680 --> 00:13:01,910
for the last five hours, but Alan was with me tonight.

232
00:13:01,910 --> 00:13:04,210
I'm sorry if that makes you feel bad, but it makes me feel

233
00:13:04,480 --> 00:13:05,530
Hold on one minute.

234
00:13:06,820 --> 00:13:09,210
I'm here to see my brother.

235
00:13:09,210 --> 00:13:10,270
My bag? I'm not gonna open my briefcase.

236
00:13:10,270 --> 00:13:11,190
I'm here to see my brother.

237
00:13:11,190 --> 00:13:14,410
- What's the problem here? - There's no problem.

238
00:13:15,320 --> 00:13:16,270
Sir.

239
00:13:16,480 --> 00:13:17,420
what do you got in the briefcase?

240
00:13:17,420 --> 00:13:18,260
Don't worry about it.

241
00:13:18,260 --> 00:13:20,820
What's in the briefcase?

242
00:13:21,150 --> 00:13:22,700
Get off of me!

243
00:13:24,470 --> 00:13:27,520
- What is this? - It's my medication.

244
00:13:27,740 --> 00:13:28,760
What kind of medication?

245
00:13:28,760 --> 00:13:30,060
Ben?

246
00:13:30,060 --> 00:13:30,860
What is going on?

247
00:13:30,860 --> 00:13:33,170
Virgil's in pain. You aren't giving him what he needs!

248
00:13:33,170 --> 00:13:36,650
We're taking good care of your brother. I told you that yesterday.

249
00:13:36,650 --> 00:13:38,220
His brother's in detox.

250
00:13:38,220 --> 00:13:39,960
He's been trying to sneak him drugs all week.

251
00:13:39,960 --> 00:13:41,210
You guys don't get it!

252
00:13:41,210 --> 00:13:43,080
That's it, out! Let's go!

253
00:13:47,680 --> 00:13:48,810
I'm sorry.

254
00:13:54,770 --> 00:13:55,710
Come on.

255
00:14:12,240 --> 00:14:13,670
What did Carl want?

256
00:14:19,400 --> 00:14:20,830
I know about Keith.

257
00:14:22,540 --> 00:14:24,120
Know what about Keith?

258
00:14:26,600 --> 00:14:29,620
That he went to Carl to cover up the Gibson boy's death.

259
00:14:30,760 --> 00:14:32,510
Keith was there, wasn't he, Sherry?

260
00:14:32,520 --> 00:14:36,210
Just because Carl wants to feed you some story doesn't mean--

261
00:14:36,210 --> 00:14:39,750
Are you sure you're not the one that's feeding me the story?

262
00:14:48,830 --> 00:14:52,290
The thing I can't understand,

263
00:14:52,290 --> 00:14:54,590
what I keep asking myself

264
00:14:56,090 --> 00:14:57,870
is why you hid this from me?

265
00:15:04,830 --> 00:15:07,200
- I wanted to tell you, David, I.. - But you didn't.

266
00:15:07,200 --> 00:15:10,120
- Carl said you'd be exposed! - Don't put this on Carl!

267
00:15:11,930 --> 00:15:14,710
You keep your own counsel, Sherry. You always have.

268
00:15:16,790 --> 00:15:18,240
Nothing I say to you is

269
00:15:18,240 --> 00:15:20,790
going to make you feel any better, I know that.

270
00:15:20,800 --> 00:15:22,900
I did what I thought was right,

271
00:15:22,900 --> 00:15:25,420
for our family and for your career.

272
00:15:37,900 --> 00:15:39,080
What about Nicole?

273
00:15:45,370 --> 00:15:46,570
Does she know, too?

274
00:15:50,820 --> 00:15:52,770
We were protecting you.

275
00:15:52,770 --> 00:15:53,890
- Really? - Yes.

276
00:15:55,300 --> 00:15:58,030
Or were you protecting your chance to move into the White House?

277
00:15:58,090 --> 00:16:00,060
I am as ambitious as you are, David.

278
00:16:00,060 --> 00:16:01,250
That's why you married me.

279
00:16:01,250 --> 00:16:03,560
No, I married you because I loved you.

280
00:16:04,570 --> 00:16:06,640
I thought we were working towards something together.

281
00:16:06,640 --> 00:16:09,180
- We still are. - It doesn't feel that way.

282
00:16:09,400 --> 00:16:10,450
David.

283
00:16:14,440 --> 00:16:16,370
David, what are you gonna do?

284
00:16:18,310 --> 00:16:19,460
I don't know.

285
00:16:20,020 --> 00:16:24,420
Look, you can be as angry at me as you want.

286
00:16:24,420 --> 00:16:27,110
But I'm telling you, we should do everything we can

287
00:16:27,110 --> 00:16:29,500
to keep this thing from coming out.

288
00:16:32,120 --> 00:16:33,490
It's too late for that.

289
00:16:39,730 --> 00:16:42,180
I'm sorry to hear you say that

290
00:16:42,490 --> 00:16:45,860
because you'll lose a lot more than the election if it does.

291
00:16:49,330 --> 00:16:52,440
Are you prepared to send our son to jail?

292
00:17:38,630 --> 00:17:40,830
Everything was always a game with Dan.

293
00:17:41,210 --> 00:17:43,320
He acted like nothing could touch him.

294
00:17:43,940 --> 00:17:45,580
And I bought into it.

295
00:17:45,830 --> 00:17:47,100
So did Janet.

296
00:17:47,720 --> 00:17:49,470
I'd give anything to turn back the clock.

297
00:17:49,470 --> 00:17:50,540
Me, too.

298
00:17:53,790 --> 00:17:56,510
I spend every day trying to get away from my mother.

299
00:17:58,180 --> 00:18:00,340
Now I can't stop wishing she were here.

300
00:18:03,470 --> 00:18:05,250
God, she must be freaking.

301
00:18:06,530 --> 00:18:09,370
Must be nice, having a mom you like.

302
00:18:09,910 --> 00:18:11,110
You don't like yours?

303
00:18:12,210 --> 00:18:14,060
Not all women are meant to be mothers.

304
00:18:16,470 --> 00:18:18,850
- Sorry. - It's not your problem.

305
00:18:22,580 --> 00:18:23,510
Rick.

306
00:18:25,620 --> 00:18:27,060
We've got to get out of here.

307
00:18:33,230 --> 00:18:34,270
Come with me.

308
00:18:38,560 --> 00:18:39,480
Let's go.

309
00:18:46,290 --> 00:18:48,910
Leave the shovel, unless you plan to use it on me.

310
00:18:58,590 --> 00:19:00,970
When I come back, your friend better be in the ground.

311
00:19:19,730 --> 00:19:23,240
- Myers. - Any word on the John Doe yet?

312
00:19:23,240 --> 00:19:24,300
Perry estimates the time of death

313
00:19:24,300 --> 00:19:26,160
between 11:00 and 12:00 last night.

314
00:19:26,170 --> 00:19:27,950
Before we were tipped on the Palmer hit.

315
00:19:27,950 --> 00:19:29,740
Is he close to making an ID?

316
00:19:29,840 --> 00:19:31,710
We did sent some tissue samples to the lab.

317
00:19:31,710 --> 00:19:33,410
They're running his DNA against all databases.

318
00:19:33,410 --> 00:19:35,020
No, that will take too long.

319
00:19:35,020 --> 00:19:36,830
We're going as fast as we can, Jack.

320
00:19:36,830 --> 00:19:39,340
Put Jamey on it, we've got to take care of this now.

321
00:19:40,080 --> 00:19:42,710
- Did you find Kim? - No, not yet.

322
00:19:42,710 --> 00:19:44,980
- Is her friend all right? - She will be.

323
00:19:44,980 --> 00:19:46,740
How about Teri? How's she holding up?

324
00:19:46,740 --> 00:19:47,960
She's fine, Nina.

325
00:19:47,960 --> 00:19:49,900
What else is going on over there?

326
00:19:50,810 --> 00:19:53,130
I think I have to apologize for Jack.

327
00:19:54,120 --> 00:19:56,180
You don't have to apologize for your husband.

328
00:19:56,380 --> 00:19:58,650
We're all... pretty wound up.

329
00:19:58,820 --> 00:20:01,650
Jack's wound up a little tighter than the rest of us.

330
00:20:03,190 --> 00:20:04,660
No argument here.

331
00:20:06,190 --> 00:20:09,430
I guess I've always accepted it as an occupational hazard.

332
00:20:10,460 --> 00:20:12,830
I thought you told me that he sat behind a desk.

333
00:20:14,350 --> 00:20:15,370
The truth is, half the time

334
00:20:15,370 --> 00:20:18,910
I don't know what he's doing. He can't tell me.

335
00:20:18,910 --> 00:20:20,510
It's a security thing.

336
00:20:21,280 --> 00:20:22,720
Must be tough on you.

337
00:20:24,180 --> 00:20:25,350
Sometimes.

338
00:20:26,220 --> 00:20:27,810
But you deal with it.

339
00:20:29,070 --> 00:20:31,230
Right now, he's just worried about Kim.

340
00:20:32,010 --> 00:20:33,370
Hopefully, when Janet wakes up,

341
00:20:33,370 --> 00:20:35,400
she'll be able to tell us where she is.

342
00:20:37,870 --> 00:20:38,860
Yeah.

343
00:20:41,660 --> 00:20:45,710
Look, I gotta go. Call me back as soon as you've got anything.

344
00:21:00,590 --> 00:21:02,190
Walk with me for a sec.

345
00:21:06,420 --> 00:21:11,060
What is it, Jack? Why is there all this security here?

346
00:21:12,220 --> 00:21:13,840
Who wants to hurt Janet?

347
00:21:18,520 --> 00:21:21,610
Today someone is going to try to kill David Palmer.

348
00:21:22,040 --> 00:21:22,990
What?

349
00:21:23,440 --> 00:21:25,510
That's why I was brought in last night.

350
00:21:27,270 --> 00:21:29,020
Why is Janet in danger?

351
00:21:30,160 --> 00:21:31,970
Because she was with Kim.

352
00:21:35,140 --> 00:21:36,550
Our daughter's missing.

353
00:21:38,800 --> 00:21:42,000
Are you saying it relates to an assassination attempt?

354
00:21:42,420 --> 00:21:45,270
They must know that I've been assigned to protect Palmer.

355
00:21:47,200 --> 00:21:49,600
And you think this person kidnapped Kim?

356
00:21:52,150 --> 00:21:54,770
Oh, my God.

357
00:21:54,770 --> 00:21:56,050
Teri.

358
00:21:57,500 --> 00:21:58,830
I'm so sorry.

359
00:22:00,520 --> 00:22:03,120
I know this is all happening because of me.

360
00:22:06,820 --> 00:22:09,990
I've tried to keep a wall between my work and my family.

361
00:22:09,990 --> 00:22:13,240
The wall's coming down, and now I don't know what to do.

362
00:22:22,530 --> 00:22:23,680
Okay.

363
00:22:32,350 --> 00:22:34,890
What do they... what do they want from you?

364
00:22:34,890 --> 00:22:35,790
I don't know yet.

365
00:22:35,790 --> 00:22:36,920
What are the police doing?

366
00:22:36,920 --> 00:22:40,320
I couldn't call them. I can't without risking Kim's life.

367
00:22:40,320 --> 00:22:43,660
- What if it's too late, Jack? - It's not too late.

368
00:22:44,550 --> 00:22:46,470
Kim is okay. They took her for a reason,

369
00:22:46,470 --> 00:22:48,290
and that was not to hurt her.

370
00:22:49,050 --> 00:22:51,420
- Okay. - Honey.

371
00:22:58,050 --> 00:23:01,030
I promise you, we are going to get her back.

372
00:23:05,550 --> 00:23:07,150
I'm so sorry.

373
00:23:33,180 --> 00:23:34,880
I need you in forensics.

374
00:23:34,880 --> 00:23:36,890
I'm about to crack the outer shell.

375
00:23:36,890 --> 00:23:38,670
You said that two hours ago.

376
00:23:39,160 --> 00:23:41,460
This keycard is our best lead on the Palmer hit.

377
00:23:41,460 --> 00:23:44,000
I'm not dropping the keycard. I've called in Milo.

378
00:23:44,040 --> 00:23:45,900
Milo's an outside contractor.

379
00:23:45,900 --> 00:23:47,540
Which is why we can trust him.

380
00:23:48,630 --> 00:23:50,640
I can do this. I'm as good as Milo.

381
00:23:50,640 --> 00:23:52,990
Not with this kind of thing you're not, and I can't wait.

382
00:23:55,060 --> 00:23:56,950
Jack wants you on this.

383
00:24:02,200 --> 00:24:03,530
I'll brief you on the way.

384
00:24:04,300 --> 00:24:06,350
He thinks it's a male Caucasian....

385
00:24:21,790 --> 00:24:24,130
- Who is it? - David.

386
00:24:27,870 --> 00:24:31,200
Sorry to wake you like this, Mike, but something's come up.

387
00:24:31,780 --> 00:24:33,450
I was hoping to keep you out of it.

388
00:24:33,520 --> 00:24:35,150
I'm your Chief of Staff, David.

389
00:24:35,160 --> 00:24:36,860
I shouldn't be kept out of anything.

390
00:24:37,370 --> 00:24:38,770
It was a private matter.

391
00:24:38,870 --> 00:24:42,040
You're running for president. Nothing's private any more.

392
00:24:50,160 --> 00:24:51,400
Where you going?

393
00:24:52,130 --> 00:24:54,300
They moved Janet upstairs to the ICU.

394
00:24:54,660 --> 00:24:56,020
She's out of recovery?

395
00:24:56,030 --> 00:24:59,040
She's a little groggy, but she's awake.

396
00:24:59,160 --> 00:25:01,870
- Alan, that's wonderful. - Yeah, thank you.

397
00:25:02,130 --> 00:25:04,260
Alan, I owe you an apology. I'm sorry.

398
00:25:04,260 --> 00:25:04,960
You don't need to be.

399
00:25:04,960 --> 00:25:07,360
I understand exactly what you're going through.

400
00:25:11,010 --> 00:25:12,040
Excuse me.

401
00:25:13,310 --> 00:25:15,360
- Bauer. - We found something.

402
00:25:15,650 --> 00:25:18,320
X-rays show a surgical pin in John Doe's ankle.

403
00:25:18,320 --> 00:25:21,560
Turns out it's not standard. It's custom-made, one-of-a-kind.

404
00:25:21,920 --> 00:25:24,980
That means we can trace it to the surgeon who implanted it.

405
00:25:24,980 --> 00:25:27,160
Jamey's searching the AMA database,

406
00:25:27,160 --> 00:25:28,810
crosschecking it with the manufacturer.

407
00:25:28,810 --> 00:25:30,790
Hopefully, we'll have this guy's name within the hour.

408
00:25:30,790 --> 00:25:32,470
Sooner is better. I gotta go.

409
00:25:32,470 --> 00:25:34,160
Call me as soon as you've got something.

410
00:25:40,620 --> 00:25:42,360
The minute Maureen breaks the story,

411
00:25:42,360 --> 00:25:44,410
you'll free-fall in the polls.

412
00:25:45,190 --> 00:25:48,460
Then the media will start churning this thing, 24/7.

413
00:25:48,460 --> 00:25:51,140
They'll pick you clean, then go to work on the bones.

414
00:25:51,140 --> 00:25:54,880
Chances are, the party will try to cut bait.

415
00:25:54,880 --> 00:25:59,870
So I'd say you're textbook unelectable.

416
00:26:01,980 --> 00:26:03,910
So I'm right to withdraw from the race.

417
00:26:03,910 --> 00:26:06,310
No, that's the last thing you should do.

418
00:26:06,440 --> 00:26:08,340
You just got through telling me I can't win.

419
00:26:08,350 --> 00:26:11,180
I told you what to expect so you can.

420
00:26:11,180 --> 00:26:16,020
If we handle this right, I think you can come back from this.

421
00:26:17,030 --> 00:26:18,140
David.

422
00:26:19,770 --> 00:26:22,460
You're the most important presidential candidate

423
00:26:22,460 --> 00:26:25,100
this country's had in a long time.

424
00:26:25,110 --> 00:26:29,210
Like it or not, fair or not, you're making history.

425
00:26:33,920 --> 00:26:37,470
My son was involved in another man's death.

426
00:26:39,500 --> 00:26:40,900
It was an accident.

427
00:26:40,900 --> 00:26:44,560
Okay, then what if some judge rules it was...

428
00:26:44,560 --> 00:26:46,900
How do we justify the cover-up?

429
00:26:47,930 --> 00:26:49,250
All of them

430
00:26:50,170 --> 00:26:54,030
Sherry, Keith, Nicole

431
00:26:54,160 --> 00:26:55,970
kept this from the police.

432
00:26:56,380 --> 00:26:58,500
I don't want to seem crass,

433
00:26:58,500 --> 00:27:02,000
but the important thing is you didn't cover it up.

434
00:27:02,100 --> 00:27:03,660
You didn't know.

435
00:27:05,270 --> 00:27:06,960
What does that say about me?

436
00:27:14,820 --> 00:27:18,110
Not knowing the most important things about my family.

437
00:27:18,300 --> 00:27:21,890
I'm not saying it's not a hard sell.

438
00:27:21,890 --> 00:27:25,510
The election is still six months away.

439
00:27:27,420 --> 00:27:30,880
The voters know how to forgive.

440
00:27:32,040 --> 00:27:35,260
You just have to know how to ask for it.

441
00:27:38,120 --> 00:27:40,330
Do you still want the job, David?

442
00:27:41,730 --> 00:27:43,040
You know I do.

443
00:27:43,660 --> 00:27:47,850
Then you need to come out with the story yourself

444
00:27:47,850 --> 00:27:50,660
before Maureen Kingsley.

445
00:27:53,350 --> 00:27:56,790
Make it the first thing you say at the breakfast.

446
00:28:05,370 --> 00:28:07,680
I just don't know how my family's going to feel about that.

447
00:28:09,300 --> 00:28:14,190
Find out fast, because you can't do this without them.

448
00:28:15,990 --> 00:28:17,630
When you come clean

449
00:28:19,300 --> 00:28:22,720
be damned sure your family is standing next to you.

450
00:28:28,760 --> 00:28:32,160
I did an extensive neurological exam which showed no spinal injury.

451
00:28:32,160 --> 00:28:33,680
She suffered multiple fractures,

452
00:28:33,680 --> 00:28:35,270
but nothing she can't recover from.

453
00:28:35,270 --> 00:28:36,570
What went wrong in surgery?

454
00:28:36,570 --> 00:28:38,530
When they tried to stop internal bleeding,

455
00:28:38,530 --> 00:28:39,900
she had a cardiac arrest.

456
00:28:39,900 --> 00:28:41,020
It happens sometimes.

457
00:28:41,020 --> 00:28:42,380
But she's okay now?

458
00:28:42,560 --> 00:28:46,100
The next six hours will be critical, but I'm optimistic.

459
00:28:46,100 --> 00:28:48,250
Is it be possible to ask her a few questions?

460
00:28:48,310 --> 00:28:50,290
- When? - As soon as possible.

461
00:28:50,290 --> 00:28:51,060
Our daughter's missing

462
00:28:51,060 --> 00:28:53,330
and Janet was the last person to see her.

463
00:28:53,470 --> 00:28:55,630
I'm not comfortable with her being interrogated.

464
00:28:55,630 --> 00:28:58,110
I'm just talking about asking her one or two questions.

465
00:28:59,590 --> 00:29:01,150
I'll leave it up to her father.

466
00:29:06,760 --> 00:29:09,490
Let me go in first, make sure she's up to it.

467
00:29:09,660 --> 00:29:10,660
Thank you.

468
00:29:24,560 --> 00:29:26,800
You know what we should do when this is over?

469
00:29:27,600 --> 00:29:28,930
Get some sleep?

470
00:29:31,380 --> 00:29:33,690
We should take that trip we always talked about.

471
00:29:33,870 --> 00:29:37,420
You know, up the coast into Canada. Just the three of us.

472
00:29:38,450 --> 00:29:39,830
That sounds nice.

473
00:29:42,980 --> 00:29:45,180
I'm sorry, Nina's following up a lead.

474
00:29:45,480 --> 00:29:46,630
That was quick.

475
00:29:47,140 --> 00:29:48,040
Do what I tell you, Jack,

476
00:29:48,040 --> 00:29:50,320
and you might see your daughter again.

477
00:29:50,320 --> 00:29:52,380
Say yes if you understand me.

478
00:29:54,050 --> 00:29:55,780
Answer me, Jack.

479
00:29:57,300 --> 00:29:58,460
Yes.

480
00:29:59,100 --> 00:30:01,540
Now smile at your wife like nothing's wrong

481
00:30:01,540 --> 00:30:03,480
and move away from the doors.

482
00:30:12,720 --> 00:30:15,510
That's right, we're watching you.

483
00:30:19,570 --> 00:30:23,900
Walk away now, or Kimberly gets a bullet in her head.

484
00:30:33,760 --> 00:30:36,580
The reception is really bad here. I'll be right back.

485
00:30:41,260 --> 00:30:43,430
Now continue down the hall.

486
00:30:47,400 --> 00:30:50,090
Come on Jack, I don't have all day.

487
00:30:54,440 --> 00:30:55,960
What do you want me to do?

488
00:30:56,930 --> 00:30:58,850
Go out the north entrance.

489
00:31:06,840 --> 00:31:07,940
Left.

490
00:31:09,260 --> 00:31:11,400
Yes, I'm still watching you.

491
00:31:12,720 --> 00:31:14,900
Let's head out the north entrance.

492
00:31:19,570 --> 00:31:21,100
She's a tough one, your daughter.

493
00:31:21,110 --> 00:31:22,500
Tell me about it.

494
00:31:26,900 --> 00:31:28,570
Would you rather go in alone?

495
00:31:29,350 --> 00:31:30,380
Do you mind?

496
00:31:44,320 --> 00:31:45,980
Daddy?

497
00:31:46,940 --> 00:31:48,290
Hello, Janet.

498
00:31:51,730 --> 00:31:53,760
You've had a rough night, haven't you?

499
00:31:56,870 --> 00:31:58,230
Who are you?

500
00:32:02,360 --> 00:32:04,020
Where's my father?

501
00:33:53,290 --> 00:33:54,590
Where am I going?

502
00:33:54,890 --> 00:33:56,970
On your left, there's a silver Taurus.

503
00:34:00,040 --> 00:34:01,150
I see it.

504
00:34:01,340 --> 00:34:02,410
Get in.

505
00:34:14,280 --> 00:34:16,030
Open the glove compartment.

506
00:34:16,030 --> 00:34:18,810
First prove to me that my daughter is still alive.

507
00:34:22,500 --> 00:34:23,190
Daddy?

508
00:34:23,190 --> 00:34:25,060
Kimberly? Are you okay?

509
00:34:25,460 --> 00:34:27,290
Yeah, they haven't hurt me, but I'm--

510
00:34:30,060 --> 00:34:33,720
There's a metal box inside the glove compartment. Take it out.

511
00:34:44,530 --> 00:34:46,110
Tuck it in your ear.

512
00:34:52,750 --> 00:34:54,260
Now say something.

513
00:34:54,500 --> 00:34:57,130
If you hurt my daughter, I will kill you.

514
00:34:57,250 --> 00:34:59,700
Good. There's a nice, clear signal.

515
00:35:00,800 --> 00:35:03,600
You won't need your phone anymore. Lose it out the window.

516
00:35:06,150 --> 00:35:08,510
Out the window, Jack.

517
00:35:18,680 --> 00:35:20,980
The keys are on the seat next to you.

518
00:35:26,950 --> 00:35:28,330
Where do you want me to go?

519
00:35:29,120 --> 00:35:31,450
You're going to the office, like everyone else.

520
00:35:31,460 --> 00:35:33,760
- CTU? - That's where you work.

521
00:36:04,030 --> 00:36:06,350
This is Jack Bauer. Leave a message.

522
00:36:06,350 --> 00:36:08,200
Jack, where are you?

523
00:36:08,660 --> 00:36:10,760
Sorry. I didn't mean to scare you.

524
00:36:10,790 --> 00:36:13,070
- Where's Jack? - He went to take a call.

525
00:36:13,070 --> 00:36:14,220
I need to talk to him.

526
00:36:14,220 --> 00:36:16,050
Why, what did Janet say? Does she know something?

527
00:36:16,050 --> 00:36:18,120
They were trying to escape.

528
00:36:18,120 --> 00:36:19,040
Escape from whom?

529
00:36:19,040 --> 00:36:21,240
A couple of boys who got too aggressive.

530
00:36:21,610 --> 00:36:23,040
She doesn't know if Kim got away.

531
00:36:23,040 --> 00:36:24,640
Kim would have called if she did.

532
00:36:24,640 --> 00:36:27,900
Janet says that they were being held in a house up in Bel Air.

533
00:36:27,900 --> 00:36:28,760
That's the address?

534
00:36:28,760 --> 00:36:30,330
We should give it to the police.

535
00:36:30,930 --> 00:36:32,520
Jack is the police.

536
00:36:37,310 --> 00:36:38,640
Jack, pick up.

537
00:36:38,640 --> 00:36:39,890
This is Jack Bauer. Leave a message.

538
00:36:39,890 --> 00:36:42,400
He's not answering. Jack, listen, it's me again.

539
00:36:42,410 --> 00:36:44,590
Janet may know where Kimberly is.

540
00:36:44,590 --> 00:36:48,150
Would you please call me as soon as you get this, Okay?

541
00:36:49,810 --> 00:36:53,850
Jack?

542
00:36:54,570 --> 00:36:57,610
He was just here. He promised me he wouldn't leave.

543
00:36:57,610 --> 00:37:00,010
Keep trying him on his cell. I'll call the police.

544
00:37:00,010 --> 00:37:01,260
No, I have to get there.

545
00:37:01,260 --> 00:37:02,750
If you want, I'll take you.

546
00:37:02,750 --> 00:37:05,200
- Well, what about Janet? - She's sleeping.

547
00:37:05,200 --> 00:37:07,070
Dr. Collier says she's not in any danger

548
00:37:07,070 --> 00:37:09,290
and she'll be out for a couple of hours, Okay?

549
00:37:09,290 --> 00:37:10,400
Okay.

550
00:37:13,270 --> 00:37:15,380
I guess I'll just call from the car.

551
00:38:08,600 --> 00:38:09,900
Come on, move it.

552
00:38:33,190 --> 00:38:34,410
Sorry, man.

553
00:38:42,930 --> 00:38:45,920
- We're gonna be okay. - Maybe.

554
00:38:47,250 --> 00:38:48,490
I just spoke to my dad.

555
00:38:48,490 --> 00:38:49,490
How?

556
00:38:49,710 --> 00:38:51,850
Gaines put me on the phone with him.

557
00:38:51,850 --> 00:38:52,840
What does Gaines want from your dad?

558
00:38:52,840 --> 00:38:54,100
- Money? - No.

559
00:38:54,100 --> 00:38:56,420
I'm not sure, but I don't think it's about money.

560
00:38:57,970 --> 00:38:59,470
My dad's gonna get us out.

561
00:38:59,620 --> 00:39:01,220
He doesn't even know where we are.

562
00:39:02,310 --> 00:39:03,490
It doesn't matter.

563
00:39:05,810 --> 00:39:06,920
He'll find us.

564
00:39:27,020 --> 00:39:28,360
What's up, Milo?

565
00:39:28,870 --> 00:39:31,590
Did you try using an S-box inversion on that keycard?

566
00:39:31,970 --> 00:39:33,270
No. Why?

567
00:39:34,380 --> 00:39:37,480
I don't know, it's just the fastest way into a file that size.

568
00:39:38,790 --> 00:39:41,240
Your hunch on the AMA database paid off.

569
00:39:41,440 --> 00:39:43,120
We just ID'd our John Doe.

570
00:40:14,880 --> 00:40:17,760
What happened to your wrist? You didn't have that before.

571
00:40:17,920 --> 00:40:19,070
Yeah, I did.

572
00:40:19,890 --> 00:40:22,270
- It happened back at the furniture store. - Oh.

573
00:40:23,390 --> 00:40:24,640
Maybe that's Jack.

574
00:40:25,320 --> 00:40:26,320
Jack?

575
00:40:26,440 --> 00:40:28,760
Teri. Hi, it's Nina Myers.

576
00:40:28,820 --> 00:40:30,200
Oh, hi, Nina.

577
00:40:30,690 --> 00:40:32,900
I have some important information for Jack.

578
00:40:32,900 --> 00:40:35,390
He's not answering and I know he's with you.

579
00:40:35,390 --> 00:40:38,780
No, he was, but he went to take a call a couple minutes ago.

580
00:40:38,780 --> 00:40:40,250
I thought it was from you.

581
00:40:40,690 --> 00:40:43,620
No, I haven't spoken to him in almost half an hour.

582
00:40:43,920 --> 00:40:45,330
Then you don't know where he is?

583
00:40:45,330 --> 00:40:46,270
No.

584
00:40:46,840 --> 00:40:48,190
Nina, what's going on?

585
00:40:49,530 --> 00:40:51,670
Um... listen Teri, if you hear from him first,

586
00:40:51,670 --> 00:40:53,470
can you give him a message?

587
00:40:53,480 --> 00:40:54,560
Of course.

588
00:40:55,540 --> 00:40:57,860
There's a murder victim he asked me to ID.

589
00:40:58,380 --> 00:41:01,620
Tell him the murder victim's name is Alan York.

590
00:41:04,600 --> 00:41:07,020
I'm sorry, Nina, could you say that again please?

591
00:41:07,170 --> 00:41:09,300
Alan York. He's an accountant from the Valley.

592
00:41:09,300 --> 00:41:12,580
Listen, I'll give Jack the details when I speak to him.

593
00:41:14,270 --> 00:41:15,200
Hello?

594
00:41:16,690 --> 00:41:17,680
Yeah.

595
00:41:18,060 --> 00:41:20,290
- Will you tell Jack? - Sure.

596
00:41:20,620 --> 00:41:22,410
Thanks, and if you hear from him,

597
00:41:22,410 --> 00:41:23,560
tell him to call in?

598
00:41:23,890 --> 00:41:25,530
- Okay. - Thanks.

599
00:41:29,770 --> 00:41:30,780
Everything all right?

600
00:41:30,790 --> 00:41:33,460
Yeah, that was just someone from Jack's office trying to find him.

