2
00:00:12,760 --> 00:00:14,020
Right now

3
00:00:14,120 --> 00:00:17,680
terrorists are plotting to assassinate a presidential candidate.

4
00:00:18,410 --> 00:00:20,780
My wife and daughter have been targeted

5
00:00:20,980 --> 00:00:24,570
and people that I work with may be involved in both.

6
00:00:25,130 --> 00:00:27,200
I'm Federal Agent Jack Bauer

7
00:00:27,500 --> 00:00:31,120
and today is the longest day of my life.

10
00:00:41,060 --> 00:00:46,060
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

11
00:00:41,060 --> 00:00:46,060
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

12
00:00:41,060 --> 00:00:46,060
{\an5}{\pos(145,252)}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

13
00:00:41,560 --> 00:00:46,060
{\pos(67,248)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

14
00:00:41,560 --> 00:00:46,060
{\pos(67,248)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

15
00:00:41,560 --> 00:00:46,060
{\pos(58,238)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

16
00:00:41,560 --> 00:00:46,060
{\pos(84,248)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

19
00:00:47,280 --> 00:01:17,280
{\an9}m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

20
00:00:46,780 --> 00:01:17,280
{\an2}{\pos(26,248)}m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

27
00:01:23,270 --> 00:01:26,420
You know, Jack, I take back what I said. It's getting dull.

28
00:01:26,460 --> 00:01:28,370
That helicopter made a fly-by for a reason.

29
00:01:28,370 --> 00:01:30,120
Maybe, maybe not.

30
00:01:31,240 --> 00:01:32,750
Come here, help me with this.

31
00:01:35,310 --> 00:01:37,820
1, 2, 3....

32
00:01:41,280 --> 00:01:43,700
There's nothing here. We're wasting our time.

33
00:01:43,920 --> 00:01:45,210
Alexis tried to pay off a power

34
00:01:45,210 --> 00:01:47,060
company official to cut off the electricity

35
00:01:47,060 --> 00:01:50,090
at this location at 7:20 for a reason.

36
00:01:50,090 --> 00:01:51,080
There's something here that they want,

37
00:01:51,080 --> 00:01:53,200
they've gone a great length to shut it down.

38
00:01:56,380 --> 00:01:57,560
Mason.

39
00:01:58,760 --> 00:02:00,240
Excellent news.

40
00:02:00,870 --> 00:02:02,080
Half an hour.

41
00:02:02,350 --> 00:02:04,510
Don't let anyone in or out until we get there.

42
00:02:04,740 --> 00:02:06,290
Alexis Drazen just out of surgery.

43
00:02:06,290 --> 00:02:08,050
We should be there when he wakes up.

44
00:02:08,170 --> 00:02:09,350
You go ahead.

45
00:02:09,370 --> 00:02:12,570
Jack, we were fed misinformation.

46
00:02:12,850 --> 00:02:14,130
The address in the file.

47
00:02:14,130 --> 00:02:16,340
The time Morgan gave you. The whole thing.

48
00:02:16,410 --> 00:02:18,620
Look around. There's nothing here. Nothing.

49
00:02:18,620 --> 00:02:21,750
- Maybe. - But you're going to stick around anyway?

50
00:02:23,380 --> 00:02:25,350
It's three minutes after seven, George.

51
00:02:25,350 --> 00:02:27,150
I want to be here at 7:20.

52
00:02:28,620 --> 00:02:30,800
You can send a car back for me, okay?

53
00:02:31,270 --> 00:02:33,320
I promise, I won't disappear on you.

54
00:02:33,910 --> 00:02:35,590
I don't have time to argue with you.

55
00:02:53,230 --> 00:02:55,100
Oh, my God.

56
00:02:55,740 --> 00:02:57,690
You sit right here. Stay right there, Teri.

57
00:03:02,030 --> 00:03:04,500
- Who the hell was that guy? - I don't know.

58
00:03:12,490 --> 00:03:14,780
Teri, it's okay.

59
00:03:14,950 --> 00:03:15,970
I'm right here.

60
00:03:15,970 --> 00:03:17,090
It's ok.

61
00:03:17,900 --> 00:03:20,370
Teri. Listen to me. Take a breath.

62
00:03:20,440 --> 00:03:22,980
I can't.

63
00:03:23,610 --> 00:03:25,810
I saw the car explode.

64
00:03:25,810 --> 00:03:27,930
- Teri.... - There was nothing left!

65
00:03:28,430 --> 00:03:30,970
Kim is alive. She got out before the explosion.

66
00:03:30,970 --> 00:03:32,820
I talked to her. All right?

67
00:03:32,970 --> 00:03:34,970
She was fine. She was worried about you.

68
00:03:35,350 --> 00:03:35,940
Now I need your help.

69
00:03:35,940 --> 00:03:37,980
I need to get you back to CTU. Come on.

70
00:03:38,850 --> 00:03:41,610
- Oh, my God. - I need your help, Teri. Come on.

71
00:03:42,510 --> 00:03:46,260
What did she say when you talked to her? Where is she?

72
00:03:46,270 --> 00:03:47,740
We don't know where she is. She wouldn't tell us.

73
00:03:47,740 --> 00:03:48,620
What do you mean you don't know where she is?

74
00:03:48,620 --> 00:03:51,010
After the safe house, she didn't trust us. I don't blame her.

75
00:03:51,160 --> 00:03:53,850
- Get in here. - We have to find her, Tony, we have to find...

76
00:03:53,850 --> 00:03:56,280
Believe me, we're looking. Teri, get in the car!

77
00:04:07,090 --> 00:04:09,430
Where's Jack? Does he know what's happening?

78
00:04:09,430 --> 00:04:11,900
He's out on assignment. I should hear from him soon, though.

79
00:04:21,330 --> 00:04:22,700
- Myers. - Nina, it's me.

80
00:04:22,700 --> 00:04:24,490
I found Teri at the Bauer house.

81
00:04:24,490 --> 00:04:25,360
Someone was trying to kill her,

82
00:04:25,370 --> 00:04:27,240
but I took the killer down before he could get to her.

83
00:04:27,240 --> 00:04:29,590
Send a team over there in case he's got backup, all right?

84
00:04:29,600 --> 00:04:31,160
Of course. Is she all right?

85
00:04:31,170 --> 00:04:32,390
She will be. She seems to suffer

86
00:04:32,390 --> 00:04:34,380
some sort of temporary memory loss.

87
00:04:34,450 --> 00:04:36,040
She's got a friend with her, too.

88
00:04:36,480 --> 00:04:38,380
I'm guessing a pretty good one, by the way he's acting.

89
00:04:38,380 --> 00:04:41,080
Wait a minute. Are you sure? Who is this guy?

90
00:04:41,080 --> 00:04:43,750
His name is Phil Parslow. She vouches for him.

91
00:04:43,750 --> 00:04:45,620
Apparently she's known him for a long time.

92
00:04:45,620 --> 00:04:47,360
He was hit, but not too badly.

93
00:04:47,360 --> 00:04:50,290
- Okay. Where are you now? - Twenty, thirty minutes away.

94
00:04:50,290 --> 00:04:53,040
Take him to the clinic. I'll send someone to question him.

95
00:04:53,040 --> 00:04:55,130
- I think you should bring Teri here. - Okay.

96
00:05:03,030 --> 00:05:04,440
Don't I get a phone call?

97
00:05:04,460 --> 00:05:06,280
Let's go, lock them down. Come on.

98
00:05:06,410 --> 00:05:09,640
- I need to talk to someone. - Don't we all?

99
00:05:09,700 --> 00:05:11,970
Don't listen to the bitch. She lies.

100
00:05:12,520 --> 00:05:15,090
You'll get a chance for that after we put you through.

101
00:05:15,090 --> 00:05:16,590
Come on with me. You're mine.

102
00:05:31,640 --> 00:05:34,690
They're going to ask you about Frank and the deal.

103
00:05:34,690 --> 00:05:36,630
I don't know anything about Frank or the deal.

104
00:05:36,630 --> 00:05:37,650
Tell them that.

105
00:05:37,650 --> 00:05:39,790
You were just at the wrong place, at the wrong time.

106
00:05:40,160 --> 00:05:42,240
I should tell them about everything else, too.

107
00:05:42,540 --> 00:05:43,890
I mean, what happened today.

108
00:05:44,520 --> 00:05:47,530
After the safe house, I'm not sure if I can trust anybody.

109
00:05:49,110 --> 00:05:50,230
You trust me, right?

110
00:05:50,860 --> 00:05:52,710
Yeah, and look where it got me.

111
00:05:54,440 --> 00:05:57,710
I trust you, I know you're trying to do the right thing.

112
00:05:57,820 --> 00:05:59,180
Okay, then listen to me.

113
00:05:59,760 --> 00:06:01,230
Tell them everything.

114
00:06:02,320 --> 00:06:04,830
What happened at the safe house has nothing to do with this.

115
00:06:06,000 --> 00:06:08,000
Whatever you tell them, I'll back it up.

116
00:06:08,400 --> 00:06:10,010
Including my part in it.

117
00:06:14,130 --> 00:06:16,790
- You're going to get in trouble. - Then I'll get in trouble.

118
00:06:17,320 --> 00:06:19,270
It's about time I faced up to what I did.

119
00:06:21,170 --> 00:06:22,300
All right.

120
00:06:23,730 --> 00:06:24,870
You're up.

121
00:07:12,410 --> 00:07:13,610
How are you feeling?

122
00:07:14,960 --> 00:07:16,410
I'm fine, daddy.

123
00:07:17,570 --> 00:07:18,990
Relieved, actually.

124
00:07:20,850 --> 00:07:22,320
I think that maybe...

125
00:07:23,250 --> 00:07:25,750
living with a secret is harder work than I thought.

126
00:07:28,810 --> 00:07:31,720
I'd be lying to you if I told you the hard work was over.

127
00:07:33,760 --> 00:07:35,640
You're going to be asked some questions.

128
00:07:35,680 --> 00:07:37,830
We all are, that we'd rather not deal with.

129
00:07:39,240 --> 00:07:40,700
But if we stick together

130
00:07:42,190 --> 00:07:43,520
we'll get through it.

131
00:08:02,000 --> 00:08:03,980
Could you give your mother and me a few minutes?

132
00:08:28,610 --> 00:08:29,820
I'm sorry.

133
00:08:32,340 --> 00:08:33,660
I

134
00:08:34,930 --> 00:08:36,870
didn't mean to interrupt your

135
00:08:37,630 --> 00:08:39,190
celebration.

136
00:08:41,810 --> 00:08:43,150
You could have joined it.

137
00:08:43,900 --> 00:08:48,260
I'm not in the mood to celebrate the end of your campaign, David.

138
00:08:51,830 --> 00:08:54,210
You just gave your concession speech.

139
00:08:54,220 --> 00:08:55,830
That remains to be seen.

140
00:08:58,620 --> 00:09:01,490
Do you really think people want a president

141
00:09:01,490 --> 00:09:05,840
who acts like some guest on a bad afternoon talk show...

142
00:09:05,840 --> 00:09:08,410
confessing his sins publicly?

143
00:09:08,490 --> 00:09:11,220
It's always possible that they want someone honest.

144
00:09:13,770 --> 00:09:16,070
Mike seems to think I still have a shot.

145
00:09:16,220 --> 00:09:19,380
It's Mike's job to tell you what you want to hear.

146
00:09:19,940 --> 00:09:21,120
Mine.

147
00:09:21,810 --> 00:09:23,540
is to tell you the truth.

148
00:09:23,540 --> 00:09:25,460
You're not qualified to tell me the truth.

149
00:09:29,150 --> 00:09:32,120
It took 13 minutes for you to tear apart

150
00:09:32,120 --> 00:09:35,860
everything that it took us 25 years to build.

151
00:09:35,970 --> 00:09:38,600
Why don't you just let me mourn that loss, okay?

152
00:09:39,520 --> 00:09:40,700
Fair enough.

153
00:09:46,730 --> 00:09:48,800
I only hope your conscience comforts you

154
00:09:48,800 --> 00:09:51,070
when you finally realize this is all over.

155
00:09:51,440 --> 00:09:53,240
You mean the campaign or us?

156
00:11:33,130 --> 00:11:34,570
Confirm, Alpha 1.

157
00:11:35,090 --> 00:11:36,380
This is Alpha 1.

158
00:11:37,180 --> 00:11:38,640
Bauer's gone below.

159
00:11:39,030 --> 00:11:40,490
Positive it was Bauer?

160
00:11:40,710 --> 00:11:41,830
Yes.

161
00:11:43,430 --> 00:11:44,670
What's he doing here?

162
00:11:44,910 --> 00:11:47,010
He wasn't invited, that's for sure.

163
00:13:10,230 --> 00:13:13,110
My name is Jack Bauer. I work for CTU.

164
00:13:14,120 --> 00:13:16,280
I know who you are, Agent Bauer. I checked you out.

165
00:13:16,710 --> 00:13:19,000
My name is DeSalvo. D.O.D.

166
00:13:19,520 --> 00:13:20,510
Whatever this place is,

167
00:13:20,510 --> 00:13:22,940
it's obvious that no one's supposed to know it's here.

168
00:13:24,090 --> 00:13:25,740
You seem to have found it okay.

169
00:13:26,380 --> 00:13:29,350
This is a prison facility. Class 3 detention center.

170
00:13:29,380 --> 00:13:30,780
What the hell are you doing here?

171
00:13:32,350 --> 00:13:33,980
At 8:00 a.m. this morning

172
00:13:34,220 --> 00:13:36,870
there was an assassination attempt on Senator Palmer.

173
00:13:36,900 --> 00:13:38,100
I'm the lead investigator.

174
00:13:38,100 --> 00:13:40,410
I was following the thread. It led me here.

175
00:13:42,820 --> 00:13:44,230
I need more than that.

176
00:13:47,120 --> 00:13:48,690
The people that want Palmer dead

177
00:13:49,010 --> 00:13:50,820
bribed someone from the power company

178
00:13:50,820 --> 00:13:52,520
to shut down the electricity to the grid

179
00:13:52,520 --> 00:13:54,020
that you're hooked into.

180
00:13:54,030 --> 00:13:56,230
They were ordered to do this at 7:20.

181
00:13:59,580 --> 00:14:01,730
Something's going to happen here then, isn't it?

182
00:14:05,290 --> 00:14:08,070
Mr. DeSalvo, you better listen to me.

183
00:14:08,090 --> 00:14:10,560
The people behind this assassination attempt

184
00:14:10,560 --> 00:14:11,930
are ex-military Serbs.

185
00:14:11,930 --> 00:14:14,440
They are working for a family called Drazen. They are vendetta.

186
00:14:14,440 --> 00:14:16,770
They've killed a lot of people and will kill more

187
00:14:16,770 --> 00:14:20,040
unless we do something. Please, sir, I'll ask one more time.

188
00:14:20,080 --> 00:14:23,110
What is happening here at 7:20?

189
00:14:31,350 --> 00:14:33,410
A prisoner's being delivered by chopper.

190
00:14:33,710 --> 00:14:34,950
Who?

191
00:14:35,390 --> 00:14:37,100
His identity is classified, even from me.

192
00:14:37,100 --> 00:14:39,970
They move him every few weeks randomly. What do these

193
00:14:40,710 --> 00:14:42,860
Drazens want with him, anyway?

194
00:14:42,860 --> 00:14:45,270
It's hard to tell unless I know who the prisoner is.

195
00:14:45,530 --> 00:14:48,080
They might want to kill him. They might want to set him free.

196
00:14:48,550 --> 00:14:51,330
Either way, you've got about five minutes.

197
00:14:51,500 --> 00:14:54,310
- Call for backup. - Backup can't get here in five minutes.

198
00:14:54,310 --> 00:14:55,580
Call anyway.

199
00:14:55,630 --> 00:14:58,450
If I'm wrong, you've gone through a little trouble.

200
00:14:58,470 --> 00:15:00,450
I'll take the heat for that. If I'm right,

201
00:15:00,500 --> 00:15:02,920
you've potentially saved every life in this building.

202
00:15:05,320 --> 00:15:06,490
Please.

203
00:15:12,950 --> 00:15:15,080
Have Wycoff call me ASAP.

204
00:15:16,320 --> 00:15:19,090
Thank you. What's your personnel here?

205
00:15:20,870 --> 00:15:24,020
Three guards plus a maintenance man, two technicians.

206
00:15:24,020 --> 00:15:25,530
Maintenance man and technicians,

207
00:15:25,530 --> 00:15:26,440
are they weapons-trained?

208
00:15:26,440 --> 00:15:28,580
No. The civilians never fired a weapon in their lives.

209
00:15:28,580 --> 00:15:30,200
The Drazens don't know that.

210
00:15:30,560 --> 00:15:33,000
Issue them full service gear. Have them stand by.

211
00:15:33,270 --> 00:15:34,610
To do what exactly?

212
00:15:34,610 --> 00:15:37,500
To make this place look more secure than it is.

213
00:15:37,880 --> 00:15:39,670
At least until backup arrives.

214
00:15:54,900 --> 00:15:56,290
It's almost time.

215
00:15:57,000 --> 00:15:58,200
Three minutes.

216
00:15:59,890 --> 00:16:03,020
- You still haven't heard from your brother? - No.

217
00:16:03,420 --> 00:16:06,360
He was supposed to verify his meeting with the power company man.

218
00:16:06,360 --> 00:16:08,460
If there was a problem, he would have called.

219
00:16:12,110 --> 00:16:13,780
You seem anxious, Harris.

220
00:16:14,580 --> 00:16:16,740
I thought professionals didn't get anxious.

221
00:16:16,740 --> 00:16:20,030
Professionals get very anxious when a plan goes off the tracks.

222
00:16:20,290 --> 00:16:21,830
There's nothing wrong with the plan.

223
00:16:22,080 --> 00:16:23,640
Then what's Bauer doing here?

224
00:16:23,640 --> 00:16:26,230
Just get your men ready. It's time.

225
00:16:55,480 --> 00:16:56,610
Come here.

226
00:16:56,660 --> 00:16:58,160
No. Like this.

227
00:16:58,390 --> 00:16:59,640
All right, let's get moving.

228
00:16:59,980 --> 00:17:02,400
Keep the stock in tight, keep your weapon down.

229
00:17:02,540 --> 00:17:04,290
- You're going to be all right. - Okay.

230
00:17:05,670 --> 00:17:08,320
- Any word on the backup? - They're looking into it.

231
00:17:10,650 --> 00:17:11,840
Weapon.

232
00:17:19,110 --> 00:17:20,260
We good?

233
00:17:20,540 --> 00:17:21,830
Yes, sir.

234
00:17:24,120 --> 00:17:25,890
- Let's go. - All right.

235
00:18:04,570 --> 00:18:07,230
Put your men in front of the lights so they can be seen.

236
00:18:07,510 --> 00:18:09,600
Form a line right in front of the lights.

237
00:18:10,370 --> 00:18:12,010
Look like you're ready for something.

238
00:18:15,010 --> 00:18:16,430
45 seconds.

239
00:18:22,870 --> 00:18:25,160
You said there'd be a warden and three guards.

240
00:18:25,540 --> 00:18:28,340
I count eight, including Bauer.

241
00:18:31,450 --> 00:18:33,990
- They're expecting us, Andre. - Doesn't matter.

242
00:18:34,350 --> 00:18:37,400
The power's going down in 25 seconds.

243
00:18:37,400 --> 00:18:39,120
The sudden darkness will disorient them.

244
00:18:39,120 --> 00:18:41,370
- What if there is no darkness? - There will be.

245
00:18:47,940 --> 00:18:50,160
Go!

246
00:18:53,350 --> 00:18:54,680
Eight more seconds.

247
00:18:55,260 --> 00:18:57,370
Five, four...

248
00:18:57,430 --> 00:19:00,080
...three, two, one.

249
00:19:00,080 --> 00:19:01,520
Perimeter lights are still on.

250
00:19:02,350 --> 00:19:03,530
Damn it!

251
00:19:10,760 --> 00:19:11,900
All right. We're still going.

252
00:19:11,910 --> 00:19:15,370
No. Security's twice what we anticipated.

253
00:19:15,370 --> 00:19:18,340
The lights are on. We'll be cut to pieces.

254
00:19:23,290 --> 00:19:26,610
- Get ready to move. - We have to stand down.

255
00:19:26,710 --> 00:19:28,320
My money, my decision.

256
00:19:28,320 --> 00:19:30,280
My crew. They'll obey my orders.

257
00:19:40,530 --> 00:19:41,690
All right.

258
00:19:42,970 --> 00:19:44,930
Plans have changed. Stand down.

259
00:20:31,370 --> 00:20:32,470
Sit down.

260
00:20:32,470 --> 00:20:34,190
My father's Jack Bauer.

261
00:20:36,940 --> 00:20:38,060
Sit.

262
00:20:42,410 --> 00:20:45,160
He's the director of the Los Angeles Bureau of CTU.

263
00:20:45,800 --> 00:20:48,390
Counter Terrorist Unit. Have you heard of it?

264
00:20:48,680 --> 00:20:50,270
I can't say that I have.

265
00:20:51,010 --> 00:20:52,310
Do you want the number?

266
00:20:55,490 --> 00:20:58,600
What I want is information on Frank Allard...

267
00:20:58,600 --> 00:21:00,460
...and his plans to buy and distribute

268
00:21:00,460 --> 00:21:02,880
1,000 hits of ecstasy, that's it.

269
00:21:03,690 --> 00:21:04,450
I don't know him.

270
00:21:04,450 --> 00:21:06,710
I met him for the first time a couple hours ago.

271
00:21:15,610 --> 00:21:18,300
Do you know that someone tried to kill David Palmer this morning?

272
00:21:20,050 --> 00:21:21,230
Yes.

273
00:21:21,480 --> 00:21:23,360
Aren't you curious how I know about it?

274
00:21:24,620 --> 00:21:25,820
I don't know. Maybe because

275
00:21:25,820 --> 00:21:28,460
it's been on the news the last 12 hours.

276
00:21:28,590 --> 00:21:30,860
I didn't realize that. I was kidnapped...

277
00:21:31,590 --> 00:21:34,330
...by the same people who are trying to kill Senator Palmer.

278
00:21:34,520 --> 00:21:36,490
I know this sounds crazy.

279
00:21:36,670 --> 00:21:39,270
They kidnapped my mother, tried to get my father to help them...

280
00:21:39,270 --> 00:21:40,470
...but he rescued us.

281
00:21:40,470 --> 00:21:43,820
And then he dropped you off at Frankie's so you could...

282
00:21:44,140 --> 00:21:46,110
...what, earn spending money dealing drugs?

283
00:21:46,120 --> 00:21:47,100
No.

284
00:21:47,100 --> 00:21:49,950
They brought us to a safe house, but it was attacked.

285
00:21:50,210 --> 00:21:52,180
And I think they captured my mother again.

286
00:21:53,560 --> 00:21:56,610
Okay. She told me you had an active imagination.

287
00:21:56,620 --> 00:21:58,930
- She wasn't kidding. - Who?

288
00:21:59,170 --> 00:22:01,400
Your friend, the one we picked you up with.

289
00:22:02,220 --> 00:22:04,930
Melanie? No.

290
00:22:04,930 --> 00:22:07,290
She's not my friend. She thinks I'm after her boyfriend.

291
00:22:07,290 --> 00:22:09,370
You can't believe anything she says about me.

292
00:22:12,170 --> 00:22:14,940
I'm going to stick you back in the holding cell.

293
00:22:14,940 --> 00:22:17,400
Maybe that will convince you not to screw around.

294
00:22:17,400 --> 00:22:18,700
Call this number.

295
00:22:19,060 --> 00:22:22,000
Tell them I am Jack Bauer's daughter and that I'm here.

296
00:22:22,000 --> 00:22:24,220
Ask them if they think I'm screwing around.

297
00:22:29,330 --> 00:22:30,510
Come on.

298
00:22:37,340 --> 00:22:38,780
DeSalvo, wait.

299
00:22:38,990 --> 00:22:41,510
Just because they haven't attacked doesn't mean they won't.

300
00:22:41,510 --> 00:22:44,360
Maybe this is a crock and there's nobody there.

301
00:22:44,370 --> 00:22:45,460
Drazen's crew is out there. Don't you get it?

302
00:22:45,460 --> 00:22:47,160
They didn't shut down the power.

303
00:22:47,160 --> 00:22:49,390
They're working on a contingency plan.

304
00:22:49,390 --> 00:22:51,120
Trust me, I know these people.

305
00:22:54,350 --> 00:22:56,270
I've requested backup. Not much else I can do.

306
00:22:56,270 --> 00:22:58,180
Actually there is. Let me talk to that prisoner.

307
00:22:58,180 --> 00:23:00,060
Forget it. I can't give access.

308
00:23:00,070 --> 00:23:03,230
My orders are explicit. I told you can't even speak to him myself.

309
00:23:03,240 --> 00:23:05,440
Do you understand everything happening here...

310
00:23:05,440 --> 00:23:07,930
...is connected to the assassination attempt on Senator Palmer?

311
00:23:07,930 --> 00:23:11,250
If you don't let me interrogate him, Palmer's life is in danger.

312
00:23:11,250 --> 00:23:12,550
Do you want that responsibility?

313
00:23:12,550 --> 00:23:15,200
Listen, Bauer, You are welcome to go over my head if you want,

314
00:23:15,200 --> 00:23:16,520
but I can't help you.

315
00:23:17,430 --> 00:23:19,180
Now, I got to process this guy.

316
00:23:19,810 --> 00:23:20,940
Wait.

317
00:23:21,940 --> 00:23:24,220
- You said you worked for the D.O.D., right? - And?

318
00:23:25,740 --> 00:23:27,150
Can I borrow your phone?

319
00:23:29,730 --> 00:23:33,340
Yes, I want to clear every interview that Nicole gives.

320
00:23:33,410 --> 00:23:34,930
Yes, personally.

321
00:23:35,090 --> 00:23:36,960
Whenever possible, I want to be there.

322
00:23:37,870 --> 00:23:39,090
Let me know.

323
00:23:42,360 --> 00:23:45,820
Is it as bad as Sherry said it would be?

324
00:23:45,920 --> 00:23:48,060
...predicted a sharp drop in Senator Palmer's numbers...

325
00:23:48,070 --> 00:23:50,110
...It's not turning out that way.

326
00:23:50,350 --> 00:23:53,430
Our instant polls indicate that the Senator's base of support...

327
00:23:53,430 --> 00:23:55,730
is holding steady in most areas of the country

330
00:23:55,730 --> 00:23:58,770
and in some cases, it's actually increasing.

331
00:23:59,160 --> 00:24:00,860
When asked if the Senator's disclosures

332
00:24:00,860 --> 00:24:02,010
made them more likely

333
00:24:02,010 --> 00:24:04,300
to vote for him in the general election

341
00:24:04,390 --> 00:24:06,660
less likely, or made no difference at all,

342
00:24:06,680 --> 00:24:09,040
60 percent said "No Difference",

343
00:24:09,040 --> 00:24:11,670
22 percent said "More likely"

344
00:24:11,670 --> 00:24:14,800
while only 18 percent said "Less likely."

345
00:24:15,550 --> 00:24:16,530
Looks like you were right.

346
00:24:16,530 --> 00:24:17,860
...over the coming months...

347
00:24:17,860 --> 00:24:20,210
seems to indicate that voters approved

348
00:24:20,210 --> 00:24:21,870
of Senator Palmer's honesty

349
00:24:21,870 --> 00:24:23,650
before a national television audience.

350
00:24:23,650 --> 00:24:25,550
a little more than a half hour ago.

351
00:24:26,990 --> 00:24:28,180
Senator.

352
00:24:28,430 --> 00:24:31,100
It's a Jack Bauer. He says it's urgent.

353
00:24:32,820 --> 00:24:34,840
Thank you. Jack, it's me.

354
00:24:35,110 --> 00:24:36,680
Did you get anything from Alexis Drazen?

355
00:24:36,680 --> 00:24:38,220
No. He's just coming out of surgery now,

356
00:24:38,230 --> 00:24:40,770
but I did followed up a lead we got from his hotel room.

357
00:24:40,840 --> 00:24:43,080
- Senator, I'm going to need your help. - Go on.

358
00:24:43,080 --> 00:24:45,430
I'm at something called Class 3 detention facility.

359
00:24:45,430 --> 00:24:47,270
It's basically a prison that doesn't exist.

360
00:24:47,270 --> 00:24:49,310
Neither does the prisoner they just brought in.

361
00:24:49,490 --> 00:24:50,190
Who's the prisoner?

362
00:24:50,190 --> 00:24:51,900
That's where I'm gonna need your help, sir.

363
00:24:51,900 --> 00:24:54,020
This place runs by the Department of Defense.

364
00:24:54,110 --> 00:24:55,260
You want me to pull strings--

365
00:24:55,270 --> 00:24:58,200
I need access to the prisoner as soon as you can make it happen.

366
00:24:58,940 --> 00:25:01,690
The facility's located in Saugus at the address you gave me.

367
00:25:01,690 --> 00:25:02,870
The warden's name is DeSalvo.

368
00:25:02,870 --> 00:25:06,190
He's a reasonable guy, right now his hands are tied.

369
00:25:06,370 --> 00:25:08,490
- I'll do what I can. - Thank you, sir.

370
00:26:36,280 --> 00:26:38,390
Come on, you son of a bitch, turn around.

371
00:26:58,140 --> 00:27:00,670
Damn it, that prisoner's identity is classified!

372
00:27:00,780 --> 00:27:02,920
I'm sorry, but I told you I need to know who that prisoner is.

373
00:27:02,920 --> 00:27:04,070
No.

374
00:27:14,780 --> 00:27:16,190
It's impossible.

375
00:27:18,860 --> 00:27:20,140
You recognize him?

376
00:27:21,460 --> 00:27:23,050
That's Victor Drazen.

377
00:27:23,950 --> 00:27:25,140
Who is he?

378
00:27:25,660 --> 00:27:27,530
A man I killed two years ago.

379
00:27:51,860 --> 00:27:53,470
All right, listen, Bauer.

380
00:27:53,550 --> 00:27:56,040
You're asking me to risk my job, maybe go to jail.

381
00:27:56,040 --> 00:27:57,820
I need some quid pro quo.

382
00:27:57,830 --> 00:27:59,610
What's your connection to this guy?

383
00:28:02,320 --> 00:28:04,950
What I'm about to tell you is secured information.

384
00:28:05,760 --> 00:28:07,940
Two years ago, a congressional subcommittee decided

385
00:28:07,940 --> 00:28:11,170
that Victor Drazen was the key threat to the peace in Bosnia.

387
00:28:11,470 --> 00:28:14,760
They authorized a mission to take him out. I led that mission.

388
00:28:15,050 --> 00:28:16,790
When we got there, things went wrong.

389
00:28:17,150 --> 00:28:18,320
Earlier today, I found out that

390
00:28:18,320 --> 00:28:21,250
Victor Drazen's wife and daughter were killed in the attack.

391
00:28:21,320 --> 00:28:22,450
I thought we'd killed Victor Drazen,

392
00:28:22,450 --> 00:28:24,140
but apparently, I was wrong.

393
00:28:24,460 --> 00:28:26,490
So now his sons want to break him out.

394
00:28:26,950 --> 00:28:29,610
More than that, they want to exact a revenge on me.

395
00:28:29,630 --> 00:28:30,080
Earlier today,

396
00:28:30,080 --> 00:28:32,080
his people kidnapped my wife and daughter.

397
00:28:32,080 --> 00:28:34,150
We got them back. They're safe for now.

398
00:28:34,500 --> 00:28:35,910
But if Victor Drazen escapes from here...

399
00:28:35,910 --> 00:28:37,100
I lose any leverage I've got

400
00:28:37,100 --> 00:28:39,230
of keeping his people away from my family.

401
00:28:41,520 --> 00:28:44,590
- I'll make another call. - We don't have time for calls.

402
00:28:44,830 --> 00:28:47,610
We need to take this prisoner and move him ourselves now.

403
00:28:48,800 --> 00:28:50,270
I said I'll make a call.

404
00:28:53,770 --> 00:28:55,790
We still need to cut the power.

405
00:28:56,120 --> 00:28:58,390
But your brother hasn't contacted us yet.

406
00:28:59,040 --> 00:29:03,030
He would have called by now if he were alive.

407
00:29:04,100 --> 00:29:06,260
We should assume Alexis is dead.

408
00:29:07,280 --> 00:29:09,160
There may be another way, though.

409
00:29:10,580 --> 00:29:13,570
The substation for this sector is a half mile from here.

410
00:29:14,340 --> 00:29:17,030
A few ounces of C-5 should be sufficient.

411
00:29:17,560 --> 00:29:19,610
To save time, we'll go in through the front.

412
00:29:21,540 --> 00:29:24,420
The idea is not to attract attention.

413
00:29:25,850 --> 00:29:28,500
The idea is to get my father out of prison.

414
00:29:30,250 --> 00:29:32,380
This is the best chance we'll ever have.

415
00:29:38,570 --> 00:29:39,900
These don't match.

416
00:29:41,700 --> 00:29:42,920
Hold on.

417
00:29:43,360 --> 00:29:45,340
Where's Jack? I thought he was with you.

418
00:29:45,340 --> 00:29:47,220
He opted to stay in the field literally.

419
00:29:47,220 --> 00:29:47,890
Where? In Saugus?

420
00:29:47,890 --> 00:29:49,800
Yeah. The address he got from the Drazen file.

421
00:29:49,800 --> 00:29:51,810
What's he doing? Why didn't he come back with you?

422
00:29:52,180 --> 00:29:55,520
I don't know. He's a stubborn guy. He insisted on staying.

423
00:29:56,190 --> 00:29:58,670
Meanwhile, Alexis Drazen came to at the hospital,

424
00:29:58,670 --> 00:30:00,890
so I headed over there to interrogate him.

425
00:30:00,980 --> 00:30:02,910
He hasn't talked yet, but I cut off his morphine.

426
00:30:02,910 --> 00:30:05,230
He should be chatty in about an hour.

427
00:30:05,300 --> 00:30:07,490
You didn't tell Jack about his family, did you?

428
00:30:07,920 --> 00:30:09,970
- What are you doing, George? - What are you doing?

429
00:30:10,690 --> 00:30:12,210
Last time I checked, it wasn't a part of my job

430
00:30:12,210 --> 00:30:14,920
to have to explain myself to my subordinates.

431
00:30:15,730 --> 00:30:18,360
Unless they've called off the hit on Palmer's life,

432
00:30:18,710 --> 00:30:21,920
you should be working on securing his day's agenda, right?

433
00:30:22,530 --> 00:30:24,400
Looks like he's going to be our next president.

434
00:30:28,020 --> 00:30:29,210
Thank you.

435
00:30:36,090 --> 00:30:39,160
Senator David Palmer has already carried New York

436
00:30:39,160 --> 00:30:42,110
and with the polls closing shortly here in California....

437
00:30:49,960 --> 00:30:52,630
Everyone's outside celebrating the latest poll.

438
00:30:53,390 --> 00:30:54,930
Come on out, sweetheart.

439
00:31:05,380 --> 00:31:07,320
What is it? David, what's wrong now?

440
00:31:09,260 --> 00:31:11,160
Before, when you said it was over...

441
00:31:12,580 --> 00:31:16,890
...and I asked you what you meant, the campaign or me?

442
00:31:16,890 --> 00:31:19,960
What I said came out of wanting to protect my family...

443
00:31:19,960 --> 00:31:21,550
...wanting to protect you.

444
00:31:22,410 --> 00:31:24,080
You can't hold that against me.

445
00:31:25,440 --> 00:31:26,630
Sherry....

446
00:31:30,290 --> 00:31:31,800
You're an amazing woman.

447
00:31:32,950 --> 00:31:36,380
Smart, determined, sure of yourself.

448
00:31:37,570 --> 00:31:39,080
You always know what you want.

449
00:31:42,500 --> 00:31:44,690
But you don't want me, not really.

450
00:31:47,840 --> 00:31:50,460
I don't think you've wanted me for a very long time.

451
00:31:51,220 --> 00:31:53,130
- That's nonsense. - Is it?

452
00:31:54,500 --> 00:31:58,050
Maybe if everything with Nicole and Keith never happened...

453
00:31:58,930 --> 00:32:00,410
...but it did happen.

454
00:32:01,730 --> 00:32:04,850
And you kept the truth from me for all these years.

455
00:32:06,210 --> 00:32:08,620
I don't think you could have done that without pulling away.

456
00:32:15,010 --> 00:32:16,220
And now....

457
00:32:22,110 --> 00:32:25,430
Now I can't help thinking that I don't trust you anymore.

458
00:32:31,000 --> 00:32:32,730
And if I can't trust you...

459
00:32:35,100 --> 00:32:36,590
...how could I love you?

460
00:32:43,290 --> 00:32:44,590
Well, David...

461
00:32:46,610 --> 00:32:51,010
...you may not love me, but you will never leave me.

462
00:33:00,630 --> 00:33:03,640
You take all the time you need to get yourself together...

463
00:33:04,370 --> 00:33:07,270
...and then you come out and you greet all the people...

464
00:33:07,850 --> 00:33:09,670
...who have given up every day...

465
00:33:10,430 --> 00:33:14,430
...and every night of their lives for the last year...

466
00:33:15,100 --> 00:33:16,650
...to put us in office.

467
00:33:18,150 --> 00:33:20,480
- Us? - Yes.

468
00:33:21,990 --> 00:33:24,870
That's right. Us.

469
00:33:27,040 --> 00:33:31,420
Because come January, when you're being sworn in...

470
00:33:32,250 --> 00:33:34,350
...make no mistake about it...

471
00:33:35,550 --> 00:33:40,170
...this woman here will be standing right next to you.

472
00:34:10,550 --> 00:34:11,860
Open up, two.

473
00:34:28,190 --> 00:34:31,170
Move away from the door. Now.

474
00:35:09,040 --> 00:35:10,160
One thing I don't get,

475
00:35:10,160 --> 00:35:12,310
if Drazen was the target, what's he doing here?

476
00:35:13,530 --> 00:35:16,160
Obversely someone thought he was more valuable alive than dead.

477
00:35:16,160 --> 00:35:18,050
By 'Someone,' you mean one of our people?

478
00:35:18,570 --> 00:35:20,680
He's probably been feeding them intelligence.

479
00:35:23,910 --> 00:35:24,790
Why put you and your men

480
00:35:24,790 --> 00:35:27,060
through the charade of trying to kill him?

481
00:35:27,060 --> 00:35:29,560
Because they wanted the rest of the world to think he was dead.

482
00:35:30,400 --> 00:35:32,710
My mission was set up to fail from the start.

483
00:35:33,300 --> 00:35:35,450
I lost every man I went in there with.

484
00:35:39,090 --> 00:35:40,200
DeSalvo.

485
00:35:41,810 --> 00:35:43,090
Yeah, he's right here.

486
00:35:44,730 --> 00:35:45,930
I understand.

487
00:35:46,020 --> 00:35:47,530
We got permission to move Drazen?

488
00:35:47,530 --> 00:35:50,190
No. That request is still working its way

489
00:35:50,190 --> 00:35:51,170
up the chain of command.

490
00:35:51,180 --> 00:35:53,160
But D.O.D. says you can interrogate him.

491
00:35:53,160 --> 00:35:54,760
- Good. - Bauer?

492
00:35:56,320 --> 00:35:57,530
Five minutes.

493
00:36:00,880 --> 00:36:02,060
Fine.

494
00:36:30,160 --> 00:36:31,740
My name is Jack Bauer.

495
00:36:38,910 --> 00:36:40,960
You'll have to pardon my surprise.

496
00:36:42,000 --> 00:36:43,450
I saw you die.

497
00:36:48,550 --> 00:36:50,440
I watched you enter a building.

498
00:36:51,800 --> 00:36:54,180
Nobody could have survived that explosion.

499
00:37:02,000 --> 00:37:05,970
Our intelligence told us the building was empty when you entered.

500
00:37:25,280 --> 00:37:27,000
Your fight is with me.

501
00:37:28,100 --> 00:37:29,440
Not my wife...

502
00:37:30,300 --> 00:37:32,360
...not my daughter, but with me.

503
00:37:33,820 --> 00:37:37,230
Please, leave my family alone.

504
00:37:48,200 --> 00:37:49,620
Mr. Drazen...

505
00:37:50,890 --> 00:37:53,890
...you have already lost your wife and your daughter.

506
00:37:54,970 --> 00:37:57,180
You don't need to lose your sons, too.

507
00:37:59,130 --> 00:38:01,380
My sons are soldiers.

508
00:38:01,610 --> 00:38:05,140
Then they will die for nothing. We know about the rescue plan.

509
00:38:05,140 --> 00:38:08,320
It was scheduled for 7:20. We stopped it.

510
00:38:08,410 --> 00:38:09,440
We've called in for backup.

511
00:38:09,440 --> 00:38:11,860
If they try again, sir, they will die.

512
00:38:12,800 --> 00:38:15,700
Then you have nothing to worry about.

513
00:38:17,880 --> 00:38:19,580
Call it off, Victor.

514
00:38:20,290 --> 00:38:21,870
How can I?

515
00:38:21,940 --> 00:38:23,470
The same way you've been communicating with them

516
00:38:23,470 --> 00:38:25,090
this entire time!

517
00:38:25,330 --> 00:38:27,920
Call it off or your sons will die!

518
00:38:35,170 --> 00:38:37,060
All right. We'll move him.

519
00:38:56,100 --> 00:38:58,560
Is there another way out of here, not on the schematic?

520
00:38:58,560 --> 00:39:01,050
- A fire or flood egress? - Yes.

521
00:39:01,050 --> 00:39:02,190
Good.

522
00:39:02,190 --> 00:39:03,920
I'll get my men ready.

523
00:39:03,930 --> 00:39:05,660
Have them armed like we did before.

524
00:39:14,440 --> 00:39:15,670
Get up.

525
00:39:18,270 --> 00:39:19,670
Get up.

526
00:39:25,210 --> 00:39:26,780
We're evacuating the prisoner.

527
00:39:26,780 --> 00:39:29,380
Grab your weapons, have personnel convene in Quarter C now.

528
00:39:29,380 --> 00:39:30,460
Yes, sir.

529
00:39:41,590 --> 00:39:42,770
Stop.

530
00:39:51,030 --> 00:39:52,910
- Move out. - Let's go.

531
00:40:11,790 --> 00:40:13,140
Get against the wall.

532
00:40:18,260 --> 00:40:20,270
Lawrence, the power's down in the west quarter.

533
00:40:20,270 --> 00:40:21,270
Copy that.

534
00:40:22,550 --> 00:40:24,150
They are here.

