2
00:00:12,460 --> 00:00:13,390
Right now

3
00:00:13,790 --> 00:00:17,290
terrorists are plotting to assassinate a presidential candidate.

4
00:00:18,020 --> 00:00:20,230
My wife and daughter have been targeted

5
00:00:20,670 --> 00:00:24,290
and people that I work with may be involved in both.

6
00:00:24,920 --> 00:00:27,060
I'm Federal Agent Jack Bauer

7
00:00:27,370 --> 00:00:30,930
and today is the longest day of my life.

10
00:00:40,270 --> 00:00:45,270
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

11
00:00:40,270 --> 00:00:45,270
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

12
00:00:40,270 --> 00:00:45,270
{\an5}{\pos(145,252)}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

13
00:00:40,770 --> 00:00:45,270
{\pos(67,248)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

14
00:00:40,770 --> 00:00:45,270
{\pos(67,248)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

15
00:00:40,770 --> 00:00:45,270
{\pos(58,238)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

16
00:00:40,770 --> 00:00:45,270
{\pos(84,248)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

19
00:00:46,490 --> 00:01:11,490
{\an9}m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

20
00:00:45,990 --> 00:01:11,490
{\an2}{\pos(26,248)}m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

26
00:00:50,560 --> 00:00:52,180
First time you invited me back here,

27
00:00:52,190 --> 00:00:53,830
you left your keys in my car.

28
00:00:54,050 --> 00:00:55,630
It was pouring rain.

29
00:00:56,380 --> 00:00:58,230
We didn't want to run back, so

30
00:01:00,000 --> 00:01:01,550
we used your hide-a-key.

31
00:01:24,580 --> 00:01:25,610
What do I do?

32
00:01:26,710 --> 00:01:27,530
I don't know what to do.

33
00:01:27,530 --> 00:01:28,580
I don't know what the code is.

34
00:01:28,580 --> 00:01:30,440
Just take your time. Maybe it'll come to you.

35
00:01:34,320 --> 00:01:36,110
Just make this stop!

36
00:01:50,450 --> 00:01:53,000
- Hello? - This is Superior Alarm.

37
00:01:53,000 --> 00:01:54,500
Could you please turn this off?

38
00:01:54,500 --> 00:01:56,070
- I'll need your password. - What?

39
00:01:56,990 --> 00:01:59,820
Ma'am, what is your password?

40
00:02:00,010 --> 00:02:01,710
I don't know the password.

41
00:02:01,830 --> 00:02:03,330
Are you having an emergency there?

42
00:02:04,880 --> 00:02:07,550
Alan Morgan, Saugus.

43
00:02:07,560 --> 00:02:11,700
- Yeah, Pacific Electric. - Got it. All right, thanks.

44
00:02:13,700 --> 00:02:14,750
Jack.

45
00:02:15,150 --> 00:02:16,840
His name was Alan Morgan.

46
00:02:16,840 --> 00:02:19,760
- He works for Pacific Electric in Saugus. - Saugus?

47
00:02:20,230 --> 00:02:21,840
OK. He was paid off by Alexis

48
00:02:21,840 --> 00:02:23,350
to kill the power in the section of the grid.

49
00:02:23,350 --> 00:02:26,170
- Did you get the coordinates? 26, GG. - GG, yes.

50
00:02:26,170 --> 00:02:27,870
That's right. We need to know where that is now.

51
00:02:27,870 --> 00:02:29,910
Okay. I'll get this to Tony. You need me to stick around?

52
00:02:29,910 --> 00:02:32,020
No. Just get a hold of me as soon as you get anything, ok?

53
00:02:32,020 --> 00:02:34,250
- Ok. See you back at the office. - Thank you.

54
00:02:37,230 --> 00:02:38,540
None of these are working.

55
00:02:39,550 --> 00:02:42,120
Superior Alarm. Stay where you are.

56
00:02:42,490 --> 00:02:43,300
Please.

57
00:02:43,310 --> 00:02:45,400
This woman, she lives here.

58
00:02:45,720 --> 00:02:47,220
She just forgot her code.

59
00:03:05,420 --> 00:03:06,860
- Thank you. - You're welcome.

60
00:03:07,310 --> 00:03:08,650
- Teri Bauer? - Yes.

61
00:03:08,760 --> 00:03:09,930
Do you have any ID?

62
00:03:12,650 --> 00:03:16,050
Sure. It's probably in my purse. I'll go check.

63
00:03:40,760 --> 00:03:43,970
No ID necessary. You obviously live here.

64
00:03:44,960 --> 00:03:47,140
She just couldn't remember her code.

65
00:03:48,170 --> 00:03:49,840
I don't usually set it.

66
00:03:50,380 --> 00:03:53,470
- My daughter must have. - It's all right. Just sign this.

67
00:03:59,560 --> 00:04:02,320
Okay. I'm going to reset the alarm...

68
00:04:02,320 --> 00:04:04,450
...and check the contacts around the outside the house.

69
00:04:04,450 --> 00:04:07,730
- That should take about 15 minutes. - Thank you.

70
00:04:11,220 --> 00:04:12,220
Thank you.

71
00:04:43,760 --> 00:04:45,300
Nice, Jack. Have you noticed...

72
00:04:45,300 --> 00:04:47,260
...how there's always a body count everywhere you go?

73
00:04:47,260 --> 00:04:49,430
I gave Hanlin clear orders not to shoot.

74
00:04:49,710 --> 00:04:52,170
- Where'd he go? - He's over there.

75
00:04:55,180 --> 00:04:57,300
- Bauer. - Jack, it's David Palmer.

76
00:04:57,300 --> 00:04:58,450
Yes, Senator?

77
00:04:58,860 --> 00:05:00,990
I just heard back from my source at the Pentagon.

78
00:05:01,520 --> 00:05:04,490
Had to twist a lot of arms to get a hold of the missing Drazen file.

79
00:05:04,490 --> 00:05:07,030
- What was in it? - Dates and locations.

80
00:05:07,030 --> 00:05:10,950
It seems to relate to the last months of Victor Drazen's life.

81
00:05:10,950 --> 00:05:13,500
- Anything we can use? - Maybe.

82
00:05:14,010 --> 00:05:18,580
The last entry is an address unrelated to everything else.

83
00:05:18,680 --> 00:05:19,800
What is it?

84
00:05:19,810 --> 00:05:21,670
21911 Kipling...

85
00:05:21,690 --> 00:05:24,780
...in a city called Saugus. I don't know where that is.

86
00:05:24,780 --> 00:05:27,230
I'm sorry, Senator. Did you just say "Saugus"?

87
00:05:27,290 --> 00:05:28,110
Does that mean anything?

88
00:05:28,110 --> 00:05:30,140
Yes, it does. I I'm gonna have to get back to you.

89
00:05:30,240 --> 00:05:32,130
Thank you, Senator. This is going to help.

90
00:05:32,130 --> 00:05:33,310
All right.

91
00:05:39,470 --> 00:05:40,570
CTU. Almeida.

92
00:05:40,570 --> 00:05:42,860
Tony, it's Jack. Take down this address for me.

93
00:05:42,860 --> 00:05:43,530
Go ahead.

94
00:05:43,530 --> 00:05:48,020
21911 Kipling Avenue in Saugus.

95
00:05:48,160 --> 00:05:50,930
I got a feeling it's gonna be in the grid coordinates Nina just gave you.

96
00:05:51,050 --> 00:05:52,240
All right, hang on.

97
00:06:00,500 --> 00:06:01,620
Yes, you're right.

98
00:06:02,220 --> 00:06:04,810
It's right in the middle of Sector 26, GG.

99
00:06:04,810 --> 00:06:07,230
Ok. Find out what's there. Get back to me on my cell.

100
00:06:07,230 --> 00:06:08,570
All right.

101
00:06:11,400 --> 00:06:12,420
Where you headed?

102
00:06:12,920 --> 00:06:14,270
I'm going to Saugus.

103
00:06:14,340 --> 00:06:15,390
Alexis paid this guy off

104
00:06:15,390 --> 00:06:17,410
to knock the power out at the specific address out there.

105
00:06:17,410 --> 00:06:19,720
- I want to know why. - Slow down, Jack.

106
00:06:19,720 --> 00:06:21,310
I'm on your side. Fill me in.

107
00:06:24,040 --> 00:06:25,450
Two and a half hours ago,

108
00:06:26,250 --> 00:06:28,170
Robert Ellis was killed in New Orleans

109
00:06:28,170 --> 00:06:30,180
because he almost found out about this location.

110
00:06:30,180 --> 00:06:31,790
We got the address from the Drazen file.

111
00:06:31,790 --> 00:06:33,480
The Senator just gave it to me.

112
00:06:35,060 --> 00:06:37,680
- Let's go. - What do you mean, "Let's"?

113
00:06:37,810 --> 00:06:40,550
If you want to go, I'm your chaperone. You want a ride?

114
00:06:47,350 --> 00:06:48,480
Yeah.

115
00:06:49,350 --> 00:06:50,570
Hop in.

116
00:06:59,770 --> 00:07:01,500
- Where's my brother? - I don't know.

117
00:07:01,500 --> 00:07:02,600
These guys are gonna be here in 20 minutes,

118
00:07:02,600 --> 00:07:03,590
if I don't have that money...

119
00:07:03,590 --> 00:07:05,190
I told you, Frank, we split up.

120
00:07:05,190 --> 00:07:07,950
He said he's gonna meet me back here with the payoff from Gaines.

121
00:07:09,210 --> 00:07:11,930
Look, if I was ripping you off, why would I come back here?

122
00:07:12,930 --> 00:07:13,950
Damn it!

123
00:07:15,260 --> 00:07:17,250
- Where you going? - Don't worry about it.

124
00:07:18,540 --> 00:07:19,380
What are you doing?

125
00:07:19,380 --> 00:07:21,170
I'm not waiting around for that lunatic to get us killed.

126
00:07:21,170 --> 00:07:22,470
- You're not going anywhere. - Melanie!

127
00:07:22,470 --> 00:07:24,210
She'll go to the police. She'll tell them about the deal.

128
00:07:24,210 --> 00:07:25,490
I don't care about the deal.

129
00:07:25,490 --> 00:07:28,040
I came here because I wanted you to help me find my mom.

130
00:07:28,040 --> 00:07:30,590
- But obviously that was a dumb idea. - You came here for Rick.

131
00:07:30,590 --> 00:07:33,040
- I did not. - Kim, don't worry about her. You should just leave.

132
00:07:33,040 --> 00:07:34,610
What do you mean don't worry about me?

133
00:07:35,820 --> 00:07:37,220
- Come with me. - I can't.

134
00:07:37,220 --> 00:07:38,280
Whatever's going on out there

135
00:07:38,280 --> 00:07:39,650
is gonna be a lot better than in here.

136
00:07:39,660 --> 00:07:42,510
You heard Frank. Nobody goes anywhere until Dan gets back.

137
00:07:42,520 --> 00:07:43,930
Dan is not coming back.

138
00:07:46,360 --> 00:07:47,440
What do you mean?

139
00:07:51,680 --> 00:07:53,550
I don't know, I just....

140
00:07:53,550 --> 00:07:54,520
- What do you mean? - I just....

141
00:07:55,230 --> 00:07:57,310
- Leave her alone. - Where is he?

142
00:08:00,670 --> 00:08:01,720
He's dead.

143
00:08:02,970 --> 00:08:04,110
What are you talking about?

144
00:08:04,750 --> 00:08:06,820
Gaines killed him. He was going to kill me, too.

145
00:08:06,820 --> 00:08:09,720
I swear to God, Frank. This guy, Gaines, was out of control.

146
00:08:33,830 --> 00:08:37,000
- Who's got the money now? - Nobody.

147
00:08:37,820 --> 00:08:39,150
Gaines never paid us.

148
00:08:47,480 --> 00:08:49,290
These guys are going to be here in half an hour.

149
00:08:50,350 --> 00:08:52,140
These are not the kind of guys you invite over to do a deal

150
00:08:52,140 --> 00:08:53,370
and come up short.

151
00:08:53,370 --> 00:08:55,690
- Then call it off. - Too late to call it off!

152
00:09:37,580 --> 00:09:39,930
What are you gonna say down there today, David?

153
00:09:44,490 --> 00:09:47,010
- He's gonna tell the truth. - Don't you start with me, Keith.

154
00:09:47,140 --> 00:09:49,620
- You've caused enough pain in this family. - Sherry!

155
00:09:49,620 --> 00:09:52,650
Well, I'm sorry, David, but somebody has to say the words.

156
00:09:53,060 --> 00:09:55,940
This whole thing wouldn't have started if Keith hadn't decided

157
00:09:55,940 --> 00:09:57,730
to take matters into his own hands.

158
00:09:59,570 --> 00:10:00,640
Listen to me.

159
00:10:02,890 --> 00:10:04,670
Nobody's defending what Keith did.

160
00:10:06,070 --> 00:10:08,230
He acted on the moment. It wasn't right.

161
00:10:08,890 --> 00:10:11,280
That doesn't make you right for covering it up.

162
00:10:11,370 --> 00:10:13,490
Doesn't make me right for not being there.

163
00:10:14,310 --> 00:10:17,580
So we're all to blame. Let's just leave it at that.

164
00:10:19,420 --> 00:10:22,790
That's right, Mom. I'm willing to pay the price for this.

165
00:10:22,940 --> 00:10:24,610
Even if it means going to jail.

166
00:10:25,880 --> 00:10:29,310
You still think this is just about you, don't you?

167
00:10:29,830 --> 00:10:33,550
When are you going to get it through your head

168
00:10:33,980 --> 00:10:35,540
that your father is

169
00:10:35,540 --> 00:10:38,610
running for President of the United States?

170
00:10:38,720 --> 00:10:40,030
A black man.

171
00:10:40,470 --> 00:10:44,300
You don't just decide to ease your conscience

172
00:10:44,300 --> 00:10:46,950
at the cost of what might be best for this country.

173
00:10:46,950 --> 00:10:49,370
- I didn't, Mom. - Both of you, calm down.

174
00:10:55,710 --> 00:10:57,130
I kept it inside.

175
00:10:58,020 --> 00:11:00,700
I was willing to suck it up for as long as it took.

176
00:11:01,630 --> 00:11:03,870
But someone murdered Dr. Ferragamo this morning

177
00:11:03,870 --> 00:11:04,730
and you can't tell me

178
00:11:04,730 --> 00:11:07,080
to hiding that is what is best for this country.

179
00:11:07,080 --> 00:11:08,170
You know what?

180
00:11:09,680 --> 00:11:11,990
I never saw it until just this minute.

181
00:11:12,730 --> 00:11:14,140
You're your father's son.

182
00:11:15,470 --> 00:11:17,200
You cover up your weakness

183
00:11:17,200 --> 00:11:19,730
with a bunch of bleeding-heart sentimentality.

184
00:11:19,730 --> 00:11:21,640
- Sherry, that's enough. - Am I wrong?

185
00:11:21,650 --> 00:11:23,850
When are you going to be man

186
00:11:23,850 --> 00:11:25,950
enough to do what it takes to be President?

187
00:11:25,950 --> 00:11:27,310
Nicole, are you okay?

188
00:11:29,330 --> 00:11:31,960
- What's wrong? Honey? - Nicole!

189
00:11:32,640 --> 00:11:34,320
Keith, get me some water.

190
00:11:35,310 --> 00:11:36,340
Come on.

191
00:11:36,870 --> 00:11:38,320
We need a doctor in here.

192
00:11:45,400 --> 00:11:46,940
Easy, relax.

193
00:11:46,940 --> 00:11:48,330
Come here. Give me your hands.

194
00:11:58,930 --> 00:12:00,550
I'm so sorry, Daddy.

195
00:12:00,550 --> 00:12:02,800
What? Sorry about what?

196
00:12:05,670 --> 00:12:06,960
Honey, talk to me.

197
00:12:12,610 --> 00:12:13,910
This is all my fault.

198
00:12:14,690 --> 00:12:17,990
Don't you ever say that. No, sweetheart, don't you say that.

199
00:12:17,990 --> 00:12:19,360
Everything's going to be fine.

200
00:12:27,660 --> 00:12:30,700
- I'm sorry, Daddy. - No, honey.

201
00:12:31,580 --> 00:12:32,870
I'm sorry.

202
00:12:35,140 --> 00:12:36,240
I just got in.

203
00:12:36,320 --> 00:12:38,600
I've got some more info on that location in Saugus.

204
00:12:38,610 --> 00:12:39,740
Okay, hold on.

205
00:12:41,340 --> 00:12:42,420
Okay, go.

206
00:12:42,630 --> 00:12:44,570
Comes up as a wildlife preserve.

207
00:12:44,610 --> 00:12:46,700
Great, we're going to a Sierra Club meeting.

209
00:12:46,820 --> 00:12:47,820
Who's with you?

210
00:12:48,200 --> 00:12:50,820
Mason. A wildlife preserve in Saugus?

211
00:12:50,820 --> 00:12:51,480
That doesn't make sense.

212
00:12:51,480 --> 00:12:54,410
Saugus is all industrial. What about the GPS maps?

213
00:12:54,610 --> 00:12:55,920
I've got three on the way.

214
00:12:55,920 --> 00:12:59,090
Good work. We'll call you when we find out what's out there.

215
00:12:59,110 --> 00:13:00,200
Yeah, okay.

216
00:13:06,440 --> 00:13:07,750
So correct me if I'm wrong

217
00:13:07,750 --> 00:13:11,170
but what this day basically boils down to is a personal vendetta

218
00:13:11,180 --> 00:13:13,570
against you and Palmer by the family of VIctor Drazen?

219
00:13:13,570 --> 00:13:16,440
Yes. Palmer authorized the mission. I carried it out.

220
00:13:17,140 --> 00:13:19,830
Today is the second anniversary of Victor Drazen's death.

221
00:13:20,140 --> 00:13:21,430
Happy anniversary.

222
00:13:24,160 --> 00:13:27,470
What is it we're expecting to find out here in Saugus?

223
00:13:27,470 --> 00:13:28,400
I don't know yet.

224
00:13:30,320 --> 00:13:33,810
I got to tell you, Jack, it never gets dull with you.

225
00:13:36,060 --> 00:13:37,170
Yeah.

226
00:13:38,770 --> 00:13:41,870
Look, for what it's worth, I'm sorry about last night.

227
00:13:42,570 --> 00:13:44,290
Shoot me in the leg with a tranq?

228
00:13:44,680 --> 00:13:46,200
Don't give it a second thought.

229
00:13:46,570 --> 00:13:48,570
Needless to say, I was pretty wound up.

230
00:13:48,570 --> 00:13:52,150
I feel a lot better now though, knowing my family is safe.

231
00:13:57,300 --> 00:13:58,380
What's the matter?

232
00:13:58,740 --> 00:14:02,550
I'm just beat, you know? I could use a little sleep.

233
00:14:03,020 --> 00:14:04,290
Tell me about it.

234
00:14:21,620 --> 00:14:22,830
How you doing?

235
00:14:23,260 --> 00:14:24,470
I don't know.

236
00:14:26,200 --> 00:14:29,200
Everything looks familiar, but I don't understand any of it.

237
00:14:29,940 --> 00:14:32,430
I don't feel anything and I should, shouldn't I?

238
00:14:32,430 --> 00:14:34,660
No, not yet.

239
00:14:36,580 --> 00:14:41,620
Sometimes music can help unlock memories.

240
00:14:57,670 --> 00:14:59,600
- Did you ever meet Kim? - No.

241
00:15:00,660 --> 00:15:02,730
You didn't want her to know you were seeing anyone.

242
00:15:03,470 --> 00:15:05,970
You said she was taking Jack's side in the separation

243
00:15:06,250 --> 00:15:08,740
and you didn't want her to be angrier with you.

244
00:15:10,310 --> 00:15:13,620
Why did my husband, Jack.... Why did Jack leave me?

245
00:15:13,760 --> 00:15:14,990
You asked him to.

246
00:15:16,110 --> 00:15:18,830
You told me he was too removed.

247
00:15:19,660 --> 00:15:21,690
There was no connection between you two anymore.

248
00:15:22,970 --> 00:15:24,260
How about you and I?

249
00:15:28,240 --> 00:15:29,630
I thought there was one.

250
00:15:30,730 --> 00:15:31,930
But what, I didn't?

251
00:15:33,520 --> 00:15:35,110
Truth is, I think you did.

252
00:15:36,010 --> 00:15:37,290
But you were scared.

253
00:15:37,700 --> 00:15:39,060
You didn't want to lose your family.

254
00:15:40,340 --> 00:15:42,710
When Jack asked to move back in, you let him.

255
00:15:48,330 --> 00:15:50,680
- It's funny. - What?

256
00:15:50,680 --> 00:15:52,080
I don't remember you at all.

257
00:15:53,330 --> 00:15:55,960
But being with you makes me feel good,

258
00:15:55,960 --> 00:15:59,810
and maybe I don't feel so scared.

259
00:16:08,800 --> 00:16:10,420
Thank you for doing this, Phil.

260
00:16:19,380 --> 00:16:20,450
The truck come through?

261
00:16:22,170 --> 00:16:23,280
I hope not.

262
00:16:23,800 --> 00:16:25,160
No, just park in the back.

263
00:16:26,460 --> 00:16:27,650
Just sit tight.

264
00:16:27,690 --> 00:16:29,390
Look, I can't stay here. I need to find my mom.

265
00:16:29,390 --> 00:16:31,220
I don't know how to get you out here.

266
00:16:31,590 --> 00:16:34,130
- I'll make a run for it. - I wouldn't. Frank's a psycho.

267
00:16:34,130 --> 00:16:35,250
You don't want to cross him.

268
00:16:38,210 --> 00:16:39,630
- I'm going to go. - No.

269
00:16:48,160 --> 00:16:51,590
Hey! No. Get in the kitchen.

270
00:16:53,290 --> 00:16:54,320
Come on in, man.

271
00:16:57,060 --> 00:16:58,200
You, be careful.

272
00:17:00,260 --> 00:17:02,650
No, he's cool. Come on.

273
00:17:06,780 --> 00:17:07,900
Let's see it.

274
00:17:19,090 --> 00:17:23,040
Yes. That's what I'm talking about.

275
00:17:23,450 --> 00:17:24,970
Are these the guys with the ecstasy?

276
00:17:24,970 --> 00:17:26,610
No, they're friends of mine.

277
00:17:27,290 --> 00:17:29,840
- Frank, what are you going to do? - What does it Iook like?

278
00:17:30,020 --> 00:17:31,830
Can't pay the dealer. We don't have any money.

279
00:17:31,960 --> 00:17:33,700
- You're going to rip them off?. - Yes.

280
00:17:50,220 --> 00:17:51,280
Thank you.

281
00:17:55,250 --> 00:17:58,200
- Are you all right, honey? - I'm absolutely fine, daddy.

282
00:17:59,460 --> 00:18:00,260
Good.

283
00:18:00,260 --> 00:18:02,380
Go ahead. They're waiting for you.

284
00:18:04,070 --> 00:18:07,060
Okay. I'm going to head down now.

285
00:18:18,290 --> 00:18:19,690
This is a test for us.

286
00:18:21,840 --> 00:18:23,310
If we love each other,

287
00:18:24,430 --> 00:18:25,700
support each other,

288
00:18:30,650 --> 00:18:31,990
nothing else will matter.

289
00:18:39,360 --> 00:18:40,380
Sherry?

290
00:18:44,730 --> 00:18:46,460
I need you now more than ever.

291
00:19:09,840 --> 00:19:12,590
I've always liked this tie on you, David.

292
00:19:16,240 --> 00:19:19,140
Senator? It's time.

293
00:19:54,430 --> 00:19:55,770
Anything look familiar?

294
00:19:56,820 --> 00:19:59,570
It's weird looking at what I did for the last couple of months.

295
00:19:59,570 --> 00:20:00,880
It doesn't mean anything to me.

296
00:20:02,640 --> 00:20:03,980
"Yvonne's birthday."

297
00:20:04,970 --> 00:20:06,930
"Kim in Cambria for the weekend."

298
00:20:09,300 --> 00:20:10,460
"Dinner with Phil."

299
00:20:11,310 --> 00:20:12,550
"Ivy at the shore."

300
00:20:14,650 --> 00:20:15,730
Was it nice?

301
00:20:16,400 --> 00:20:18,770
Well, the wait was over an hour, so

302
00:20:20,240 --> 00:20:22,990
we decided to walk down the pier and have some hot dogs.

303
00:20:25,660 --> 00:20:27,170
And you beat me in air hockey.

304
00:20:32,600 --> 00:20:33,610
Air hockey?

305
00:20:40,970 --> 00:20:42,150
What's in there for today?

306
00:20:43,790 --> 00:20:44,860
Nothing.

307
00:20:45,890 --> 00:20:48,090
But yesterday, I had a conference call with Kitty,

308
00:20:48,090 --> 00:20:49,420
whoever that is.

309
00:20:49,790 --> 00:20:52,020
Kitty, she's a friend of yours. You work with her sometimes.

310
00:20:53,250 --> 00:20:55,300
You do commercial interior design.

311
00:20:55,300 --> 00:20:57,280
It's just freelance right now...

312
00:20:57,280 --> 00:20:59,930
but you want to expand when Kim goes to college.

313
00:21:01,320 --> 00:21:02,780
How can I sort of remember air hockey...

314
00:21:02,780 --> 00:21:04,810
but I can't remember what I do for a living?

315
00:21:08,140 --> 00:21:09,100
Maybe that's Jack.

316
00:21:09,100 --> 00:21:10,640
No, he wouldn't ring the bell.

317
00:21:10,640 --> 00:21:12,740
It's probably my friend Chris, remember?

318
00:21:12,740 --> 00:21:14,070
I told you I wanted to have someone here,

319
00:21:14,070 --> 00:21:15,430
just to be on the safe side.

320
00:21:16,370 --> 00:21:18,840
- Yes. - Stay here just in case.

321
00:21:31,840 --> 00:21:34,250
- Teri, this is Chris. - Hi.

322
00:21:35,920 --> 00:21:36,790
Why does he have a gun?

323
00:21:36,790 --> 00:21:38,010
I told you he's here to protect...

324
00:21:38,010 --> 00:21:39,010
I don't care. I don't wanna guns.

325
00:21:39,010 --> 00:21:40,730
Get him out of the house with that gun.

326
00:21:40,730 --> 00:21:43,160
Chris, will you just give us a couple minute, okay?

327
00:21:44,160 --> 00:21:46,770
- Sure. - Thanks.

328
00:21:51,260 --> 00:21:53,240
Teri,Chris is a friend of mine. I called him.

329
00:21:53,240 --> 00:21:54,710
That doesn't mean anything to me.

330
00:21:55,630 --> 00:21:58,020
I don't know who you are. I don't know who he is.

331
00:21:58,020 --> 00:21:59,700
I didn't... I don't want any guns.

332
00:21:59,700 --> 00:22:02,220
Okay, I'll tell him to stay outside.

333
00:22:02,220 --> 00:22:03,390
Is that okay?

334
00:22:04,420 --> 00:22:06,710
But we need him here, just in case.

335
00:22:07,510 --> 00:22:10,350
Teri, your husband could have been the one who roughed you up.

336
00:22:11,410 --> 00:22:12,980
I want you safe.

337
00:22:15,900 --> 00:22:17,040
Teri, Iook at me.

338
00:22:18,920 --> 00:22:20,060
Look at me.

339
00:22:22,850 --> 00:22:24,120
I'm your friend.

340
00:22:25,180 --> 00:22:26,470
You trust me.

341
00:22:26,820 --> 00:22:28,260
You told me so yourself.

342
00:22:29,180 --> 00:22:30,910
So you're going to have to trust my judgment.

343
00:22:34,400 --> 00:22:35,500
- Okay. - Okay.

344
00:22:37,730 --> 00:22:39,040
What's going on over there?

345
00:22:39,540 --> 00:22:41,550
The wife is here.

346
00:22:42,040 --> 00:22:43,680
- And the daughter? - No.

347
00:22:44,490 --> 00:22:45,830
What are you waiting for?

348
00:22:46,060 --> 00:22:49,690
There's a little interference, but it will pass soon.

349
00:22:49,900 --> 00:22:52,050
- Did you find Alexis? - Not yet.

350
00:22:53,080 --> 00:22:55,600
- Call me when it's done. - Yes.

351
00:23:10,740 --> 00:23:14,900
Ladies and gentlemen of the press, please take your seats now.

352
00:23:15,380 --> 00:23:19,160
Senator Palmer is just about here. We will begin.

353
00:23:34,180 --> 00:23:35,500
Senator Palmer?

354
00:23:38,580 --> 00:23:42,260
Last night, I received a phone call regarding my son, Keith...

355
00:23:42,830 --> 00:23:44,120
and my daughter, Nicole.

356
00:23:44,960 --> 00:23:48,140
That call has unfortunately set off a chain of events...

357
00:23:48,150 --> 00:23:50,470
that has culminated in a terrible tragedy.

358
00:23:52,170 --> 00:23:55,310
Whether or not what I have to say jeopardizes my campaign...

359
00:23:55,310 --> 00:23:57,030
is for the voters to decide.

360
00:23:58,150 --> 00:23:59,860
I'm doing this for my family.

361
00:24:01,890 --> 00:24:06,270
A large portion of the financial support for my campaign...

362
00:24:06,270 --> 00:24:08,980
comes from a group of businessmen right here in Los Angeles.

363
00:24:10,830 --> 00:24:13,400
Every presidential campaign relies on these monetary...

364
00:24:13,400 --> 00:24:15,870
- I'll take care of it. - from a variety of sources.

365
00:24:16,550 --> 00:24:18,420
Too late, Carl.

366
00:24:20,530 --> 00:24:23,290
I have apparently misjudged these local businessmen.

367
00:24:23,590 --> 00:24:26,350
More importantly, they have misjudged me.

368
00:24:34,960 --> 00:24:37,520
How it was acquired, I am not at liberty to say.

369
00:24:40,050 --> 00:24:41,430
I've already handed

371
00:24:41,430 --> 00:24:44,720
this incriminating tape over to the Justice Department.

372
00:24:45,740 --> 00:24:47,650
Whether or not it's admissible in court...

373
00:24:48,870 --> 00:24:50,170
it will still implicate

374
00:24:50,170 --> 00:24:52,560
the men who have been supporting my campaign.

375
00:24:54,650 --> 00:24:55,910
I'll emphasize again...

376
00:24:56,830 --> 00:25:01,490
that these men acted without my consent or my knowledge.

377
00:25:03,830 --> 00:25:05,200
As for my son, Keith...

378
00:25:06,920 --> 00:25:09,350
he is prepared to turn himself in

379
00:25:09,350 --> 00:25:11,130
and face whatever consequences

380
00:25:11,310 --> 00:25:13,170
a grand jury deems necessary.

381
00:25:15,080 --> 00:25:18,350
He is my son, and I love him...

382
00:25:18,890 --> 00:25:20,500
and I will stand by him.

383
00:25:21,370 --> 00:25:24,460
I am confident that when presented with the facts...

384
00:25:24,460 --> 00:25:25,580
it will be clear

385
00:25:25,630 --> 00:25:28,300
that there was no criminal intent or wrongdoing.

386
00:25:29,100 --> 00:25:31,800
He will only be guilty of not reporting an accident.

387
00:25:34,500 --> 00:25:36,090
As for my daughter, Nicole...

388
00:25:39,190 --> 00:25:41,270
It is important for everyone to remember...

389
00:25:41,740 --> 00:25:44,000
she was a victim of a horrible crime.

390
00:25:44,730 --> 00:25:47,420
A physical and psychological crime.

391
00:25:48,640 --> 00:25:52,140
She is not a source of information.

392
00:25:54,090 --> 00:25:57,070
This is about a cover-up of an accidental death.

393
00:25:58,710 --> 00:26:00,080
This is not about rape.

394
00:26:01,750 --> 00:26:05,960
So, I am asking you now as a father,

395
00:26:05,960 --> 00:26:06,710
please find your humanity...

396
00:26:07,000 --> 00:26:08,840
and spare Nicole the indignity of

397
00:26:08,840 --> 00:26:11,390
having to relive this nightmare.

398
00:26:14,980 --> 00:26:16,750
After that, we lost track of both of them.

399
00:26:16,750 --> 00:26:18,910
Wait a minute. How long have you known this?

400
00:26:19,380 --> 00:26:20,500
- Why didn't you tell me this early? -Nina.

401
00:26:20,500 --> 00:26:22,030
- Does Jack know about this? - Nina.

402
00:26:22,030 --> 00:26:23,280
Not that I'm aware of.

403
00:26:23,550 --> 00:26:26,160
- Did you know the safe house was hit? - Relax, okay?

404
00:26:26,760 --> 00:26:28,130
Tony, answer me.

405
00:26:28,910 --> 00:26:31,420
- Yes, I knew. - Why didn't you tell me?

406
00:26:31,940 --> 00:26:33,390
Look, Mason didn't want you to know

407
00:26:33,390 --> 00:26:34,940
because he didn't want you to tell Jack.

408
00:26:36,070 --> 00:26:38,360
His family is missing. Don't you think he should know that?

409
00:26:38,580 --> 00:26:40,000
Yes. I'm with you on this.

410
00:26:40,450 --> 00:26:42,620
Look, Mason gave the order, all right?

411
00:26:42,930 --> 00:26:45,840
He's deployed resources. He's called locals to help find them.

412
00:26:46,080 --> 00:26:48,740
You should have told me. You work for me.

413
00:26:48,740 --> 00:26:50,170
And you work for Mason.

414
00:26:52,610 --> 00:26:56,120
This is my fault. I should never have left Teri and Kim.

415
00:26:56,880 --> 00:26:59,330
Nina, you're not a field agent, all right?

416
00:26:59,550 --> 00:27:02,490
- What could you have done? - Jack needs to know about this.

417
00:27:09,020 --> 00:27:09,720
Mason.

418
00:27:09,720 --> 00:27:12,660
George, have you told Jack about his family yet?

419
00:27:12,810 --> 00:27:14,380
No. We're not there yet.

420
00:27:14,790 --> 00:27:17,440
You can't do this. You have to tell him.

421
00:27:18,710 --> 00:27:21,410
Why not let him know so he can help us find them?

422
00:27:21,430 --> 00:27:23,060
George, they're out there. They're exposed.

423
00:27:23,060 --> 00:27:24,520
If Drazen's people find them first...

424
00:27:24,520 --> 00:27:25,740
That's a good idea.

425
00:27:25,910 --> 00:27:27,140
Listen to me, George.

426
00:27:27,720 --> 00:27:30,460
If anything happens to them, he's going to hold you responsible.

427
00:27:30,460 --> 00:27:31,760
You better think about that.

428
00:27:31,760 --> 00:27:34,260
I will. Okay. Let me know if you have any progress.

429
00:27:34,490 --> 00:27:35,630
George!

430
00:27:36,860 --> 00:27:38,100
Nina.

431
00:27:43,790 --> 00:27:47,200
Jack, my battery just died. Can I use your phone for a second?

432
00:27:47,300 --> 00:27:48,380
Yes, sure.

433
00:27:51,170 --> 00:27:52,150
Thanks.

434
00:28:00,810 --> 00:28:02,110
Yes, it's me.

435
00:28:02,770 --> 00:28:03,460
All I want to say is just

436
00:28:03,460 --> 00:28:05,580
keep the backup units on standby, all right?

437
00:28:05,580 --> 00:28:09,060
This cellular customer you are trying to reach is unavallable.

438
00:28:10,080 --> 00:28:11,850
- Okay. - I've got a signal.

439
00:28:37,560 --> 00:28:39,020
What did Nina have to say?

440
00:28:39,340 --> 00:28:40,970
She was just checking our location.

441
00:28:40,970 --> 00:28:42,300
What does the GPS say?

442
00:28:42,970 --> 00:28:45,410
Doesn't make sense, it's saying the address is right up ahead.

443
00:28:46,760 --> 00:28:48,210
I know the whole thing was hush-hush,

444
00:28:48,220 --> 00:28:50,280
but who exactly was Victor Drazen?

445
00:28:50,280 --> 00:28:52,570
Victor Drazen was Milosevic's shadow.

446
00:28:52,580 --> 00:28:54,740
He was in charge of all of his covert operations.

447
00:28:54,840 --> 00:28:55,990
He was responsible for

448
00:28:55,990 --> 00:28:57,830
organizing all the ethnic cleansing campaigns...

449
00:28:57,830 --> 00:29:00,870
in Kosovo, Sarajevo and Bosnia.

450
00:29:02,240 --> 00:29:04,180
- Your unit took him out? - That's right.

451
00:29:04,730 --> 00:29:06,610
- You rolled the whole deal up? - Yep.

452
00:29:09,060 --> 00:29:10,810
So, who do you think would have the influence...

453
00:29:10,810 --> 00:29:13,800
to be able to run an operation like this against you and Palmer?

454
00:29:14,170 --> 00:29:15,840
My guess would be Serbian military exiles.

455
00:29:15,840 --> 00:29:17,260
I mean they could pull this off.

456
00:29:17,610 --> 00:29:18,990
Somehow, Alexis and Andre

457
00:29:18,990 --> 00:29:20,820
pulled together a cell without us knowing.

458
00:29:21,060 --> 00:29:21,950
It's a hell of a cell

459
00:29:21,950 --> 00:29:25,120
being able to infiltrate the CTU, turn Jamey.

460
00:29:25,310 --> 00:29:27,780
I agree, it's hard to believe that Jamey could move so freely

461
00:29:27,780 --> 00:29:30,310
to work against us without some kind of umbrella.

462
00:29:32,680 --> 00:29:36,080
Any ideas on why the Serbs would want to spend this much money

463
00:29:36,080 --> 00:29:38,150
to turn the power off in the middle of the woods?

464
00:29:39,060 --> 00:29:40,180
No.

465
00:29:43,080 --> 00:29:46,020
George. Look, a power transformer.

466
00:29:58,150 --> 00:29:59,460
The lock on it is new.

467
00:30:01,680 --> 00:30:04,240
Why would this be designated as a wildlife sanctuary?

468
00:30:04,370 --> 00:30:05,500
I mean, think about it.

469
00:30:05,770 --> 00:30:07,970
There's no water. No water, no wetlands.

470
00:30:07,970 --> 00:30:10,120
No wetlands, no birds, no animals.

471
00:30:10,540 --> 00:30:12,380
No nothing as far as I can make out.

472
00:30:22,010 --> 00:30:23,190
Here they are, man.

473
00:30:24,460 --> 00:30:25,480
Let's get ready.

474
00:30:34,390 --> 00:30:36,680
Right on time. I like that.

475
00:30:50,100 --> 00:30:51,360
Who the hell is this?

476
00:30:51,410 --> 00:30:53,730
Just some friends of mine. Don't worry about it.It's cool

477
00:30:58,950 --> 00:31:00,360
How do you know Frankie?

478
00:31:01,740 --> 00:31:03,000
I'm a friend of Rick's.

479
00:31:03,900 --> 00:31:05,030
Who's Rick?

480
00:31:07,750 --> 00:31:09,000
I am.

481
00:31:10,030 --> 00:31:11,020
What happened to you?

482
00:31:11,020 --> 00:31:13,430
Are we going to play "20 questions" Or do some business?

484
00:31:13,600 --> 00:31:16,220
I just want to know who's in the room. You got a problem with that?

485
00:31:18,990 --> 00:31:21,410
No. Knock yourself out.

486
00:31:21,410 --> 00:31:23,780
Get a medical history and a urine sample for all I care.

487
00:31:23,780 --> 00:31:25,340
Let's just get on with it, come on.

488
00:31:28,540 --> 00:31:30,720
Fine, let's do this. You got cash, Frankie?

489
00:31:30,720 --> 00:31:32,930
I got what you need. Don't worry. Let's see the E first.

490
00:31:38,580 --> 00:31:42,160
Pure MDMA. No caffeine.

491
00:31:42,750 --> 00:31:45,400
- Want to check it? - No, man, I trust you.

492
00:31:48,370 --> 00:31:49,650
All right, homey.

493
00:31:50,840 --> 00:31:52,080
Where's the money?

494
00:31:53,810 --> 00:31:54,990
Did you hear that?

495
00:31:56,440 --> 00:31:59,590
This guy called me "Homey." I got your money.

496
00:32:01,030 --> 00:32:02,070
It's right here.

497
00:32:09,150 --> 00:32:10,160
Stand down!

498
00:32:15,540 --> 00:32:16,930
Come on, homey.

499
00:32:17,420 --> 00:32:18,990
Stand down, or you're eating one.

500
00:32:19,770 --> 00:32:21,580
Pull that trigger and you're going down, too.

501
00:32:24,880 --> 00:32:28,970
Let's just do him! Just do him!

502
00:32:33,270 --> 00:32:37,030
Everybody chill out, man.

503
00:32:37,030 --> 00:32:39,030
It's all cool. Put the guns down, all right?

504
00:32:39,040 --> 00:32:41,120
Put them down nice and easy.

505
00:32:41,430 --> 00:32:43,290
- Going down. - Let's go.

506
00:32:43,430 --> 00:32:45,080
See what else they got on them, man.

507
00:32:48,240 --> 00:32:50,430
All this because you couldn't keep my brother alive?

508
00:33:09,190 --> 00:33:11,290
They might not have registered with their real names.

509
00:33:12,450 --> 00:33:14,980
No. Just use the description that we sent you, okay?

510
00:33:15,410 --> 00:33:16,520
We'll do our best.

511
00:33:18,270 --> 00:33:20,550
- You checking the hospitals? - Yes.

512
00:33:21,710 --> 00:33:24,490
I don't understand how Teri and Kim just disappeared.

513
00:33:25,160 --> 00:33:26,470
It might be a good thing, you know?

514
00:33:26,470 --> 00:33:28,120
If Drazen's people had them,

515
00:33:28,120 --> 00:33:29,410
we would have heard about it by now.

516
00:33:30,490 --> 00:33:33,240
After all, Jack and Palmer are the primary targets.

517
00:33:33,240 --> 00:33:34,590
What about Jack's house?

518
00:33:34,930 --> 00:33:37,040
I sent Williams over, but I'll call and check.

519
00:33:37,220 --> 00:33:38,240
And Kim's phone call?

520
00:33:38,240 --> 00:33:39,350
We traced it to a phone booth.

521
00:33:39,350 --> 00:33:40,640
We're checking the whole area.

522
00:33:41,430 --> 00:33:44,170
Nina, we're doing everything we can, all right?

523
00:33:44,350 --> 00:33:45,520
Are you?

524
00:34:14,210 --> 00:34:17,320
What are you going to do now, man? You're going to kill us?

525
00:34:25,460 --> 00:34:26,590
Yes.

526
00:34:31,690 --> 00:34:32,830
I'll kill you

527
00:34:34,180 --> 00:34:35,680
if I ever see you again.

528
00:34:39,510 --> 00:34:40,870
You should get that stitched.

529
00:34:43,370 --> 00:34:44,780
How's that for a nose job?

530
00:34:44,880 --> 00:34:46,580
It's pretty good. Yes, I like that.

531
00:34:49,640 --> 00:34:50,650
Frankie?

532
00:34:51,360 --> 00:34:52,730
What's that, homey?

533
00:34:56,410 --> 00:34:57,490
Speak up.

534
00:34:59,720 --> 00:35:01,520
You have the right to remain silent.

535
00:35:10,580 --> 00:35:11,720
Put them down!

536
00:35:11,800 --> 00:35:12,970
Put them down!

537
00:35:13,290 --> 00:35:15,280
Right now! Drop the gun now!

538
00:35:19,690 --> 00:35:20,870
Arrest all of them.

539
00:35:20,870 --> 00:35:22,940
Please, don't do this. We didn't do anything.

540
00:35:23,920 --> 00:35:24,940
We're not a part of this.

541
00:35:24,940 --> 00:35:27,110
- Arms up. - Up against the wall.

542
00:35:29,480 --> 00:35:30,520
Let me have your handy.

543
00:35:35,020 --> 00:35:37,770
This is Krugman. We got a code four.

544
00:35:38,010 --> 00:35:40,430
One suspect down. Five being booked.

545
00:35:42,720 --> 00:35:44,490
I think I got a broken nose.

546
00:35:49,130 --> 00:35:50,300
Look, I'll say it again.

547
00:35:51,050 --> 00:35:54,040
I bear full responsibility for not knowing about it.

548
00:35:56,310 --> 00:36:00,150
A senator's duty, a president's duty

549
00:36:00,730 --> 00:36:04,250
an elected representative's duty is not only to his country

550
00:36:05,210 --> 00:36:06,720
but also to his family.

551
00:36:08,740 --> 00:36:09,960
If he cannot manage

552
00:36:09,960 --> 00:36:12,060
the interactions of the people close to him

553
00:36:13,740 --> 00:36:15,660
then he can't expect the electorate

554
00:36:15,660 --> 00:36:17,880
to believe in his ability to lead a nation.

555
00:36:19,750 --> 00:36:21,670
I don't deny I made a mistake.

556
00:36:22,810 --> 00:36:24,000
A serious one.

557
00:36:25,420 --> 00:36:27,190
I only ask you to consider

558
00:36:27,810 --> 00:36:31,430
that I am not the first person in public office to make one.

559
00:36:33,080 --> 00:36:34,120
Thank you.

560
00:36:37,850 --> 00:36:38,840
Senator Palmer?

561
00:36:39,580 --> 00:36:40,620
Senator?

562
00:36:57,720 --> 00:36:58,890
I love you, Dad.

563
00:37:01,070 --> 00:37:02,300
I love you, son.

564
00:37:26,380 --> 00:37:28,120
This is Emily. She's 11.

565
00:37:28,120 --> 00:37:31,340
And this is Jennifer. She just turned 9.

566
00:37:32,400 --> 00:37:34,390
- I didn't meet them? - No.

567
00:37:35,110 --> 00:37:37,150
We decided to leave everyone else out of it

568
00:37:37,590 --> 00:37:39,050
until you were sure what you wanted.

569
00:37:41,300 --> 00:37:42,250
I'll get it.

570
00:38:08,170 --> 00:38:09,590
She made this for me.

571
00:38:11,330 --> 00:38:12,940
You want milk or sugar in it?

572
00:38:14,150 --> 00:38:15,310
Yes.

573
00:38:17,670 --> 00:38:19,780
Phii, I think I'm remembering something.

574
00:38:19,790 --> 00:38:21,890
Really? I'll be right there.

575
00:38:26,670 --> 00:38:28,790
- Restroom? - Right down the hall.

576
00:38:35,290 --> 00:38:36,460
Oh, my God.

577
00:38:48,130 --> 00:38:49,150
Where's the girl?

578
00:38:52,370 --> 00:38:54,650
Your daughter, where is she?

579
00:38:56,460 --> 00:38:58,170
I don't know.

580
00:38:59,010 --> 00:39:00,040
Tell me where she is

581
00:39:00,040 --> 00:39:03,320
and I'll make this painless for both of you, I promise.

582
00:39:03,620 --> 00:39:05,580
I don't know.

583
00:39:07,420 --> 00:39:08,530
Fine.

584
00:39:11,870 --> 00:39:13,580
Oh, my God.

585
00:39:14,950 --> 00:39:18,380
Teri? Step away. Move away, Teri.

586
00:39:19,760 --> 00:39:21,740
- Oh, my God. - Teri, step away, please.

587
00:39:25,270 --> 00:39:28,960
The car. Oh, my God. The car.

588
00:39:29,350 --> 00:39:30,600
I lost Kimberly. No....

589
00:39:30,600 --> 00:39:33,600
Teri? Teri, it's okay. You're safe.

590
00:39:34,430 --> 00:39:36,710
I lost my baby.

591
00:39:36,970 --> 00:39:38,130
Teri?

592
00:39:39,290 --> 00:39:40,480
Oh, my God.

593
00:40:01,470 --> 00:40:03,030
GPS says this is it.

594
00:40:04,520 --> 00:40:05,840
Right.

595
00:40:14,320 --> 00:40:15,780
What is that, reconnaissance?

596
00:40:18,140 --> 00:40:19,650
Someone knows we're here.

