2
00:00:12,350 --> 00:00:13,840
Right now...

3
00:00:13,920 --> 00:00:17,680
terrorists are plotting to assassinate a presidential candidate.

4
00:00:18,120 --> 00:00:20,750
My wife and daughter are in danger

5
00:00:20,830 --> 00:00:24,630
and people that I work with may be involved in both.

6
00:00:25,400 --> 00:00:27,260
I'm Federal Agent Jack Bauer.

7
00:00:27,980 --> 00:00:30,660
And this is the longest day of my life.

10
00:00:40,310 --> 00:00:45,310
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

11
00:00:40,310 --> 00:00:45,310
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

12
00:00:40,310 --> 00:00:45,310
{\an5}{\pos(145,252)}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

13
00:00:40,810 --> 00:00:45,310
{\pos(67,248)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

14
00:00:40,810 --> 00:00:45,310
{\pos(67,248)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

15
00:00:40,810 --> 00:00:45,310
{\pos(58,238)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

16
00:00:40,810 --> 00:00:45,310
{\pos(84,248)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

19
00:00:46,530 --> 00:01:11,530
{\an9}m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

20
00:00:46,030 --> 00:01:11,530
{\an2}{\pos(26,248)}m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

26
00:01:03,550 --> 00:01:05,400
I can go over your head, Mr. Almeida.

27
00:01:05,820 --> 00:01:06,550
And I assure you,

28
00:01:06,550 --> 00:01:08,460
there will be consequences.

29
00:01:08,770 --> 00:01:11,490
I apologize, Senator, but we do have protocol.

30
00:01:11,560 --> 00:01:13,180
Our district director, Ryan Chappelle,

31
00:01:13,180 --> 00:01:14,800
is working on a clearance right now.

32
00:01:14,800 --> 00:01:16,100
But if I could tell him why you're here...

33
00:01:16,100 --> 00:01:17,450
All he needs to know

34
00:01:18,240 --> 00:01:21,710
is that I need to talk to Jack Bauer, and I need to do it now.

35
00:01:24,070 --> 00:01:25,790
- Can I get you anything while... - No.

36
00:01:47,560 --> 00:01:48,650
Chappelle.

37
00:01:48,810 --> 00:01:51,370
Yeah, I don't think I can stall the Senator much longer.

38
00:01:51,400 --> 00:01:53,050
He wants to know why he can't see Jack.

39
00:01:53,300 --> 00:01:54,750
What did you tell him?

40
00:01:56,820 --> 00:01:58,520
I told him you were working on it.

41
00:01:59,130 --> 00:02:01,320
And he still didn't say why he was here?

42
00:02:01,320 --> 00:02:03,370
No, he just wants to see Jack.

43
00:02:04,600 --> 00:02:07,530
Until I know more I don't want to put those two together.

44
00:02:07,790 --> 00:02:09,510
I'm checking it out now.

45
00:02:09,520 --> 00:02:10,500
All right.

46
00:02:15,170 --> 00:02:16,290
So?

47
00:02:17,080 --> 00:02:19,570
- You find out what Palmer's doing here? - Not yet.

48
00:02:19,570 --> 00:02:22,220
Any new intel on the backup shooters?

49
00:02:22,330 --> 00:02:24,750
Yeah. An Alexis Drazen.

50
00:02:24,750 --> 00:02:25,920
Looks like he's connected

51
00:02:25,920 --> 00:02:27,420
to two other shooters, but for some reasons,

52
00:02:27,430 --> 00:02:28,620
he stopped in DC for a couple of days

53
00:02:28,620 --> 00:02:31,340
before landing in LAX on Saturday.

54
00:02:31,340 --> 00:02:33,990
There's other inconsistencies. I'm still working on it.

55
00:02:34,360 --> 00:02:37,250
- Where's the report? - I routed it to Nina's computer.

56
00:02:37,580 --> 00:02:39,720
- Send me a copy, would you? - Yeah.

57
00:02:44,880 --> 00:02:47,880
I still don't understand why you're taking us to a safe house.

58
00:02:47,880 --> 00:02:50,620
Weren't we supposed to answer questions at Jack's office?

59
00:02:50,700 --> 00:02:52,750
We're going to do that at the safe house, now.

60
00:02:52,750 --> 00:02:54,710
Is my dad going to be there?

61
00:02:54,710 --> 00:02:57,200
Not right away. Maybe when he's done at CTU.

62
00:03:00,110 --> 00:03:01,690
Are we okay, Nina?

63
00:03:02,130 --> 00:03:03,390
Everything's fine.

64
00:03:03,390 --> 00:03:04,840
Right now, a small, controlled environment

65
00:03:04,840 --> 00:03:06,860
is the most secure place for both of you.

66
00:03:06,860 --> 00:03:07,950
Does Jack know you're taking us?

67
00:03:07,950 --> 00:03:10,060
Of course. Myers.

68
00:03:11,080 --> 00:03:13,680
We're moving Teri and Kim to the safe house now.

69
00:03:13,690 --> 00:03:14,990
We should be there soon.

70
00:03:14,990 --> 00:03:18,760
Mom, you never told me what the doctor said.

71
00:03:21,790 --> 00:03:24,350
It was a cyst that burst.

72
00:03:24,350 --> 00:03:26,120
She said it wasn't serious.

73
00:03:28,930 --> 00:03:31,330
- Then why did she... - Honey, there's nothing to worry about.

74
00:03:32,180 --> 00:03:34,660
She said it would go away all by itself.

75
00:03:39,640 --> 00:03:42,230
Gaines first made contact with me on my cell phone.

76
00:03:42,230 --> 00:03:43,090
And he directed me to a car

77
00:03:43,090 --> 00:03:44,990
in a parking lot of St. Mark's hospital.

78
00:03:44,990 --> 00:03:46,910
The transmitter was in the car?

79
00:03:46,910 --> 00:03:49,210
Yeah, that's when he asked me to put it in my ear.

80
00:03:50,840 --> 00:03:52,860
Can we take a break for a second?

81
00:03:53,320 --> 00:03:54,410
Please, could you find out for me

82
00:03:54,410 --> 00:03:56,510
how my wife and daughter are doing at the clinic?

83
00:03:56,510 --> 00:03:58,760
Teri and Kim have already left the clinic.

84
00:03:58,920 --> 00:03:59,700
What?

85
00:03:59,700 --> 00:04:01,170
They're fine. The doctor has cleared them.

86
00:04:01,170 --> 00:04:02,520
Nina's even moving them to a safe house.

87
00:04:02,530 --> 00:04:05,710
You knew they were moving my family and you didn't tell me?

88
00:04:06,560 --> 00:04:09,150
That's it. This is over.

89
00:04:09,150 --> 00:04:12,040
I don't say another word. I want to speak to Chappelle.

90
00:04:14,490 --> 00:04:16,320
Now, Alberta!

91
00:04:26,820 --> 00:04:28,250
You're exhausting.

92
00:04:29,590 --> 00:04:32,250
I was surprised you called last night.

93
00:04:32,630 --> 00:04:35,760
I didn't think I'd see you again after DC.

94
00:04:37,790 --> 00:04:40,230
Not really that easy, you know.

95
00:04:42,030 --> 00:04:44,680
Will you have another break later in the day?

96
00:04:52,240 --> 00:04:55,020
The Senator has to leave town this afternoon.

97
00:04:55,020 --> 00:04:58,010
He's going to Nevada.

98
00:04:58,620 --> 00:05:00,500
Only a few of us were told about it

99
00:05:00,510 --> 00:05:05,180
and I am one of the ones who has to go with him.

100
00:05:05,460 --> 00:05:08,330
- You have to hold his hand? - In so many words.

101
00:05:11,870 --> 00:05:13,210
Is it too much to hope

102
00:05:13,210 --> 00:05:16,160
that you might have some free time in Nevada?

103
00:05:16,780 --> 00:05:18,350
You would want to come?

104
00:05:19,160 --> 00:05:20,700
If you want me.

105
00:05:40,780 --> 00:05:42,550
You know, this is a pretty big shower.

106
00:05:42,550 --> 00:05:44,050
There's room enough for two.

107
00:05:44,080 --> 00:05:45,960
I'm on my way.

108
00:05:47,060 --> 00:05:48,270
Alan.

109
00:05:48,270 --> 00:05:50,570
Senator Palmer, what can I do for you?

110
00:05:50,570 --> 00:05:53,440
I'm trying to talk to a CTU agent named Jack Bauer.

111
00:05:53,440 --> 00:05:55,740
- Where are you? - CTU Los Angeles.

112
00:05:56,070 --> 00:05:59,370
They say I need clearance, but it's taking forever.

113
00:05:59,370 --> 00:06:01,880
Not a problem. Who's in charge over there?

114
00:06:01,880 --> 00:06:03,500
Ryan Chappelle.

115
00:06:03,500 --> 00:06:06,610
Yeah, okay. I'll take care of this right away.

116
00:06:06,610 --> 00:06:07,790
Thank you, Alan.

117
00:06:08,020 --> 00:06:09,060
I owe you.

118
00:06:12,460 --> 00:06:13,820
Senator Palmer.

119
00:06:14,550 --> 00:06:15,910
Ryan Chappelle.

120
00:06:16,580 --> 00:06:18,540
What seems to be the problem, Ryan?

121
00:06:18,550 --> 00:06:20,710
Why can't I get in to see agent Bauer?

122
00:06:20,710 --> 00:06:22,400
Please forgive the wait.

123
00:06:22,400 --> 00:06:24,650
When an agent is under internal investigation,

124
00:06:24,650 --> 00:06:26,070
procedure is to keep him

125
00:06:26,070 --> 00:06:28,510
isolated until he's been fully interrogated.

126
00:06:28,520 --> 00:06:31,270
It's really out of my hands.

127
00:06:31,460 --> 00:06:33,880
Even if I could help you with your investigation?

128
00:06:34,040 --> 00:06:35,540
Mr. Chappelle.

129
00:06:35,950 --> 00:06:38,680
Alan Optican from the Pentagon is on the line for you.

130
00:06:39,580 --> 00:06:40,710
Excuse me.

131
00:06:42,440 --> 00:06:43,540
Chappelle.

132
00:06:43,540 --> 00:06:45,620
Alan Optican, Department of Defense.

133
00:06:45,620 --> 00:06:46,370
Yes, sir.

134
00:06:46,380 --> 00:06:49,580
From now on, the Senator is to be given carte blanche.

135
00:06:49,580 --> 00:06:51,490
You make sure he gets whatever he needs.

136
00:06:51,490 --> 00:06:52,310
Yes, sir.

137
00:06:52,310 --> 00:06:53,640
- Understood? - Of course, sir.

138
00:06:53,640 --> 00:06:54,620
Thank you.

139
00:06:55,590 --> 00:06:57,880
Bring Jack Bauer down here right away.

140
00:07:05,460 --> 00:07:06,570
Thanks

141
00:07:06,950 --> 00:07:10,780
for helping me cut through the red tape.

142
00:07:12,530 --> 00:07:15,770
I want all your cameras and recording equipment shut down.

143
00:07:17,610 --> 00:07:19,770
This is going to be a private conversation.

144
00:07:20,650 --> 00:07:21,960
I understand.

145
00:07:22,540 --> 00:07:24,560
I'll make sure the room is secure.

146
00:07:24,820 --> 00:07:25,920
Thank you.

147
00:07:30,870 --> 00:07:32,520
Hey, Jack.

148
00:07:32,710 --> 00:07:36,100
Nina called, wanted me to tell you Teri and Kim are fine.

149
00:07:37,540 --> 00:07:40,080
- Who's guarding the house? - Paulson and Breeher.

150
00:07:40,310 --> 00:07:41,480
Okay, good.

151
00:07:41,830 --> 00:07:45,240
Also, Chappelle wants to see you in the conference room.

152
00:07:45,430 --> 00:07:46,460
Good.

153
00:07:49,910 --> 00:07:51,220
Thanks a lot, Tony.

154
00:07:59,110 --> 00:08:02,130
Milo, sorry I had to switch the cards on you last night.

155
00:08:02,130 --> 00:08:03,440
I had no choice.

156
00:08:03,500 --> 00:08:06,370
No problem. We understand what you were going through.

157
00:08:06,370 --> 00:08:07,610
Thanks for your help.

158
00:08:18,230 --> 00:08:19,520
Senator Palmer.

159
00:08:20,420 --> 00:08:21,610
Leave us.

160
00:08:24,760 --> 00:08:26,580
- I'll be outside. - Thank you.

161
00:08:26,860 --> 00:08:28,060
Close the door.

162
00:08:30,110 --> 00:08:31,240
Sit.

163
00:08:31,830 --> 00:08:33,080
Yes, sir.

164
00:08:36,900 --> 00:08:38,720
I want to know who's working with you.

165
00:08:39,510 --> 00:08:41,460
In which context, sir?

166
00:08:41,460 --> 00:08:43,410
Right here, right now.

167
00:08:43,480 --> 00:08:44,730
We're going to put an end to this.

168
00:08:44,730 --> 00:08:46,200
Sir, I don't know what the people here have been telling you

169
00:08:46,200 --> 00:08:47,870
I know why you want me dead, Mr. Bauer.

170
00:08:47,870 --> 00:08:48,680
Want you dead, senator?

171
00:08:48,680 --> 00:08:50,120
I don't know what you're talking about.

172
00:08:50,120 --> 00:08:51,260
Kosovo.

173
00:08:53,530 --> 00:08:54,660
Kosovo?

174
00:08:54,660 --> 00:08:57,920
I know you hold me responsible for the men you lost there.

175
00:08:57,920 --> 00:08:59,660
Two years ago today.

176
00:09:00,330 --> 00:09:02,610
You know about Operation Nightfall?

177
00:09:02,610 --> 00:09:04,650
I authorized the mission.

178
00:09:05,420 --> 00:09:08,240
I know you took out Victor Drazen and his inner circle.

179
00:09:08,900 --> 00:09:10,870
I know you lost six men in the process.

180
00:09:10,870 --> 00:09:13,630
- You think I want revenge for the death of my men? - Yes, I do.

181
00:09:13,640 --> 00:09:14,770
With all due respect, Senator,

182
00:09:14,770 --> 00:09:17,360
I almost died today trying to protect you.

183
00:09:17,370 --> 00:09:18,520
If I blame anyone for the death

184
00:09:18,520 --> 00:09:19,900
of my men in Kosovo, sir,

185
00:09:19,900 --> 00:09:21,040
I blame myself.

186
00:09:21,040 --> 00:09:23,240
- Then what were you doing at the power plant? - I was trying...

187
00:09:28,150 --> 00:09:31,030
The reason why I went for that Secret Service agent's gun

188
00:09:31,030 --> 00:09:33,980
was to try and get you out of the room without giving myself away.

189
00:09:36,410 --> 00:09:39,430
The people that want you dead, they had kidnapped my family.

190
00:09:39,430 --> 00:09:40,420
They threatened to kill them if

191
00:09:40,420 --> 00:09:42,990
I didn't assist them in the assassination attempt.

192
00:09:47,150 --> 00:09:48,390
They didn't tell you any of this

193
00:09:48,390 --> 00:09:50,100
when you came in, did they, sir?

194
00:09:51,560 --> 00:09:52,550
No.

195
00:10:03,940 --> 00:10:05,500
It's the truth.

196
00:10:05,700 --> 00:10:07,720
You can verify it with Chappelle.

197
00:10:28,940 --> 00:10:30,660
They're just arriving at the safe house.

198
00:10:30,660 --> 00:10:31,380
Copy that.

199
00:10:31,390 --> 00:10:32,330
Show visuals.

200
00:10:42,750 --> 00:10:44,100
This way, Mrs. Bauer.

201
00:10:45,720 --> 00:10:48,410
These are agents Ted Paulson and Jeff Breeher.

202
00:10:48,410 --> 00:10:51,410
They've worked with Jack for many years. They're two of our best.

203
00:10:51,410 --> 00:10:53,980
This is Jack's wife, Teri, and their daughter Kim.

204
00:10:53,990 --> 00:10:55,410
- Hi. - Hi, Kim.

205
00:10:56,550 --> 00:10:57,630
Where do you want us?

206
00:10:57,630 --> 00:10:58,890
One in and one out.

207
00:11:11,590 --> 00:11:14,500
It's not exactly home, but it's relatively comfortable.

208
00:11:23,290 --> 00:11:25,470
There are motion detectors every ten yards.

209
00:11:26,340 --> 00:11:27,890
How long do we have to stay here?

210
00:11:27,930 --> 00:11:30,300
We'll worry about that after we finish debriefing you.

211
00:11:31,680 --> 00:11:33,040
Nina, where's the bathroom?

212
00:11:33,040 --> 00:11:33,670
Oh, yeah.

213
00:11:33,670 --> 00:11:36,080
There's one in each bedroom, right through there.

214
00:11:36,230 --> 00:11:39,290
If you'd both like to clean up before we get started, please do.

216
00:12:26,420 --> 00:12:27,830
I was the head of the

217
00:12:27,830 --> 00:12:30,450
Special Defense Appropriations Committee in the Senate.

218
00:12:31,320 --> 00:12:34,840
Which is just a euphemism for "Covert operations."

219
00:12:34,950 --> 00:12:37,540
Three years ago, the CIA brought to my attention

220
00:12:37,540 --> 00:12:41,190
atrocities committed by Victor Drazen In Kosovo.

221
00:12:41,560 --> 00:12:45,370
Massacres, torture, ethnic cleansing.

222
00:12:45,370 --> 00:12:46,910
The man was a monster.

223
00:12:47,450 --> 00:12:48,960
And was gaining support.

224
00:12:49,560 --> 00:12:51,520
I tried to go through the usual channels

225
00:12:51,530 --> 00:12:54,120
but I couldn't get anyone to work quickly enough.

226
00:12:54,760 --> 00:12:57,610
So I contacted the one person I knew

227
00:12:57,610 --> 00:12:59,180
who could get the job done.

228
00:12:59,240 --> 00:13:01,490
Have him terminated, off the books.

229
00:13:02,260 --> 00:13:03,980
And that would be Robert Ellis?

230
00:13:04,280 --> 00:13:05,430
That's right.

231
00:13:07,540 --> 00:13:10,800
Ellis was funded through a discretionary fund of my committee.

232
00:13:10,800 --> 00:13:13,370
His job was to implement the covert missions

233
00:13:13,370 --> 00:13:15,490
and see to it that no names were leaked.

234
00:13:17,400 --> 00:13:19,720
Now we're both on somebody's list.

235
00:13:22,390 --> 00:13:24,820
So this is payback for what happened that day.

236
00:13:26,130 --> 00:13:27,910
That's the only thing that makes sense.

237
00:13:28,370 --> 00:13:31,450
But if someone could put your name and my name on a list together

238
00:13:32,180 --> 00:13:34,730
that means they should be able to find Robert Ellis, too.

239
00:13:36,170 --> 00:13:37,210
You're right.

241
00:13:44,420 --> 00:13:45,860
Four sixes.

242
00:13:49,790 --> 00:13:50,850
Let's see 'em.

243
00:13:55,670 --> 00:13:58,340
I knew it. I saw it in your eyes.

244
00:13:59,140 --> 00:14:00,050
If you could read what's in my eyes

245
00:14:00,050 --> 00:14:02,650
you'd crawl under a rock and cry.

246
00:14:08,690 --> 00:14:09,850
Go again.

247
00:14:17,560 --> 00:14:20,270
- Ellis. - Bobby, this is David Palmer.

248
00:14:20,730 --> 00:14:22,030
You've got to be kidding.

249
00:14:22,040 --> 00:14:24,690
I'm not. I'm here with Jack Bauer.

250
00:14:26,930 --> 00:14:27,940
Get lost.

251
00:14:31,270 --> 00:14:33,640
What are you doing in the same room with Bauer?

252
00:14:33,640 --> 00:14:34,460
I went through a lot of trouble

253
00:14:34,460 --> 00:14:36,540
to make sure you two never meet each other.

254
00:14:36,540 --> 00:14:38,910
Someone close to Victor Drazen seems to

255
00:14:38,910 --> 00:14:40,020
have connected us.

256
00:14:40,440 --> 00:14:41,430
Why?

257
00:14:41,810 --> 00:14:43,430
Someone wants me dead,

258
00:14:43,530 --> 00:14:46,880
and it appears they want Bauer, too. Today.

259
00:14:46,880 --> 00:14:49,000
The two-year anniversary of Nightfall.

260
00:14:49,350 --> 00:14:50,670
I'm the only one who even

261
00:14:50,670 --> 00:14:52,880
knows you both were involved in Nightfall.

262
00:14:52,880 --> 00:14:54,170
Apparently not.

263
00:14:54,200 --> 00:14:57,220
And if we're on the list, it's likely you are, too.

264
00:14:57,290 --> 00:15:00,120
- Let me talk to Bauer. - I'm right here, Bob.

265
00:15:00,120 --> 00:15:01,370
Jack.

266
00:15:01,400 --> 00:15:03,800
- You still at CTU? - Yeah.

267
00:15:03,800 --> 00:15:06,450
If we are gonna source this, we gonna need each other's help.

268
00:15:06,450 --> 00:15:08,450
Unfortunately, over the last 12 hours

269
00:15:08,450 --> 00:15:10,400
I've had to cut a few corners.

270
00:15:10,400 --> 00:15:13,270
I'm being investigated right now. My hands are tied.

271
00:15:13,280 --> 00:15:16,580
Get them untied. David can help you there.

272
00:15:16,580 --> 00:15:17,910
If this is about revenge,

273
00:15:17,910 --> 00:15:20,110
it has to be someone connected to your team...

274
00:15:20,110 --> 00:15:21,150
No, that's not possible.

275
00:15:21,150 --> 00:15:23,610
No one on my team knew of the Senator's involvement.

276
00:15:23,610 --> 00:15:25,810
Then it has to be Drazen's group.

277
00:15:25,970 --> 00:15:28,410
I'll retrieve the closed file on Nightfall.

278
00:15:28,860 --> 00:15:32,000
It'll contain the names of Drazen's associates.

279
00:15:32,000 --> 00:15:33,450
That'll take a few minutes.

280
00:15:33,450 --> 00:15:36,180
In the meantime, you need to pick up a trail on the money.

281
00:15:36,180 --> 00:15:38,340
Odds are it's funded through Belgium.

282
00:15:38,420 --> 00:15:40,210
Can you get to your K-3 accounts from there?

283
00:15:40,210 --> 00:15:41,820
Yes, if I get reinstated.

284
00:15:42,170 --> 00:15:43,520
All right, start there.

285
00:15:44,830 --> 00:15:48,100
We'll compare names when we talk again. Where can I reach you?

286
00:15:48,100 --> 00:15:50,320
CTU, Los Angeles office.

287
00:15:50,590 --> 00:15:51,890
All right.

288
00:16:39,800 --> 00:16:40,710
Teri?

289
00:16:42,280 --> 00:16:43,200
Yes?

290
00:16:43,570 --> 00:16:45,680
I put some clean clothes on the bed.

291
00:16:46,580 --> 00:16:47,630
Thank you.

292
00:17:00,160 --> 00:17:02,430
They called me back in and said you decided not to fly out.

293
00:17:02,440 --> 00:17:04,180
What happened? Aren't we going to Nevada?

294
00:17:04,180 --> 00:17:05,000
Apparently not,

295
00:17:05,000 --> 00:17:07,560
the Senator felt he needed to take care of something first.

296
00:17:07,560 --> 00:17:08,920
He thought we'd be safest here.

297
00:17:08,920 --> 00:17:10,110
Are you going to take a later flight?

298
00:17:10,110 --> 00:17:11,840
I don't know. I hope so.

299
00:17:11,850 --> 00:17:13,230
Call the Times, tell them

300
00:17:13,230 --> 00:17:15,020
I'll do that phoner, 45 minutes.

301
00:17:15,020 --> 00:17:15,870
Sure.

302
00:17:33,780 --> 00:17:35,040
Hello.

303
00:17:35,040 --> 00:17:37,240
- You miss me yet? - Of course.

304
00:17:37,240 --> 00:17:39,280
I hope you didn't book your flight to Nevada.

305
00:17:39,280 --> 00:17:41,600
I was just about to.

306
00:17:41,670 --> 00:17:42,580
Why?

307
00:17:43,270 --> 00:17:44,820
We might not be going.

308
00:17:45,820 --> 00:17:47,080
When will you know?

309
00:17:47,350 --> 00:17:48,660
About an hour.

310
00:17:50,650 --> 00:17:53,450
If you stay in town, will you remain at the hotel?

311
00:17:53,450 --> 00:17:54,050
I don't know,

312
00:17:54,050 --> 00:17:56,990
they might switch us at the last minute for security reasons.

313
00:17:56,990 --> 00:17:59,310
Either way, I'll let you know where I am.

314
00:18:00,300 --> 00:18:04,270
I can still smell your perfume on my skin.

315
00:18:04,480 --> 00:18:07,210
I'll call you as soon as I know.

316
00:18:09,300 --> 00:18:11,480
- Is that the girl? - Yes.

317
00:18:12,290 --> 00:18:14,750
Palmer might not be leaving after all.

318
00:18:15,300 --> 00:18:16,720
Better for us.

319
00:18:18,250 --> 00:18:21,180
Was there any problem getting rid of Gaines' people?

320
00:18:21,250 --> 00:18:22,220
No.

321
00:18:23,840 --> 00:18:27,820
You should never have used him. I told you it was a mistake.

322
00:18:27,830 --> 00:18:30,500
Fine. You fixed the mistake.

323
00:18:30,500 --> 00:18:31,920
Now let's move on.

324
00:18:40,240 --> 00:18:42,320
She looks like Martina.

325
00:18:46,080 --> 00:18:48,380
Our sister is dead, Andre.

326
00:18:49,140 --> 00:18:50,620
Leave it alone.

327
00:18:55,430 --> 00:18:57,260
Have you spoken to Jovan and Mishko?

328
00:18:57,290 --> 00:18:59,570
They have their targets in sight.

329
00:19:00,870 --> 00:19:02,530
And as for Palmer

330
00:19:02,980 --> 00:19:06,110
I give you my word, he will be dead by midnight.

331
00:19:14,940 --> 00:19:17,300
- Do you have any toothpaste? - Yeah, honey, it's right there.

332
00:19:28,430 --> 00:19:29,090
That's nothing.

333
00:19:29,100 --> 00:19:32,190
The doctor just wanted me to take it as a precaution.

334
00:19:39,560 --> 00:19:40,820
You scared me.

335
00:19:42,030 --> 00:19:42,990
Kim?

336
00:19:43,840 --> 00:19:44,810
What?

337
00:19:49,390 --> 00:19:50,830
You're pregnant.

338
00:19:57,010 --> 00:19:58,380
I don't understand.

339
00:19:58,380 --> 00:20:00,270
What happened to you today? How is that possible?

340
00:20:00,270 --> 00:20:01,830
No, it was dad, of course,

341
00:20:01,830 --> 00:20:04,420
but, with tests like this, it takes time...

342
00:20:04,420 --> 00:20:05,670
You and dad were trying to have a kid

343
00:20:05,670 --> 00:20:07,130
and you didn't tell me about it?

344
00:20:07,140 --> 00:20:09,290
No, honey, it wasn't like that.

345
00:20:09,710 --> 00:20:10,480
Kim.

346
00:20:11,250 --> 00:20:12,160
Kim.

347
00:20:12,440 --> 00:20:13,700
- What? - Please.

348
00:20:14,270 --> 00:20:17,420
This is just as much a shock to me as it is to you.

349
00:20:17,850 --> 00:20:19,590
Dad and I used birth control.

350
00:20:19,590 --> 00:20:22,220
It's protection, but It's never 100 percent.

351
00:20:22,220 --> 00:20:23,170
No, whatever. It's your life.

352
00:20:23,170 --> 00:20:24,760
You don't need my permission to do anything.

353
00:20:24,770 --> 00:20:27,950
I'm not asking for your permission, Kimberly.

354
00:20:29,240 --> 00:20:30,040
Once in a while,

355
00:20:30,050 --> 00:20:33,600
you have to think about what another person is going through.

356
00:20:34,510 --> 00:20:37,260
Honey, I just found out I'm pregnant.

357
00:20:39,770 --> 00:20:41,960
You don't think that terrifies me?

358
00:20:44,740 --> 00:20:46,230
It does.

359
00:20:51,490 --> 00:20:54,060
Mom, I'm sorry.

360
00:21:05,500 --> 00:21:06,420
Are there any other names

361
00:21:06,420 --> 00:21:08,910
on the HK Iist that you recognize, David?

362
00:21:09,060 --> 00:21:11,590
Rich Dolan, Michael Redman. That's it.

363
00:21:11,810 --> 00:21:14,190
- They weren't cleared till after the op. - Come on in.

364
00:21:14,230 --> 00:21:15,980
I'll use what we have so far.

365
00:21:15,980 --> 00:21:18,790
I shouldn't be here. Green's got me on priority.

366
00:21:18,790 --> 00:21:20,050
I cleared it with Green.

367
00:21:20,050 --> 00:21:22,840
- Okay, Bob, he's here. - Milo.

368
00:21:22,840 --> 00:21:24,890
Yeah. Who are you?

369
00:21:25,030 --> 00:21:26,320
Don't worry about me.

370
00:21:26,660 --> 00:21:29,340
I see you opened some sockets up to MI5.

371
00:21:30,090 --> 00:21:32,480
- Yeah, how did you know that? - Doesn't matter.

372
00:21:32,480 --> 00:21:34,350
Right now, we're trying to hook up some names.

373
00:21:34,350 --> 00:21:35,440
I'm going to help you.

374
00:21:35,840 --> 00:21:37,860
What's your login ID and password?

375
00:21:39,000 --> 00:21:40,210
Give it to him.

376
00:21:42,820 --> 00:21:45,400
The login ID is "L-F-N."

377
00:21:45,810 --> 00:21:50,750
Password's "foothill 94022" lower case.

378
00:21:52,130 --> 00:21:53,540
Okay, hang on.

379
00:21:55,470 --> 00:21:58,430
Okay. Looks like we've got some partial results.

380
00:21:58,430 --> 00:21:59,450
Partial?

381
00:21:59,450 --> 00:22:02,400
Yeah. Looks like there's something missing here.

382
00:22:02,740 --> 00:22:03,920
What do you mean, Bob?

383
00:22:07,660 --> 00:22:09,490
Something's been removed.

384
00:22:09,920 --> 00:22:11,600
I'll look into it.

385
00:22:12,240 --> 00:22:14,360
Meanwhile, Milo, I'm going to...

386
00:22:15,680 --> 00:22:18,030
I'm going to send a file to your server.

387
00:22:19,230 --> 00:22:22,530
Why don't you print out hard copies for Jack and David?

388
00:22:23,160 --> 00:22:25,660
- Yeah, sure. - Thanks, Milo.

389
00:22:40,280 --> 00:22:41,750
All right, here we go.

390
00:22:44,850 --> 00:22:46,670
Feels like I haven't eaten in years.

391
00:22:52,510 --> 00:22:53,690
Feels good, doesn't it?

392
00:22:54,140 --> 00:22:55,600
Not being afraid anymore.

393
00:22:56,410 --> 00:22:57,370
Yeah.

394
00:23:01,020 --> 00:23:03,430
I'm sorry, Mom. I was being really stupid before.

395
00:23:06,720 --> 00:23:08,440
When are you going to tell Dad?

396
00:23:13,480 --> 00:23:14,380
You know what?

397
00:23:17,250 --> 00:23:18,470
Right now.

398
00:23:18,810 --> 00:23:19,670
Come on.

399
00:23:34,830 --> 00:23:36,130
CTU, Almeida.

400
00:23:36,160 --> 00:23:37,990
Hi, Tony, it's Teri Bauer calling.

401
00:23:37,990 --> 00:23:39,300
Could I talk to Jack, please?

402
00:23:39,410 --> 00:23:41,900
Hi, Teri. Actually, it's a bad time.

403
00:23:41,910 --> 00:23:43,230
He's kind of busy right now.

404
00:23:44,820 --> 00:23:47,300
Could you tell him to call me back? It's important.

405
00:23:47,300 --> 00:23:48,400
Sure.

406
00:23:50,990 --> 00:23:52,760
I really wanted to hear his reaction.

407
00:23:54,160 --> 00:23:57,010
I'm so lucky to have you. Baby.

408
00:24:05,320 --> 00:24:08,530
Hi. Sorry, but we really need to start the debrief.

409
00:24:08,530 --> 00:24:10,360
CTU's eager to find out what you know.

410
00:24:10,360 --> 00:24:11,980
- We're ready. - Yeah.

411
00:24:11,980 --> 00:24:14,450
Great. I'd like to start with just you, Teri.

412
00:24:14,600 --> 00:24:15,490
Fine.

413
00:24:19,860 --> 00:24:21,360
I think I'm going to go to my room.

414
00:24:21,370 --> 00:24:23,440
That's a good idea, honey. You should try and get some rest.

415
00:24:27,560 --> 00:24:31,330
This is standard procedure. We're going to put you on videotape.

416
00:24:31,350 --> 00:24:32,170
Okay.

417
00:25:02,840 --> 00:25:04,690
- Yeah. - Hi, Rick?

418
00:25:05,420 --> 00:25:07,390
Hey, Kim.

419
00:25:07,520 --> 00:25:08,810
Are you okay?

420
00:25:09,000 --> 00:25:11,330
Yeah. I just lost a little blood.

421
00:25:11,530 --> 00:25:14,140
You need to see a doctor. You don't sound good.

422
00:25:14,620 --> 00:25:16,850
I need a few days' rest, that's all.

423
00:25:16,850 --> 00:25:19,440
You should turn yourself in. I mean, you can get medical attention.

424
00:25:19,440 --> 00:25:21,220
I can also get arrested.

425
00:25:21,910 --> 00:25:24,390
You helped us escape. I mean, I'll tell them that.

426
00:25:24,390 --> 00:25:25,410
No!

427
00:25:27,460 --> 00:25:29,610
Don't tell them anything about me.

428
00:25:31,170 --> 00:25:32,090
It's too late.

429
00:25:32,090 --> 00:25:33,330
My mom's already being questioned.

430
00:25:33,330 --> 00:25:34,750
They're going to ask about you.

431
00:25:35,150 --> 00:25:37,050
I'm next. I can't lie.

432
00:25:37,780 --> 00:25:38,780
Okay.

433
00:25:39,310 --> 00:25:40,400
Don't.

434
00:25:42,450 --> 00:25:44,050
Just tell them that I

435
00:25:44,060 --> 00:25:45,760
didn't know anything about what was going on,

436
00:25:45,760 --> 00:25:47,960
and that Dan threatened me. He had a gun.

437
00:25:50,710 --> 00:25:52,900
Okay, but promise me you'll turn yourself in.

438
00:25:54,870 --> 00:25:57,950
I got to think this through. I'm not like you, Kim.

439
00:25:57,990 --> 00:25:59,620
I don't come from a good family.

440
00:25:59,650 --> 00:26:01,460
System's not going to give me a break.

441
00:26:01,670 --> 00:26:03,760
It's your only way out of this, Rick.

442
00:26:04,870 --> 00:26:06,490
I brought you to Gaines.

443
00:26:06,980 --> 00:26:08,300
That's kidnapping.

444
00:26:08,770 --> 00:26:10,850
They could put me in jail for the rest of my life.

445
00:26:23,960 --> 00:26:25,310
What's incredible to me is that none of this

446
00:26:25,310 --> 00:26:28,580
has nothing to do with me running for president.

447
00:26:30,220 --> 00:26:34,030
It has nothing to do with the primary.

448
00:26:36,670 --> 00:26:39,750
It has nothing to do with my being black.

449
00:26:43,770 --> 00:26:47,640
It's just revenge for taking out Victor Drazen.

450
00:26:49,270 --> 00:26:50,270
Yes.

451
00:26:56,230 --> 00:26:58,630
- Hello? - David, It's Sherry.

452
00:26:58,630 --> 00:27:00,560
Are you back at the hotel?

453
00:27:00,560 --> 00:27:03,180
Yes. Where are you? - I'm at CTU,

454
00:27:03,180 --> 00:27:04,410
a government agency.

455
00:27:04,590 --> 00:27:05,550
Why?

456
00:27:07,180 --> 00:27:09,230
There are some things I have to take care of.

457
00:27:09,380 --> 00:27:11,780
David, what's going on?

458
00:27:12,910 --> 00:27:16,870
I'm trying to find out who's attempting to kill me, Sherry.

459
00:27:16,920 --> 00:27:20,220
I've got to go. Just wait for me at the hotel, okay?

460
00:27:20,220 --> 00:27:21,620
- Okay. - Bye.

461
00:27:28,570 --> 00:27:30,360
It just doesn't stop.

462
00:27:33,320 --> 00:27:35,240
I'm sorry this is happening to you, sir.

463
00:27:39,570 --> 00:27:41,260
You've been detained.

464
00:27:42,020 --> 00:27:43,950
Your family's been kidnapped

465
00:27:44,470 --> 00:27:46,360
and you're concerned about me?

466
00:27:50,560 --> 00:27:52,670
That didn't have anything to do with the election.

467
00:27:54,160 --> 00:27:55,590
That was about my son.

468
00:27:56,560 --> 00:27:57,570
Is he okay?

469
00:27:59,080 --> 00:28:00,740
I just realized today...

470
00:28:02,090 --> 00:28:04,420
...that I haven't always been there for him.

471
00:28:07,230 --> 00:28:08,670
And what's killing me

472
00:28:11,090 --> 00:28:13,280
is that he's always been there for me.

473
00:28:18,610 --> 00:28:20,810
Being the son of a politician isn't easy.

474
00:28:23,510 --> 00:28:26,200
Being a son, or a daughter,

475
00:28:27,760 --> 00:28:29,020
or a father,

476
00:28:30,180 --> 00:28:31,710
none of it is easy.

477
00:28:37,630 --> 00:28:39,030
Your wife and daughter okay?

478
00:28:41,930 --> 00:28:43,290
I don't know.

479
00:28:45,970 --> 00:28:47,330
I hope so.

480
00:28:58,160 --> 00:29:02,570
Okay. Try to be relaxed. I just have a few questions.

481
00:29:04,020 --> 00:29:07,610
This just came in from Ellis. I organized it into three sections.

482
00:29:07,610 --> 00:29:09,280
Cross-references are in the first part.

483
00:29:09,280 --> 00:29:12,010
After that is a summary of Operation Nightfall.

484
00:29:12,290 --> 00:29:14,900
Details that may or may not be important, I put in the last part.

485
00:29:14,910 --> 00:29:17,620
- Any word on the missing file? - No, not yet.

486
00:29:17,630 --> 00:29:18,840
Okay, thanks, Milo.

487
00:29:24,710 --> 00:29:27,200
What is the ambassador to Libya doing on this list?

488
00:29:27,210 --> 00:29:30,180
Probably helped keep Drazen's money separate from the government.

489
00:29:30,510 --> 00:29:32,910
We've had our eye on him for quite some time.

490
00:29:34,310 --> 00:29:36,130
Do you know Raniel Bonnier?

491
00:29:36,770 --> 00:29:39,510
- No. Who's he? - He's out of North Africa.

492
00:29:39,510 --> 00:29:41,010
Some higher-ups at District thought

493
00:29:41,010 --> 00:29:43,630
he was trying to set up terrorist cells in the U.S.

494
00:29:54,510 --> 00:29:56,830
Jack. Page 4.

495
00:29:57,100 --> 00:29:58,610
Second paragraph down.

496
00:30:06,920 --> 00:30:08,910
Drazen's wife and daughter were in the bunker?

497
00:30:09,390 --> 00:30:10,550
Did you know about this?

498
00:30:11,480 --> 00:30:13,340
This wasn't in our initial report.

499
00:30:13,490 --> 00:30:15,210
They died in the explosion.

500
00:30:16,250 --> 00:30:17,480
My God.

501
00:30:19,350 --> 00:30:20,980
This is an eye for an eye.

502
00:30:21,690 --> 00:30:23,710
We took out Drazen and his family,

503
00:30:23,860 --> 00:30:25,560
and now someone wants mine.

504
00:30:26,220 --> 00:30:28,070
Who's in charge of protecting your family?

505
00:30:30,050 --> 00:30:31,150
Jack!

506
00:30:31,470 --> 00:30:34,420
Who has the authority to add security to your family?

507
00:30:34,420 --> 00:30:35,690
Chappelle.

508
00:30:37,000 --> 00:30:38,240
Yes, Senator?

509
00:30:38,240 --> 00:30:40,160
Could you send in Mr. Chappelle right away?

510
00:30:40,160 --> 00:30:41,240
Yes, sir.

511
00:30:42,660 --> 00:30:44,610
So there was nothing else you saw or heard...

512
00:30:44,610 --> 00:30:46,890
...that gave you a glimpse Into their operation?

513
00:30:47,010 --> 00:30:48,630
No. That's it.

514
00:30:48,890 --> 00:30:51,200
They really didn't talk much in front of us.

515
00:30:51,670 --> 00:30:54,000
Tell me about this boy Rick. You said he helped you?

516
00:30:54,000 --> 00:30:55,270
- Yeah. - How?

517
00:30:55,850 --> 00:30:57,530
Different ways. But mainly,

518
00:30:57,530 --> 00:31:00,320
he gave us a gun and he helped us escape.

519
00:31:01,100 --> 00:31:02,540
How'd he get a gun?

520
00:31:03,070 --> 00:31:04,290
I don't know.

521
00:31:04,630 --> 00:31:06,990
- You don't know his last name? - No.

522
00:31:06,990 --> 00:31:09,550
I don't think Kimberly does, either, but you can ask her.

523
00:31:09,620 --> 00:31:10,990
How did she meet him?

524
00:31:11,360 --> 00:31:13,730
Through her friend Janet York.

525
00:31:16,890 --> 00:31:19,880
Everyone used to tell me, "Wait until she's a teenager.

526
00:31:19,880 --> 00:31:22,590
"You'll finally understand the meaning of the word 'worry."'

527
00:31:24,110 --> 00:31:25,650
I'm sure she'll grow out of it.

528
00:31:25,710 --> 00:31:28,230
Jack says she's basically a level-headed kid.

529
00:31:28,980 --> 00:31:30,560
Jack talks about Kim?

530
00:31:31,350 --> 00:31:33,090
Just the usual stuff.

531
00:31:34,150 --> 00:31:35,610
That surprises me.

532
00:31:36,570 --> 00:31:39,230
Jack's work always seems so serious and secretive.

533
00:31:39,240 --> 00:31:40,060
It's hard to picture him

534
00:31:40,060 --> 00:31:42,520
sitting around the office talking about his family.

535
00:31:43,860 --> 00:31:45,200
Sometimes...

536
00:31:45,680 --> 00:31:49,250
...at lunch, he'll bring up something if something's on his mind.

537
00:31:53,610 --> 00:31:56,140
So do you think Rick had the confidence of Ira Gaines,

538
00:31:56,140 --> 00:31:57,470
the leader of the group?

539
00:31:58,360 --> 00:32:00,140
I really couldn't tell you that.

540
00:32:01,780 --> 00:32:03,360
Nina, could I ask you a question?

541
00:32:03,930 --> 00:32:04,800
Sure.

542
00:32:05,740 --> 00:32:07,790
When Jack and I were separated...

543
00:32:11,760 --> 00:32:13,900
...did he ever talk about me?

544
00:32:17,230 --> 00:32:19,910
Jack never discussed his marriage.

545
00:32:21,500 --> 00:32:24,680
Sometimes he would talk about Kim.

546
00:32:24,690 --> 00:32:25,690
You know.

547
00:32:32,180 --> 00:32:36,090
We all knew he was going through a very hard time,

548
00:32:36,140 --> 00:32:38,630
and that he missed you both very much.

549
00:32:44,710 --> 00:32:47,040
When Jack and I got back together again,

550
00:32:48,650 --> 00:32:51,240
he told me that he'd been with someone else.

551
00:32:55,500 --> 00:32:59,280
I told him it didn't matter what I did, what he did,

552
00:32:59,960 --> 00:33:01,930
when we were apart, that was in the past

553
00:33:01,930 --> 00:33:03,040
that the only thing that

554
00:33:03,050 --> 00:33:05,670
mattered was what we did from that point on.

555
00:33:13,550 --> 00:33:15,720
It was you, wasn't it?

556
00:33:18,580 --> 00:33:19,610
Teri.

557
00:33:23,790 --> 00:33:27,380
I saw it when we got off the helicopter.

558
00:33:28,580 --> 00:33:30,330
I saw it when you looked at him.

559
00:33:44,780 --> 00:33:46,810
After you were separated...

560
00:33:47,800 --> 00:33:50,000
Yes, we saw each other.

561
00:33:50,710 --> 00:33:52,210
But it didn't last long.

562
00:33:52,220 --> 00:33:55,060
He realized it was a mistake and he went back to you.

563
00:33:56,190 --> 00:33:57,390
What about you?

564
00:33:58,220 --> 00:33:59,440
What about me?

565
00:34:00,340 --> 00:34:02,270
Did you think it was a mistake?

566
00:34:06,960 --> 00:34:09,230
- Are you still sleeping with him? - No.

567
00:34:10,230 --> 00:34:11,340
Teri.

568
00:34:11,910 --> 00:34:15,100
It was over before he went back to you.

569
00:34:15,110 --> 00:34:16,230
That is the truth.

570
00:34:21,250 --> 00:34:24,720
Look, I realize this is a terrible time for you to discover all this.

571
00:34:25,650 --> 00:34:27,880
When do you think a good time would be, Nina?

572
00:34:30,830 --> 00:34:32,230
I'm sorry.

573
00:34:33,910 --> 00:34:36,180
We have to get through the rest of this.

574
00:34:36,180 --> 00:34:38,580
I need to take a break.

575
00:34:55,880 --> 00:34:57,180
Yeah, Mike, I know.

576
00:34:57,800 --> 00:34:59,990
We'll be leaving in about five minutes.

577
00:35:02,270 --> 00:35:04,700
I can't wait for Ellis to get back to us, so I've got to go.

578
00:35:04,700 --> 00:35:07,090
Senator, they won't let me continue to work here.

579
00:35:07,090 --> 00:35:09,560
I'm technically still under arrest.

580
00:35:10,590 --> 00:35:11,710
Come on.

581
00:35:13,860 --> 00:35:14,920
Ryan.

582
00:35:17,160 --> 00:35:18,530
Yes, Senator?

583
00:35:18,680 --> 00:35:20,660
I understand you have Jack under arrest.

584
00:35:20,720 --> 00:35:23,510
I told the Senator I was being detained for questioning.

585
00:35:23,510 --> 00:35:25,050
There's an ongoing crisis...

586
00:35:25,050 --> 00:35:27,900
...that supersedes any charges that might be filed against him.

587
00:35:29,720 --> 00:35:30,550
But, Senator...

588
00:35:30,550 --> 00:35:33,560
I want him reinstated to his previous position, effective now.

589
00:35:33,570 --> 00:35:35,430
I'm sorry, sir, but you don't have the authority

590
00:35:35,430 --> 00:35:36,500
to make that decision.

591
00:35:36,500 --> 00:35:38,550
Alberta, please.

592
00:35:39,030 --> 00:35:40,080
Sir...

593
00:35:40,570 --> 00:35:43,050
...what you are asking isn't possible.

594
00:35:43,050 --> 00:35:45,650
The charges against Agent Bauer are serious.

595
00:35:45,660 --> 00:35:48,560
We would be held in contempt of agency regulations

596
00:35:48,560 --> 00:35:50,520
if we reinstated him without a hearing.

597
00:35:50,520 --> 00:35:54,220
Ryan, you don't have to reinstate me. Not permanently.

598
00:35:54,430 --> 00:35:58,070
Look, nobody here has as much information about this situation as I do.

599
00:35:58,070 --> 00:36:00,860
Give me provisional status just till the end of the day.

600
00:36:00,890 --> 00:36:03,480
Then you can take me back into custody, do whatever you want.

601
00:36:12,570 --> 00:36:14,250
Fine, Jack.

602
00:36:14,910 --> 00:36:17,140
You work the case out of CTU,

603
00:36:17,140 --> 00:36:18,990
but you answer to me.

604
00:36:21,630 --> 00:36:23,490
Good luck with your campaign, Senator.

605
00:36:24,490 --> 00:36:25,690
Thank you.

606
00:36:28,610 --> 00:36:30,000
Walk with me.

607
00:36:34,640 --> 00:36:37,330
Secret Service wants me to leave the state.

608
00:36:37,760 --> 00:36:40,290
- They say it's not safe. - I agree with them.

609
00:36:42,540 --> 00:36:46,160
The one thing we know is that Drazen's people are here,

610
00:36:46,160 --> 00:36:49,990
and they want us today. And it's almost 3:00 now.

611
00:36:49,990 --> 00:36:51,640
The day is more than half over.

612
00:36:52,300 --> 00:36:53,780
I'm going to stay.

613
00:36:54,470 --> 00:36:57,050
Let's flush them out into the open and deal with them.

614
00:36:57,800 --> 00:37:00,290
Otherwise, you and I and our families...

615
00:37:00,290 --> 00:37:02,990
...will be looking over our shoulders for the rest of our lives.

616
00:37:03,800 --> 00:37:05,160
I understand.

617
00:37:05,690 --> 00:37:06,950
I'll follow up with Ellis.

618
00:37:06,950 --> 00:37:07,910
I'll keep you posted.

619
00:37:07,920 --> 00:37:09,740
You know how to get in touch with me.

620
00:37:09,900 --> 00:37:10,860
Jack.

621
00:37:13,270 --> 00:37:14,950
I'm sorry that I misjudged you.

622
00:37:20,640 --> 00:37:22,010
Thank you, Senator.

623
00:37:25,430 --> 00:37:26,510
Excuse me.

624
00:37:32,030 --> 00:37:34,340
Before my mom came, nobody talked to me.

625
00:37:34,340 --> 00:37:36,400
They put me in the room, I was locked in there.

626
00:37:36,800 --> 00:37:37,920
What about Rick?

627
00:37:38,770 --> 00:37:40,270
Rick? What about Rick?

628
00:37:40,730 --> 00:37:42,450
He was one of your kidnappers, right?

629
00:37:43,350 --> 00:37:44,710
Not exactly.

630
00:37:44,720 --> 00:37:47,580
What do you mean? I thought he and Dan brought you to Gaines.

631
00:37:47,590 --> 00:37:50,440
It was mostly Dan. Not Rick.

632
00:37:50,440 --> 00:37:51,830
I think he was actually just

633
00:37:51,840 --> 00:37:54,140
as surprised as we were about what was happening.

634
00:37:54,480 --> 00:37:55,610
Really?

635
00:37:56,000 --> 00:37:57,170
Yeah.

636
00:37:57,310 --> 00:37:59,680
He was fighting with Dan the entire time.

637
00:37:59,770 --> 00:38:01,710
He actually helped us escape.

638
00:38:02,080 --> 00:38:04,100
Okay, hold on, let's not get ahead of ourselves.

639
00:38:04,100 --> 00:38:05,180
Can we...

640
00:38:06,500 --> 00:38:08,010
Hold on.

641
00:38:17,340 --> 00:38:19,450
- Myers. - Hey, it's me.

642
00:38:19,450 --> 00:38:20,640
Chappelle just reinstated me to

643
00:38:20,640 --> 00:38:22,710
provisional status for the rest of the day...

644
00:38:22,720 --> 00:38:24,170
...at Palmer's request.

645
00:38:24,170 --> 00:38:25,370
That's great, Jack.

646
00:38:25,370 --> 00:38:27,380
Yeah. How's everything going over there?

647
00:38:28,020 --> 00:38:29,110
Not bad.

648
00:38:29,620 --> 00:38:32,290
- We're sending over two more teams. - Why?

649
00:38:32,290 --> 00:38:34,680
Looks like Teri and Kim were targets as well.

650
00:38:34,680 --> 00:38:35,910
Nina,

651
00:38:36,430 --> 00:38:38,880
it is not information they need to know, okay?

652
00:38:39,020 --> 00:38:40,190
No, of course.

653
00:38:40,190 --> 00:38:41,280
Good. Thanks.

654
00:38:41,550 --> 00:38:44,330
- Let me speak to Teri, okay? - Sure.

655
00:38:51,160 --> 00:38:52,260
Teri?

656
00:38:55,470 --> 00:38:56,940
It's Jack.

657
00:39:01,020 --> 00:39:03,240
- Hi, Jack. - Hey, sweetheart.

658
00:39:03,360 --> 00:39:04,920
You okay? How you doing?

659
00:39:05,970 --> 00:39:07,010
I'm okay.

660
00:39:07,510 --> 00:39:08,850
How's Kim?

661
00:39:08,850 --> 00:39:10,050
She's fine.

662
00:39:10,070 --> 00:39:12,970
Tony gave me a message that you wanted to tell me something important.

663
00:39:15,310 --> 00:39:17,640
No, it's nothing important.

664
00:39:18,760 --> 00:39:20,510
Are you sure? You sound funny.

665
00:39:22,440 --> 00:39:24,100
It's nothing. I just...

666
00:39:24,510 --> 00:39:25,730
I just...

667
00:39:26,680 --> 00:39:28,360
I'm so tired.

668
00:39:29,160 --> 00:39:31,750
Why don't you just try and get some rest, then, sweetheart.

669
00:39:31,900 --> 00:39:32,890
Listen, if...

670
00:39:34,320 --> 00:39:36,160
If you need anything from the house,

671
00:39:36,160 --> 00:39:38,160
Nina will make sure that someone will go get it for you. Okay?

672
00:39:38,160 --> 00:39:39,440
Yeah, okay.

673
00:39:41,320 --> 00:39:43,500
I got to go. I love you, okay?

674
00:39:43,500 --> 00:39:45,180
I'll call you as soon as I can.

675
00:39:45,990 --> 00:39:47,630
Okay. Bye-bye.

676
00:40:03,870 --> 00:40:06,180
Mom. I'll be right back.

677
00:40:13,610 --> 00:40:14,910
So what did he say?

678
00:40:15,810 --> 00:40:17,320
I didn't tell him.

679
00:40:17,620 --> 00:40:18,800
Why not?

680
00:40:19,100 --> 00:40:20,930
It wasn't the right time.

681
00:40:21,130 --> 00:40:23,120
Just go back and finish with Nina, honey.

682
00:40:24,000 --> 00:40:25,170
What's wrong?

683
00:40:26,530 --> 00:40:27,600
Nothing.

684
00:40:27,600 --> 00:40:29,910
I just think you should finish answering Nina's questions.

685
00:40:37,820 --> 00:40:38,820
Bauer.

686
00:40:39,360 --> 00:40:41,420
- Jack, it's Bob. - Hey, Bob.

687
00:40:42,370 --> 00:40:44,490
I shot over a few more things to Milo

688
00:40:44,960 --> 00:40:47,230
but I still can't locate the missing file.

689
00:40:47,340 --> 00:40:48,610
How can I help?

690
00:40:48,710 --> 00:40:49,970
I gave Milo enough for him

691
00:40:49,970 --> 00:40:51,490
to try it on your end.

692
00:40:51,890 --> 00:40:54,520
The more I look at this, the more I'm convinced

693
00:40:54,520 --> 00:40:56,510
the file was taken out deliberately.

694
00:40:58,780 --> 00:41:00,940
Which leads me to believe

695
00:41:01,700 --> 00:41:03,840
it contains what we're looking for.

696
00:41:03,850 --> 00:41:05,150
Can you give me an estimate

697
00:41:05,150 --> 00:41:07,220
of when you think the file was stolen?

698
00:41:07,220 --> 00:41:08,370
Also, a list of people who

699
00:41:08,370 --> 00:41:10,770
you think could have had access to get in there?

700
00:41:10,770 --> 00:41:13,760
Not yet, but you tell Milo that I got some ideas on how...

701
00:41:16,690 --> 00:41:17,710
Bob?

702
00:41:19,610 --> 00:41:20,910
Bob?

703
00:41:25,130 --> 00:41:26,550
Bob!

704
00:41:27,490 --> 00:41:28,810
Can you hear me?

705
00:41:30,460 --> 00:41:31,750
Bob!

