2
00:00:12,260 --> 00:00:13,620
Right now

3
00:00:13,730 --> 00:00:17,820
terrorists are plotting to assassinate a presidential candidate.

4
00:00:17,960 --> 00:00:20,590
My wife and daughter have been targeted

5
00:00:20,700 --> 00:00:24,230
and people that I work with may be involved in both.

6
00:00:24,840 --> 00:00:27,100
I'm Federal Agent Jack Bauer

7
00:00:27,310 --> 00:00:30,800
and today is the longest day of my life.

10
00:00:40,010 --> 00:00:45,010
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

11
00:00:40,010 --> 00:00:45,010
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

12
00:00:40,010 --> 00:00:45,010
{\an5}{\pos(145,252)}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

13
00:00:40,510 --> 00:00:45,010
{\pos(67,248)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

14
00:00:40,510 --> 00:00:45,010
{\pos(67,248)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

15
00:00:40,510 --> 00:00:45,010
{\pos(58,238)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

16
00:00:40,510 --> 00:00:45,010
{\pos(84,248)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

19
00:00:46,230 --> 00:01:16,230
{\an9}m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

20
00:00:45,730 --> 00:01:16,230
{\an2}{\pos(26,248)}m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

28
00:00:45,990 --> 00:00:48,150
It's official. The polls have just closed...

29
00:00:48,260 --> 00:00:50,660
...minutes ago in California, and the big story:

30
00:00:50,760 --> 00:00:53,820
Senator David Palmer seems to have swept California...

31
00:00:53,930 --> 00:00:55,090
...and every other state...

32
00:00:55,200 --> 00:00:57,170
...that held a primary this super Tuesday.

33
00:00:57,270 --> 00:01:00,140
It looks like he may have gotten a boost in the late vote...

34
00:01:00,240 --> 00:01:02,760
...based on the roller coaster events of his day.

35
00:01:02,880 --> 00:01:04,000
Earlier this evening,

36
00:01:04,000 --> 00:01:06,110
the Senator held an emergency press conference...

37
00:01:06,210 --> 00:01:07,440
...to disclose the details

38
00:01:07,450 --> 00:01:09,340
of the scandal involving both his son...

39
00:01:09,450 --> 00:01:11,350
...and his primary financial backers.

40
00:01:11,480 --> 00:01:12,930
Palmer claims to have been

41
00:01:12,930 --> 00:01:15,220
unaware of any wrongdoing until recently.

42
00:02:00,430 --> 00:02:01,730
You're in my seat.

43
00:02:03,340 --> 00:02:04,390
Fine.

44
00:02:15,620 --> 00:02:17,480
I said that's my seat.

45
00:02:38,340 --> 00:02:39,770
- How about you? - Well...

46
00:02:39,870 --> 00:02:42,140
Would you excuse us for a moment?

47
00:02:42,240 --> 00:02:44,040
Thanks a lot. I'll see you soon.

48
00:02:44,140 --> 00:02:45,940
11 for 11, my friend.

49
00:02:46,110 --> 00:02:48,980
- Congratulations. You did it. - We did it.

50
00:02:50,320 --> 00:02:51,780
That's not the best part.

51
00:02:51,880 --> 00:02:54,320
Fox News just did an instant poll.

52
00:02:54,420 --> 00:02:55,970
83% approve of the way

53
00:02:55,970 --> 00:02:58,290
you handled the Ferragamo situation.

54
00:02:59,190 --> 00:03:00,520
That is great.

55
00:03:02,860 --> 00:03:04,890
Have we heard from Ames or his people?

56
00:03:05,000 --> 00:03:06,400
They're all too busy running

57
00:03:06,400 --> 00:03:08,560
for cover and we don't want to get cocky...

58
00:03:08,900 --> 00:03:12,100
...but so far, it couldn't have turned out better.

59
00:03:19,810 --> 00:03:21,540
Everyone, listen up.

60
00:03:24,380 --> 00:03:27,250
In a bit, I'm going to give a speech to the country.

61
00:03:27,350 --> 00:03:30,690
We have a number of primaries in the coming months...

62
00:03:30,790 --> 00:03:32,820
...so technically it's not a victory speech.

63
00:03:34,360 --> 00:03:36,830
But I'm going to make it sound like one anyway.

64
00:03:41,630 --> 00:03:43,120
As you know...

65
00:03:43,240 --> 00:03:46,760
...in many ways, this has been a difficult day for my family...

66
00:03:46,870 --> 00:03:48,400
...and I'm confident that

67
00:03:48,400 --> 00:03:51,330
being open and honest was the right thing to do.

68
00:03:51,440 --> 00:03:55,400
And that things will be resolved fairly for everyone concerned...

69
00:03:55,550 --> 00:03:57,520
...and in the meantime...

70
00:03:58,350 --> 00:04:01,050
...I want to thank everyone in this room for their support.

71
00:04:02,860 --> 00:04:04,190
This is our victory.

72
00:04:06,560 --> 00:04:08,150
This is our night!

73
00:04:10,460 --> 00:04:13,230
And I just want to give one last order...

74
00:04:13,430 --> 00:04:16,400
...which will be obeyed, with no exceptions whatsoever.

75
00:04:17,840 --> 00:04:19,400
Enjoy the rest of the evening!

76
00:04:23,310 --> 00:04:24,620
Division wants an update on

77
00:04:24,620 --> 00:04:26,750
the Palmer threat-assessment in a half hour.

78
00:04:26,850 --> 00:04:29,540
With Alexis under control that threat may be minimal.

79
00:04:29,920 --> 00:04:31,880
Nina, that's your line.

80
00:04:32,320 --> 00:04:34,750
- Go ahead. - Try to get everyone together on it.

81
00:04:34,850 --> 00:04:38,020
Nina Myers's line. It's Bauer.

82
00:04:38,930 --> 00:04:40,150
I got it.

83
00:04:42,760 --> 00:04:44,750
- Jack, what the hell's going on? - George, listen up.

84
00:04:44,860 --> 00:04:46,560
That field that we were standing in...

85
00:04:46,670 --> 00:04:48,830
...is hiding an underground detention facility.

86
00:04:48,940 --> 00:04:51,270
It's being used as a prison to house Victor Drazen.

87
00:04:51,770 --> 00:04:54,330
What are you talking about? You said you took him out two years ago.

88
00:04:54,440 --> 00:04:57,710
Apparently not. I'm staring at him. There's a team in place.

89
00:04:57,810 --> 00:05:00,340
They're ready to attack. They've cut off the power.

90
00:05:00,450 --> 00:05:03,110
I need you to send in a field unit now.

91
00:05:04,480 --> 00:05:06,820
George, what are you going to do?

92
00:05:06,920 --> 00:05:08,470
- All right. I'll call Division. - Forget about the Division.

93
00:05:08,470 --> 00:05:09,890
By the time you get approval...

94
00:05:09,990 --> 00:05:11,740
...this whole thing will be over.

95
00:05:11,740 --> 00:05:13,760
If Drazen escapes, it'll be our fault.

96
00:05:13,860 --> 00:05:15,450
George, you know what this man can do.

97
00:05:18,060 --> 00:05:19,400
You decide.

98
00:05:21,700 --> 00:05:23,260
What's going on?

99
00:05:27,070 --> 00:05:28,270
Dispatch a field unit...

100
00:05:28,370 --> 00:05:30,340
...to the location Jack and I were checking in Saugus.

101
00:05:30,440 --> 00:05:31,960
I'll clear it from my end.

102
00:05:31,960 --> 00:05:33,470
Get a hold of Chappelle immediately.

103
00:05:33,650 --> 00:05:36,550
George, what is going on? Is Jack all right?

104
00:05:36,980 --> 00:05:39,280
It's a shame. You're wasting the best years...

105
00:05:39,390 --> 00:05:42,380
- ...of your life on a married man. - George...

106
00:05:42,490 --> 00:05:45,080
Picking up Almeida on the rebound. What's that about?

107
00:05:45,190 --> 00:05:49,320
- That is out of line. - You're out of line. Think about it.

108
00:05:49,600 --> 00:05:52,090
I'm just trying to be a friend here.

109
00:05:52,670 --> 00:05:53,830
George.

110
00:05:54,200 --> 00:05:56,190
- Just tell me if he... - Nina!

111
00:05:56,400 --> 00:05:57,840
Where's Jack?

112
00:05:59,140 --> 00:06:01,330
Teri, thank God, you're okay.

113
00:06:01,940 --> 00:06:03,400
Any word on Kim?

114
00:06:03,410 --> 00:06:05,840
No, not yet, but we're working on it.

115
00:06:06,350 --> 00:06:08,580
- I need to talk to Jack. - You can't. He is not here.

116
00:06:08,680 --> 00:06:10,200
He's on assignment.

117
00:06:10,200 --> 00:06:11,220
Assignment?

118
00:06:11,220 --> 00:06:13,250
Has he been told what happened at the safe house?

119
00:06:13,350 --> 00:06:14,980
- Not yet. - Why not?

120
00:06:15,120 --> 00:06:16,770
Because we can't get a hold of him.

121
00:06:16,770 --> 00:06:18,420
Get a hold of him now.

122
00:06:18,520 --> 00:06:20,670
Teri, I'm sorry, it's just not possible.

123
00:06:20,670 --> 00:06:22,520
Nina, I want to talk to Jack.

124
00:06:22,520 --> 00:06:24,470
I understand, but Jack's in a situation

125
00:06:24,470 --> 00:06:25,390
where he needs our support.

126
00:06:25,500 --> 00:06:28,560
We're doing everything we can to give it to him.

127
00:06:31,300 --> 00:06:33,130
What kind of situation?

128
00:06:33,140 --> 00:06:34,970
That's all I can tell you right now.

129
00:06:35,070 --> 00:06:37,390
what I need you to do is come to the conference room,

130
00:06:37,390 --> 00:06:39,700
tell me what happened to your house before Tony arrived.

131
00:06:39,810 --> 00:06:41,750
I've already told Tony everything in the car.

132
00:06:41,750 --> 00:06:43,020
It won't hurt to go over it again.

133
00:06:43,020 --> 00:06:44,780
Any details you can give us will help us

134
00:06:44,780 --> 00:06:47,550
and they will help Jack.

135
00:06:49,560 --> 00:06:53,550
All right, but I need to know what's going on with my family.

136
00:06:53,990 --> 00:06:55,600
I know, and I promise I'll

137
00:06:55,600 --> 00:06:58,120
give you an update as soon as I have one.

138
00:06:58,960 --> 00:07:00,190
All right?

139
00:07:03,670 --> 00:07:05,530
Stand against the door.

140
00:07:06,640 --> 00:07:09,900
Lawrence, what's going on out there?

141
00:07:10,380 --> 00:07:12,610
Lawrence, do you copy?

142
00:07:15,580 --> 00:07:17,780
Ray, this is DeSalvo. Come in.

143
00:07:18,820 --> 00:07:21,750
- Ray! - We gotta get out of here. Which way?

144
00:07:21,990 --> 00:07:24,180
The flood egress is to the right.

145
00:07:24,960 --> 00:07:26,720
Open the door slowly.

146
00:07:35,470 --> 00:07:37,960
Step out into the middle of the hall.

147
00:07:44,610 --> 00:07:46,340
Turn to your right.

148
00:07:46,650 --> 00:07:48,040
Keep moving.

149
00:08:07,230 --> 00:08:08,330
Lawrence, where are you?

150
00:08:09,170 --> 00:08:10,450
Lawrence, do you copy?

151
00:08:10,450 --> 00:08:13,200
We have to get out of this hall way. We're too exposed.

152
00:08:14,210 --> 00:08:16,040
All right. What's the plan?

153
00:08:16,040 --> 00:08:17,720
How are they going to break you out of here?

154
00:08:19,580 --> 00:08:21,670
You son of a bitch, if any of my men die...

155
00:08:21,880 --> 00:08:24,310
What area of this building is most defendable?

156
00:08:33,230 --> 00:08:34,860
Let's get out of here, move.

157
00:08:34,860 --> 00:08:36,460
Fall back. Defender retreat!

158
00:08:38,430 --> 00:08:39,350
Turn around.

159
00:08:58,120 --> 00:09:00,330
I've been trying to get a hold of Chappelle for 10 minutes.

160
00:09:00,330 --> 00:09:03,520
Look Whatever he's doing this is more important, trust me.

161
00:09:03,520 --> 00:09:05,870
- Important? How? - For starters...

162
00:09:05,870 --> 00:09:09,190
...I sent a CTU field unit to a D.O.D. Facility.

163
00:09:09,190 --> 00:09:10,820
I need some unity of command.

164
00:09:10,820 --> 00:09:12,960
All I can do is give him the message.

165
00:09:12,970 --> 00:09:15,970
- All right. Get him to call me soon. - I'll work on it.

166
00:09:16,440 --> 00:09:17,540
Mrs. Bauer.

167
00:09:18,270 --> 00:09:19,340
Teri.

168
00:09:19,470 --> 00:09:21,740
George Mason. I thought you were being debriefed.

169
00:09:21,740 --> 00:09:23,880
I know You're busy, but Nina won't tell me anything.

170
00:09:23,880 --> 00:09:25,940
I need to know what's going on with Kim.

171
00:09:26,050 --> 00:09:30,080
I don't know any more than Nina, but I'm sure Kim's safe.

172
00:09:30,650 --> 00:09:33,550
I wish I could believe that, but based on what?

173
00:09:33,550 --> 00:09:35,820
I haven't been fully briefed, but according to Tony...

174
00:09:35,820 --> 00:09:38,630
...the man that attacked you at your house asked where she was, right?

175
00:09:39,060 --> 00:09:40,310
Yes.

176
00:09:40,390 --> 00:09:42,260
That means they're looking for her, too.

177
00:09:42,260 --> 00:09:45,230
As time passes, it gets harder for them, easier for us.

178
00:09:45,230 --> 00:09:46,580
There's only a few of them...

179
00:09:46,700 --> 00:09:49,590
...whereas we can cover the whole city and believe me, we are.

180
00:09:53,040 --> 00:09:56,040
I want you to know Jack is extremely important to all of us here.

181
00:09:56,040 --> 00:09:57,630
Nobody's going to rest easy

182
00:09:57,640 --> 00:09:59,490
until your daughter's back, safe and sound.

183
00:10:00,750 --> 00:10:01,830
Thank you.

184
00:10:03,880 --> 00:10:05,340
Just doing my job.

185
00:10:10,060 --> 00:10:12,320
- Mason. - George, it's Nina.

186
00:10:14,260 --> 00:10:16,690
Our unit will be on-site in about 15 minutes.

187
00:10:16,700 --> 00:10:18,890
They want to know who's in command, us or D.O.D.?

188
00:10:18,930 --> 00:10:20,760
We are. Let me know as soon as they're on-site.

189
00:10:20,770 --> 00:10:21,940
All right.

190
00:10:23,540 --> 00:10:24,590
Was that about Jack?

191
00:10:25,570 --> 00:10:27,270
Teri, we've got a lot going on right now.

192
00:10:27,270 --> 00:10:29,200
Soon as we get word from Jack, we'll let you know.

193
00:10:29,910 --> 00:10:31,300
You've been very kind.

194
00:10:31,440 --> 00:10:33,240
My assistant Rebecca will look after you.

195
00:10:33,250 --> 00:10:35,110
You let her know if you need anything, okay?

196
00:10:36,620 --> 00:10:38,920
Do me a favor. Keep your chin up.

197
00:10:45,490 --> 00:10:47,200
- Rebecca. - Yes, George?

198
00:10:47,260 --> 00:10:49,650
I'm sending Jack's wife down. Babysit her for me. Will you?

199
00:10:49,650 --> 00:10:51,850
OK sure, but what do you want me to do with her?

200
00:10:51,850 --> 00:10:53,780
Whatever, I don't care what you do with her,

201
00:10:53,780 --> 00:10:56,130
just keep her out of my face. OK?

202
00:10:56,140 --> 00:10:57,110
Got it.

203
00:11:01,740 --> 00:11:02,770
Where's Patty?

204
00:11:03,340 --> 00:11:04,920
She's finishing up the speech.

205
00:11:05,910 --> 00:11:08,100
Hold that for me? Be right back.

206
00:11:10,680 --> 00:11:12,280
- Senator.... - Congratulations.

207
00:11:12,280 --> 00:11:13,950
Looks like you're moving to the White House.

208
00:11:14,390 --> 00:11:16,830
You know what? We'll know by the end of the day.

209
00:11:17,020 --> 00:11:18,170
Congratulations.

210
00:11:18,290 --> 00:11:20,550
We missed you out there.

211
00:11:20,830 --> 00:11:25,170
I'm just going through it one last time.

212
00:11:30,170 --> 00:11:32,390
I made the changes you asked for.

213
00:11:36,480 --> 00:11:38,380
Yeah, that's much better.

214
00:11:40,450 --> 00:11:42,180
I'm glad you like it.

215
00:11:47,390 --> 00:11:50,640
I can't believe you won all 11 primaries.

216
00:11:50,790 --> 00:11:53,090
You and your family must be so happy.

217
00:11:54,990 --> 00:11:56,270
Yeah, we are.

218
00:11:58,130 --> 00:12:02,160
- Are you okay? - Yeah, it's just all catching up with me.

219
00:12:02,400 --> 00:12:03,840
It's been a long day.

220
00:12:08,770 --> 00:12:10,190
You know what, Patty?

221
00:12:11,140 --> 00:12:13,780
Why don't we move the second paragraph to the end?

222
00:12:13,950 --> 00:12:16,770
I'll close with the note about party unity.

223
00:12:16,920 --> 00:12:18,390
That's a good idea.

224
00:12:22,050 --> 00:12:23,020
Senator?

225
00:12:23,820 --> 00:12:24,930
Yes, Patty.

226
00:12:25,660 --> 00:12:29,710
There's something I've been wanting to tell you, but...

227
00:12:30,330 --> 00:12:33,780
...every time I start it just seems inappropriate.

228
00:12:34,200 --> 00:12:35,190
What is it?

229
00:12:35,670 --> 00:12:38,030
It's just that...

230
00:12:39,670 --> 00:12:42,740
...I wanted to tell you how much I admire you.

231
00:12:45,880 --> 00:12:48,200
I don't see very many people who stand

232
00:12:48,200 --> 00:12:50,460
by their principles the way that you do,

233
00:12:51,240 --> 00:12:53,630
and I truly believe our country would be a better place

234
00:12:53,630 --> 00:12:55,000
with you leading it.

235
00:13:03,760 --> 00:13:07,100
- What is it? - Nothing. I'm just a little flustered.

236
00:13:09,740 --> 00:13:12,830
What a wonderful and unexpected compliment.

237
00:13:16,640 --> 00:13:20,140
I'll just switch those paragraphs.

238
00:13:21,710 --> 00:13:22,640
All right.

239
00:13:35,290 --> 00:13:37,900
This is Mason. What's your 20?

240
00:13:37,900 --> 00:13:39,510
We're approaching the site!

241
00:13:40,200 --> 00:13:41,810
What's going on down there, Lawrence?

242
00:13:44,800 --> 00:13:46,850
Looks like the door has been blown in!

243
00:13:47,410 --> 00:13:50,110
- Are the hostiles inside? - They must be.

244
00:13:50,110 --> 00:13:53,250
There's no activity here. We're preparing to go in.

245
00:14:13,620 --> 00:14:15,530
Take cover! Take cover!

246
00:14:16,180 --> 00:14:18,000
- Father! - Andre!

247
00:14:18,000 --> 00:14:20,340
- Get down or I'll shoot him! - Let him go.

248
00:14:20,340 --> 00:14:22,240
Let my father go, Bauer!

249
00:14:22,240 --> 00:14:23,560
Drop your weapons!

250
00:14:24,510 --> 00:14:26,890
Stay back or I will shoot him!

251
00:14:27,450 --> 00:14:29,090
Drop it or he's dead!

252
00:14:29,090 --> 00:14:30,620
Drop it now, you're surrounded!

253
00:14:30,620 --> 00:14:33,820
Back off! Drop your weapons or I will shoot!

254
00:14:34,050 --> 00:14:36,790
Let my father go right now or this man dies.

255
00:14:36,790 --> 00:14:38,760
- Drop your weapons! - I'll kill him.

256
00:14:38,760 --> 00:14:40,670
- Don't do it, Bauer! - Back off!

257
00:14:40,680 --> 00:14:43,410
- Don't release that prisoner. - Drop them or I'll shoot him!

258
00:14:44,160 --> 00:14:45,630
- Drop your weapon! - Don't do it, Bauer! Don't do it.

259
00:14:45,630 --> 00:14:48,430
- Drop it! - I'll give you three seconds.

260
00:14:48,500 --> 00:14:49,120
One...

261
00:14:49,640 --> 00:14:50,310
...two....

262
00:14:51,440 --> 00:14:52,650
My weapon's up.

263
00:14:58,310 --> 00:14:59,490
No!

264
00:14:59,850 --> 00:15:01,690
- Father. - Andre.

265
00:15:05,880 --> 00:15:09,050
- Where is Alexis? - He's been out of touch for a while.

266
00:15:09,920 --> 00:15:11,540
We have to assume the worst.

267
00:15:21,070 --> 00:15:23,230
Hostiles outside the main entrance.

268
00:15:23,240 --> 00:15:26,320
- How many? - At least a dozen, all well-armed.

269
00:15:26,570 --> 00:15:29,030
Collapse the corridor immediately.

270
00:15:29,040 --> 00:15:31,750
- Let's hustle, men. - Down here.

271
00:15:31,840 --> 00:15:34,660
Take him. We may need him as a bargaining chip.

272
00:15:53,430 --> 00:15:54,740
Go! Go! Go!

273
00:16:05,680 --> 00:16:08,380
That was a mistake. Now you're trapped.

274
00:16:08,380 --> 00:16:09,790
We will see.

275
00:16:12,820 --> 00:16:15,150
I told you, don't mess with me.

276
00:16:15,150 --> 00:16:16,970
You got something that belongs to me,

277
00:16:16,970 --> 00:16:19,190
better give it right now.

278
00:16:19,190 --> 00:16:22,090
- I ain't got nothing. - We cool. It's all good.

279
00:16:22,190 --> 00:16:24,650
We cool if you and your girls back off.

280
00:16:26,000 --> 00:16:27,180
Get her feet!

281
00:16:34,770 --> 00:16:37,960
You holding out on me? You're a bad girl.

282
00:16:51,520 --> 00:16:52,570
When we get out of here

283
00:16:52,570 --> 00:16:54,660
maybe I'll mess you up just like that.

284
00:16:54,660 --> 00:16:56,940
- What is your problem? - You.

285
00:16:56,960 --> 00:16:59,900
Me? The only reason I'm here is because you told the cops...

286
00:16:59,900 --> 00:17:01,270
...I was a part of the deal.

287
00:17:01,270 --> 00:17:02,790
You were a part of the deal.

288
00:17:03,000 --> 00:17:04,760
I didn't even know it was happening.

289
00:17:05,270 --> 00:17:06,990
Nobody told you to come over.

290
00:17:07,770 --> 00:17:09,820
If this is about Rick--

291
00:17:09,830 --> 00:17:11,880
Rick? You think I care about that loser?

292
00:17:11,880 --> 00:17:13,510
- He's not a loser. - He kidnaps you...

293
00:17:13,520 --> 00:17:16,140
...almost gets you killed, and you defend him?

294
00:17:16,350 --> 00:17:17,820
He didn't know what was going on.

295
00:17:17,820 --> 00:17:19,530
Like I said, he's a loser.

296
00:17:20,950 --> 00:17:22,900
What are you shaking your head for?

297
00:17:22,900 --> 00:17:24,800
You're daddy's little girl.

298
00:17:25,120 --> 00:17:27,790
- You get everything handed to you. - Shut up!

299
00:17:27,830 --> 00:17:29,840
I have been listening to this crap all day

300
00:17:29,840 --> 00:17:31,960
about how I get everything I want...

301
00:17:31,960 --> 00:17:34,500
...how my life is great and everyone else's sucks.

302
00:17:34,500 --> 00:17:37,580
You want to know something? You don't know anything about me.

303
00:17:37,770 --> 00:17:40,710
Last night I was kidnapped, tied up in the back of a trunk...

304
00:17:40,710 --> 00:17:43,470
...and then I got to see your friend Dan get shot in the head.

305
00:17:43,640 --> 00:17:46,840
Take all the bad luck you've had, it wouldn't fit into half...

306
00:17:46,850 --> 00:17:48,910
...of what's happened to me in the past 24 hours.

307
00:17:48,910 --> 00:17:51,720
So messing me up may not be as easy as you think...

308
00:17:51,720 --> 00:17:54,520
...but if you want to try, bring it on.

309
00:17:54,520 --> 00:17:57,780
Here, outside, any place you like.

310
00:18:40,830 --> 00:18:43,040
You think I am a monster...

311
00:18:43,240 --> 00:18:44,800
...because I want revenge...

312
00:18:44,800 --> 00:18:48,020
...on your wife and daughter as well as on you.

313
00:18:48,110 --> 00:18:50,800
You were a monster long before you ever heard of me.

314
00:18:51,980 --> 00:18:53,210
I see.

315
00:18:53,210 --> 00:18:55,660
You consider yourself informed.

316
00:18:56,150 --> 00:18:58,640
You have read magazines.

317
00:18:58,780 --> 00:19:01,290
You've studied intelligence reports...

318
00:19:01,290 --> 00:19:02,550
...filed by people

319
00:19:02,550 --> 00:19:05,970
who tell their superiors only what they want to hear.

320
00:19:06,260 --> 00:19:09,060
And you have the audacity to judge me?

321
00:19:10,500 --> 00:19:12,850
So when does your suffering end, Victor?

322
00:19:13,230 --> 00:19:15,400
After you've killed me and Senator Palmer...

323
00:19:15,400 --> 00:19:17,800
...and all the thousands of other enemies you have?

324
00:19:18,340 --> 00:19:19,340
Yes.

325
00:19:20,310 --> 00:19:22,000
Simple, is it not?

326
00:19:23,980 --> 00:19:25,450
You're insane.

327
00:19:25,540 --> 00:19:27,620
It's a psychotic fantasy.

328
00:19:34,650 --> 00:19:39,190
A fantasy which is coming closer and closer to a reality.

329
00:19:44,830 --> 00:19:48,220
This is Victor Drazen. Whom am I speaking to?

330
00:19:48,300 --> 00:19:49,530
This is George Mason.

331
00:19:49,530 --> 00:19:52,300
The district director of the Counter Terrorist Unit in LA.

332
00:19:52,300 --> 00:19:55,530
You will be the person I will be negotiating with?

333
00:19:55,540 --> 00:19:59,210
Negative. We do not negotiate with terrorists.

334
00:19:59,410 --> 00:20:01,260
I'm willing to listen to your concerns.

335
00:20:01,510 --> 00:20:05,290
My main concern is Jack Bauer.

336
00:20:05,450 --> 00:20:07,790
- Do you know him? - Yes, I know him.

337
00:20:07,790 --> 00:20:10,310
Do you want to see him alive again?

338
00:20:11,420 --> 00:20:12,970
How do I know he's alive?

339
00:20:18,360 --> 00:20:20,560
- George? - Yeah, it's me.

340
00:20:20,570 --> 00:20:23,870
I've counted six of them, heavily armed with assault rifles--

341
00:20:23,870 --> 00:20:25,890
As you hear, he is alive.

342
00:20:26,100 --> 00:20:28,530
I'll be speaking with my superiors and I'll get back to you.

343
00:20:32,640 --> 00:20:36,170
Drazen's taken over command of the facility. He's got Jack.

344
00:20:36,180 --> 00:20:38,140
There's at least six, they've got assault weapons,

345
00:20:38,140 --> 00:20:40,960
explosives. Get that information to the field unit.

346
00:20:44,460 --> 00:20:46,370
Bring up the layout of the facility.

347
00:20:48,190 --> 00:20:51,440
- How did Jack sound? - Alive.

348
00:20:52,500 --> 00:20:54,500
It'll be a long, drawn-out process, Nina.

349
00:20:54,500 --> 00:20:55,920
I know the drill.

350
00:20:56,430 --> 00:20:58,390
You know it may not turn out well.

351
00:20:58,900 --> 00:21:00,450
If you want me to put somebody

352
00:21:00,450 --> 00:21:02,610
else that's less emotionally involved on this, I will.

353
00:21:03,340 --> 00:21:05,070
I can do my job, George.

354
00:21:06,710 --> 00:21:07,820
Okay.

355
00:21:13,150 --> 00:21:16,050
- Any word from Chappelle? - I still can't get a hold of him.

356
00:21:16,050 --> 00:21:17,590
Unbelievable.

357
00:21:17,590 --> 00:21:19,120
I hope that bastard doesn't plan on blaming me

358
00:21:19,120 --> 00:21:20,340
if things go wrong.

359
00:21:48,620 --> 00:21:50,350
- Take it. - No way.

360
00:21:50,360 --> 00:21:52,330
- I said take it! - No.

361
00:21:56,390 --> 00:21:57,820
Who's smoking pot?

362
00:21:58,140 --> 00:22:00,000
That one over there.

363
00:22:00,000 --> 00:22:01,990
No. She threw it at me.

364
00:22:01,990 --> 00:22:03,270
Bitch, why you lying?

365
00:22:03,340 --> 00:22:04,300
Give it to me.

366
00:22:05,540 --> 00:22:07,110
Give it to me!

367
00:22:13,810 --> 00:22:16,220
- And who are you? - I swear, it wasn't me.

368
00:22:19,680 --> 00:22:21,540
You're coming with me.

369
00:22:23,360 --> 00:22:24,900
She's telling the truth.

370
00:22:27,160 --> 00:22:29,100
Don't make a liar out of me, blondie.

371
00:22:29,100 --> 00:22:31,070
No need, you are one.

372
00:22:36,970 --> 00:22:37,700
Stop it!

373
00:22:40,810 --> 00:22:43,600
- Stop it now! - Wait, I didn't do nothing!

374
00:22:43,680 --> 00:22:46,940
Get off of me! I didn't do nothing!

375
00:22:50,550 --> 00:22:53,620
I'm going to get you back, blondie, don't you worry!

376
00:22:56,760 --> 00:22:57,870
Officer.

377
00:22:59,520 --> 00:23:00,630
Wait.

378
00:23:03,030 --> 00:23:05,330
I want to talk to the cop that busted me today.

379
00:23:05,330 --> 00:23:07,210
I think his name is Krugman.

380
00:23:07,400 --> 00:23:10,340
- You want to talk to him about what? - What happened today.

381
00:23:11,500 --> 00:23:15,740
He wants to know about it, so tell him I'm ready to talk.

382
00:23:17,180 --> 00:23:18,050
Come on.

383
00:23:33,390 --> 00:23:35,480
Two years ago in Kosovo...

384
00:23:36,230 --> 00:23:38,830
...the man that went into the building before the explosion...

385
00:23:39,260 --> 00:23:40,720
...obviously wasn't you.

386
00:23:41,900 --> 00:23:45,740
- You were using a double. - A common technique.

387
00:23:45,780 --> 00:23:48,930
I am surprised your people were fooled by it.

388
00:23:49,440 --> 00:23:51,270
That's not my point, Victor.

389
00:23:51,480 --> 00:23:53,480
What is your point, Jack?

390
00:23:53,550 --> 00:23:55,320
You were using a double.

391
00:23:56,380 --> 00:23:58,410
It means you thought you were a target.

392
00:23:59,450 --> 00:24:01,260
You let that man get near your family,

393
00:24:01,260 --> 00:24:02,500
you put your family in danger.

394
00:24:02,500 --> 00:24:05,340
You're responsible for their deaths.

395
00:24:05,790 --> 00:24:07,950
They were away on a trip.

396
00:24:08,490 --> 00:24:10,190
My daughter was ill.

397
00:24:12,030 --> 00:24:15,630
They returned one day earlier than expected.

398
00:24:17,340 --> 00:24:18,330
But yes...

399
00:24:19,800 --> 00:24:22,040
...I should have been more careful.

400
00:24:29,480 --> 00:24:30,600
Father, are you all right?

401
00:24:38,420 --> 00:24:40,470
Over the last two years...

402
00:24:42,030 --> 00:24:43,690
...I have accepted my share

403
00:24:43,690 --> 00:24:46,680
of responsibility for the death of my family.

404
00:24:48,100 --> 00:24:49,570
This is the day...

405
00:24:51,440 --> 00:24:53,060
...you accept...

406
00:24:53,640 --> 00:24:54,960
...your share.

407
00:24:59,080 --> 00:25:00,440
Come, Dad.

408
00:25:03,780 --> 00:25:06,770
Make sure he does not die.

409
00:25:31,040 --> 00:25:32,180
Come.

410
00:25:39,080 --> 00:25:40,380
Is this what you wanted?

411
00:25:47,330 --> 00:25:48,540
Much better.

412
00:25:48,660 --> 00:25:50,530
- Senator? - Yeah, Elaine?

413
00:25:50,530 --> 00:25:52,880
Mike says they're ready for you downstairs anytime.

414
00:25:52,960 --> 00:25:55,140
Okay. Tell them I'll be down in 20 minutes.

415
00:25:55,400 --> 00:25:57,560
You have a copy for the teleprompter?

416
00:25:57,600 --> 00:25:59,560
It's this one....

417
00:25:59,870 --> 00:26:01,230
All but the last page.

418
00:26:03,440 --> 00:26:04,860
Okay, thanks.

419
00:26:05,310 --> 00:26:07,860
Would you like to be left alone?

420
00:26:08,350 --> 00:26:10,210
No. You can work in here if you want.

421
00:26:40,850 --> 00:26:41,880
I'm sorry.

422
00:26:42,780 --> 00:26:43,690
What is it?

423
00:26:45,520 --> 00:26:48,910
It's just that I feel bad that this day's been tainted for you.

424
00:26:50,590 --> 00:26:52,100
Don't feel bad for me.

425
00:26:53,560 --> 00:26:55,780
It's Keith and Nicole who've been suffering.

426
00:26:56,060 --> 00:26:59,030
Excuse me for saying this, Senator, but you do that too much.

427
00:26:59,030 --> 00:27:02,210
- Do what? - You worry about everybody else.

428
00:27:02,600 --> 00:27:05,200
You take care of everybody else. Who takes care of you?

429
00:27:05,200 --> 00:27:06,890
You all take care of me.

430
00:27:09,910 --> 00:27:11,850
We all want to, but...

431
00:27:12,340 --> 00:27:15,010
planning schedules and writing speeches

432
00:27:15,010 --> 00:27:16,560
isn't taking care of someone.

433
00:27:18,780 --> 00:27:20,110
I'm fine, Patty.

434
00:27:34,830 --> 00:27:36,100
Just relax.

435
00:27:38,940 --> 00:27:40,600
You need this.

436
00:27:43,140 --> 00:27:46,420
That does feel good.

437
00:28:04,630 --> 00:28:06,350
I appreciate it, Patty.

438
00:28:08,030 --> 00:28:09,190
I really do.

439
00:28:11,140 --> 00:28:14,170
But if I get too comfortable, I may not get off this couch.

440
00:28:18,640 --> 00:28:22,930
I'll just go prepare tomorrow's briefing with Mike. Excuse me.

441
00:28:39,160 --> 00:28:40,540
CTU, Myers.

442
00:28:40,540 --> 00:28:41,800
Ryan Chappelle calling for Mason.

443
00:28:41,800 --> 00:28:43,010
Yes, I'll put you through.

444
00:28:47,570 --> 00:28:49,130
- Mason. - It's Chappelle.

445
00:28:51,410 --> 00:28:54,310
Ryan, it's about time. I've been trying to reach you for the past half hour.

446
00:28:54,310 --> 00:28:57,810
While I've been getting reamed by D.O.D. And the Pentagon.

447
00:28:57,820 --> 00:29:00,610
I think I've managed to untangle the mess you've made.

448
00:29:00,890 --> 00:29:03,000
The mess I've made? What are you talking about?

449
00:29:03,690 --> 00:29:07,670
You should've kept Bauer on a tighter leash. A lot tighter.

450
00:29:07,930 --> 00:29:10,040
I'm not in love with the guy either, but he delivers.

451
00:29:10,430 --> 00:29:11,340
Really?

452
00:29:12,160 --> 00:29:13,770
Come on, let's face it.

453
00:29:13,800 --> 00:29:16,200
If it wasn't for Jack, Victor would've escaped.

454
00:29:16,200 --> 00:29:18,750
It would've been embarrassing for high-ranking individuals

455
00:29:18,750 --> 00:29:20,140
if I'm not mistaken.

456
00:29:20,140 --> 00:29:21,790
You're very mistaken.

457
00:29:21,840 --> 00:29:25,910
- I beg your pardon? - Come on, Geogre, think it through.

458
00:29:25,910 --> 00:29:28,850
Drazen wasn't officially a prisoner, right?

459
00:29:28,910 --> 00:29:30,660
So he couldn't officially escape.

460
00:29:30,670 --> 00:29:32,680
It wouldn't have embarrassed anyone.

461
00:29:32,680 --> 00:29:35,020
- It would've been.... - A nonevent.

462
00:29:35,020 --> 00:29:38,660
Exactly. Instead, we've got an assault team out there...

463
00:29:38,660 --> 00:29:40,660
with all kinds of people in the loop.

464
00:29:40,660 --> 00:29:42,330
Soon the cops will get wind of it...

465
00:29:42,330 --> 00:29:44,660
...and then, God forbid, the press.

466
00:29:44,660 --> 00:29:46,460
You want to talk about embarrassing?

467
00:29:49,200 --> 00:29:50,870
Now we have to end this thing.

468
00:29:50,870 --> 00:29:53,690
And I'm not talking hours, I'm talking minutes.

469
00:29:55,640 --> 00:29:56,880
What about Bauer?

470
00:30:00,380 --> 00:30:02,390
Nobody asked him to go out there tonight.

471
00:30:03,350 --> 00:30:07,560
Now, get on with it, or I'll find someone who will.

472
00:30:19,060 --> 00:30:20,850
I'm going to have to order a full assault.

473
00:30:21,330 --> 00:30:23,030
Starting in about five minutes.

474
00:30:24,200 --> 00:30:26,260
Team's making their final preparations.

475
00:30:27,440 --> 00:30:28,330
I'm sorry.

476
00:30:40,650 --> 00:30:42,240
Teri, it's Tony. Can you pick up?

477
00:30:43,720 --> 00:30:46,160
- Hello? - Look, we found Kim.

478
00:30:46,160 --> 00:30:47,760
She's fine. She's at a local precinct.

479
00:30:47,760 --> 00:30:49,160
They're bringing her over.

480
00:30:49,460 --> 00:30:51,700
Are you sure she's okay? Can I talk to her?

481
00:30:51,700 --> 00:30:53,960
Not now, we'll put you through as soon as we can.

482
00:30:53,970 --> 00:30:56,730
Okay. Patch her through as soon as she calls.

483
00:30:56,930 --> 00:30:58,870
- Thank you so much, Tony. - Okay.

484
00:30:58,870 --> 00:31:01,040
- They found Kim. - They did?

485
00:31:01,040 --> 00:31:03,080
- Yeah. - That's great.

486
00:31:04,440 --> 00:31:05,490
I'm so relieved.

487
00:31:13,650 --> 00:31:16,310
Teri, I have some information about Jack.

488
00:31:18,820 --> 00:31:20,180
Why don't you sit down?

489
00:31:24,660 --> 00:31:27,320
We think He may have been captured

490
00:31:27,320 --> 00:31:29,840
by the same group that was after you and Kim.

491
00:31:32,270 --> 00:31:33,560
Oh, my God.

492
00:31:35,440 --> 00:31:37,200
I know that sounds bad,

493
00:31:37,200 --> 00:31:39,080
but we have rescue teams on the site...

494
00:31:39,080 --> 00:31:42,280
and the people who have Jack have been completely surrounded.

495
00:31:50,920 --> 00:31:51,810
Teri...

496
00:31:53,690 --> 00:31:55,420
I know Jack.

497
00:31:56,860 --> 00:31:59,570
I know he will get out of this.

498
00:32:09,210 --> 00:32:11,460
I knew you'd want to be told.

499
00:32:47,580 --> 00:32:50,540
Charges have been placed. We are good to go.

500
00:32:55,790 --> 00:32:57,770
- Yeah? - This is it.

501
00:33:02,990 --> 00:33:05,480
- All right. - What about Bauer?

502
00:33:09,600 --> 00:33:11,380
Just make sure you get Drazen.

503
00:33:12,840 --> 00:33:13,650
Go.

504
00:33:14,440 --> 00:33:16,160
- Hit it.- Go.

505
00:33:20,910 --> 00:33:22,690
Go!Go!

506
00:33:47,070 --> 00:33:47,930
Kimberly.

507
00:33:48,770 --> 00:33:49,650
What is it?

508
00:33:50,810 --> 00:33:53,110
- We're releasing you. - Did you speak to my dad?

509
00:33:53,110 --> 00:33:55,270
No, but I talked to the people he works with.

510
00:34:01,020 --> 00:34:01,970
Melanie told me she lied.

511
00:34:01,970 --> 00:34:05,080
Before she admitted you had nothing to do

512
00:34:05,080 --> 00:34:07,570
with the drug deal. I called the number you gave me.

513
00:34:07,630 --> 00:34:08,960
Everything checked out.

514
00:34:09,280 --> 00:34:10,660
Sounds like you had a pretty tough day.

515
00:34:10,660 --> 00:34:12,740
Yeah. Did you speak to my mom?

516
00:34:12,740 --> 00:34:14,510
She's waiting for you at CTU.

517
00:34:14,510 --> 00:34:16,060
- Are you serious? - I'm serious.

518
00:34:16,200 --> 00:34:17,970
I'll drive you there myself.

519
00:34:22,510 --> 00:34:24,690
- Ready? - I think so.

520
00:34:25,440 --> 00:34:28,350
- Would you do me a favor, David? - What's that, Mike?

521
00:34:28,350 --> 00:34:29,350
Smile.

522
00:34:30,880 --> 00:34:33,330
Not a politician's smile, a real one.

523
00:34:34,120 --> 00:34:35,870
You've been through hell today...

524
00:34:36,190 --> 00:34:37,600
but you've come through it.

525
00:34:37,960 --> 00:34:40,820
And tomorrow morning the fight starts again.

526
00:34:41,390 --> 00:34:43,260
But tonight you need to celebrate.

527
00:34:44,660 --> 00:34:46,170
I'll be fine, Mike.

528
00:34:47,330 --> 00:34:50,360
Let go of it, just for a little bit.

529
00:34:51,140 --> 00:34:52,570
I can't.

530
00:34:53,600 --> 00:34:55,800
This thing with Keith is just beginning.

531
00:34:56,870 --> 00:34:59,740
As for Sherry and me, you've had a front-row seat today.

532
00:34:59,740 --> 00:35:00,980
You know it's not good.

533
00:35:03,880 --> 00:35:05,900
Let me explain something to you.

534
00:35:06,850 --> 00:35:08,660
Once you're in the White House,

535
00:35:08,660 --> 00:35:11,880
everything defers to the office.

536
00:35:11,990 --> 00:35:15,890
It's what you need to do the job.

537
00:35:18,200 --> 00:35:22,070
If it's your marriage that helps you, that's great.

538
00:35:22,470 --> 00:35:23,700
But if not...

539
00:35:24,940 --> 00:35:26,650
that's okay, too.

540
00:35:30,170 --> 00:35:32,820
You can have whatever you want. do you?

541
00:35:40,750 --> 00:35:41,960
All right, Mike.

542
00:35:42,950 --> 00:35:43,990
Let's go.

543
00:36:02,240 --> 00:36:03,150
Report.

544
00:36:04,280 --> 00:36:05,550
One dead body.

545
00:36:06,380 --> 00:36:09,580
No hostiles. Sector One secure.

546
00:36:19,920 --> 00:36:21,760
Sector Two secure.

547
00:36:22,090 --> 00:36:26,350
One dead body. Appears to be Warden DeSalvo. No hostiles.

548
00:36:27,330 --> 00:36:30,260
Drake, this is Mason. What's going on down there?

549
00:36:30,400 --> 00:36:32,650
The entire staff, including the warden, is dead.

550
00:36:32,950 --> 00:36:36,200
But Drazen's gone and so is anyone else who was here.

551
00:36:45,550 --> 00:36:47,480
They broke through one of the walls.

552
00:36:47,820 --> 00:36:50,920
Some sort of tunnel. Maybe an old sewer system.

553
00:36:50,920 --> 00:36:51,890
Follow them.

554
00:37:01,300 --> 00:37:02,200
Drake?

555
00:37:06,140 --> 00:37:07,470
It's booby-trapped.

556
00:37:07,670 --> 00:37:09,220
Laser mines.

557
00:37:09,840 --> 00:37:12,140
- Can you disarm? - Given time.

558
00:37:12,140 --> 00:37:13,160
How much?

559
00:37:16,950 --> 00:37:18,450
About a half-hour.

560
00:37:20,420 --> 00:37:21,640
Do what you can.

561
00:37:28,830 --> 00:37:30,180
Get your hands up on your head.

562
00:37:35,270 --> 00:37:36,210
Well done.

563
00:37:41,940 --> 00:37:44,670
- We have less than three hours left. - Get down.

564
00:37:45,680 --> 00:37:48,160
Wait! Wait! Wait! Wait!

565
00:37:48,180 --> 00:37:50,880
I will offer you one consolation.

566
00:37:53,020 --> 00:37:56,420
Your family will be joining you soon.

567
00:37:56,420 --> 00:37:59,090
Your son Alexis, do you want to see him again?

568
00:38:00,420 --> 00:38:01,840
Alexis is dead.

569
00:38:01,840 --> 00:38:03,260
No, he's not. We've got him.

570
00:38:03,260 --> 00:38:04,320
You are lying.

571
00:38:05,630 --> 00:38:08,070
How else would I know that he was to have a meeting

572
00:38:08,170 --> 00:38:09,990
with one of Senator Palmer's staff?

573
00:38:10,060 --> 00:38:11,570
A woman named Elizabeth Nash.

574
00:38:11,570 --> 00:38:14,240
In Room 1243 at 4:30 this afternoon.

575
00:38:15,370 --> 00:38:17,080
That much is true.

576
00:38:17,080 --> 00:38:20,120
We captured him. I know where he is.

577
00:38:32,220 --> 00:38:33,580
Get him in!

578
00:38:56,810 --> 00:38:59,080
- Can I borrow your phone? - Yeah.

579
00:39:12,030 --> 00:39:14,460
- Hello? - Mom, it's me.

580
00:39:14,670 --> 00:39:16,770
- Hi, honey. - I can't wait to see you.

581
00:39:16,770 --> 00:39:19,940
I can't wait to see you either. I'm so glad you're okay. I thought--

582
00:39:19,940 --> 00:39:21,960
I know. I thought they had you again.

583
00:39:22,810 --> 00:39:24,480
How did you end up in jail?

584
00:39:24,980 --> 00:39:27,620
I'll tell you everything when I get there. Where's Dad?

585
00:39:28,780 --> 00:39:31,410
He's not here. He's working.

586
00:39:31,750 --> 00:39:34,030
I'm hoping he'll call in very soon.

587
00:39:35,290 --> 00:39:37,030
I love you so much, Mom.

588
00:39:37,520 --> 00:39:39,570
I'm going to be there in a few minutes. OK?

589
00:39:41,060 --> 00:39:42,610
I love you, too, honey.

590
00:39:43,660 --> 00:39:46,080
- Bye. - Bye.

591
00:39:53,770 --> 00:39:55,200
Thanks.

592
00:40:05,780 --> 00:40:08,390
I'm sorry about not believing you at first.

593
00:40:08,390 --> 00:40:09,290
Don't worry about it.

594
00:40:09,290 --> 00:40:12,660
I'm not sure if I believe it myself. Watch out!

595
00:40:26,040 --> 00:40:27,600
No! No!

596
00:40:28,170 --> 00:40:29,490
Get off of me!

597
00:40:32,040 --> 00:40:33,800
No! Get off me!

598
00:40:35,780 --> 00:40:37,690
No!

