2
00:00:13,020 --> 00:00:14,400
There are terrorists planning

3
00:00:14,400 --> 00:00:17,210
to assassinate a presidential candidate.

4
00:00:17,980 --> 00:00:20,400
My wife and daughter have been kidnapped.

5
00:00:21,110 --> 00:00:24,820
And the people that I work with may be involved in both.

6
00:00:25,260 --> 00:00:27,380
I'm Federal Agent Jack Bauer.

7
00:00:27,710 --> 00:00:30,820
This, is the longest day of my life.

10
00:00:40,900 --> 00:00:43,410
This is Dave Thompson with Jet Copter Three.

11
00:00:43,410 --> 00:00:46,740
It's just 9:00 on Primary Day in Southern California.

12
00:00:46,740 --> 00:00:49,200
And freeways are looking pretty good.

13
00:00:49,200 --> 00:00:52,260
Usual delays in the Sepulveda Pass southbound,

14
00:00:52,260 --> 00:00:53,900
but it loosens up at Culver.

15
00:00:53,900 --> 00:00:57,130
We'll have a complete report in six minutes. Back to you, Bill.

16
00:00:57,340 --> 00:00:58,490
Thanks, Dave.

17
00:00:58,690 --> 00:01:01,720
In the news, we haven't learned any more about the incident

18
00:01:01,720 --> 00:01:03,680
at the San Clarita power plant

19
00:01:03,680 --> 00:01:06,400
where Senator Palmer was rushed out this morning.

20
00:01:06,410 --> 00:01:08,820
We're told the Senator was unharmed

21
00:01:08,820 --> 00:01:10,700
but Secret Service and the FBI

22
00:01:10,700 --> 00:01:12,840
haven't released any new information.

23
00:01:13,040 --> 00:01:15,570
- Get the drip started. - I'm on it.

24
00:01:16,960 --> 00:01:18,100
Find me a pulse.

25
00:01:21,980 --> 00:01:24,960
I've got a pulse. 140/30.

26
00:01:26,520 --> 00:01:30,820
Pupils not reactive. Respiration shallow. 48.

27
00:01:32,080 --> 00:01:34,380
Let's start two large-bore IVs, bilateral.

28
00:01:37,880 --> 00:01:39,180
She's lost a lot of blood.

29
00:01:40,740 --> 00:01:43,040
- We should start the other line. - All right.

30
00:01:43,370 --> 00:01:45,570
Start exactly there.

31
00:01:47,490 --> 00:01:48,390
Is it in?

32
00:01:52,080 --> 00:01:55,660
Ready, one, two, three.

33
00:01:56,220 --> 00:02:01,220
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

34
00:01:56,220 --> 00:02:01,220
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

35
00:01:56,220 --> 00:02:01,220
{\an5}{\pos(145,252)}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

36
00:01:56,720 --> 00:02:01,220
{\pos(67,248)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

37
00:01:56,720 --> 00:02:01,220
{\pos(67,248)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

38
00:01:56,720 --> 00:02:01,220
{\pos(58,238)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

39
00:01:56,720 --> 00:02:01,220
{\pos(84,248)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

42
00:02:02,440 --> 00:02:32,440
{\an9}m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

43
00:02:01,940 --> 00:02:32,440
{\an2}{\pos(26,248)}m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

50
00:02:03,600 --> 00:02:04,420
Ready?

51
00:02:05,900 --> 00:02:06,760
Lift!

52
00:02:25,200 --> 00:02:26,110
Excuse me.

53
00:02:30,410 --> 00:02:31,930
- I've got the door. - Okay.

54
00:02:39,040 --> 00:02:39,970
Everyone...

55
00:02:40,860 --> 00:02:41,740
I'm sorry to tell you

56
00:02:41,740 --> 00:02:44,590
that Jamey Farrell tried to commit suicide a few minutes ago.

57
00:02:45,050 --> 00:02:47,090
Fortunately, she's still alive...

58
00:02:47,550 --> 00:02:49,940
And they're doing everything they can to keep her that way.

59
00:02:52,730 --> 00:02:54,650
I know it won't be easy to put this out of our minds,

60
00:02:54,650 --> 00:02:56,200
but we have no choice.

61
00:02:56,700 --> 00:02:57,700
There's still reason to believe

62
00:02:57,700 --> 00:02:59,420
Senator Palmer's life is in danger

63
00:02:59,420 --> 00:03:02,320
which means we all have to get back to work, now.

64
00:03:06,760 --> 00:03:08,900
- You wanna look at this? - Not now.

65
00:03:08,900 --> 00:03:12,270
Call Jamey's mom, explain what happened. Have her pick up Kyle.

66
00:03:28,470 --> 00:03:29,690
CTU, Myers.

67
00:03:29,690 --> 00:03:31,630
Hey, it's me. Hold on.

68
00:03:32,270 --> 00:03:34,530
- Okay. - Did you get the car?

69
00:03:34,530 --> 00:03:36,810
Yes, and I got the care package, too. Thanks.

70
00:03:37,070 --> 00:03:39,020
- Jack, Teri called. - What?

71
00:03:39,020 --> 00:03:40,460
About 20 minutes ago.

72
00:03:40,950 --> 00:03:42,040
Where is She? What'd she say?

73
00:03:42,050 --> 00:03:44,190
I don't know. She barely had time to say her name

74
00:03:44,190 --> 00:03:45,490
before she got disconnected.

75
00:03:45,490 --> 00:03:46,550
What happened?

76
00:03:46,720 --> 00:03:47,550
She didn't call back

77
00:03:47,550 --> 00:03:50,180
and when I tried to redial, the number was blocked.

78
00:03:50,700 --> 00:03:52,540
But I can tell she sounded alright.

79
00:03:52,550 --> 00:03:54,550
The police have thrown a net over this entire area.

80
00:03:54,550 --> 00:03:57,220
There's nothing I can do to help Teri until I get through it.

81
00:03:57,500 --> 00:03:59,680
Maybe you should think about turning yourself in.

82
00:04:00,200 --> 00:04:01,980
- Tell your side of the story. - No.

83
00:04:02,140 --> 00:04:03,460
Gaines will keep Teri and Kim alive

84
00:04:03,460 --> 00:04:05,460
as long as he thinks I can be useful to him.

85
00:04:05,460 --> 00:04:07,090
If I'm in custody, I won't be.

86
00:04:07,090 --> 00:04:08,040
Scan the police frequencies,

87
00:04:08,040 --> 00:04:10,350
see if you can locate any of these roadblocks for me.

88
00:04:10,350 --> 00:04:11,250
All right.

89
00:04:13,560 --> 00:04:14,620
Just a minute.

90
00:04:17,720 --> 00:04:18,650
Okay.

93
00:04:18,960 --> 00:04:20,550
Jamey give you anything else?

94
00:04:20,560 --> 00:04:21,480
Jack...

95
00:04:22,420 --> 00:04:24,120
Jamey tried to kill herself.

96
00:04:25,510 --> 00:04:28,530
Jack, did you hear me?

97
00:04:30,640 --> 00:04:31,550
Jack?

98
00:04:31,860 --> 00:04:34,220
Yeah, you said she tried?

99
00:04:34,510 --> 00:04:36,550
We sent her to County, but it doesn't look good.

100
00:04:37,930 --> 00:04:39,930
Are you sure it was a suicide attempt?

101
00:04:40,130 --> 00:04:41,750
Yeah, she slit her wrists.

102
00:04:43,210 --> 00:04:44,710
Where was her son Kyle?

103
00:04:45,130 --> 00:04:47,430
He didn't see anything. We've already called Jamey's mom.

104
00:04:47,430 --> 00:04:49,100
She's on her way to pick him up.

105
00:04:49,680 --> 00:04:51,020
Okay, send someone down to County

106
00:04:51,020 --> 00:04:53,180
to question Jamey in case she makes it.

107
00:04:53,410 --> 00:04:55,990
Right now she's still our best source of information.

108
00:04:55,990 --> 00:04:56,940
Okay.

109
00:05:00,820 --> 00:05:02,990
- Damn it! - What? What's wrong?

110
00:05:03,010 --> 00:05:04,770
They set up a road block at Montana.

111
00:05:04,770 --> 00:05:06,960
Nina, I could have used the heads-up here.

112
00:05:07,200 --> 00:05:09,690
I'm sorry, they must have set it up before I started scanning.

113
00:05:12,940 --> 00:05:14,330
Find me another route.

114
00:05:14,340 --> 00:05:16,650
All right, give me a second to pull up LA traffic.

115
00:05:18,150 --> 00:05:19,050
Okay.

116
00:05:19,050 --> 00:05:21,150
You go to the window. You let me know if somebody comes.

117
00:05:39,630 --> 00:05:41,740
Tony, Line 3, can you get it?

118
00:05:42,140 --> 00:05:43,040
Almeida.

119
00:05:43,040 --> 00:05:47,390
Okay, it looks like roadblocks aren't your only problem.

120
00:05:47,780 --> 00:05:50,770
They sent a description of you to all the units in the area.

121
00:05:52,010 --> 00:05:55,090
Nina, it's Teri Bauer.

122
00:05:55,510 --> 00:05:56,840
Jack, hold on a minute.

123
00:05:59,820 --> 00:06:01,960
- Teri? - Nina, thank God.

124
00:06:01,960 --> 00:06:02,820
Where are you?

125
00:06:02,820 --> 00:06:04,510
I don't know, but I got ahold of a phone.

126
00:06:04,670 --> 00:06:07,310
Okay, is Kim with you? Are you all right?

127
00:06:07,320 --> 00:06:10,030
Yeah, I'm fine, Kimberly's fine. Do you know where Jack is?

128
00:06:10,030 --> 00:06:13,050
Yeah, listen, I'm gonna connect you with him right now.

129
00:06:13,050 --> 00:06:15,540
Leave the line open as long as you can so we can set up a trace.

130
00:06:15,540 --> 00:06:17,320
- Do you understand? - Yeah.

131
00:06:18,060 --> 00:06:20,070
Have Milo set up the trace on Line 3.

132
00:06:21,950 --> 00:06:23,490
Jack? I've got Teri.

133
00:06:23,590 --> 00:06:26,450
- Patch her through. - Mom, someone's coming.

134
00:06:27,540 --> 00:06:28,540
He's here!

135
00:06:29,290 --> 00:06:30,840
Teri? Teri?

136
00:06:34,850 --> 00:06:36,230
What do you want from us?

137
00:06:40,180 --> 00:06:42,190
I think I left my phone in here. You seen it?

138
00:06:43,340 --> 00:06:44,590
No, I haven't.

139
00:06:45,570 --> 00:06:47,860
Jack, I've muted our side of the conversation.

140
00:06:47,860 --> 00:06:49,550
Have you set up a trace on the call?

141
00:06:49,550 --> 00:06:51,330
Yeah. I told Teri to leave the line open.

142
00:06:51,330 --> 00:06:54,960
Good. Keep our side muted. I don't want to give away this phone.

143
00:06:58,810 --> 00:07:00,570
You better not be lying, bitch.

144
00:07:18,500 --> 00:07:19,380
Bitch.

145
00:07:36,390 --> 00:07:39,440
They moved everything around in here. Damn it!

146
00:07:39,710 --> 00:07:41,160
Rick, you see it anywhere?

147
00:07:45,620 --> 00:07:46,660
No.

148
00:07:56,820 --> 00:07:58,340
Got anything on that trace?

149
00:07:59,020 --> 00:08:01,090
Latitude is somewhere north of the 10.

150
00:08:01,230 --> 00:08:02,850
I should have a rough longitude in a couple of minutes.

151
00:08:02,850 --> 00:08:05,760
Though triangulating the longitude is gonna be trickier.

152
00:08:08,480 --> 00:08:11,110
This is Dave Thompson in Jet Copter 3.

153
00:08:11,110 --> 00:08:11,920
We're seeing some congestion

154
00:08:11,920 --> 00:08:13,970
in North Hollywood at Verdugo

155
00:08:13,970 --> 00:08:16,010
around the Grant Street Elementary School.

156
00:08:16,010 --> 00:08:18,610
Senator Palmer is due to make an appearance there,

157
00:08:18,610 --> 00:08:19,430
and it looks like

158
00:08:19,430 --> 00:08:22,450
supporters and media are hoping to catch a glimpse

159
00:08:22,450 --> 00:08:24,730
of the presidential candidate, who apparently,

160
00:08:24,730 --> 00:08:26,600
is not letting this morning's incident

161
00:08:26,610 --> 00:08:28,250
interfere with his schedule.

162
00:08:28,250 --> 00:08:31,830
I don't understand the rationale behind it. No, listen to me.

163
00:08:31,830 --> 00:08:36,500
Why? Why defend something that you don't need to defend?

164
00:08:36,500 --> 00:08:38,850
Maureen Kingsley is not coming out with the story today.

165
00:08:38,850 --> 00:08:41,270
- She will. - We don't know that.

166
00:08:41,270 --> 00:08:44,000
Look, if not now, tomorrow.

167
00:08:44,010 --> 00:08:47,760
If not her, someone else. Our son is accused of murder.

168
00:08:47,770 --> 00:08:50,130
- The story's too big to hide. - Mike.

169
00:08:50,130 --> 00:08:51,180
He's right, Sherry.

170
00:08:51,180 --> 00:08:54,390
We need to control when and how this story comes out.

171
00:08:54,390 --> 00:08:58,260
One hour ago, someone tried to kill my husband.

172
00:08:58,260 --> 00:09:01,090
That bought us time and we should use it.

173
00:09:01,120 --> 00:09:04,100
The assassination attempt might even work for us

174
00:09:04,100 --> 00:09:06,400
if we break the story about Keith.

175
00:09:06,780 --> 00:09:10,460
It might put the public in a more forgiving frame of mind.

176
00:09:10,710 --> 00:09:12,750
- You're making a mistake. - It's my mistake to make.

177
00:09:12,750 --> 00:09:14,230
No, it isn't, David,

178
00:09:14,230 --> 00:09:16,570
because you didn't get here by yourself.

179
00:09:16,570 --> 00:09:18,740
Do not go against me on this, Sherry!

180
00:09:19,590 --> 00:09:20,600
Promise me.

181
00:09:22,270 --> 00:09:24,280
I can't promise you anything.

182
00:09:50,810 --> 00:09:52,910
Jack, we've got a preliminary read on the trace.

183
00:09:52,920 --> 00:09:54,430
It's a pretty big area.

184
00:09:55,990 --> 00:09:57,030
I'm listening.

185
00:09:57,500 --> 00:09:59,840
North of the 10, east of the 405.

186
00:10:03,050 --> 00:10:04,100
Did you hear me?

187
00:10:06,890 --> 00:10:07,670
Jack?

188
00:10:09,270 --> 00:10:12,470
Well, that's a start. Now get me through these cops.

189
00:10:14,580 --> 00:10:17,030
Your best bet is east on Thurston.

190
00:10:17,770 --> 00:10:19,450
But I don't think you should be moving yet.

191
00:10:19,450 --> 00:10:20,860
I'll get through the net somehow.

192
00:10:20,860 --> 00:10:22,300
Nina, just stay on that trace

193
00:10:22,300 --> 00:10:24,130
and help me find my family, please.

194
00:10:31,890 --> 00:10:34,020
Tony, open an extra socket for me on 1.

195
00:10:39,820 --> 00:10:40,840
Did you hear me?

196
00:10:40,970 --> 00:10:42,620
Come here for a second. You gotta check this out.

197
00:10:53,000 --> 00:10:53,560
What is it?

198
00:10:53,560 --> 00:10:56,470
I was checking Jamey's disk to see if I could find any e-mails.

199
00:10:56,470 --> 00:10:58,090
She was pretty careful about cleaning everything up,

200
00:10:58,090 --> 00:11:00,010
but she didn't have time to get rid of this one.

201
00:11:00,590 --> 00:11:01,720
That's from this morning.

206
00:11:02,400 --> 00:11:04,100
To an anonymous recipient.

207
00:11:04,100 --> 00:11:06,480
- What about the encryption? - I'll get Milo on that.

208
00:11:06,730 --> 00:11:08,550
But you can still see the subject.

212
00:11:09,210 --> 00:11:12,560
Ted Cofell. Find out who he is.

213
00:11:18,360 --> 00:11:19,690
I'm busy.

214
00:11:28,130 --> 00:11:28,900
Yeah?

215
00:11:28,930 --> 00:11:30,970
Yeah, Milo, I need you to do something for me.

216
00:11:30,970 --> 00:11:32,120
I'm working on this trace.

217
00:11:32,120 --> 00:11:33,500
You gonna have to do two things at once.

218
00:11:33,500 --> 00:11:35,150
I need this e-mail decrypted, all right?

219
00:11:42,540 --> 00:11:43,810
CTU, Almeida.

220
00:11:50,990 --> 00:11:51,920
Okay.

221
00:11:53,870 --> 00:11:54,790
Thanks.

222
00:12:08,260 --> 00:12:11,690
Nina, that was the clinic.

223
00:12:13,210 --> 00:12:14,480
Jamey didn't make it.

224
00:12:42,680 --> 00:12:44,280
Mom, it's clear. They're gone.

225
00:12:44,440 --> 00:12:46,330
Hello, Jack? Are you there?

226
00:12:46,630 --> 00:12:49,080
Teri, it's Nina. You okay to talk?

227
00:12:49,080 --> 00:12:50,440
I'll put you through to Jack.

228
00:12:51,180 --> 00:12:52,630
Jack, I've got Teri.

229
00:12:53,230 --> 00:12:55,650
- Teri? - Jack? Can you talk? Where are you?

230
00:12:55,650 --> 00:12:57,910
I'm on my way to get you out of there, sweetheart. You okay?

231
00:12:57,910 --> 00:13:00,360
- Yeah, I'm hanging in there. - Good, thank God.

232
00:13:00,360 --> 00:13:02,960
Nina's tracing the cellular signal to your location.

233
00:13:02,960 --> 00:13:04,220
How long will that take to find it?

234
00:13:04,220 --> 00:13:05,090
Nina?

235
00:13:06,870 --> 00:13:07,850
Twenty minutes.

236
00:13:07,850 --> 00:13:10,060
Milo's narrowed the signal to four repeater antennas

237
00:13:10,060 --> 00:13:13,330
which is still about 500 square miles.

238
00:13:13,330 --> 00:13:14,720
Oh, God.

239
00:13:14,720 --> 00:13:16,860
Teri, don't worry, we're closing in on it.

240
00:13:20,950 --> 00:13:23,250
Sir, would you please pull over to the curb.

241
00:13:23,250 --> 00:13:24,180
Jack?

242
00:13:24,420 --> 00:13:25,760
I'm still here, honey.

243
00:13:25,760 --> 00:13:28,920
Is there anything you can tell us that might help us find you?

244
00:13:28,920 --> 00:13:31,400
I know we're at least a few miles out of the city.

245
00:13:32,240 --> 00:13:34,560
This is gonna take me about a minute. Hold on.

246
00:15:09,670 --> 00:15:12,000
11-8-19. Code 6 North.

247
00:15:31,700 --> 00:15:34,860
11-8-19. North sector. Nothing so far.

248
00:15:37,200 --> 00:15:38,460
Jack, are you all right?

249
00:15:46,150 --> 00:15:49,240
- Jack? - Yeah, I'm fine.

250
00:15:50,080 --> 00:15:52,410
It would really help us out if you could tell us

251
00:15:52,410 --> 00:15:54,260
everything you know about where you are.

252
00:15:54,520 --> 00:15:55,110
I don't know much.

253
00:15:55,110 --> 00:15:56,780
They blindfolded me when they picked me up.

254
00:15:57,430 --> 00:16:00,360
- Where was that? - On Mulholland, near Coldwater.

255
00:16:00,660 --> 00:16:01,580
How long did it take for you

256
00:16:01,580 --> 00:16:03,530
to get from there to where you are now?

257
00:16:03,780 --> 00:16:05,310
I'm not sure. Half an hour?

258
00:16:06,380 --> 00:16:07,830
Surface streets or freeways?

259
00:16:07,830 --> 00:16:09,820
- Freeways, I think. - Milo.

260
00:16:09,830 --> 00:16:11,000
Already on it.

264
00:16:11,000 --> 00:16:14,220
Anything else, any sounds or smells?

265
00:16:14,290 --> 00:16:16,550
Can you hear cars or airplanes? Anything?

266
00:16:17,450 --> 00:16:18,780
No, it's pretty quiet.

267
00:16:18,780 --> 00:16:22,490
There's hills, and some eucalyptus trees.

268
00:16:23,080 --> 00:16:25,330
It may be the North Valley, somewhere inland.

269
00:16:25,330 --> 00:16:28,290
- It's pretty remote. - That helps.

270
00:16:31,260 --> 00:16:32,740
I've got it narrowed down to three sectors.

271
00:16:32,750 --> 00:16:33,770
But check it out, okay?

272
00:16:33,770 --> 00:16:36,360
The closer we get, the longer each iteration's gonna take.

273
00:16:36,930 --> 00:16:37,910
What does that mean?

274
00:16:39,560 --> 00:16:41,340
It's just techno-talk, Teri.

275
00:16:41,730 --> 00:16:43,910
Don't worry, we're making good progress.

276
00:16:50,850 --> 00:16:53,330
Jack, are you there?

277
00:16:54,380 --> 00:16:55,730
Yeah, baby, I'm still here.

278
00:16:58,990 --> 00:17:02,490
Teri, I'm gonna find you. I promise.

279
00:17:04,090 --> 00:17:05,090
I know you will.

280
00:17:07,000 --> 00:17:09,030
Nina's tracing the call right now.

281
00:17:09,630 --> 00:17:12,090
We're gonna have your location in a couple of minutes...

282
00:17:12,090 --> 00:17:14,800
...but it's important you don't hang up that phone, okay?

283
00:17:14,800 --> 00:17:17,470
Even if you can't talk, don't hang up the phone.

284
00:17:21,030 --> 00:17:24,010
Sweetheart, are you sure you're all right?

285
00:17:25,390 --> 00:17:26,860
They didn't hurt you, did they?

286
00:17:28,480 --> 00:17:31,080
I'm fine. So is Kim.

287
00:17:32,390 --> 00:17:34,820
- Is she there with you? - Yeah, she's right here.

288
00:17:38,040 --> 00:17:39,850
Put her on the phone so both of you can hear.

289
00:17:40,390 --> 00:17:41,270
Okay.

290
00:17:46,500 --> 00:17:47,270
Dad?

291
00:17:49,080 --> 00:17:50,230
Hey, sweetheart.

292
00:17:51,010 --> 00:17:52,060
You okay?

293
00:17:52,600 --> 00:17:56,260
Yeah. Who are these guys? Why are they doing this?

294
00:17:56,260 --> 00:17:56,960
I don't know honey,

295
00:17:56,960 --> 00:17:58,590
but I'm gonna find out, I promise.

296
00:17:58,660 --> 00:17:59,760
Right now I just want to make sure

297
00:17:59,760 --> 00:18:01,910
that you and mommy get home safely, okay?

298
00:18:03,660 --> 00:18:07,350
Honey, look...

299
00:18:09,300 --> 00:18:11,680
...I know I haven't always been there when you've needed me.

300
00:18:11,680 --> 00:18:13,230
Jack, you don't have to do this.

301
00:18:13,270 --> 00:18:17,940
I want both of you to know that I'm here for you now.

302
00:18:17,940 --> 00:18:20,620
I love you more than anything in the whole world...

303
00:18:20,860 --> 00:18:24,160
...and I promise you, I am gonna get you both out of there, okay?

304
00:18:26,300 --> 00:18:28,810
So no matter what happens, don't give up.

305
00:18:29,450 --> 00:18:32,180
We're a family, we're gonna get through this like a family.

306
00:18:34,440 --> 00:18:35,420
Okay?

307
00:18:37,290 --> 00:18:40,460
Sweetie, don't forget, I'm coming to get you.

308
00:18:46,290 --> 00:18:51,540
Sweetheart, stay on the phone. I'm gonna be right back.

309
00:19:21,870 --> 00:19:23,200
Honey, you still there?

310
00:19:23,200 --> 00:19:24,200
Mom, he's coming back.

311
00:19:24,200 --> 00:19:26,320
Jack, I need to get off the phone. He's coming back.

312
00:19:26,320 --> 00:19:29,070
Who's coming? Teri, keep the line open.

313
00:19:30,860 --> 00:19:32,130
Dude, it's just a phone.

314
00:19:32,130 --> 00:19:34,830
It's how Gaines gets ahold of me when he needs me.

315
00:19:35,010 --> 00:19:36,420
You already looked here.

316
00:19:39,780 --> 00:19:40,740
Where is it?

317
00:19:41,540 --> 00:19:42,850
I told you, I don't know.

318
00:19:45,930 --> 00:19:48,400
- Where's my phone? - She doesn't know either.

319
00:19:50,140 --> 00:19:52,790
Stay away from her. Stop it! What are you doing?

320
00:19:52,790 --> 00:19:54,250
Don't you touch her!

321
00:19:54,480 --> 00:19:55,470
Can't speak for yourself?

322
00:19:55,470 --> 00:19:57,110
I don't know where your stupid--

323
00:19:57,540 --> 00:19:59,290
Don't hurt her. Come on!

324
00:20:00,940 --> 00:20:02,040
Take it easy!

325
00:20:14,760 --> 00:20:16,860
- Nina, what's going on? - I don't know.

326
00:20:18,590 --> 00:20:19,780
The signal's dying.

327
00:20:37,450 --> 00:20:38,600
Who'd you call?

328
00:20:42,740 --> 00:20:43,820
Who is this?

329
00:20:44,790 --> 00:20:46,190
I'm the last thing that you'll ever see

330
00:20:46,200 --> 00:20:48,830
if anything happens to my wife or my daughter.

331
00:20:51,630 --> 00:20:53,590
- Where you going? - To tell Gaines they called for help.

332
00:20:53,590 --> 00:20:54,450
What do you think he's gonna do

333
00:20:54,450 --> 00:20:56,500
when he finds out they used your phone?

334
00:20:57,310 --> 00:21:00,300
Jack, get us out of here, please. Hurry!

335
00:21:01,370 --> 00:21:03,590
Teri, I'm going to find you. I promise.

336
00:21:03,730 --> 00:21:04,470
Teri...

337
00:21:07,230 --> 00:21:08,970
Think about it. They called on your phone.

338
00:21:20,730 --> 00:21:21,610
Nina.

339
00:21:24,100 --> 00:21:25,810
Tell me you got that trace.

340
00:21:28,920 --> 00:21:30,080
We didn't get it.

341
00:21:43,500 --> 00:21:45,400
We've located Bauer's car.

342
00:21:46,990 --> 00:21:47,870
That’s right.

343
00:22:40,780 --> 00:22:42,380
Nina, it's Jack. You still there?

344
00:22:42,380 --> 00:22:45,070
- What's happening, Jack? - I got a car.

345
00:22:45,210 --> 00:22:47,160
How close did Milo get with the trace?

346
00:22:47,970 --> 00:22:49,500
Twenty-five mile radius.

347
00:22:49,500 --> 00:22:51,600
- Damn it, that's not good enough. - Sorry.

348
00:22:51,710 --> 00:22:52,520
Look, I've gotta do something.

349
00:22:52,520 --> 00:22:54,880
Come on, Nina, anything, please help me out.

350
00:22:54,880 --> 00:22:56,020
What about Jamey?

351
00:22:56,650 --> 00:22:58,130
She didn't make it, Jack.

352
00:22:58,390 --> 00:23:02,090
I don't believe this. Nina, please, I've got to find them.

353
00:23:02,100 --> 00:23:03,090
Hold on.

354
00:23:03,280 --> 00:23:05,480
Did you get anything yet with that e-mail address?

355
00:23:05,480 --> 00:23:07,910
- Yeah, it's coming through now. - Patch into Line 2.

356
00:23:10,540 --> 00:23:11,780
Hey, Jack, it's Tony.

357
00:23:11,860 --> 00:23:13,400
I found something on Jamey's computer

358
00:23:13,400 --> 00:23:14,300
that might be a significant lead.

359
00:23:14,300 --> 00:23:15,120
What?

360
00:23:15,570 --> 00:23:18,680
The name, Ted Cofell. I did a search of LA...

361
00:23:18,690 --> 00:23:19,670
...and found Ted Cofell

362
00:23:19,670 --> 00:23:22,960
as a CEO of an investment banking firm in Burbank.

363
00:23:23,560 --> 00:23:24,430
That's it?

364
00:23:24,540 --> 00:23:25,580
- So far.. - There's something..

365
00:23:25,580 --> 00:23:28,580
Hold on. Speak one at a time. Tony, you go first.

366
00:23:28,580 --> 00:23:30,280
So far that's it.

367
00:23:30,280 --> 00:23:32,070
We have Milo decoding the e-mail right now.

368
00:23:32,070 --> 00:23:33,580
We should have more in few minutes.

369
00:23:33,580 --> 00:23:36,690
Fine. I'm gonna head to Cofell's office. What's the address?

370
00:23:37,510 --> 00:23:39,730
It's 21500 Riverside Drive.

371
00:23:39,760 --> 00:23:41,990
21500 Riverside Drive, fine.

372
00:23:41,990 --> 00:23:44,500
Tony, Gaines is gonna probably try to contact Jamey.

373
00:23:44,510 --> 00:23:47,340
He doesn't know she's dead. Make sure you keep it that way, okay?

374
00:23:47,610 --> 00:23:49,850
Nina, you help me navigate through traffic.

375
00:23:49,850 --> 00:23:50,700
All right.

379
00:24:08,550 --> 00:24:09,450
Gaines.

380
00:24:09,450 --> 00:24:10,680
Hello, Ira.

381
00:24:13,620 --> 00:24:16,320
Mr. Drazen. Where are you?

382
00:24:16,330 --> 00:24:18,290
Flying into Los Angeles.

383
00:24:18,580 --> 00:24:21,200
I'd like to know why the David Palmer situation

384
00:24:21,200 --> 00:24:23,140
hasn't been taken care of.

385
00:24:23,410 --> 00:24:26,700
I don't have to tell you, my brother and I are very disappointed.

386
00:24:26,700 --> 00:24:29,330
We had some bad luck, that's all.

387
00:24:29,480 --> 00:24:31,530
Bad luck or bad management,

388
00:24:31,530 --> 00:24:34,170
we have every reason to void the contract.

389
00:24:34,180 --> 00:24:35,520
There's no need for that.

390
00:24:35,530 --> 00:24:37,480
To have Jack Bauer and David Palmer

391
00:24:37,480 --> 00:24:39,800
in the same city on the same day...

392
00:24:39,800 --> 00:24:43,280
...and let them slip through our fingers would be intolerable.

393
00:24:44,080 --> 00:24:46,520
Don't worry. Palmer will be dead by the end of the day,

394
00:24:46,530 --> 00:24:48,040
just as we agreed.

395
00:24:48,050 --> 00:24:49,130
How?

396
00:24:49,710 --> 00:24:52,900
We still have Bauer's family as leverage.

397
00:24:53,040 --> 00:24:56,090
We'll find Bauer and use him, just like we did before.

398
00:24:56,480 --> 00:24:59,900
If plan 'A' doesn't work, you should have a plan 'B'.

399
00:24:59,900 --> 00:25:02,140
Not plan 'A' recycled.

400
00:25:02,140 --> 00:25:05,550
Like I said, we still have his family.

401
00:25:05,550 --> 00:25:09,130
If we sit tight, there's a good chance Bauer will find us.

402
00:25:09,130 --> 00:25:12,220
Then we'll make him the scapegoat, just as before.

403
00:25:12,520 --> 00:25:15,490
My brother wants me to assess the situation personally.

404
00:25:15,900 --> 00:25:20,240
I land in half an hour. I'll join you by 10:30.

405
00:25:20,240 --> 00:25:21,450
Suit yourself.

406
00:25:21,450 --> 00:25:23,540
If I don't see a substantial improvement

407
00:25:23,540 --> 00:25:25,620
in things in the next hour...

408
00:25:25,620 --> 00:25:28,950
...I'm going to ask Mr. Cofell to empty the accounts.

409
00:25:29,140 --> 00:25:30,740
You will get zero.

410
00:25:31,460 --> 00:25:32,050
Mr. Drazen--

411
00:25:32,050 --> 00:25:35,580
Ira, you may be in this for the money,

412
00:25:35,580 --> 00:25:38,390
but for my family, it's personal.

413
00:25:38,880 --> 00:25:41,800
- I realize that. - Then realize this.

414
00:25:42,220 --> 00:25:43,680
If things continue to go wrong...

415
00:25:43,680 --> 00:25:47,200
...the money isn't all you'll lose. You understand?

416
00:25:51,980 --> 00:25:54,010
- This is Sherry Palmer. - Hello, Sherry.

417
00:25:54,010 --> 00:25:57,240
I'm sure you're just as surprised as I am that I'm calling you.

418
00:25:57,240 --> 00:25:59,330
I'm only surprised you waited this long.

419
00:26:00,210 --> 00:26:01,730
I assume you're calling because

420
00:26:01,730 --> 00:26:04,240
David still plans to make the announcement...about Keith,

421
00:26:04,240 --> 00:26:05,690
and you can't stop him.

422
00:26:06,190 --> 00:26:08,580
So, now you want me to stop him?

423
00:26:09,020 --> 00:26:11,820
You've lost whatever influence you once had with David...

424
00:26:11,820 --> 00:26:14,310
...so I'm sure that's gonna be a problem.

425
00:26:14,710 --> 00:26:17,060
But you might be able to stop Maureen Kingsley.

426
00:26:17,070 --> 00:26:17,830
How?

427
00:26:18,010 --> 00:26:22,090
I don't know. I'm sure she has a weakness somewhere.

428
00:26:22,740 --> 00:26:24,900
Look, Carl, you don't need to ask me for any advice

429
00:26:24,900 --> 00:26:26,390
on stuff like this.

430
00:26:26,640 --> 00:26:27,720
As a matter of fact,

431
00:26:27,720 --> 00:26:30,450
I've already taken care of the evidence against Keith.

432
00:26:33,380 --> 00:26:37,000
Taken care of it? How?

433
00:26:37,000 --> 00:26:38,500
That's all you really need to know.

434
00:26:41,320 --> 00:26:43,560
I'm not sure I'm understanding you.

435
00:26:43,690 --> 00:26:44,890
You don't have to.

436
00:26:45,530 --> 00:26:49,070
But Sherry if we give David a way out of this,

437
00:26:49,070 --> 00:26:50,440
make sure he takes it.

438
00:27:00,840 --> 00:27:02,460
- Got it. - Send it to me.

439
00:27:02,460 --> 00:27:04,990
A wire transfer to Ira Gaines at 2:10 this morning

440
00:27:04,990 --> 00:27:07,190
from a Swiss account: $1,000,000.

441
00:27:07,190 --> 00:27:08,780
What does Cofell have to do with this?

442
00:27:10,180 --> 00:27:12,030
I don't know. Maybe it was his money.

443
00:27:12,210 --> 00:27:14,040
It makes sense. Cofell's in finance.

444
00:27:17,650 --> 00:27:18,720
Yeah, it's Jack.

445
00:27:18,970 --> 00:27:21,070
Jack, looks like we have the right Cofell.

446
00:27:21,070 --> 00:27:22,500
Good. What have you got on him?

447
00:27:24,050 --> 00:27:26,890
All right. Born in Philadelphia. Went to Colgate.

448
00:27:26,900 --> 00:27:28,940
MBA from UCLA in '88.

449
00:27:29,030 --> 00:27:30,190
Worked in investment banking,

450
00:27:30,190 --> 00:27:32,610
started his own firm about five years ago.

451
00:27:32,930 --> 00:27:35,140
Net worth is in excess of $35 million.

452
00:27:35,140 --> 00:27:37,460
Okay, good, patch me through to his office.

453
00:27:41,590 --> 00:27:42,870
Cofell Enterprises.

454
00:27:42,870 --> 00:27:44,260
Hi, is Ted there, please?

455
00:27:44,270 --> 00:27:46,290
Mr. Cofell's in a meeting. May I take a message?

456
00:27:46,290 --> 00:27:48,090
I'm a friend from business school.

457
00:27:48,090 --> 00:27:50,410
I'm in town today. I was hoping we could get together.

458
00:27:50,410 --> 00:27:53,570
Unfortunately, as soon as he's out of the meeting, he's going out of town.

459
00:27:53,570 --> 00:27:56,550
That's too bad. How much longer will he be in his office?

460
00:27:56,550 --> 00:28:00,140
He plans to leave no later than 10:00. Would you like to leave your name?

461
00:28:12,960 --> 00:28:15,550
Tell Milo to be ready in case Teri calls back.

462
00:28:17,330 --> 00:28:20,920
Nina, Division gave me a heads-up.

463
00:28:21,630 --> 00:28:23,990
They're sending in a provisional replacement for Jack.

464
00:28:26,280 --> 00:28:27,980
They didn't waste any time, did they?

465
00:28:29,720 --> 00:28:30,610
Who is it?

466
00:28:31,920 --> 00:28:33,060
Alberta Green.

467
00:28:34,750 --> 00:28:36,410
Didn't she work for you over at Division?

468
00:28:36,410 --> 00:28:39,070
Yes, she did. When's she coming?

469
00:28:39,390 --> 00:28:41,260
Scheduled to arrive at 9:45.

470
00:28:42,620 --> 00:28:43,510
Okay.

471
00:28:47,610 --> 00:28:48,310
CTU, Myers.

472
00:28:48,310 --> 00:28:50,640
Cofell's there, but he's leaving at 10:00.

473
00:28:50,640 --> 00:28:53,710
I'm passing Culver. What's the traffic like moving east?

474
00:28:53,710 --> 00:28:54,850
Hang on, I'll check.

478
00:28:57,400 --> 00:28:58,850
Jack, there's another thing.

479
00:29:00,400 --> 00:29:02,900
They're bringing in Alberta Green to run things.

480
00:29:03,690 --> 00:29:05,560
She's gonna be here in a few minutes.

481
00:29:05,710 --> 00:29:09,620
Damn it! Whatever, look, we'll deal with it.

482
00:29:09,650 --> 00:29:11,780
Tell me how to get out of this traffic.

483
00:29:11,780 --> 00:29:13,760
You'll hit gridlock in about two miles.

484
00:29:13,760 --> 00:29:14,990
How is Riverside?

485
00:29:15,210 --> 00:29:17,510
It's a little better. You might want to get off.

486
00:29:19,090 --> 00:29:22,090
I'm getting off at the next exit. I'm gonna cut over.

487
00:29:25,930 --> 00:29:28,770
Mom, tell me what happened between you and Dad.

488
00:29:30,830 --> 00:29:32,000
Why did he move out?

489
00:29:34,920 --> 00:29:36,360
Kim, let's not talk about this now.

490
00:29:36,360 --> 00:29:37,180
Why not?

491
00:29:38,580 --> 00:29:41,110
I mean, we both know there might not be a later.

492
00:29:41,550 --> 00:29:43,530
- Kim - Please, Mom.

493
00:29:45,330 --> 00:29:46,410
I wanna know.

494
00:29:57,450 --> 00:29:59,750
I think your father is the best man that I've ever known.

495
00:30:02,440 --> 00:30:06,600
But he can be difficult...

496
00:30:07,960 --> 00:30:09,510
...and his job doesn't help.

497
00:30:13,420 --> 00:30:14,240
You remember a couple of years ago,

498
00:30:14,240 --> 00:30:16,140
when he went away for a few weeks?

499
00:30:17,650 --> 00:30:21,170
Yeah, for some.. training thing.

500
00:30:22,800 --> 00:30:25,400
That's what he told us, but I'm sure it was a mission.

501
00:30:27,340 --> 00:30:30,020
He wouldn't say, and maybe he probably couldn't.

502
00:30:31,740 --> 00:30:34,300
Anyway, when he came back, he was...

503
00:30:36,850 --> 00:30:37,350
...different.

504
00:30:37,350 --> 00:30:41,910
He was distant and preoccupied...

505
00:30:41,910 --> 00:30:45,430
...and other times he was just angry.

506
00:30:48,240 --> 00:30:50,350
He did everything he could to keep it from you...

507
00:30:52,980 --> 00:30:56,980
...but things between us weren't so great.

508
00:30:59,460 --> 00:31:01,770
I suppose I could have been more patient.

509
00:31:06,720 --> 00:31:09,910
So we decided to try being apart.

510
00:31:12,850 --> 00:31:14,130
But it didn't work.

511
00:31:16,070 --> 00:31:16,920
No.

512
00:31:21,430 --> 00:31:22,290
Good.

513
00:31:25,580 --> 00:31:28,540
I just want us to be together again.

514
00:31:43,380 --> 00:31:44,990
Cofell is taking a private plane

515
00:31:44,990 --> 00:31:47,830
and we got a copy of his flight plan from the FAA.

516
00:31:48,160 --> 00:31:49,490
He's going to Denver.

517
00:31:50,780 --> 00:31:52,720
- What does that tell us? - We're not sure.

518
00:31:52,730 --> 00:31:54,500
We're checking people in the Denver area

519
00:31:54,930 --> 00:31:56,870
who have known terrorist connections.

520
00:31:57,340 --> 00:31:59,040
So far we haven't got much.

521
00:32:15,420 --> 00:32:17,830
- Hello, Nina. - Hello, Alberta.

522
00:32:17,830 --> 00:32:20,500
Nice to see you. You know why I'm here.

523
00:32:20,500 --> 00:32:21,360
Yes.

524
00:32:23,480 --> 00:32:25,340
Gather everyone around, will you?

525
00:32:27,510 --> 00:32:30,240
Could everyone stop what they're doing for just a moment?

526
00:32:30,360 --> 00:32:31,750
I have something to tell you.

527
00:32:32,390 --> 00:32:34,750
I'd like to introduce you to Alberta Green.

528
00:32:35,320 --> 00:32:38,250
Jack Bauer has been relieved of his duties here indefinitely.

529
00:32:39,480 --> 00:32:43,770
In the meantime, Alberta's been appointed Acting Director of CTU.

530
00:32:45,810 --> 00:32:49,450
Good morning. Things have been out of control here today.

531
00:32:49,780 --> 00:32:52,470
Starting now, they're back in control.

532
00:32:53,470 --> 00:32:54,810
Most of you know an attempt

533
00:32:54,810 --> 00:32:58,080
was made on Senator Palmer at 8:00 this morning.

534
00:32:58,080 --> 00:32:59,450
You may not know

535
00:32:59,450 --> 00:33:03,220
that Jack Bauer was apparently involved in that attempt.

536
00:33:03,800 --> 00:33:05,850
The nature of his involvement isn't clear...

537
00:33:05,870 --> 00:33:09,010
but he has escaped custody, and is considered a fugitive.

538
00:33:09,340 --> 00:33:11,220
We therefore have two objectives:

539
00:33:11,430 --> 00:33:14,880
Find Jack Bauer, and make a quick and accurate assessment

540
00:33:14,880 --> 00:33:17,830
of the threat, if any, facing Senator Palmer.

541
00:33:19,250 --> 00:33:22,400
I know most of you have been up more than 24 hours.

542
00:33:22,720 --> 00:33:23,810
Too bad.

543
00:33:24,820 --> 00:33:28,190
Nobody so much as yawns until we accomplish our objective.

544
00:33:28,220 --> 00:33:29,400
If anyone has a problem with that,

545
00:33:29,400 --> 00:33:31,440
now would be a good time to resign.

546
00:33:38,100 --> 00:33:40,650
Good. Let's get back to work.

547
00:33:41,200 --> 00:33:42,310
Specific assignments

548
00:33:42,310 --> 00:33:45,300
will be confirmed or revised within the hour.

549
00:33:53,520 --> 00:33:54,650
Obviously this is awkward,

550
00:33:54,650 --> 00:33:56,730
but we'll get through this. We're pros.

551
00:33:58,050 --> 00:33:58,950
Of course.

552
00:34:00,230 --> 00:34:01,290
We'll talk later.

553
00:34:12,980 --> 00:34:15,630
Let me see that.

554
00:34:15,630 --> 00:34:16,640
This is terrific.

555
00:34:16,640 --> 00:34:18,080
Hold on a minute.

556
00:34:19,860 --> 00:34:21,690
Is it true you played basketball?

557
00:34:21,730 --> 00:34:23,830
I sure did. Georgetown.

558
00:34:24,110 --> 00:34:26,460
My daddy says Georgetown sucks!

559
00:34:27,400 --> 00:34:29,500
I need to have a little talk with your daddy.

560
00:34:29,960 --> 00:34:31,060
My daddy also says

561
00:34:31,060 --> 00:34:33,660
there will never be a black president in this country.

562
00:34:33,900 --> 00:34:34,700
Ever.

563
00:34:37,180 --> 00:34:38,950
Would you give your daddy a message for me?

564
00:34:41,120 --> 00:34:43,560
You tell him I understand where he's coming from,

565
00:34:44,410 --> 00:34:45,470
but he's wrong.

566
00:34:46,310 --> 00:34:47,530
and I'm gonna prove it.

567
00:34:49,410 --> 00:34:51,590
- Tell him that, okay? - Okay.

568
00:34:52,830 --> 00:34:54,530
I have Frank Ames on the phone.

569
00:34:55,170 --> 00:34:57,120
- What does he want? - He wouldn't tell me.

570
00:34:57,270 --> 00:34:58,420
I'll call him back.

571
00:34:58,750 --> 00:35:00,160
He said it was urgent.

572
00:35:02,560 --> 00:35:05,830
He's your biggest contributor. You can't just blow him off.

573
00:35:11,790 --> 00:35:15,680
I am very sorry. Would you excuse me for a minute?

574
00:35:15,680 --> 00:35:17,510
Ok.

575
00:35:18,650 --> 00:35:20,980
Senator.

576
00:35:22,580 --> 00:35:24,300
Here you go.

577
00:35:25,110 --> 00:35:27,300
Frank? This is kind of a bad time.

578
00:35:27,300 --> 00:35:29,200
Well, it's about to get worse.

579
00:35:29,800 --> 00:35:30,690
What do you mean?

580
00:35:30,750 --> 00:35:32,310
I just got out of a meeting with Carl,

581
00:35:32,310 --> 00:35:34,060
Phil Tuttle and Bob Jorgensen.

582
00:35:34,060 --> 00:35:35,230
A meeting about what?

583
00:35:35,360 --> 00:35:38,140
George Ferragamo, your son's therapist.

584
00:35:38,420 --> 00:35:41,540
Freshmen and the transfers from the Dufton school are

585
00:35:42,080 --> 00:35:43,330
I know the three of you

586
00:35:43,330 --> 00:35:45,390
have given a lot of money to my campaign

587
00:35:45,390 --> 00:35:47,830
but I'm not sure that make my son's therapist your business.

588
00:35:47,830 --> 00:35:50,020
It is when he's accusing your son of murder.

589
00:35:50,910 --> 00:35:54,810
He's a problem, and Tuttle and Jorgensen don't like problems.

590
00:35:54,990 --> 00:35:57,910
They told Carl to get rid of it, permanently.

591
00:35:59,150 --> 00:36:01,360
I've played hardball all my life, but this...

592
00:36:01,360 --> 00:36:03,520
What are you trying to say? They told Carl to

593
00:36:03,520 --> 00:36:07,900
Listen, I am washing my hands of this and your whole campaign.

594
00:36:07,900 --> 00:36:10,500
- Frank! - I am out of it, David.

595
00:36:15,750 --> 00:36:16,780
What was that about?

596
00:36:19,860 --> 00:36:23,180
I need to talk to Carl, now.

597
00:36:50,410 --> 00:36:51,660
You wanted to see me?

598
00:36:56,490 --> 00:36:58,530
- Give us five minutes. - Certainly.

599
00:37:02,180 --> 00:37:03,470
Alberta, I don't know where Jack is.

600
00:37:03,470 --> 00:37:05,380
I haven't talked to him since this morning.

601
00:37:05,430 --> 00:37:07,300
Since he escaped from custody with a hostage?

602
00:37:07,300 --> 00:37:09,510
- That's right. - I'm not sure I believe you.

603
00:37:13,750 --> 00:37:15,520
If you tell me where he is

604
00:37:15,760 --> 00:37:18,510
I'll do what I can to make sure nothing heavy falls on you.

605
00:37:18,750 --> 00:37:20,090
I told you, I don't know.

606
00:37:23,570 --> 00:37:24,150
From what I've heard,

607
00:37:24,150 --> 00:37:26,760
There are very few secrets between you and Jack.

608
00:37:27,430 --> 00:37:30,150
Jack doesn't trust anyone, including me.

609
00:37:31,050 --> 00:37:31,970
Getting involved with Jack

610
00:37:31,970 --> 00:37:34,210
was one of the biggest mistakes I've ever made.

611
00:37:35,150 --> 00:37:36,810
Not that I'm judging you, Nina,

612
00:37:38,080 --> 00:37:40,010
but there's a right way to do these things.

613
00:37:40,570 --> 00:37:42,870
Let them screw you, don't let them screw you over.

614
00:37:43,880 --> 00:37:45,210
If you don't have any more pearls of wisdom,

615
00:37:45,210 --> 00:37:47,020
I'd like to get back to work.

616
00:37:48,050 --> 00:37:49,280
By all means.

617
00:37:54,110 --> 00:37:55,050
Cofell Enterprises.

618
00:37:55,050 --> 00:37:57,680
Hey, it's Ted's friend from business school again.

619
00:37:57,680 --> 00:37:59,230
Look, I'm sorry, but I'm in the building.

620
00:37:59,230 --> 00:38:01,630
I was hoping I could come up and say a quick hello.

621
00:38:02,020 --> 00:38:03,900
Is Ted gonna be there for a few more minutes?

622
00:38:03,900 --> 00:38:05,870
I'm sorry, sir, he's on his way out.

623
00:38:06,990 --> 00:38:08,820
What floor is Cofell Enterprises on?

624
00:38:09,160 --> 00:38:10,160
Fourteenth.

625
00:38:10,820 --> 00:38:11,690
Thank you.

626
00:38:20,020 --> 00:38:22,660
- Nancy, could you call my car please? - Okay.

627
00:38:23,020 --> 00:38:25,040
I should head to the airport a little early today.

628
00:38:25,220 --> 00:38:27,240
The radio said the traffic was a little slow.

629
00:38:27,310 --> 00:38:29,600
Of course. Mr. Cofell,

630
00:38:30,030 --> 00:38:32,660
a friend of yours from business school is on the way to see you.

631
00:38:33,610 --> 00:38:36,130
- On his way up now? - I tried to stop him.

632
00:38:36,630 --> 00:38:37,720
He say who it was?

633
00:38:37,720 --> 00:38:39,100
It's funny, he didn't give his name.

634
00:38:39,100 --> 00:38:41,020
He's probably trying to sell you something.

635
00:38:41,020 --> 00:38:42,260
Don't give him my cell number.

636
00:38:42,260 --> 00:38:43,600
I won't, have a good trip.

637
00:38:43,600 --> 00:38:44,540
Thank you.

638
00:38:44,540 --> 00:38:45,970
- Don't forget your phone. - Great.

639
00:38:47,190 --> 00:38:48,310
Hey Louis, this is Tracy.

640
00:38:48,310 --> 00:38:50,950
I just wanted to let you know that Mr. Cofell is on his way down.

641
00:38:51,260 --> 00:38:53,550
Excuse me, where's Mr. Cofell?

642
00:38:53,760 --> 00:38:55,910
I'm so sorry, he just stepped into the elevator.

643
00:38:59,120 --> 00:39:01,160
Where was he going? Down to the parking garage?

644
00:39:01,280 --> 00:39:02,490
It's all right. Never mind.

645
00:39:17,170 --> 00:39:18,220
There's nothing to worry about.

646
00:39:18,220 --> 00:39:19,210
There's a 30-second reset,

647
00:39:19,210 --> 00:39:21,240
then we'll continue down automatically.

648
00:39:21,810 --> 00:39:24,010
It's probably a false alarm anyhow.

649
00:40:08,490 --> 00:40:11,340
Excuse me, are you Mr. Cofell's driver?

650
00:40:11,340 --> 00:40:13,620
- Yeah, that's right. - I'm a Federal Agent.

651
00:40:14,300 --> 00:40:17,050
- Where are you going today? - To the airport.

652
00:40:17,060 --> 00:40:18,300
On what business?

653
00:40:19,060 --> 00:40:20,590
Look, I'm just his driver.

654
00:40:20,890 --> 00:40:23,230
- Is there a problem here? - Come with me a second.

655
00:40:38,330 --> 00:40:41,760
- Thank you. - Have a nice day, Mr. Cofell.

656
00:40:44,370 --> 00:40:45,380
Valet.

657
00:40:55,740 --> 00:40:57,570
Mark, could you turn the air on back here, please?

658
00:41:22,280 --> 00:41:23,890
Then they began to laugh.

659
00:41:23,890 --> 00:41:27,620
They began to say things like, "You remember him, don't you?"

660
00:41:27,620 --> 00:41:30,770
Doesn't he live with you? Yeah, sure he does.

661
00:41:40,050 --> 00:41:41,180
Are you okay?

662
00:41:41,250 --> 00:41:43,250
Yeah, I'm fine. It's nothing.

663
00:41:43,530 --> 00:41:46,310
- He hurt you, didn't he? - No, honey. I'm fine.

