5
00:00:25,880 --> 00:00:30,880
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

6
00:00:25,880 --> 00:00:30,880
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

7
00:00:25,880 --> 00:00:30,880
{\an5}{\pos(145,252)}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

8
00:00:26,380 --> 00:00:30,880
{\pos(67,248)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

9
00:00:26,380 --> 00:00:30,880
{\pos(67,248)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

10
00:00:26,380 --> 00:00:30,880
{\pos(58,238)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

11
00:00:26,380 --> 00:00:30,880
{\pos(84,248)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

14
00:00:32,100 --> 00:01:07,100
{\an9}m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

15
00:00:31,600 --> 00:01:07,100
{\an2}{\pos(26,248)}m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

23
00:01:19,230 --> 00:01:20,380
Authorization?

24
00:01:20,470 --> 00:01:22,890
Bauer, 4-3-9-3, CTU.

31
00:01:58,080 --> 00:01:59,150
Okay, we're on it.

32
00:01:59,150 --> 00:02:01,380
Get back to me as soon as you've got a match.

33
00:02:12,980 --> 00:02:15,330
- Bauer. - Jack, I talked to her.

34
00:02:16,570 --> 00:02:18,180
Thank god. What did she say?

35
00:02:18,310 --> 00:02:20,410
She and Janet went to some party.

36
00:02:20,900 --> 00:02:22,130
So, you gonna go pick them up?

37
00:02:22,130 --> 00:02:23,690
No, I don't know where she is, she wouldn't tell me.

38
00:02:23,690 --> 00:02:24,470
What?

39
00:02:25,790 --> 00:02:27,270
I don't know, maybe I'm being paranoid,

40
00:02:27,270 --> 00:02:29,920
but she sounded... different, I don't know...

41
00:02:29,920 --> 00:02:33,140
She told me that she loved me before she hung up.

42
00:02:33,150 --> 00:02:34,470
That's not Kim.

43
00:02:34,520 --> 00:02:36,100
Well, she knows she's going to get grounded.

44
00:02:36,100 --> 00:02:38,130
She's just trying to reduce the sentence.

45
00:02:38,150 --> 00:02:39,550
Yeah, you're probably right.

46
00:02:39,800 --> 00:02:42,320
How are you? Are you okay?

47
00:02:42,430 --> 00:02:44,440
Yeah, yeah, I'm fine, um...

48
00:02:44,780 --> 00:02:46,680
Look, is that guy York still with you?

49
00:02:46,890 --> 00:02:48,420
Yeah. He's gonna take me home now.

50
00:02:48,430 --> 00:02:50,420
Don't you think you should wait by Janet's car?

51
00:02:50,970 --> 00:02:52,010
I mean, who knows what kind of shape

52
00:02:52,010 --> 00:02:54,100
the girls are gonna be in when they get dropped off.

53
00:02:54,210 --> 00:02:57,670
Well no, Alan doesn't seem to think that's necessary.

54
00:02:58,220 --> 00:03:00,010
Why don't you put Alan on the phone?

55
00:03:00,650 --> 00:03:01,890
Jack. Don't do this.

56
00:03:01,890 --> 00:03:03,620
Teri, just put him on the phone.

57
00:03:04,180 --> 00:03:05,430
Okay.

58
00:03:06,420 --> 00:03:09,190
Alan, my husband would like to speak with you.

59
00:03:11,480 --> 00:03:14,020
- Hi, this is Alan. - Alan, Jack Bauer.

60
00:03:14,620 --> 00:03:16,850
I can't thank you enough for helping us out with this.

61
00:03:18,050 --> 00:03:19,930
Yeah, I'm just glad the girls are with each other.

62
00:03:19,930 --> 00:03:21,890
Yeah, me too. Look, I'm stuck at work.

63
00:03:21,890 --> 00:03:22,900
I'm in a bit of an emergency.

64
00:03:22,900 --> 00:03:24,860
- Yeah, Teri said-- - I would really appreciate it...

65
00:03:24,860 --> 00:03:25,750
if you wouldn't mind hanging

66
00:03:25,760 --> 00:03:27,950
out at the store and waiting for them to return.

67
00:03:28,940 --> 00:03:30,350
The thing is, I don't think they're

68
00:03:30,350 --> 00:03:32,320
going to be back for at least a couple of hours.

69
00:03:32,320 --> 00:03:34,610
The thing is, Alan, it's a pretty rough neighborhood.

70
00:03:34,610 --> 00:03:36,830
And I would hate for there to be a problem when they return.

71
00:03:38,040 --> 00:03:39,060
Sure, we'll stay.

72
00:03:39,060 --> 00:03:40,290
Thank you.

73
00:03:41,380 --> 00:03:42,550
Thank you.

74
00:03:43,150 --> 00:03:45,720
You've got to be kidding me. We had a deal, Mandy.

75
00:03:46,400 --> 00:03:47,720
You promised to deliver Belkin's

76
00:03:47,720 --> 00:03:51,110
ID in exchange for $1 million, now she wants to double it?

77
00:03:51,110 --> 00:03:53,530
I apologize. She doesn't know how this works.

78
00:03:53,530 --> 00:03:54,650
This is your fault!

79
00:03:54,650 --> 00:03:57,110
You should've never involved an amateur in our business.

80
00:03:57,110 --> 00:03:58,410
If I'm such an amateur, how--

81
00:04:00,140 --> 00:04:01,960
I'm just trying to get us more money.

82
00:04:01,960 --> 00:04:04,420
There is no money.

83
00:04:04,950 --> 00:04:06,120
Not anymore.

84
00:04:06,120 --> 00:04:09,190
Ira, don't turn this into something else. I will fix it.

85
00:04:14,040 --> 00:04:14,640
What?

86
00:04:17,300 --> 00:04:19,600
No, we don't have it yet.

87
00:04:19,600 --> 00:04:20,460
Yes.

88
00:04:20,460 --> 00:04:22,210
No, of course.

89
00:04:22,900 --> 00:04:26,040
I will get back to you as soon as we're ready.

90
00:04:33,730 --> 00:04:36,790
Talk to her. Explain what I do.

91
00:04:37,800 --> 00:04:39,200
I will, but our deal stands.

92
00:04:39,200 --> 00:04:40,340
Take care of it!

93
00:04:52,920 --> 00:04:54,830
I need to get out of here, my friend.

94
00:04:56,140 --> 00:04:57,090
It'll just be a little longer.

96
00:05:10,860 --> 00:05:11,930
We've been getting death threats

97
00:05:11,930 --> 00:05:14,630
since my husband announced his candidacy.

98
00:05:14,630 --> 00:05:16,840
What is different about this one?

99
00:05:16,840 --> 00:05:19,380
Well, I'm not privy to that kind of information.

100
00:05:21,090 --> 00:05:24,090
All I can tell you is that my unit is only called in

101
00:05:24,090 --> 00:05:26,190
when the threat becomes more serious.

102
00:05:26,240 --> 00:05:28,440
Then why did you let him walk out on his own?

103
00:05:29,300 --> 00:05:31,200
We will find him, Mrs. Palmer.

104
00:05:34,890 --> 00:05:36,600
I know. I'm sorry.

105
00:05:36,650 --> 00:05:38,640
We're grateful to have you here.

106
00:05:39,760 --> 00:05:41,400
He's not down in the lobby. I looked everywhere.

107
00:05:41,400 --> 00:05:43,450
Keith, you shouldn't be leaving the suites.

108
00:05:43,450 --> 00:05:45,140
Let these men do their job.

109
00:05:45,410 --> 00:05:47,740
Look, there's an all-night coffee shop a couple of blocks down.

110
00:05:47,740 --> 00:05:48,980
I bet he just wanted to be by himself.

111
00:05:48,980 --> 00:05:49,990
- I'm going to go get him. - No.

112
00:05:49,990 --> 00:05:52,350
Keith, Keith. You're not going anywhere.

113
00:05:52,600 --> 00:05:55,280
Secret Service knows this city a lot better than we do.

114
00:05:55,720 --> 00:05:56,760
- Mom, I'll be right back. - No.

115
00:05:56,760 --> 00:05:59,570
I'm sorry, son. We need you to stay here.

116
00:06:00,540 --> 00:06:01,220
Why?

117
00:06:01,270 --> 00:06:03,080
We treat a threat on a candidate's life

118
00:06:03,120 --> 00:06:04,940
as a threat to the entire family.

119
00:06:05,180 --> 00:06:06,910
We need to protect you as well.

120
00:06:07,800 --> 00:06:08,880
Keith.

121
00:06:10,070 --> 00:06:12,070
Your father's going to be fine.

122
00:06:41,600 --> 00:06:42,580
Yeah?

123
00:06:42,740 --> 00:06:44,830
I need an update on the Bauer girl.

124
00:06:45,020 --> 00:06:47,650
Everything's copa. We're just waiting for you.

125
00:06:47,970 --> 00:06:49,440
I'm running a little late.

126
00:06:49,440 --> 00:06:50,730
We're not going anywhere.

127
00:06:52,090 --> 00:06:53,920
That's right, you're not.

128
00:06:55,140 --> 00:06:56,500
She's in a lot of pain, man,

129
00:06:56,500 --> 00:06:57,650
I think you broke her arm.

130
00:06:58,390 --> 00:07:00,900
You think so? Should we take her to the hospital

131
00:07:00,900 --> 00:07:02,260
to get some X-rays?

132
00:07:04,250 --> 00:07:06,990
Gaines is running late. Gonna smoke another "J". You want one?

133
00:07:07,800 --> 00:07:08,770
Sure.

134
00:07:15,990 --> 00:07:16,900
My arm!

135
00:07:16,900 --> 00:07:18,890
Try not to move.

136
00:07:20,730 --> 00:07:23,340
Dan, please. She needs to see a doctor.

137
00:07:29,160 --> 00:07:30,850
At least give her something, man.

138
00:07:30,880 --> 00:07:32,720
I'm not wasting my stash on her.

139
00:07:36,910 --> 00:07:39,420
So, what, is Dan the boss and you have to do everything he says?

140
00:07:55,710 --> 00:07:56,750
I thought I told you!

141
00:08:01,510 --> 00:08:02,850
Don't press me, man.

142
00:08:08,970 --> 00:08:10,490
I should've never used you.

143
00:08:26,960 --> 00:08:28,240
You're going to give her that?

144
00:08:29,530 --> 00:08:31,290
Want me to take away the pain, or not?

147
00:10:05,510 --> 00:10:07,510
Hey, this is a private lot, homie.

148
00:10:07,960 --> 00:10:09,250
You got to pay to park here.

149
00:10:09,600 --> 00:10:10,620
I see.

150
00:10:11,300 --> 00:10:12,660
And you're the attendant?

151
00:10:13,150 --> 00:10:17,630
That's right. It's going to cost you $100. So give it up.

152
00:10:28,360 --> 00:10:31,170
You're that dude! Palmer!

153
00:10:31,170 --> 00:10:34,520
- No, that's not me. - Yeah, it's you! Damn!

154
00:10:34,520 --> 00:10:36,350
Dude, this guy's running for president.

155
00:10:36,350 --> 00:10:37,760
I seen him on TV.

156
00:10:39,240 --> 00:10:40,400
Yeah?

157
00:10:40,830 --> 00:10:43,520
Yeah? Yeah, yeah... yeah!

158
00:10:44,000 --> 00:10:46,820
What you going to do for me, Mr. President?

159
00:10:47,250 --> 00:10:48,640
See, that's your problem.

160
00:10:49,430 --> 00:10:51,090
You want everyone else to do the work.

161
00:10:51,920 --> 00:10:53,360
What are you going to do for yourselves?

162
00:10:54,460 --> 00:10:58,070
See, man, all y'all, you all got the same rap.

163
00:10:59,460 --> 00:11:00,930
Keep going like this

164
00:11:01,860 --> 00:11:04,160
and you'll be dead in five years.

165
00:11:04,610 --> 00:11:06,370
Man, like you know my life.

166
00:11:06,540 --> 00:11:07,920
More than you think.

168
00:12:03,730 --> 00:12:05,070
CTU, Myers.

169
00:12:05,080 --> 00:12:07,410
- Hey, it's me. - Jack, where are you?

170
00:12:07,750 --> 00:12:08,860
I'm about a block away.

171
00:12:09,180 --> 00:12:10,470
I need you to print up a hard copy

172
00:12:10,480 --> 00:12:13,270
of Tony's passenger breakdown, put it on my desk.

173
00:12:13,370 --> 00:12:14,020
Okay.

174
00:12:14,020 --> 00:12:17,100
I want you wait there for me, I wanna talk to you but not front the others.

175
00:12:17,100 --> 00:12:18,560
- Sure. - Great, I'll be there in a minute.

176
00:12:18,560 --> 00:12:20,390
- Okay. Bye. - Bye.

177
00:12:49,410 --> 00:12:50,620
Keep working.

178
00:12:51,360 --> 00:12:53,890
Has Division responded to the two dead agents?

179
00:12:53,890 --> 00:12:55,320
Yeah, they are picking them up now.

180
00:12:55,320 --> 00:12:56,450
Good.

181
00:12:56,950 --> 00:12:59,190
- Anyone we know? - Someone we know.

182
00:13:00,480 --> 00:13:02,090
I'm afraid it was Richard Walsh.

183
00:13:04,180 --> 00:13:06,310
I'm sorry, Jamey, I know what he meant to you.

184
00:13:09,230 --> 00:13:11,950
What is going on? Does this have anything to do with Palmer?

185
00:13:11,950 --> 00:13:13,600
That's what we got to find out. Look,

186
00:13:13,600 --> 00:13:16,170
I don't have time to go into all the details

187
00:13:16,930 --> 00:13:19,160
but I've got to put you in a very difficult position.

188
00:13:19,160 --> 00:13:20,870
You're the only person I can trust.

189
00:13:21,560 --> 00:13:22,870
What do you mean?

190
00:13:23,650 --> 00:13:25,890
Walsh said that we've got a problem on the inside.

191
00:13:25,890 --> 00:13:27,680
He told me to talk only to you.

192
00:13:32,540 --> 00:13:34,520
This is the keycard I sent you.

193
00:13:35,040 --> 00:13:37,380
On it is pertinent information to the hit on Palmer.

194
00:13:37,380 --> 00:13:40,110
How long is it going to take to pull all the data off of it?

195
00:13:41,140 --> 00:13:44,570
Depending on the kind of encryption, it could take hours.

196
00:13:45,120 --> 00:13:46,860
Palmer's day starts at 6:00.

197
00:13:51,220 --> 00:13:52,630
I need it before then.

198
00:13:57,320 --> 00:13:58,810
One more thing.

199
00:13:59,070 --> 00:14:01,000
I need to be absolutely certain

200
00:14:01,010 --> 00:14:03,220
that it was Nina's computer that burned that card.

201
00:14:03,220 --> 00:14:04,190
Why?

202
00:14:05,550 --> 00:14:07,250
Because if it was, she's dirty.

203
00:14:09,580 --> 00:14:12,080
I'll need a few minutes alone at her workstation.

204
00:14:12,240 --> 00:14:13,420
Fine, you got it.

205
00:14:15,610 --> 00:14:16,930
Did you cut yourself?

206
00:14:19,430 --> 00:14:21,500
Yeah. What are you working on?

207
00:14:21,500 --> 00:14:22,920
I gave Nina the passenger list,

208
00:14:22,920 --> 00:14:25,010
I was just cross-checking everything else we got.

209
00:14:25,550 --> 00:14:27,720
Good. I'll be down in a sec.

210
00:14:38,680 --> 00:14:40,490
Will you tell me why you were at Dunlop Plaza?

211
00:14:40,490 --> 00:14:42,150
I had a meeting with Walsh.

212
00:14:42,250 --> 00:14:44,200
- Is that the passenger list? - Yes.

213
00:14:45,510 --> 00:14:46,660
Anything unusual?

214
00:14:47,430 --> 00:14:49,800
There's one red flag. A man in first class.

215
00:14:50,140 --> 00:14:51,570
His information is inconsistent.

216
00:14:51,570 --> 00:14:53,160
I'm trying to piece it together now.

217
00:14:53,640 --> 00:14:54,620
Good.

218
00:14:58,610 --> 00:15:00,810
Jack. Look, I don't wanna tell you how to do your job,

219
00:15:01,290 --> 00:15:02,040
but you're leaving without letting me

220
00:15:02,040 --> 00:15:04,500
know where you are, holding back information.

221
00:15:04,710 --> 00:15:06,580
How can I help you without you letting me?

222
00:15:14,090 --> 00:15:16,300
Do you think that it's possible

223
00:15:16,920 --> 00:15:19,290
that someone from within the agency

224
00:15:19,350 --> 00:15:21,200
is behind the hit on Palmer?

225
00:15:22,530 --> 00:15:24,090
Anything is possible.

226
00:15:24,440 --> 00:15:26,210
Do you have a lead?

227
00:15:29,690 --> 00:15:31,770
No, not really.

228
00:15:33,580 --> 00:15:34,680
No.

229
00:15:35,070 --> 00:15:37,330
Why do I feel like you're not telling me the truth?

230
00:15:42,080 --> 00:15:43,140
Jack, if you've got something,

231
00:15:43,140 --> 00:15:45,030
share it with me, I'll work it up with you.

232
00:15:45,030 --> 00:15:46,620
No, I'm....

233
00:15:48,370 --> 00:15:50,540
I'm just thinking out loud.

234
00:15:51,120 --> 00:15:52,630
Okay, fine.

235
00:15:56,090 --> 00:15:57,370
Is there anything else?

236
00:15:59,020 --> 00:16:00,080
No.

237
00:16:02,330 --> 00:16:03,620
Actually, there is.

238
00:16:07,800 --> 00:16:09,320
Are you seeing Tony?

239
00:16:13,330 --> 00:16:14,270
Why?

240
00:16:18,850 --> 00:16:20,240
Is it serious?

241
00:16:20,880 --> 00:16:22,190
What is this, Jack?

242
00:16:23,170 --> 00:16:24,970
What do you want to know, am I over you?

243
00:16:25,360 --> 00:16:27,410
Why are we talking about this now?

244
00:16:27,410 --> 00:16:30,530
I'm just trying to understand why he's been giving me such a hard time.

245
00:16:30,760 --> 00:16:33,080
I can't answer that for you.

246
00:16:40,260 --> 00:16:41,490
Hold on.

247
00:16:44,950 --> 00:16:45,860
Yeah?

248
00:16:46,260 --> 00:16:47,690
I confirmed that the file on the keycard

249
00:16:47,690 --> 00:16:49,580
definitely came from Nina's computer.

250
00:16:56,450 --> 00:16:57,510
Okay, thank you.

251
00:17:02,710 --> 00:17:03,890
It's Division.

252
00:17:04,870 --> 00:17:07,280
They want the passenger breakdown. Please send it to them.

253
00:17:08,500 --> 00:17:09,520
Sure.

254
00:17:14,280 --> 00:17:15,700
By the way, your wife called.

255
00:17:36,140 --> 00:17:37,790
- Bauer. - This is Data Services.

256
00:17:37,790 --> 00:17:40,240
You called in a thumbprint for an ID match?

257
00:17:40,240 --> 00:17:41,010
Yeah.

258
00:17:41,010 --> 00:17:43,020
We checked every database we have.

259
00:17:43,110 --> 00:17:45,290
Nothing. Either this guy doesn't exist,

260
00:17:45,290 --> 00:17:47,600
or his identity has been wiped off the record.

261
00:17:47,790 --> 00:17:48,860
Thank you.

262
00:18:03,520 --> 00:18:04,820
It'll be better for both of us..

263
00:18:04,820 --> 00:18:08,320
Better than what, Bridget? Where is the ID?

264
00:18:08,320 --> 00:18:10,710
Look, this is not some secret I'm keeping from you.

265
00:18:10,720 --> 00:18:12,350
This is for both of us.

266
00:18:14,040 --> 00:18:15,570
Do you want to get both of us killed?

267
00:18:15,580 --> 00:18:17,750
They hired you to blow up a plane.

268
00:18:17,970 --> 00:18:20,980
Another $1 million doesn't mean anything to these people.

269
00:18:20,980 --> 00:18:22,250
You're wrong. Money is the only thing that

270
00:18:22,250 --> 00:18:23,860
these people care about.

271
00:18:28,290 --> 00:18:29,970
Let's do it anyway.

272
00:18:32,050 --> 00:18:33,780
You know he can't hurt us.

273
00:18:36,960 --> 00:18:38,130
Baby.

274
00:18:40,730 --> 00:18:43,520
Nobody can hurt us.

275
00:18:46,350 --> 00:18:48,010
$1 million for you.

276
00:18:49,240 --> 00:18:50,990
$1 million for me.

277
00:18:53,170 --> 00:18:55,180
Don't you like the way that sounds?

278
00:19:10,180 --> 00:19:11,360
Okay.

279
00:19:14,960 --> 00:19:16,920
We are going to do this your way.

280
00:19:17,160 --> 00:19:18,440
Great.

281
00:19:18,750 --> 00:19:20,650
- Okay, let's tell him. - No.

282
00:19:21,320 --> 00:19:23,070
It'll be better if I do it myself.

283
00:19:27,030 --> 00:19:28,960
You're always looking out for me.

284
00:19:35,110 --> 00:19:37,160
I know you're just helping.

285
00:19:40,180 --> 00:19:41,470
What happened?

286
00:19:42,070 --> 00:19:43,290
Do you remember anything?

287
00:19:43,870 --> 00:19:44,920
Yeah.

288
00:19:46,070 --> 00:19:50,910
We were at the furniture store, dancing. Where's Dan?

289
00:19:53,340 --> 00:19:54,650
Dan broke your arm.

290
00:19:55,530 --> 00:19:57,010
Break my arm?

291
00:19:57,300 --> 00:19:59,700
- Dan likes me. - Yeah? Look at it.

292
00:20:06,150 --> 00:20:07,270
Come on.

293
00:20:10,160 --> 00:20:13,540
Listen to me. This is serious. We're being kidnapped.

294
00:20:13,550 --> 00:20:16,610
We need to escape. Can you walk?

295
00:20:18,390 --> 00:20:19,310
I guess.

296
00:20:19,310 --> 00:20:21,410
Okay. Come on.

297
00:20:27,260 --> 00:20:30,740
Get ready. When I say go, we go.

298
00:20:30,970 --> 00:20:32,100
Go where?

299
00:20:32,700 --> 00:20:34,240
Just stay with me, okay?

300
00:20:35,100 --> 00:20:37,620
You've got to understand this, okay?

301
00:20:37,840 --> 00:20:41,260
We could die if we don't get out of here. Hold my hand.

302
00:20:42,970 --> 00:20:44,160
Ready.

303
00:20:45,010 --> 00:20:46,100
Go!

304
00:20:53,530 --> 00:20:55,750
No! Get back here!

305
00:20:58,630 --> 00:20:59,900
We've got to get them!

306
00:21:05,090 --> 00:21:07,060
- Go get them! - I am!

307
00:21:07,060 --> 00:21:09,740
This is your fault! This is what I was talking about!

308
00:21:09,790 --> 00:21:10,920
Shut up!

309
00:21:13,880 --> 00:21:15,400
Get back here!

310
00:21:15,400 --> 00:21:17,300
We've got to get them. They cannot get away.

311
00:21:17,300 --> 00:21:20,590
This is good work. Keep me informed. Thank you.

312
00:21:24,260 --> 00:21:25,590
Shut the door.

313
00:21:29,600 --> 00:21:31,200
Are we saying Nina's a traitor?

314
00:21:31,200 --> 00:21:33,360
We're not saying anything. We need to know more.

315
00:21:33,360 --> 00:21:36,790
Until we find out for sure, should I shut down her confidential access?

316
00:21:36,790 --> 00:21:38,260
No, that'll slow everything down.

317
00:21:38,260 --> 00:21:41,120
There's got to be an explanation for ths.

318
00:21:41,120 --> 00:21:44,020
Right now, what I really need is the data off of that card.

319
00:21:44,020 --> 00:21:45,590
Aren't we obligated to

320
00:21:45,590 --> 00:21:47,860
seal off her channels with this much evidence?

321
00:21:49,160 --> 00:21:51,640
Look, you were seeing her, weren't you?

322
00:21:53,070 --> 00:21:54,800
That is none of your business.

323
00:21:55,240 --> 00:21:56,920
I think in this case it is.

324
00:22:00,870 --> 00:22:04,530
Yes. Yes, when my wife and I were separated, I was seeing Nina.

325
00:22:04,530 --> 00:22:06,970
- Did you tell her anything you shouldn't have? - No!

326
00:22:12,080 --> 00:22:13,460
I don't think so.

327
00:22:14,080 --> 00:22:15,310
I trusted her

328
00:22:15,400 --> 00:22:17,560
with everything that was coming through here, but....

329
00:22:22,360 --> 00:22:23,690
Fine, shut down her access.

330
00:22:23,690 --> 00:22:25,110
Okay, what's she working on?

331
00:22:25,110 --> 00:22:27,350
747 passenger breakdown list.

332
00:22:27,360 --> 00:22:29,660
Good, it's not a secure socket. I can do it without her knowing.

333
00:22:29,660 --> 00:22:31,010
Good.

334
00:22:34,610 --> 00:22:35,760
Jamey?

335
00:22:36,740 --> 00:22:38,490
Don't worry. I won't say anything.

336
00:22:39,300 --> 00:22:40,570
Thank you.

337
00:22:56,440 --> 00:22:57,780
We gotta get them!

338
00:23:05,750 --> 00:23:06,960
Hey, get out of here.

339
00:23:07,290 --> 00:23:08,620
Where'd they go?

340
00:23:15,520 --> 00:23:19,470
- Forget it. - Come on, man. Don't...

341
00:23:19,920 --> 00:23:22,690
Hey, come back. Scumbag.

342
00:23:22,690 --> 00:23:25,710
You just cost me $50. You're going to pay for this!

343
00:23:29,210 --> 00:23:30,420
What up?

344
00:23:30,920 --> 00:23:32,750
See two girls run past here?

345
00:23:34,350 --> 00:23:36,850
- Yeah, I seen 'em. - Which way'd they go?

346
00:23:39,180 --> 00:23:41,360
- Who are they? - Did you see them or not?

347
00:23:47,100 --> 00:23:48,700
They went down Central.

348
00:23:50,960 --> 00:23:51,950
Check it out.

349
00:23:51,950 --> 00:23:53,400
I'll look around here.

350
00:23:54,180 --> 00:23:56,470
- Yeah? - It's Gaines. How's it going?

351
00:23:56,620 --> 00:23:57,760
Everything's fine.

352
00:23:58,300 --> 00:24:00,720
Change of plans. We're going to meet at a new location.

353
00:24:00,930 --> 00:24:02,840
Just let me know. I'll meet you there.

354
00:24:05,110 --> 00:24:08,190
- We need to get to a phone. - No, you need to pay up!

355
00:24:29,470 --> 00:24:30,800
Is this real?

356
00:24:31,930 --> 00:24:33,400
Thank you very much.

357
00:25:28,260 --> 00:25:29,530
What couldn't wait until morning?

358
00:25:29,540 --> 00:25:31,170
Kingsley? She called me about an hour ago.

359
00:25:31,170 --> 00:25:33,080
Said she had some new information.

360
00:25:34,670 --> 00:25:36,070
David, you got me out of bed at 2:00 A.M. in the morning.

361
00:25:36,070 --> 00:25:37,460
What did she say?

362
00:25:37,460 --> 00:25:40,860
She said the Gibson boy, the one who raped Nicole...

363
00:25:41,120 --> 00:25:42,610
...didn't commit suicide.

364
00:25:43,140 --> 00:25:45,770
That he was... thrown out of a window.

365
00:25:47,560 --> 00:25:50,240
So, he was thrown out of a window. Who cares?

366
00:25:50,250 --> 00:25:51,680
She said it was Keith!

367
00:25:55,600 --> 00:25:58,840
She's going to publicly accuse my son of murder.

368
00:26:02,270 --> 00:26:04,200
Ok. There's a couple of ways to handle this.

369
00:26:04,200 --> 00:26:05,780
It's a lie, Carl!

370
00:26:06,220 --> 00:26:08,740
It's dirty politics, and I won't stand for it.

371
00:26:10,320 --> 00:26:12,440
My family had to live through that nightmare years ago.

372
00:26:12,450 --> 00:26:14,310
I won't put Nicole through it again.

373
00:26:14,730 --> 00:26:16,210
And Keith couldn't--

374
00:26:16,210 --> 00:26:18,490
This bastard Hodges waits 'til

375
00:26:18,490 --> 00:26:20,720
the primary so you don't have time to respond.

376
00:26:20,720 --> 00:26:22,940
I don't care what day it is. It's a lie--

377
00:26:22,940 --> 00:26:25,780
I know, I know, but we can't pretend that day isn't important.

378
00:26:25,780 --> 00:26:29,060
I'll put a lid on Kingsley, at least until the polls close.

379
00:26:29,060 --> 00:26:31,600
We win the primary, then take it from there.

380
00:26:31,600 --> 00:26:34,800
No. We've got to find out who's sourcing this and get them to recant.

381
00:26:34,800 --> 00:26:38,350
I'll figure out where this is coming from and I'll cut it off.

382
00:26:38,350 --> 00:26:40,090
But, David....

383
00:26:41,210 --> 00:26:42,780
We go back a few years.

384
00:26:42,780 --> 00:26:45,500
You have your principles, you don't compromise. Blah, blah, blah.

385
00:26:45,500 --> 00:26:46,320
That's why I love you,

386
00:26:46,320 --> 00:26:48,650
but you knew the gloves were going to come off.

387
00:26:48,680 --> 00:26:50,200
Well, they are off.

388
00:26:50,240 --> 00:26:51,580
That's why you have me.

389
00:26:52,710 --> 00:26:55,080
Go back and forget about this.

390
00:26:55,740 --> 00:26:56,900
I'm on it.

391
00:26:59,910 --> 00:27:02,690
I can't let them throw my son to the wolves.

392
00:27:02,720 --> 00:27:05,290
David. I'll take care of it.

393
00:27:07,810 --> 00:27:09,700
- Is that you? - Yeah. You better get lost.

394
00:27:11,420 --> 00:27:12,700
I'll call you in an hour.

395
00:27:18,780 --> 00:27:20,110
It's okay, fellas.

396
00:27:21,770 --> 00:27:22,960
I'm fine.

397
00:27:43,510 --> 00:27:44,680
Damn it.

398
00:27:50,670 --> 00:27:52,470
Let's go back to the front and wait for them to leave.

399
00:27:52,470 --> 00:27:53,620
Okay.

400
00:27:55,810 --> 00:27:57,040
They're not on Central.

401
00:27:57,900 --> 00:27:59,690
Just keep looking! We gotta find them.

402
00:27:59,690 --> 00:28:02,200
I'll take the side streets. They're around here somewhere.

403
00:28:04,980 --> 00:28:06,990
- We've gotta find them! - Okay.

404
00:28:14,220 --> 00:28:15,670
You're in my space.

405
00:28:15,670 --> 00:28:16,960
I'm sorry, we'll leave.

406
00:28:22,280 --> 00:28:23,790
Is there a phone around here?

407
00:28:24,400 --> 00:28:25,540
No.

408
00:28:25,550 --> 00:28:26,820
What are you looking for?

409
00:28:27,540 --> 00:28:28,770
Wanna score some dope?

410
00:28:28,930 --> 00:28:31,050
We need to get rid of those guys.

411
00:28:31,050 --> 00:28:32,910
Is there any way you can help us get to a phone?

412
00:28:32,940 --> 00:28:34,490
You want me to help you?

413
00:28:37,450 --> 00:28:40,950
What are your little designer jeans worth? $500?

414
00:28:42,640 --> 00:28:45,490
And those kicks, another $125?

415
00:28:51,100 --> 00:28:53,270
You want to trade places with me for a while?

416
00:28:54,350 --> 00:28:55,840
Want to turn tricks

417
00:28:55,840 --> 00:28:59,000
while I snuggle with your daddy in the Hollywood foothills?

418
00:29:05,630 --> 00:29:06,820
Go away.

419
00:29:20,430 --> 00:29:21,900
We've been kidnapped.

420
00:29:23,310 --> 00:29:26,270
I don't know... Her arm is broken.

421
00:29:27,350 --> 00:29:29,330
Those guys are still out there.

422
00:29:37,170 --> 00:29:38,820
Welcome to the neighborhood.

423
00:29:42,530 --> 00:29:45,070
Is there any other way out besides the front door?

424
00:29:47,930 --> 00:29:51,090
- But if we could just... - But nothing. Get out!

425
00:29:51,500 --> 00:29:53,090
Go!

426
00:30:22,780 --> 00:30:24,830
How long have you been playing me?

427
00:30:25,790 --> 00:30:27,160
Playing you?

428
00:30:27,420 --> 00:30:28,660
Playing me!

429
00:30:28,740 --> 00:30:30,240
What are you doing?

430
00:30:31,550 --> 00:30:33,370
Why don't you tell me about this?

431
00:30:33,580 --> 00:30:34,600
Tell you what, Jack?

432
00:30:34,600 --> 00:30:36,850
Skip the "I don't know what you're talking about" phase.

433
00:30:36,850 --> 00:30:38,740
You loaded this card with intel.

434
00:30:38,740 --> 00:30:40,210
I wanna know who you're working for

435
00:30:40,210 --> 00:30:41,930
and who you smuggled this card to.

436
00:30:41,930 --> 00:30:43,420
You're delirious!

437
00:30:44,030 --> 00:30:47,390
- Who are you working for? - I work for you.

438
00:30:47,390 --> 00:30:49,520
Who are you working for?

439
00:30:49,910 --> 00:30:52,570
- Who are you working for? - I work for you!

440
00:30:52,570 --> 00:30:55,890
Whoever programmed this card is involved with the hit on Palmer.

441
00:30:55,970 --> 00:30:58,260
This came from your computer.

442
00:30:59,760 --> 00:31:02,700
I don't care where it came from. I didn't do it.

443
00:31:07,200 --> 00:31:09,690
And I can't believe that you think I did.

444
00:31:20,860 --> 00:31:22,940
There it is. $1 million in your account

445
00:31:22,940 --> 00:31:24,980
in addition to what we already agreed on.

446
00:31:24,980 --> 00:31:27,310
Now, where's the ID?

447
00:31:27,960 --> 00:31:29,120
Let's get it.

448
00:31:30,400 --> 00:31:31,930
No, just the three of us.

449
00:31:32,720 --> 00:31:34,170
And why do I trust you?

450
00:31:34,930 --> 00:31:36,330
Because you want the ID.

451
00:31:49,480 --> 00:31:51,130
I'm going to miss you, Mandy.

452
00:32:05,480 --> 00:32:08,070
- How's your arm? - It's okay if I don't move it.

453
00:32:08,210 --> 00:32:09,460
Then don't move it.

454
00:32:45,230 --> 00:32:48,710
I know you're in here. I can smell your perfume.

455
00:32:51,180 --> 00:32:52,280
Where are you?

456
00:32:53,950 --> 00:32:56,250
This is starting to piss me off!

457
00:33:16,570 --> 00:33:18,160
He's going to be ready.

458
00:33:20,440 --> 00:33:21,670
I'm telling you.

459
00:33:22,000 --> 00:33:24,630
No, I saw him work out yesterday. He looked good.

460
00:33:25,040 --> 00:33:27,060
He's going to be ready.

461
00:33:27,490 --> 00:33:28,660
Excuse me.

462
00:33:28,660 --> 00:33:29,980
I'll call you back.

463
00:33:32,150 --> 00:33:33,190
You looking for something?

464
00:33:33,190 --> 00:33:35,310
Can you help us? These guys are after us.

465
00:33:36,020 --> 00:33:37,090
What guys?

466
00:33:37,130 --> 00:33:39,840
I'll pay you whatever you want. Just get us out of here!

467
00:33:41,310 --> 00:33:42,510
Let's see the money.

468
00:33:43,260 --> 00:33:45,420
I don't have it on me. When you get us home,

469
00:33:45,420 --> 00:33:47,570
my parents will pay you whatever you want.

470
00:33:48,140 --> 00:33:50,600
Sorry, I run a cash-up-front business.

471
00:33:51,690 --> 00:33:53,060
What's your name, sweetheart?

472
00:33:53,060 --> 00:33:54,080
Janet.

473
00:33:58,320 --> 00:34:01,340
Can't we just use your phone at least, please?

474
00:34:04,310 --> 00:34:05,530
Come here!

475
00:34:06,630 --> 00:34:10,150
Go! Run! Take the phone and run! Go, go, go!

476
00:34:11,860 --> 00:34:12,970
Go!

477
00:34:22,900 --> 00:34:24,230
Run!

478
00:34:25,930 --> 00:34:27,070
It's cool, man.

479
00:34:49,960 --> 00:34:51,120
Is this right?

480
00:34:52,390 --> 00:34:53,380
What?

481
00:34:53,380 --> 00:34:55,030
They just posted a memorandum.

482
00:34:55,920 --> 00:34:57,560
Richard Walsh is dead.

483
00:34:59,630 --> 00:35:02,190
That can't be. He was just here an hour ago.

484
00:35:02,350 --> 00:35:03,670
That's what it says.

485
00:35:14,250 --> 00:35:15,940
Oh, my God.

486
00:35:18,890 --> 00:35:20,560
Can you find out what happened?

487
00:35:21,460 --> 00:35:23,570
Jack's got me working on something.

488
00:35:24,760 --> 00:35:27,180
All right. Can you open up a socket on my terminal?

489
00:35:27,180 --> 00:35:28,590
I'll check it myself.

490
00:35:31,790 --> 00:35:33,020
Sure.

491
00:35:33,550 --> 00:35:34,610
Thanks.

492
00:35:46,560 --> 00:35:47,200
Farrell.

493
00:35:47,250 --> 00:35:49,190
I need you up here now. Do you have it yet?

494
00:35:49,640 --> 00:35:51,160
Almost. Another couple minutes.

495
00:35:51,160 --> 00:35:52,990
As soon as you're done, come up.

496
00:36:41,930 --> 00:36:43,000
Thank you.

497
00:37:07,070 --> 00:37:09,140
That job this summer. You in?

498
00:37:21,880 --> 00:37:22,870
Yes.

499
00:37:24,480 --> 00:37:26,340
Okay, Jonathan, you're done.

500
00:37:42,030 --> 00:37:43,620
I had no choice.

501
00:38:02,730 --> 00:38:05,400
The keycard was definitely programmed from Nina's computer.

502
00:38:05,400 --> 00:38:08,350
The log-in time was 10:14 P.M.

503
00:38:09,070 --> 00:38:11,930
Looks like the next 20 minutes were spent gathering data...

504
00:38:12,600 --> 00:38:14,770
...and another seven to burn it into the keycard.

505
00:38:15,220 --> 00:38:18,500
Log-out was 10:41, January 14.

506
00:38:18,500 --> 00:38:20,870
It goes on to specify which files were accessed.

507
00:38:20,870 --> 00:38:22,830
If you want more details, there's about two screens--

508
00:38:22,830 --> 00:38:24,190
Wait a minute.

509
00:38:24,260 --> 00:38:27,430
- What was the date? - January 14, a few months ago.

510
00:38:27,730 --> 00:38:29,760
Second weekend in January, Jack.

511
00:38:30,140 --> 00:38:31,280
That's all I got.

512
00:38:34,120 --> 00:38:36,030
Thank you, Jamey. That's all I need right now.

513
00:38:45,390 --> 00:38:48,390
That was the same weekend that we were in Santa Barbara together.

514
00:38:55,930 --> 00:38:58,290
That means someone from this office hacked your log-in code.

515
00:38:58,300 --> 00:38:59,690
They're in your system.

516
00:39:00,520 --> 00:39:02,190
You were way off on this one, Jack.

517
00:39:02,200 --> 00:39:04,300
- I'm sorry, Nina. - How could you?

518
00:39:36,390 --> 00:39:37,660
Division, please.

519
00:39:37,660 --> 00:39:39,370
This is Tony Almeida at CTU.

520
00:39:40,060 --> 00:39:43,150
Look, you better get down here right away.

521
00:39:45,110 --> 00:39:47,450
Jack Bauer needs to be relieved of his command.

522
00:40:03,980 --> 00:40:06,120
- Hello? - Mom, you've got to come get us!

523
00:40:06,130 --> 00:40:08,300
Kim? What's wrong? Are you still at the party?

524
00:40:08,300 --> 00:40:10,360
There was no party. They made us say that.

525
00:40:10,370 --> 00:40:10,960
Who?

526
00:40:10,960 --> 00:40:14,300
These guys. Listen, we're in North Hollywood, behind....

527
00:40:14,300 --> 00:40:16,350
- Platt's Auto Body! - Platt's Auto Body!

528
00:40:16,350 --> 00:40:17,590
Kim, they're coming!

529
00:40:17,590 --> 00:40:19,970
- Mom you got to come now! - Kim!

530
00:40:19,970 --> 00:40:22,020
What's going on? Teri?

531
00:40:22,170 --> 00:40:23,340
911 Emergency.

532
00:40:23,340 --> 00:40:24,620
Listen, my daughter's in trouble.

533
00:40:24,620 --> 00:40:27,120
She's in North Hollywood, behind Platt's Auto Body.

534
00:40:27,120 --> 00:40:29,000
It sounded like someone was chasing her!

535
00:40:35,190 --> 00:40:36,460
Come on, Kim!

536
00:40:52,770 --> 00:40:53,800
No!

537
00:40:53,800 --> 00:40:56,620
No, look at me.

538
00:40:57,040 --> 00:41:00,170
Look at me. Oh, god, oh god.

539
00:41:00,850 --> 00:41:02,290
No!

540
00:41:02,640 --> 00:41:03,510
I told you to chill.

541
00:41:03,510 --> 00:41:06,040
- Why didn't you listen? - Let go of me! No!

542
00:41:06,040 --> 00:41:07,410
Shut up!

543
00:41:08,180 --> 00:41:09,620
- Let go! - Come on.

544
00:41:09,620 --> 00:41:10,250
What about her?

545
00:41:10,250 --> 00:41:12,430
Forget her, we got what we need.

546
00:41:12,690 --> 00:41:14,410
- Come on! - No!

547
00:41:17,760 --> 00:41:19,190
Keep moving!

548
00:41:23,950 --> 00:41:25,920
Shut up.

