2
00:00:12,310 --> 00:00:14,920
Right now, terrorists are plotting to

3
00:00:14,920 --> 00:00:17,430
assassinate a presidential candidate.

4
00:00:18,010 --> 00:00:20,540
My wife and daughter have been targeted

5
00:00:20,720 --> 00:00:24,800
and people that I work with may be involved in both.

6
00:00:25,230 --> 00:00:27,590
I'm Federal Agent Jack Bauer

7
00:00:27,590 --> 00:00:31,430
and today is the longest day of my life.

10
00:01:45,120 --> 00:01:50,120
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

11
00:01:45,120 --> 00:01:50,120
{\an5}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

12
00:01:45,120 --> 00:01:50,120
{\an5}{\pos(145,252)}m 211 -8 b 217 -6 217 -4 217 -2 l 217 24 b 217 26 217 29 211 31 l 31 31 b 26 29 26 26 26 24 l 26 -2 b 26 -4 26 -6 31 -8

13
00:01:45,620 --> 00:01:50,120
{\pos(67,248)}m 20 0 l 209 0 b 218 0 229 11 229 20 l 229 209 b 229 218 218 228 209 228 l 20 228 b 11 228 0 218 0 209 l 0 20 b 0 11 11 0 20 0

14
00:01:45,620 --> 00:01:50,120
{\pos(67,248)}m 115 64 l 115 35 l 171 0 l 177 0 l 133 46 l 143 52 l 179 0 l 184 0 l 159 63 l 229 107 l 229 182 l 145 96 l 135 122 l 207 227 l 137 227 l 115 172 l 115 93 l 126 76 l 115 64 l 104 76 l 115 93 l 115 172 l 93 227 l 23 227 l 95 122 l 84 96 l 0 182 l 0 107 l 70 63 l 45 0 l 50 0 l 87 52 l 97 46 l 52 0 l 59 0 l 115 35

15
00:01:45,620 --> 00:01:50,120
{\pos(58,238)}m 71 60 b 71 0 161 0 161 60 b 161 120 71 120 71 60

16
00:01:45,620 --> 00:01:50,120
{\pos(84,248)}m 325 0 l 355 0 l 332 47 l 354 47 l 399 136 l 369 136 l 328 53 l 288 136 l 257 136 l 325 0 m 467 0 l 497 0 l 474 47 l 496 47 l 541 136 l 511 136 l 470 53 l 430 136 l 399 136 l 467 0 m 545 1 l 583 1 l 583 14 l 568 14 l 568 19 l 583 19 l 583 30 l 568 30 l 568 34 l 599 34 l 599 30 l 583 30 l 583 19 l 599 19 l 599 14 l 583 14 l 583 1 l 611 1 b 616 1 622 6 622 10 l 622 36 l 652 0 l 678 0 l 644 41 l 622 41 l 622 47 l 596 47 l 597 54 l 625 54 l 625 68 l 541 68 l 541 54 l 572 54 l 571 47 l 545 47 l 545 1 m 583 72 l 583 85 l 569 85 l 569 90 l 598 90 l 598 85 l 583 85 l 583 72 l 611 72 b 615 72 621 78 621 82 l 653 44 l 678 44 l 644 86 l 621 86 l 621 103 l 597 103 l 597 136 l 570 136 l 564 126 l 562 136 l 542 136 l 548 107 l 568 107 l 565 121 l 571 121 l 571 103 l 547 103 l 547 72 l 583 72 m 600 107 l 620 107 l 624 124 l 653 89 l 679 89 l 642 136 l 615 136 l 618 132 l 606 132 l 600 107 m 689 0 l 716 0 l 721 15 l 732 15 l 732 30 l 718 56 l 731 56 l 735 100 l 721 100 l 717 59 l 714 64 l 714 136 l 693 136 l 693 79 l 676 79 l 707 30 l 679 30 l 679 15 l 694 15 l 689 0 m 738 0 l 804 0 b 807 0 813 6 813 9 l 813 87 l 794 87 l 794 14 l 756 14 l 756 87 l 763 77 l 763 21 l 787 21 l 787 91 l 798 91 l 798 120 l 820 120 l 812 136 l 778 136 l 778 90 l 748 136 l 723 136 l 756 87 l 738 87 l 738 0 m 257 151 l 275 151 l 297 182 l 319 151 l 337 151 l 304 197 l 304 227 l 290 227 l 290 197 l 257 151 m 337 151 l 355 151 l 377 182 l 399 151 l 417 151 l 384 197 l 384 227 l 370 227 l 370 197 l 337 151 m 425 192 l 447 192 b 445 181 427 181 425 192 l 410 192 b 414 162 458 162 462 192 l 462 206 l 425 206 b 425 210 429 212 433 213 l 462 213 l 462 227 l 433 227 b 412 227 408 203 410 192 m 462 151 l 532 151 l 532 165 l 504 165 l 504 227 l 489 227 l 489 165 l 462 165 l 462 151 m 580 172 l 580 186 l 549 186 b 543 186 543 192 549 192 l 565 192 b 589 192 589 227 565 227 l 532 227 l 532 213 l 565 213 b 570 213 570 206 565 206 l 549 206 b 524 206 524 172 549 172 l 580 172 m 592 213 l 606 213 l 606 227 l 592 227 l 592 213 m 639 172 l 665 172 l 665 186 l 639 186 b 623 186 623 213 639 213 l 665 213 l 665 227 l 639 227 b 603 227 603 172 639 172 m 700 184 b 722 184 722 215 700 215 l 700 229 b 740 229 740 170 700 170 b 660 170 660 229 700 229 l 700 215 b 680 215 680 184 700 184 m 737 172 l 782 172 b 803 172 813 177 813 198 l 813 228 l 799 228 l 799 198 b 799 186 793 187 782 187 l 782 228 l 768 228 l 768 187 l 752 187 l 752 228 l 737 228 l 737 172

19
00:01:51,340 --> 00:02:21,340
{\an9}m 200 -1 l 200 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

20
00:01:50,840 --> 00:02:21,340
{\an2}{\pos(26,248)}m 38 -1 l 44 6 l 38 13 l 19 13 b 14 12 14 6 14 6 b 14 6 14 0 19 -1

27
00:00:44,560 --> 00:00:46,910
Bob, what just happened? I can't hear you.

28
00:00:48,350 --> 00:00:50,040
Bob, can you hear me?

29
00:00:51,700 --> 00:00:53,170
Bob?

30
00:00:53,800 --> 00:00:55,400
Bob, can you hear me?

31
00:00:57,730 --> 00:00:59,490
Bob, pick up the phone.

32
00:01:01,370 --> 00:01:03,390
Somebody, pick up the phone.

33
00:01:10,020 --> 00:01:11,540
Bob, can you hear me?

34
00:01:13,700 --> 00:01:15,920
Whoever's there, just pick up the phone.

35
00:01:17,940 --> 00:01:19,280
Bob?

36
00:01:20,790 --> 00:01:22,650
Can anyone hear me?

37
00:01:23,230 --> 00:01:25,040
Just pick up the phone.

38
00:01:25,920 --> 00:01:27,310
Pick up the...

39
00:01:32,370 --> 00:01:35,190
At the beep, leave a message for Bob Ellis...

40
00:01:35,920 --> 00:01:37,380
Oh, God. No.

41
00:01:42,640 --> 00:01:44,480
Think, Jack. Just think.

42
00:01:52,780 --> 00:01:55,120
- Routing Operator. - Yes, this is Jack Bauer.

43
00:01:55,120 --> 00:01:55,850
I want you to transfer me

44
00:01:55,850 --> 00:01:58,200
to Agent Watson in our New Orleans office.

45
00:01:58,200 --> 00:02:00,600
- Hold on, one moment please. - Thank you.

46
00:02:03,010 --> 00:02:04,920
CTU, New Orleans. Watson speaking.

47
00:02:04,920 --> 00:02:06,990
This is Jack Bauer in Los Angeles.

48
00:02:06,990 --> 00:02:09,460
You've got a floating NSA operative in your region.

49
00:02:09,460 --> 00:02:10,810
His name is Robert Ellis.

50
00:02:10,810 --> 00:02:12,520
I think something terrible has happened to him.

51
00:02:12,520 --> 00:02:14,020
All right. What would you like us to do?

52
00:02:14,020 --> 00:02:15,140
I'm gonna transfer you over our comm

53
00:02:15,140 --> 00:02:16,270
and they can get you an address.

54
00:02:16,270 --> 00:02:17,230
I want you to check it out.

55
00:02:17,240 --> 00:02:19,010
Phone me as soon as you've got anything, okay?

56
00:02:19,010 --> 00:02:21,030
- Jack? - I'll transfer you now.

57
00:02:21,030 --> 00:02:22,560
- Jack? - Not right now. I'm busy.

58
00:02:22,560 --> 00:02:24,370
- You've got to see this. - What?

59
00:02:24,370 --> 00:02:28,860
These are surveillance shots of all three backup shooters.

60
00:02:28,860 --> 00:02:30,330
I cross-referenced the files that

61
00:02:30,330 --> 00:02:32,680
Ellis sent us with our Interpol records.

62
00:02:33,070 --> 00:02:35,910
- How long ago? - Just now.

63
00:02:36,060 --> 00:02:38,700
Any or all of them could still be targeting Palmer.

64
00:02:39,140 --> 00:02:40,390
Or you.

65
00:02:41,020 --> 00:02:43,920
- Right. - I already sent the photos to Secret Service, so...

66
00:02:44,140 --> 00:02:46,280
Make sure they brief Palmer's staff.

67
00:02:46,280 --> 00:02:47,940
I want them to keep their eyes open.

68
00:02:47,940 --> 00:02:49,950
Right. There's one more thing, though.

69
00:02:50,040 --> 00:02:51,870
Johnny cool guy, here.

70
00:02:52,090 --> 00:02:54,120
His name is Alexis Drazen.

71
00:02:54,330 --> 00:02:56,180
He's Victor Drazen's son.

72
00:02:56,180 --> 00:02:58,910
He was trained in Belgrade, Special Forces.

73
00:03:02,780 --> 00:03:04,100
Good work.

74
00:03:11,420 --> 00:03:13,960
- Hello. - It's me.

75
00:03:14,130 --> 00:03:17,300
Look, I wanted to tell you we're not leaving town today after all.

76
00:03:17,300 --> 00:03:20,440
What made the Senator decide to change his plans?

77
00:03:20,440 --> 00:03:22,390
He didn't say and I didn't ask.

78
00:03:22,390 --> 00:03:25,000
I was just happy that I would get to see you again so soon.

79
00:03:25,000 --> 00:03:27,560
Well, I'm leaving a meeting right now.

80
00:03:27,850 --> 00:03:30,030
But I can be back at the hotel...

81
00:03:31,260 --> 00:03:32,290
by 4:30.

82
00:03:32,290 --> 00:03:35,270
- Okay. I know where to find you. - Okay.

83
00:03:44,610 --> 00:03:46,100
Daniels in position 10-98.

84
00:03:46,100 --> 00:03:47,840
Can you give me a Delta check?

85
00:03:47,840 --> 00:03:50,240
This is Daniels. I'm in position.

86
00:03:50,250 --> 00:03:52,160
Touch your ear if you hear me.

87
00:03:55,960 --> 00:03:57,760
Paulson, do you read me?

88
00:03:58,320 --> 00:03:59,620
Yeah.

89
00:04:03,640 --> 00:04:04,900
Breeher, talk to me.

90
00:04:04,900 --> 00:04:06,280
How you looking?

91
00:04:06,530 --> 00:04:08,290
It's quiet on my end.

92
00:04:20,710 --> 00:04:22,040
Paulson.

93
00:04:22,040 --> 00:04:23,560
Yeah, Jack. Hold on.

94
00:04:28,790 --> 00:04:30,780
Excuse me, Mrs. Bauer?

95
00:04:34,300 --> 00:04:35,690
It's Jack.

96
00:04:36,070 --> 00:04:37,460
Thank you.

97
00:04:44,320 --> 00:04:45,450
Jack?

98
00:04:45,450 --> 00:04:46,760
How you doing?

99
00:04:46,900 --> 00:04:49,890
I'm doing okay. Just trying to get some rest.

100
00:04:51,130 --> 00:04:54,120
Look, I couldn't help but feeling, after I hung up...

101
00:04:54,320 --> 00:04:57,120
I don't know, that something was wrong.

102
00:04:57,120 --> 00:04:58,630
No, I'm fine.

103
00:05:02,250 --> 00:05:04,610
A lot has happened and...

104
00:05:05,870 --> 00:05:07,710
I really need to talk to you.

105
00:05:07,720 --> 00:05:09,330
Fine, then let's talk.

106
00:05:09,330 --> 00:05:11,210
No, not now. Now is not the time.

107
00:05:11,210 --> 00:05:12,440
Why not?

108
00:05:15,520 --> 00:05:16,810
You do what you have to do

109
00:05:16,810 --> 00:05:19,230
and we'll talk when this is all over, okay?

110
00:05:22,520 --> 00:05:23,920
Okay.

111
00:05:25,270 --> 00:05:27,800
I'm here at CTU if you need me.

112
00:05:28,580 --> 00:05:29,910
I know.

113
00:05:31,850 --> 00:05:33,150
Okay, bye.

114
00:05:39,470 --> 00:05:40,660
The Senator's just arrived.

115
00:05:40,660 --> 00:05:42,340
All right, folks. I know you're all busy,

116
00:05:42,340 --> 00:05:44,650
so I'll be as brief as I can.

117
00:05:44,650 --> 00:05:46,940
Good, you're just in time.

118
00:05:46,940 --> 00:05:47,780
What's going on?

119
00:05:47,780 --> 00:05:50,760
Bauer sent photos of the people targeting you.

120
00:05:50,950 --> 00:05:53,210
The threat against Senator Palmer

121
00:05:53,220 --> 00:05:55,050
remains a high probability.

122
00:05:55,050 --> 00:05:58,040
But we have gotten a significant piece

123
00:05:58,040 --> 00:06:00,290
of heads-up intelligence.

124
00:06:01,630 --> 00:06:03,230
These three men...

129
00:06:06,110 --> 00:06:08,260
are the suspected shooters.

130
00:06:09,200 --> 00:06:12,220
Since you're all on the front line of this campaign...

131
00:06:12,220 --> 00:06:15,420
we're hoping you can expand our surveillance reach.

132
00:06:16,660 --> 00:06:19,560
We can always use more eyes and ears in the field.

133
00:06:19,900 --> 00:06:22,410
If you see anyone who you suspect

134
00:06:22,410 --> 00:06:24,180
as being one of these people...

135
00:06:24,180 --> 00:06:27,300
let an agent know immediately.

136
00:06:27,810 --> 00:06:29,310
Everybody clear on that?

137
00:06:29,310 --> 00:06:30,470
Lisa, what's wrong?

138
00:06:30,470 --> 00:06:31,490
All right?

139
00:06:32,440 --> 00:06:34,890
Okay, Kim. The fact is, Rick ran away before we could talk to him.

140
00:06:34,890 --> 00:06:37,930
- He was scared. - Apparently.

141
00:06:41,580 --> 00:06:42,920
Whatever explanation he has

142
00:06:42,920 --> 00:06:45,280
doesn't change the fact that he's a fugitive.

143
00:06:45,280 --> 00:06:47,190
If you know where he is and aren't saying,

144
00:06:47,190 --> 00:06:48,990
that constitutes for a very serious...

145
00:06:48,990 --> 00:06:51,120
I don't know where he is.

146
00:06:51,750 --> 00:06:52,820
Are you sure?

147
00:06:52,820 --> 00:06:55,120
What I'm sure of is he helped us escape.

148
00:06:55,120 --> 00:06:56,480
And if it wasn't for him,

149
00:06:56,480 --> 00:06:58,560
we would have never got out of there.

150
00:07:00,810 --> 00:07:01,990
Kim.

151
00:07:04,360 --> 00:07:06,380
When people are taken hostage,

152
00:07:07,010 --> 00:07:09,660
it's not uncommon for them to feel

153
00:07:09,740 --> 00:07:12,540
a certain bond with their kidnappers.

154
00:07:12,540 --> 00:07:14,740
Rick isn't a kidnapper.

155
00:07:15,490 --> 00:07:18,210
Anyway, I don't know where he is.

156
00:07:19,210 --> 00:07:21,270
I'm sorry, Nina.

157
00:07:21,270 --> 00:07:22,680
I thought you were finished.

158
00:07:24,120 --> 00:07:25,070
Whenever you're ready,

159
00:07:25,070 --> 00:07:27,050
we can pick up where we left off.

160
00:07:27,690 --> 00:07:29,040
Okay.

161
00:07:30,590 --> 00:07:32,320
Why don't you take a break

162
00:07:32,340 --> 00:07:34,810
and your mother and I can finish up in here?

163
00:07:39,830 --> 00:07:41,220
You okay?

164
00:07:44,440 --> 00:07:45,590
You sure you're okay to do this?

165
00:07:45,590 --> 00:07:48,280
Yes. Sure. Are you?

166
00:07:48,510 --> 00:07:49,900
Yeah.

167
00:07:50,170 --> 00:07:51,720
Listen, Nina...

168
00:07:53,690 --> 00:07:56,200
I don't want you to have to tiptoe around me.

169
00:07:57,980 --> 00:08:00,940
Jack and I were separated when you slept with him.

170
00:08:01,830 --> 00:08:04,940
I'm not going to hold that against you, okay?

171
00:08:16,350 --> 00:08:17,750
Okay.

172
00:08:19,320 --> 00:08:22,970
You and Kim have both said that Rick helped you.

173
00:08:23,820 --> 00:08:25,440
But talking to Kim, I get the sense

174
00:08:25,440 --> 00:08:28,380
that she's withholding something.

175
00:08:30,040 --> 00:08:31,450
Based on what?

176
00:08:32,870 --> 00:08:34,020
She's protecting Rick.

177
00:08:34,020 --> 00:08:37,860
She seems to have feelings for him, from what I can tell.

178
00:08:39,140 --> 00:08:41,970
There may have been an attraction when she met him last night

179
00:08:41,970 --> 00:08:43,450
but if Kimberly knew anything,

180
00:08:43,450 --> 00:08:45,080
I'm sure she'd tell you.

181
00:08:45,090 --> 00:08:47,590
- Are you sure about that? - She's my daughter.

182
00:08:47,590 --> 00:08:49,350
I think I know her better than you.

183
00:08:58,140 --> 00:08:59,410
Bauer.

184
00:08:59,470 --> 00:09:01,130
It's David Palmer.

185
00:09:01,250 --> 00:09:03,860
- Sir, is everything all right? - I'm not sure.

186
00:09:04,160 --> 00:09:05,520
What's going on?

187
00:09:06,260 --> 00:09:09,540
A member of my Advance Team, Elizabeth Nash,

188
00:09:09,550 --> 00:09:11,530
she recognized one of the assassins

189
00:09:11,530 --> 00:09:13,870
in the photos you sent Secret Service.

190
00:09:13,870 --> 00:09:16,240
It's Victor Drazen's son, Alexis.

191
00:09:16,370 --> 00:09:17,980
Does she know where he is?

192
00:09:17,980 --> 00:09:19,560
They're in contact.

193
00:09:19,560 --> 00:09:20,750
Contact? What do you mean?

194
00:09:20,750 --> 00:09:22,370
In which context?

195
00:09:23,990 --> 00:09:25,300
Intimate.

196
00:09:27,450 --> 00:09:30,240
Senator, is this person in a position

197
00:09:30,240 --> 00:09:32,030
to endanger your security?

198
00:09:33,460 --> 00:09:35,060
I'm afraid so.

199
00:09:35,120 --> 00:09:36,880
Look, she's pretty shaken up.

200
00:09:36,880 --> 00:09:38,340
But she wants to help.

201
00:09:38,340 --> 00:09:40,450
Good. We're gonna have to bring her into CTU right away

202
00:09:40,450 --> 00:09:41,590
and question her.

203
00:09:41,590 --> 00:09:43,660
I'll get a helicopter over to you in a few minutes.

204
00:09:43,660 --> 00:09:45,160
I'll have her ready.

205
00:09:45,490 --> 00:09:46,840
Jack, what about Ellis?

206
00:09:46,840 --> 00:09:49,960
Was he able to retrieve the missing file on Operation Nightfall?

207
00:09:49,960 --> 00:09:51,930
I lost contact with Ellis.

208
00:09:52,390 --> 00:09:53,690
Lost contact? What do you mean?

209
00:09:53,690 --> 00:09:56,300
I mean we got interrupted in the middle of our phone call.

210
00:09:56,300 --> 00:09:57,320
Sir, I have to be honest with you.

211
00:09:57,330 --> 00:09:59,560
I've got a very bad feeling about this.

212
00:09:59,560 --> 00:10:01,110
So what are you telling me?

213
00:10:01,110 --> 00:10:02,220
I'm telling you that for now,

214
00:10:02,220 --> 00:10:04,340
we have to assume that Ellis is dead.

215
00:10:06,150 --> 00:10:07,200
Keep me posted.

216
00:10:07,200 --> 00:10:08,490
Yes, sir.

217
00:10:10,560 --> 00:10:13,150
Milo, get me Chopper Command.

218
00:10:37,150 --> 00:10:39,420
- Hello? - Rick, It's Kim.

219
00:10:41,380 --> 00:10:43,990
This woman here, she's really pushing me hard.

220
00:10:44,580 --> 00:10:46,020
- What'd you tell her? - I told her the truth.

221
00:10:46,020 --> 00:10:47,830
I told her that you helped us escape.

222
00:10:47,830 --> 00:10:49,850
That's really going to save my ass.

223
00:10:52,080 --> 00:10:55,110
I'm sorry. I'm a little edgy right now.

224
00:10:55,110 --> 00:10:58,220
Look, I just think if you tell her what happened, it'll work out.

225
00:10:58,490 --> 00:11:00,120
She won't believe me.

226
00:11:00,160 --> 00:11:02,910
I don't know how much longer I can keep covering for you.

227
00:11:02,910 --> 00:11:04,290
Okay.

228
00:11:04,570 --> 00:11:07,580
- Can she prove anything? - I don't think so.

229
00:11:08,160 --> 00:11:09,830
That's all that matters.

230
00:11:10,190 --> 00:11:12,820
Listen, I appreciate what you're doing and all,

231
00:11:12,820 --> 00:11:14,900
but you probably shouldn't call here.

232
00:11:14,900 --> 00:11:17,300
- At least not for a while. - How long?

233
00:11:17,560 --> 00:11:19,830
I don't know. Got to go.

234
00:11:22,120 --> 00:11:24,850
- Who's that? - I don't know. Just a wrong number.

235
00:11:28,540 --> 00:11:29,110
I'm worked.

236
00:11:29,110 --> 00:11:30,920
I'm going to crash for a while, okay?

237
00:11:53,510 --> 00:11:56,700
So, is there anything else you can tell me about Gaines?

238
00:11:56,700 --> 00:11:59,010
Maybe a conversation you overheard?

239
00:12:01,930 --> 00:12:02,620
Who's Gaines?

240
00:12:02,620 --> 00:12:05,380
Ira Gaines, the leader of the group.

241
00:12:06,120 --> 00:12:07,390
Right.

242
00:12:10,830 --> 00:12:13,210
- Teri. - No, I'm fine.

243
00:12:13,590 --> 00:12:15,380
Maybe we should take another break.

244
00:12:15,380 --> 00:12:16,660
Maybe you should do your job, Nina.

245
00:12:16,670 --> 00:12:18,500
Don't you have a job to do?

246
00:12:20,330 --> 00:12:22,170
I wish it were that simple.

247
00:12:22,170 --> 00:12:25,220
Things tend to get complicated when you screw your boss.

248
00:12:27,440 --> 00:12:29,670
Look, this obviously isn't working.

249
00:12:29,990 --> 00:12:31,510
No, it's not.

250
00:12:33,500 --> 00:12:34,880
Sorry. I thought I could stay calm

251
00:12:34,880 --> 00:12:36,910
and rational about this, but I can't do it.

252
00:12:36,920 --> 00:12:39,960
- I'm sorry. - There's no apology needed.

253
00:12:40,100 --> 00:12:42,500
But I think Paulson should finish up here.

254
00:12:55,820 --> 00:12:57,250
George.

255
00:12:57,410 --> 00:12:59,050
What are you doing here?

256
00:12:59,050 --> 00:13:01,090
I'm the new quarterback.

257
00:13:01,100 --> 00:13:03,660
- Since when? - Since right now.

258
00:13:03,660 --> 00:13:05,660
What about Alberta Green?

259
00:13:05,660 --> 00:13:07,230
Back at District.

260
00:13:08,790 --> 00:13:10,540
So, Chappelle thought you'd do a better job

261
00:13:10,540 --> 00:13:12,760
keeping an eye on me than she would.

262
00:13:13,570 --> 00:13:15,150
I don't know, Jack.

263
00:13:15,730 --> 00:13:17,480
Something like that, I guess.

264
00:13:21,640 --> 00:13:26,030
So, it's really Drazen's boys that are after Palmer?

265
00:13:26,030 --> 00:13:27,630
This whole thing's been a revenge play

266
00:13:27,630 --> 00:13:29,430
for killing their father.

267
00:13:29,560 --> 00:13:30,580
I know why they're gunning for you,

268
00:13:30,580 --> 00:13:32,630
but why are they after Palmer?

269
00:13:34,710 --> 00:13:36,460
Senator Palmer was head of the subcommittee

270
00:13:36,470 --> 00:13:38,440
that authorized the mission.

271
00:13:40,310 --> 00:13:42,890
Got Ellis tracking down the file on that operation, right?

272
00:13:42,890 --> 00:13:44,510
I had Ellis.

273
00:13:45,110 --> 00:13:47,380
I lost contact with him 20 minutes ago.

274
00:13:47,380 --> 00:13:49,070
You think they took him out?

275
00:13:49,950 --> 00:13:51,300
Yes, I do.

276
00:13:51,300 --> 00:13:53,620
We got a break on another front, though.

277
00:13:54,460 --> 00:13:56,200
A Miss Elizabeth Nash,

278
00:13:56,200 --> 00:13:58,030
part of the Senator's Advance Team

279
00:13:58,030 --> 00:13:59,940
identified one of the shooters from the series of photos

280
00:13:59,940 --> 00:14:01,290
that I'd sent over.

281
00:14:01,290 --> 00:14:02,280
She'd been dating him.

282
00:14:02,280 --> 00:14:04,100
Ovbiously she had no idea who he was.

283
00:14:04,100 --> 00:14:04,940
She's shaken up,

284
00:14:04,940 --> 00:14:07,220
but she's on her way here for a debriefing.

285
00:14:07,230 --> 00:14:09,110
Which one of them was she seeing?

286
00:14:10,500 --> 00:14:11,980
Alexis Drazen.

287
00:14:11,980 --> 00:14:14,900
She's supposed to meet him in his hotel room in an hour.

288
00:14:14,920 --> 00:14:17,360
Good. That'll give us time to stage an arrest.

289
00:14:17,690 --> 00:14:19,140
George, think about this.

290
00:14:19,140 --> 00:14:21,050
What if she keeps her date?

291
00:14:21,560 --> 00:14:23,760
We'd have the upper hand in this thing for the first time.

292
00:14:23,760 --> 00:14:24,720
See what we could learn.

293
00:14:24,720 --> 00:14:25,940
It's a little risky, isn't it, Jack?

294
00:14:25,940 --> 00:14:27,360
I'd have a squad across the hall, ready

295
00:14:27,360 --> 00:14:30,220
to go in that room before anything could possibly happen.

296
00:14:32,550 --> 00:14:36,960
George, I think this is too big an opportunity just to pass up.

297
00:14:38,920 --> 00:14:41,540
- What time is she getting here? - Ten minutes.

298
00:14:42,780 --> 00:14:46,180
- We'll talk to her, then we'll make up our minds. - Absolutely.

299
00:14:52,270 --> 00:14:54,400
She's going to the CTU office right now.

300
00:14:54,400 --> 00:14:55,680
Why are they taklng her there?

301
00:14:55,680 --> 00:14:56,840
They want to find out everything

302
00:14:56,840 --> 00:14:58,820
they can about Alexis Drazen.

303
00:14:58,820 --> 00:15:01,900
- Is that the brother? - No, it's his son.

304
00:15:02,480 --> 00:15:03,450
Let me call you back.

305
00:15:03,450 --> 00:15:05,360
All right, I'll wait for your call.

306
00:15:06,050 --> 00:15:07,390
Keith, come here.

307
00:15:11,490 --> 00:15:12,680
What's up?

308
00:15:13,360 --> 00:15:16,110
We haven't had much of a chance to talk since last night

309
00:15:16,110 --> 00:15:18,400
and it seems like every time we do

310
00:15:19,000 --> 00:15:20,890
we're at each other's throats.

311
00:15:21,530 --> 00:15:23,730
Everything's okay between you and me.

312
00:15:26,000 --> 00:15:29,960
I guess you've noticed we haven't been quite on the same page today.

313
00:15:29,970 --> 00:15:31,900
Yes, it's been kind of hard to miss.

314
00:15:32,220 --> 00:15:33,600
The pressure's on.

315
00:15:34,310 --> 00:15:35,980
It's testing all of us.

316
00:15:37,100 --> 00:15:38,460
For sure.

317
00:15:39,260 --> 00:15:41,060
That's what I wanted to talk about.

318
00:15:43,410 --> 00:15:47,120
It stayed in my head, what you said a couple of hours ago

319
00:15:48,510 --> 00:15:51,780
about how Dr. Ferragamo has always been there for you

320
00:15:51,780 --> 00:15:53,940
when you needed someone, and I wasn't.

321
00:15:53,960 --> 00:15:58,170
I'm sorry, but that's just how it was then.

322
00:15:59,870 --> 00:16:01,490
It's all going to change.

323
00:16:03,110 --> 00:16:04,600
Starting now.

324
00:16:06,650 --> 00:16:09,570
I know I can't earn your trust overnight.

325
00:16:10,480 --> 00:16:13,120
But if you just come to me when you need to talk

326
00:16:14,460 --> 00:16:15,820
I promise you, son

327
00:16:16,900 --> 00:16:18,560
I'll always be there.

328
00:16:23,690 --> 00:16:25,000
Thanks, Dad.

329
00:16:29,330 --> 00:16:31,780
So, what about Dr. Ferragamo?

330
00:16:31,790 --> 00:16:33,390
The police say anything?

331
00:16:34,750 --> 00:16:36,310
We haven't called yet.

332
00:16:38,740 --> 00:16:40,240
What are we waiting for?

333
00:16:40,600 --> 00:16:42,440
We're not putting anything off, Keith.

334
00:16:42,440 --> 00:16:44,330
It's just something else has come up.

335
00:16:44,330 --> 00:16:45,590
Listen to me.

336
00:16:45,590 --> 00:16:47,900
We have a security breach in our staff.

337
00:16:48,070 --> 00:16:50,030
We have to deal with that first.

338
00:16:50,540 --> 00:16:52,390
What kind of security breach?

339
00:16:55,200 --> 00:16:56,040
I can't tell you.

340
00:16:56,050 --> 00:16:57,410
Dad, you can't tell me anything...

341
00:16:57,410 --> 00:16:59,990
Look, Keith, I have to be able to make decisions

342
00:16:59,990 --> 00:17:02,330
around here without you challenging me.

343
00:17:02,500 --> 00:17:04,210
Look, everything you're feeling...

344
00:17:04,900 --> 00:17:06,980
Now's the time I need you, Dad.

345
00:17:07,240 --> 00:17:10,890
Not just to talk to me, but to do the right thing.

346
00:17:13,450 --> 00:17:15,890
Keith!

347
00:17:16,870 --> 00:17:18,790
I will do the right thing

348
00:17:19,850 --> 00:17:21,440
at the right time.

349
00:17:22,660 --> 00:17:23,940
Yes.

350
00:17:24,300 --> 00:17:25,700
I'm sure you will.

351
00:17:32,730 --> 00:17:34,330
I found Bauer's wife and daughter.

352
00:17:34,330 --> 00:17:36,460
They were moved to a safe house.

353
00:17:36,460 --> 00:17:37,750
Where are you?

354
00:17:37,940 --> 00:17:40,040
I'm almost in.

355
00:17:40,540 --> 00:17:42,490
How many men are guarding them?

356
00:17:43,180 --> 00:17:45,720
I'm handling the situation, Andre.

357
00:17:45,720 --> 00:17:46,920
Rest assured.

358
00:17:46,920 --> 00:17:49,170
The women will be dead soon.

359
00:17:49,330 --> 00:17:51,320
Call me the minute it's done.

360
00:18:42,880 --> 00:18:45,740
- Milo, can you help me out with some over here? - Yes.

361
00:18:45,920 --> 00:18:47,960
What's wrong with the system? My terminal's locked.

362
00:18:47,960 --> 00:18:49,690
I just downloaded all my files to here.

364
00:18:50,010 --> 00:18:51,390
Now I can't... Damn it!

365
00:18:53,970 --> 00:18:56,330
Hold on a second. Let me see.

367
00:18:58,660 --> 00:19:00,250
Why can't I log in?

368
00:19:01,600 --> 00:19:03,390
What do you mean? Mason didn't tell you?

369
00:19:03,400 --> 00:19:04,680
Tell me what?

370
00:19:05,920 --> 00:19:08,110
They downgraded your privileges to 3-W.

371
00:19:08,110 --> 00:19:10,130
You're the same as everyone else downhere.

372
00:19:11,090 --> 00:19:12,420
I see.

373
00:19:13,780 --> 00:19:15,120
Look here.

374
00:19:15,120 --> 00:19:18,620
This should get you into anything you need.

375
00:19:18,620 --> 00:19:20,950
- Thanks. - Jack, don't worry.

376
00:19:20,950 --> 00:19:23,270
You're going to be back up in your office by tomorrow.

377
00:19:23,770 --> 00:19:26,580
By tomorrow I'll be lucky if I'm not in federal custody.

378
00:19:27,160 --> 00:19:29,210
I'm only on provisional status until the end of the day.

379
00:19:29,220 --> 00:19:30,690
As soon as Senator Palmer leaves the state,

380
00:19:30,700 --> 00:19:32,760
I have to face these charges.

381
00:19:37,170 --> 00:19:39,380
I'm sorry. You're all set here.

382
00:19:39,380 --> 00:19:42,030
Thanks.

383
00:19:44,940 --> 00:19:47,050
- Milo. - Yeah?

384
00:19:49,980 --> 00:19:50,950
Have you noticed anyone

385
00:19:50,950 --> 00:19:53,530
accessing anything unusual on the servers?

386
00:19:53,530 --> 00:19:54,750
What do you mean by unusual?

387
00:19:54,750 --> 00:19:55,860
I don't know.  Anything received

388
00:19:55,860 --> 00:19:58,980
or relating to sensitive intel?

389
00:19:59,410 --> 00:20:02,040
No. But I mean, I haven't been looking for it.

390
00:20:03,690 --> 00:20:05,140
Start looking.

391
00:20:05,610 --> 00:20:08,260
Wait, you think there's another mole inside CTU?

392
00:20:08,260 --> 00:20:10,930
I don't know. Just let me know if you find anything, okay?

393
00:20:11,100 --> 00:20:12,770
Okay.

394
00:20:16,230 --> 00:20:17,820
All I'm saying is, don't test me.

395
00:20:17,820 --> 00:20:19,230
I'm not testing you, Keith.

396
00:20:19,230 --> 00:20:20,960
I will do what I said!

397
00:20:21,240 --> 00:20:21,790
Keith.

398
00:20:21,790 --> 00:20:24,830
I'm serious man because I have nothing left to lose. Not anymore.

399
00:20:24,830 --> 00:20:26,070
I know you're upset.

400
00:20:26,070 --> 00:20:28,140
- That's right. - Okay, I think we should talk.

401
00:20:28,140 --> 00:20:29,460
I'm glad you understand.

402
00:20:29,460 --> 00:20:31,430
You know the Griffith Park Observatory?

403
00:20:31,430 --> 00:20:32,600
Yeah.

404
00:20:32,600 --> 00:20:34,300
Can you meet me there now?

405
00:20:34,680 --> 00:20:37,980
Yeah, I can be there. Fifteen minutes.

406
00:20:39,540 --> 00:20:41,990
- Be where? - Nowhere.

407
00:20:41,990 --> 00:20:44,210
- Keith. - I'm trying to protect you.

408
00:20:44,210 --> 00:20:46,910
The last time you tried to protect me, someone died.

409
00:20:46,910 --> 00:20:48,560
Nicole, please.

410
00:20:49,170 --> 00:20:52,090
I'm sorry. That was a terrible thing to say.

411
00:20:52,090 --> 00:20:52,860
The less you know...

412
00:20:52,860 --> 00:20:55,200
What's going on? Who were you talking to on the phone?

413
00:20:56,710 --> 00:20:58,180
You trust me, don't you?

414
00:20:58,180 --> 00:21:00,550
Trust goes both ways, Keith.

415
00:21:02,240 --> 00:21:03,550
Carl.

416
00:21:05,060 --> 00:21:05,850
Why?

417
00:21:05,850 --> 00:21:07,620
Because I don't want to spend the rest of my life with

418
00:21:07,620 --> 00:21:10,160
the same regret I've been living with for the past seven years.

419
00:21:10,170 --> 00:21:12,040
You didn't kill Gibson intentionally.

420
00:21:12,040 --> 00:21:14,010
But I kept the truth from coming out...

421
00:21:14,260 --> 00:21:16,320
and now with Dr. Ferragamo dead...

422
00:21:17,250 --> 00:21:19,660
Look. I can't do that again, Nicole. I won't.

423
00:21:20,040 --> 00:21:22,260
- I need your help. - For what?

424
00:21:23,740 --> 00:21:26,540
Listen. This Secret Service guy has been dogging me all day.

425
00:21:27,090 --> 00:21:28,540
I need you to help me get past him.

426
00:21:28,540 --> 00:21:29,770
He's here to protect us.

427
00:21:29,770 --> 00:21:31,690
Everything that's been happening today.

428
00:21:31,690 --> 00:21:33,590
Everything that's still happening.

429
00:21:33,880 --> 00:21:37,410
It's not too late to change the way this all plays out.

430
00:21:39,990 --> 00:21:41,730
Now, do you trust me or not?

431
00:21:46,370 --> 00:21:48,100
All right, good. Okay.

432
00:21:48,160 --> 00:21:49,430
All right.

433
00:22:05,780 --> 00:22:07,180
Excuse me.

434
00:22:07,240 --> 00:22:10,430
I was on the phone, and I heard a clicking sound,

435
00:22:10,610 --> 00:22:12,890
and I'm wondering If that's my dad being bugged,

436
00:22:12,890 --> 00:22:15,030
or If I'm just being paranoid.

437
00:22:15,330 --> 00:22:17,220
Why don't we just check it out?

438
00:22:51,770 --> 00:22:54,060
Victor Drazen had two sons.

439
00:22:54,060 --> 00:22:56,230
We know Alexis Drazen is here.

440
00:22:56,530 --> 00:22:59,140
I think we should assume Andre Drazen Is here as well.

441
00:22:59,140 --> 00:23:00,860
Who else there's at least two other shooters, right?

442
00:23:00,870 --> 00:23:03,770
Potentially a third, assuming Ellis is dead.

443
00:23:04,840 --> 00:23:06,110
Here she comes.

444
00:23:11,410 --> 00:23:14,310
Miss Nash? George Mason, District Director.

445
00:23:14,320 --> 00:23:16,280
This is agent Jack Bauer.

446
00:23:16,540 --> 00:23:17,840
Mr. Bauer.

447
00:23:18,080 --> 00:23:19,420
Senator Palmer told me about you.

448
00:23:19,420 --> 00:23:21,390
He said I should do whatever you tell me

449
00:23:21,390 --> 00:23:23,740
and I could be sure that I'd be in good hands.

450
00:23:23,740 --> 00:23:25,110
I appreciate that.

451
00:23:25,120 --> 00:23:27,570
I also have to tell you, that if you wish a lawyer present,

452
00:23:27,570 --> 00:23:28,600
you're entitled to that,

453
00:23:28,600 --> 00:23:30,910
but we in no way consider you a suspect.

454
00:23:30,910 --> 00:23:32,870
We just want to ask you a few questions.

455
00:23:32,870 --> 00:23:33,920
I don't need a lawyer.

456
00:23:33,920 --> 00:23:35,850
I'll cooperate in any way I can.

457
00:23:35,850 --> 00:23:37,040
Okay.

458
00:23:37,040 --> 00:23:38,260
Come on in.

459
00:23:43,430 --> 00:23:45,570
Can I have something to drink?

460
00:23:45,570 --> 00:23:47,340
I'll get you a glass of water.

461
00:23:53,070 --> 00:23:56,300
How did Alexis Drazen represent himself to you?

462
00:23:56,350 --> 00:24:01,000
He told me he ran an importing company out of Berlin.

463
00:24:01,640 --> 00:24:03,180
He seemed successful.

464
00:24:03,180 --> 00:24:05,010
He gave me this on our third date.

465
00:24:05,010 --> 00:24:07,630
It must have cost him $10,000. It's real.

466
00:24:07,630 --> 00:24:11,420
Which is more than I can say for him.

467
00:24:12,580 --> 00:24:13,530
When did you meet him?

468
00:24:13,530 --> 00:24:15,970
About a month ago, in DC.

469
00:24:16,450 --> 00:24:18,590
I'm with the Senator's Advance Team.

470
00:24:19,350 --> 00:24:22,610
We had some downtime and a few of us went out for drinks.

471
00:24:22,930 --> 00:24:24,660
So you met him in a bar?

472
00:24:26,610 --> 00:24:27,800
When you're working on a campaign,

473
00:24:27,800 --> 00:24:31,620
you basically put your life on hold for a year.

474
00:24:32,000 --> 00:24:34,610
There's always people around, but it's lonely.

475
00:24:36,350 --> 00:24:37,720
You're supposed to meet Mr. Drazen

476
00:24:37,720 --> 00:24:39,970
in his hotel room in about an hour?

477
00:24:40,750 --> 00:24:42,080
That's right.

478
00:24:42,980 --> 00:24:44,420
Miss Nash.

479
00:24:46,390 --> 00:24:49,470
Would you be willing to keep your appointment with Alexis?

480
00:24:50,160 --> 00:24:51,690
You want me to spy on him?

481
00:24:51,690 --> 00:24:53,860
Only if you feel comfortable.

482
00:24:53,860 --> 00:24:55,650
If you have any doubts at all.

483
00:24:55,750 --> 00:24:57,340
We'd keep it simple.

484
00:24:57,780 --> 00:24:59,820
We want you to plant a tracking device on him

485
00:24:59,820 --> 00:25:01,810
so we can trace his locations.

486
00:25:05,470 --> 00:25:08,270
It's just the thought of seeing him again.

487
00:25:08,270 --> 00:25:09,700
We would make it so that we could hear

488
00:25:09,700 --> 00:25:11,980
and see everything that took place at that room.

489
00:25:12,730 --> 00:25:14,150
You would be safe.

490
00:25:16,950 --> 00:25:18,620
It's okay, we understand.

491
00:25:18,630 --> 00:25:20,100
Jack, you want to head over to the hotel?

492
00:25:20,100 --> 00:25:22,280
I'll finish debriefing Miss Nash.

493
00:25:22,280 --> 00:25:23,560
Yeah.

494
00:25:27,410 --> 00:25:28,810
Mr. Bauer?

495
00:25:29,700 --> 00:25:32,340
You say that this might help protect the Senator?

496
00:25:34,380 --> 00:25:35,650
Yes, I think it would.

497
00:25:35,650 --> 00:25:37,460
The Senator is perfectly safe.

498
00:25:37,460 --> 00:25:39,760
There's a team of Secret Service men with him round the clock.

499
00:25:39,770 --> 00:25:42,220
That didn't stop Alexis from getting to me, did it?

500
00:25:42,220 --> 00:25:46,220
If they got to me, they might have gotten to somebody else.

501
00:25:50,850 --> 00:25:53,420
I'll do it. If something happened to Senator Palmer

502
00:25:53,420 --> 00:25:55,130
that I might have prevented,

503
00:25:55,140 --> 00:25:56,430
I could never forgive myself.

504
00:25:56,430 --> 00:25:57,590
Please,

505
00:25:58,450 --> 00:26:00,090
I have to do this.

506
00:26:06,690 --> 00:26:08,540
He looks familiar, too.

507
00:26:08,850 --> 00:26:11,230
I think I heard them call him Jenson.

509
00:26:14,230 --> 00:26:15,630
Recognize him?

510
00:26:20,680 --> 00:26:22,000
How about him?

511
00:26:25,940 --> 00:26:27,340
You know this one?

516
00:26:30,540 --> 00:26:31,890
Yeah.

517
00:26:33,850 --> 00:26:34,990
He was one of the guards.

518
00:26:34,990 --> 00:26:37,180
I think they called him Eli.

519
00:26:38,340 --> 00:26:41,490
- Can you tell me anything about him? - No.

520
00:26:53,990 --> 00:26:55,710
Daniels, this is Breeher.

521
00:26:59,550 --> 00:27:01,700
Daniels, this is Breeher.

522
00:27:24,170 --> 00:27:25,560
These rooms with the monitors.

523
00:27:25,560 --> 00:27:28,220
You say they had your father under surveillance.

524
00:27:28,240 --> 00:27:29,710
From what I saw.

525
00:27:29,900 --> 00:27:31,500
Even at CTU?

526
00:27:32,890 --> 00:27:34,300
I don't know.

527
00:27:34,300 --> 00:27:36,270
What about you, Mrs. Bauer?

528
00:27:38,420 --> 00:27:39,910
Mrs. Bauer?

529
00:27:41,300 --> 00:27:43,930
Mrs. Bauer. It's very important we get through these questions.

530
00:27:43,930 --> 00:27:46,240
Agent Paulson, I think we need to take a break.

531
00:27:46,240 --> 00:27:48,000
My mom's very tired.

532
00:27:48,560 --> 00:27:49,970
Yes, okay.

533
00:28:02,580 --> 00:28:04,180
Mom, are you okay?

534
00:28:13,170 --> 00:28:14,350
Mom.

535
00:28:36,550 --> 00:28:37,830
Ron.

536
00:28:42,460 --> 00:28:43,640
Ron.

537
00:28:54,990 --> 00:28:56,920
- Come with me. - What?

538
00:28:57,270 --> 00:28:58,650
- Let's go. - Mom.

539
00:29:04,850 --> 00:29:07,490
- Come on, go. - Come on.

540
00:29:11,810 --> 00:29:13,030
In here.

541
00:29:17,350 --> 00:29:18,600
Lock the door.

542
00:29:41,390 --> 00:29:43,180
Come out with your hands up where I can see them

543
00:29:43,180 --> 00:29:45,250
- Don't shoot. I'm coming out. - Now!

544
00:29:45,250 --> 00:29:46,710
I'm coming out.

545
00:29:48,010 --> 00:29:49,300
Drop the gun!

546
00:29:51,050 --> 00:29:53,570
Get down. Down!

547
00:30:01,330 --> 00:30:02,630
Hurry.

548
00:30:16,750 --> 00:30:17,940
Go!

549
00:30:21,620 --> 00:30:22,910
Get down!

550
00:30:37,260 --> 00:30:38,400
Get down!

551
00:30:57,970 --> 00:30:59,680
We're ready to go, gentlemen.

552
00:30:59,780 --> 00:31:02,050
I'll fill you in with the rest when we get to the hotel.

553
00:31:02,050 --> 00:31:03,910
That's where you'll meet the whole team.

554
00:31:03,910 --> 00:31:04,930
Don't want you to be nervous.

555
00:31:04,930 --> 00:31:06,740
I'll be with you every step of the way.

556
00:31:06,740 --> 00:31:08,420
Jack, Jack, I got to talk to you.

557
00:31:08,420 --> 00:31:10,130
Secret Service'll take you to the helicopter.

558
00:31:10,130 --> 00:31:11,770
I'll be there in one second.

559
00:31:12,330 --> 00:31:13,520
What?

560
00:31:13,520 --> 00:31:14,820
They just found Ellis' body

561
00:31:14,820 --> 00:31:16,890
in a men's room in the French Quarter.

562
00:31:20,640 --> 00:31:23,410
- Do we have any leads yet? - No, not yet.

563
00:31:27,540 --> 00:31:28,930
Keep me posted.

564
00:31:32,200 --> 00:31:33,640
What are you doing here?

565
00:31:34,570 --> 00:31:35,580
There was no reason to stay.

566
00:31:35,580 --> 00:31:36,920
Teri and Kim are doing fine.

567
00:31:36,920 --> 00:31:39,840
I specifically asked you to stay to make them feel safe.

568
00:31:39,840 --> 00:31:42,070
They are safe, Jack. I settled them in.

569
00:31:42,070 --> 00:31:43,380
Paulson and Breeher are taklng care of them

570
00:31:43,390 --> 00:31:45,940
and the extra security team is in place.

571
00:32:11,700 --> 00:32:13,080
Hang on, Kim.

572
00:32:43,920 --> 00:32:45,860
- You okay, honey? - Yeah.

573
00:32:46,610 --> 00:32:48,130
I think we lost them.

574
00:32:48,330 --> 00:32:49,050
I'm just going to go check.

575
00:32:49,050 --> 00:32:51,310
I want you to stay right here, okay?

576
00:32:51,310 --> 00:32:52,640
stay right here

577
00:34:05,440 --> 00:34:07,310
He's dead, Ferragamo's dead

578
00:34:07,310 --> 00:34:09,740
- I have no idea. - Don't try to blow me off, Carl.

579
00:34:09,740 --> 00:34:11,260
The authorities are looking to it.

580
00:34:11,260 --> 00:34:12,430
Let them do their jobs.

581
00:34:12,430 --> 00:34:13,930
We both know they won't find anything.

582
00:34:13,930 --> 00:34:16,090
Look, Keith. I've already gone through this with your father.

583
00:34:16,090 --> 00:34:18,110
- My father is his own man and so am I. - Okay.

584
00:34:18,110 --> 00:34:19,770
Now you can go through it with me.

585
00:34:19,770 --> 00:34:21,060
Let's just go. What do you need?

586
00:34:21,070 --> 00:34:22,410
Tell me what you need.

587
00:34:22,610 --> 00:34:25,340
Ferragamo was there for me when nobody else was.

588
00:34:25,340 --> 00:34:27,890
I might not be alive today if it wasn't for him.

589
00:34:27,990 --> 00:34:30,590
He also betrayed your confidence, Keith.

590
00:34:30,600 --> 00:34:32,700
He's the one who went to Maureen Kingsley.

591
00:34:32,700 --> 00:34:34,540
That still doesn't justify murder.

592
00:34:34,540 --> 00:34:36,760
What exactly are you hoping to do?

593
00:34:36,770 --> 00:34:37,720
Bring him back to life?

594
00:34:37,720 --> 00:34:40,060
- No, I want justice. - Justice?

595
00:34:40,120 --> 00:34:42,850
Well, justice is a tricky thing, Keith.

596
00:34:43,180 --> 00:34:45,410
Take Lyle Gibson, for example.

597
00:34:45,410 --> 00:34:47,030
You want justice for that?

598
00:34:48,020 --> 00:34:49,440
Gibson's death was an accident.

599
00:34:49,440 --> 00:34:52,130
Maybe so, but let's be objective.

600
00:34:52,330 --> 00:34:54,130
He rapes your sister, you pay him a visit.

601
00:34:54,130 --> 00:34:55,830
He ends up dead.

602
00:34:55,830 --> 00:34:57,810
Accident could be a tough sell.

603
00:35:00,360 --> 00:35:03,010
So if I go public with the truth about Ferragamo

604
00:35:03,600 --> 00:35:05,750
you go public with the lie about Lyle Gibson?

605
00:35:05,750 --> 00:35:07,110
Is that what you're saying?

606
00:35:08,590 --> 00:35:10,040
Oh, brother.

607
00:35:10,430 --> 00:35:11,900
There's one catch, Carl.

608
00:35:11,960 --> 00:35:13,410
There are two cover-ups

609
00:35:13,410 --> 00:35:15,020
and you're involved in both of them

610
00:35:15,020 --> 00:35:16,800
so however it plays out is bad for you.

611
00:35:16,800 --> 00:35:18,180
I can take care of myself.

612
00:35:18,180 --> 00:35:21,610
No, no, no. The moneymen behind my father's campaign take care of you.

613
00:35:21,910 --> 00:35:23,540
But if things get ugly,

614
00:35:23,540 --> 00:35:25,080
they'll make sure you're the one who takes the fall.

615
00:35:25,080 --> 00:35:26,420
Won't they, Carl?

616
00:35:29,060 --> 00:35:31,910
Or maybe they'll do to you what you did to Dr. Ferragamo.

617
00:35:32,450 --> 00:35:34,930
You are in way over your head.

618
00:35:35,500 --> 00:35:38,750
And you're getting nervous. I can smell it.

619
00:35:40,470 --> 00:35:42,340
Okay, you listen to me.

620
00:35:42,350 --> 00:35:45,940
Whatever you think you can do to me or anyone else

621
00:35:45,940 --> 00:35:48,530
it will be 100 times worse for you.

622
00:35:49,290 --> 00:35:52,190
- I'm not so sure. - Well, I am.

623
00:35:52,190 --> 00:35:53,530
Because if you push things too far,

624
00:35:53,530 --> 00:35:55,930
they will do whatever they have to do.

625
00:35:57,170 --> 00:35:59,760
Killing David Palmer's son might get a little messy.

626
00:35:59,760 --> 00:36:02,450
I think they'd be a little more subtle than that.

627
00:36:03,420 --> 00:36:05,010
I'm not following you.

628
00:36:07,780 --> 00:36:09,440
There is some physical evidence

629
00:36:09,440 --> 00:36:11,740
in George Ferragamo's office

630
00:36:11,740 --> 00:36:14,280
that leads directly to you.

631
00:36:14,530 --> 00:36:15,970
Subtle enough so the fire marshals

632
00:36:15,970 --> 00:36:18,050
didn't find it the first time around

633
00:36:18,050 --> 00:36:20,950
but with a little help, they'll find it.

634
00:36:23,110 --> 00:36:25,220
So I'll be framed for Ferragamo's murder.

635
00:36:25,220 --> 00:36:27,360
Like I said, whatever it takes.

636
00:36:27,980 --> 00:36:29,950
That's why your father backed off

637
00:36:30,310 --> 00:36:32,110
and that's why you'll back off.

638
00:36:55,850 --> 00:36:58,050
So I'll be framed for Ferragamo's murder.

639
00:36:58,050 --> 00:37:00,160
Like I said, whatever It takes.

640
00:37:00,780 --> 00:37:02,730
That's why your father backed off

641
00:37:03,030 --> 00:37:04,900
and that's why you'll back off.

642
00:39:16,490 --> 00:39:17,830
Are you okay?

643
00:39:21,710 --> 00:39:23,720
What happened?

644
00:39:26,290 --> 00:39:27,650
What's your name?

645
00:39:30,440 --> 00:39:31,900
I don't remember.

646
00:39:33,670 --> 00:39:35,240
You don't even know your name?

647
00:39:43,150 --> 00:39:45,220
You can't stand in the middle of the road.

648
00:39:50,850 --> 00:39:53,030
Come on, get in. I'll give you a ride.

649
00:39:54,100 --> 00:39:55,490
Thank you.

650
00:40:08,420 --> 00:40:11,770
I'm sorry. Thank you.

651
00:41:31,420 --> 00:41:32,690
Mom!

652
00:41:35,620 --> 00:41:36,860
Mom!

